<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<FairyChallengeViewModel xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <FairyChallengeBags>
  
  
    <FairyChallengeBag>
  <dbLocationName>candystore_shelves</dbLocationName>
  <IntroText>[p]You turn the corner to find Jewdewfae the fairy trying to unscrew the lid from a jar of gummy bear candies.  She is too small and light to twist it off, but she seems to be having too much fun just trying to do it by herself.  She giggles and turns to you.[/p]

[p][fae]“Heya there, big buddy,”[/fae] she giggles.  She begins zipping around various candy jars and boxes, pulling out chocolates and other types of sweets and throwing them generally in your direction.  Most fall at your feet.  [fae]“Want some candy?  This kind here is my favorite!  No, wait!  This kind!  Or this one!  I love them all!  Wanna eat some candy with me?  But I mean a LOT of candy, I don’t want to leave here without trying a little bit of everything...”[/fae][/p]</IntroText>
  <CorrectFormText>[p]Before you can respond, Jewdewfae zips over to your mouth and tosses what is to her an entire armful of different kinds of candy--chocolates, gummies, jawbreakers, bubble gum, licorice, and plenty others you cannot distinguish by taste mixed in with all the others.  Surprised, you gulp and swallow it all down in a single swallow, but all it does is get your stomach growling for more.  You look up to see Jewdewfae growing into an equally plump sister, pulling jars off the shelves and pouring half of its contents into her mouth at once, throwing handfuls more at you, pelting your open mouth and body with sugary goodness.[/p]

[p]The two of you pig out for some time.  When you are both finally satisfied--and most of the candy appears to be gone, though somehow jars that you thought were empty seem to be back on the shelves and full as ever--you slumber over side by side in a food-coma nap.[/p]

[p][fae]“Mmm, that was fun,” Jewdewfae sighs contently as she shrinks back down to her regular fairy body and perches on your belly.  “Thanks for playing with me.  here, have this…”[/fae] she zaps you, fueling your arcane knowledge with fairy magic before zipping off to find another partner to play with.[/p]</CorrectFormText>
  <FailureText>[p]Jewdewfae giggles.  [fae]“No, I don’t think you have the right body right now for this.  I want to play with someone who won’t mind packing on a dozen pounds in an hour or two, say, maybe a Massively Obese Woman…”[/fae][/p]</FailureText>
  <RequiredForm>form_Massively_Obese_Woman_Aethar</RequiredForm>
</FairyChallengeBag>



    <FairyChallengeBag>
  <dbLocationName>medclinic_lobby</dbLocationName>
  <IntroText>[p]You walk inside to find Jewdewfae perched on the counter of the payee window, trying to reach into the jar of lollipops and pulling one out.  When she notices you standing there she giggles and abandons her task, letting the glass lid fall back down with a clink.  However, she doesn’t move her tiny fingers away fast enough and some of them get struck with the lid on the way down.[/p]

[p][fae]“Owwwww,”[/fae] she moans, zipping over to you, leaving behind a trail of fairy dust lingering in the air, her flight instead.  She lands on your shoulder and holds her fingers over to your lips as you turn your head to look.  [fae]“Are you a nurse?  I want someone to kiss my fingers and make them feel better.  And then kiss me on the lips, and then kiss me between my thighs…”[/fae][/p]</IntroText>
  <CorrectFormText>[p]Before you can respond, Jewdewfae zips over to your mouth and tosses what is to her an entire armful of different kinds of candy--chocolates, gummies, jawbreakers, bubble gum, licorice, and plenty others you cannot distinguish by taste mixed in with all the others.  Surprised, you gulp and swallow it all down in a single swallow, but all it does is get your stomach growling for more.  You look up to see Jewdewfae growing into an equally plump sister, pulling jars off the shelves and pouring half of its contents into her mouth at once, throwing handfuls more at you, pelting your open mouth and body with sugary goodness.[/p]

[p]The two of you pig out for some time.  When you are both finally satisfied--and most of the candy appears to be gone, though somehow jars that you thought were empty seem to be back on the shelves and full as ever--you slumber over side by side in a food-coma nap.[/p]

[p][fae]“Mmm, that was fun,” Jewdewfae sighs contently as she shrinks back down to her regular fairy body and perches on your belly.  “Thanks for playing with me.  here, have this…”[/fae] she zaps you, fueling your arcane knowledge with fairy magic before zipping off to find another partner to play with.[/p]</CorrectFormText>
  <FailureText>[p][fae]“Oh good, you’re just what the doctor ordered!”[/fae] Jewdewfae sticks her fingers between your lipstick-red lips.  Just as she promised, she then plants her tiny lips against your plump bottom lip, kissing you passionately as her body grows from nine inches tall to a voluptuous five foot woman without her fairy wings.  [fae]“Come here, you!  I need you to come and check out this strange little pain I’ve been having down here...”[/fae]  She pulls you toward the emergency room and leaps onto a rolling gurney, rubbing her inner thigh.[/p]

[p]You oblige, rubbing some lotion along her legs and thighs as she directs you along her “boo-boos” closer and closer to her clitoris.  She stares with you with a wide grin and you focus your attention on her steaming womanhood, pleasuring her with your fingers as she writhes on the gurney in lust.  She gasps loudly and collapses down, sweaty and satisfied.  [fae]“You’re the bestest nurse ever!  Let me pay you back… Here, have this…”[/fae] she zaps you, fueling your arcane knowledge with a bit of fairy magic before returning to her regular body and zipping off to find another partner to play with.[/p]</FailureText>
  <RequiredForm>form_Slutty_Nurse_Ashley_Maid</RequiredForm>
</FairyChallengeBag>
	
	<FairyChallengeBag>
  <dbLocationName>mansion_bedroom</dbLocationName>
  <IntroText>[p]As you carefully step into the room you see Jewdewfae the fairy perched at the top of the headboard in the bedroom’s canopy bed.  She hangs off of it with one hand, poised to leap down onto the mattress below.  You watch as she pushes off into the air, giggling and twirling around as she plummets down onto the sheets below.  But when she lands she is greeted by a cloud of dust rising off of every nearby surface, causing her to quickly fly up into the air covering her eyes and wheezing.[/p]

[p]Blinded, Jewdewfae collides with you and clutches onto your neck as she hacks the last bit of dust out of her tiny lungs.  [fae]“That was so much fun, if only this place were a little bit cleaner…”[/fae] she looks up at you, recoiling in mock surprise that she just-so-happened to have flown right into someone.  [fae]“Oh heya!  Are you the new Mincing Maid I ordered?  Would you help me clean out this bed so I can play on it without getting dirty?  Well, at least not dirty from dirt...”[/fae][/p]</IntroText>
  <CorrectFormText>[p][fae]“Oh!  Perfect!  Hola, madamoiselle!  Did I get that right?  Oh, it doesn’t matter.  Come here!”[/fae] Jewdewfae sends a bolt of energy at you, striking your body and making you gasp and strike a sexy pose against your will.  You find yourself blushing as Jewdewfae eyes your body, whistling in approval as she grows into a full-sized woman wearing fine velvet robes, clearly someone rich and powerful.[/p]

[p][fae]“Okay, now, go change those bedsheets, dust the mirror, vacuum the floor, mop up the kitchen, mend up this little tear in my dress, paint the walls a slightly lighter shade of blue, and have my dinner all ready for me in half an hour!  Heehee!  Oh, isn’t this fun, me bossing you around like that?  But maybe you need a sister to help you?”[/fae] in the blink of an eye Jewdewfae’s clothes vanish, replaced instantly by a dress just like yours. [fae] “Oui, oui, let’s get to cleaning!”[/fae][/p]

[p]Cleaning begins and ends with you and Jewdewfae changing the bedsheets but somehow tripping and becoming entangled in them with your clothing mysteriously slipping away.  Ultimately the bed remains as dirty as ever, perhaps with a few more fluids drying on them.  [fae]“Bestest maids ever,”[/fae] Jewdewfae sighs.  [fae]“Time for your paycheck!”[/fae]  She zaps you, filling you with some fairy magic in reward as she flies off.[/p]</CorrectFormText>
  <FailureText>[p][fae]“Where’s your outfit?” Jewdewfae giggles.  “Where’s your sexy sweet French accent?  Where’s your feather duster?  This whole bedroom is messy, messy, messy, and I need a real veteran cleaning lady here, not… whatever you are!”[/fae][/p]</FailureText>
  <RequiredForm>form_Mincing_Maid_Ellipsis</RequiredForm>
</FairyChallengeBag>



<FairyChallengeBag>
  <dbLocationName>park_rose_garden</dbLocationName>
  <IntroText>[p]As you enter the rose garden you see Jewdewfae the fairy sitting on the edge of a wooden bench, her blue dress lying beside her leaving her completely naked in the wind.  She has a pile of rose petals sitting on her lap and around her and she appears to be weaving them into some kind of tiny dress using a needle three inches long which is a third the height of her entire body.  Needless to say she is not doing a very good job.[/p]

[p]As your shadow falls over her she looks up, shrieking in fake innocence as she holds two rose petals up to cover her naked breasts.  [fae]“Oops, oh my, the wind,”[/fae] she giggles as she releases them into the breeze. [fae] “You know those springtime fairies that make their own dresses out of flowers?  Well, they’re having this dance tonight out in the Scarlet Forest and I need a pretty little dress, but these rose petals tear way too easily.  And I think that new girl Jaylee Dewtoes already has one.  Oh, what am I going to do…”[/fae][/p]

[p]She sighs glumly, then looks up, her face glowing.  [fae]“Oh, I know!  I want to make a dress from those big pretty pink flowers that those pretty Alraune girls all grow!  I don’t suppose you could let me, um, ‘borrow’ one from you?”[/fae][/p]</IntroText>
  <CorrectFormText>[p][fae]“Oh, perfect!”[/fae] Jewdewfae zips over to you and begins to tug at one of the large pink petals growing out of your hair, but it won’t come out and the more she pulls the more it starts to hurt.  Before you need to ask her to stop hurting you, she gives up on her own.  [fae]“Screw this.  But you know what, I do love the way you smell.  Oh!  I just had the best idea--I’m going to just collect some of that sweet aroma of yours, mkay?”[/fae][/p]

[p]She finds the cap of an acorn and begins to scrape it along your flowers instead, collecting some of the sweet pollen and syrupy juices that your body emits to produce its powerful aroma.  You enjoy the tickling sensation of her actions, tingling with the sensation of being groomed. [fae]“Perfect!  Thankies!  I’m going to smell so wonderful tonight.  Here, have this, you deserve it.”[/fae]  She zaps you, filling you with some fairy magic in reward as she flies off.[/p]</CorrectFormText>
  <FailureText>[p][fae]“You’re not a flower, silly!”[/fae] Jewdewfae giggles.  [fae]“You know, I could just turn you straight into an Alraune petal dress, but that’s not half as fun.  Did I ever tell you about the time I spent a day s a pair of boots?  Blech.  Your big people feet are stinky.”[/fae][/p]</FailureText>
  <RequiredForm>form_Alraune_Foxpower93</RequiredForm>
</FairyChallengeBag>


<FairyChallengeBag>
  <dbLocationName>clothing_womens</dbLocationName>
  <IntroText>[p]As you walk inside the clothing store you see four mannequins posed out in the middle of the aisle, each wearing a different dress, though none of them seem to fit the mannequin quite right and some appear to have been torn by the effort of forcing them on them.  You don’t sense any human consciousness coming from them--just plain old non-former-human store props.  Just as you breath a sigh of relief and try to walk past, a small voice calls out [fae]“Hey!  You!  You’re blocking my view, you clumsy biggie!”[/fae][/p]

[p]Startled, you look around and see Jewdewfae the fairy sitting on a stack of folded jeans, staring at the mannequins intently.  She sighs, appearing to be lost in deep contemplation. [fae] “You know, these dresses just aren’t doing it for me.  Would you mind helping me pick one out?  Nah, I don’t want you to tell me what you like, I have my own style.  I just need you to wear them and stand super still, just like these mannequins over here.  Why don’t you get yourself turned into one of those Magical Mannequin women I’ve seen here and there?”[/fae][/p]</IntroText>
  <CorrectFormText>[p][fae]“Perfect!”[/fae]  Jewdewfae flies over a line of dresses neatly hanging on a metal rack and begins to hum, picking out a select few but letting most drop to the floor and get wrinkled.  Finally she finishes her selection and flies back over, weighed down by the heap of cloth in her arms.  [fae]“Okay, arms up, let me put this red one on you.  And don’t move.  Unless you’re putting your arms up.  Now put them back down.  And don’t move.  Unless you’re… well, you get what I mean, silly.”[/fae][/p]

[p]You stand perfectly still--something you’re certainly quite adept at in your faceless, enchanted wooden body--and watch through the magic of the rune on your head as Jewdewfae slips on a slinky pink dress over your body and flies back to her heap of jeans, resuming her contemplation.  [fae]“Hm… no… not quite... let me go grab another…”[/fae][/p]

[p]After repeating this process for what feels like hours, you suddenly hear Jewdewfae shriek in delight as she flies out of a heap of clothing clutching an ugly skintight yellow dress that makes your inner fashion sense want to leap off of a cliff..   [fae]“This one is awesome!  You don’t even have to try it on for me, I just have a good feeling about it.  Thanks for your help, biggie.”[/fae]  She sends a zap your way, gifting you with a portion of her fairy magic and vanishes into a dressing room.[/p]</CorrectFormText>
  <FailureText>[p][fae]“Hm, I don’t think you can stand still enough for me in that body of yours.  You’ll move too much and then I won’t be able to concentrate.  Come back later when you’ve got yourself turned into wood.”[/fae][/p]</FailureText>
  <RequiredForm>form_Magical_Mannequin_plzTryMySpell</RequiredForm>
</FairyChallengeBag>



<FairyChallengeBag>
  <dbLocationName>apartment_dog_park</dbLocationName>
  <IntroText>[p]As you walk around the corner and into the apartment complex’s dog park you hear Jewdewfae the fairy screaming, but you can’t quite discern if it’s in delight or fear.  At first you can’t see her, but then you notice that she’s carrying a chewed-up plastic frisbee and trying to fly away with it, pursued by a Husky intent on recovering its chew toy.  [fae]“Go away, dumb dog!  Mine!”[/fae] Jewdewfae scolds. [fae] “We’re playing fetch, not tug-o-war!  Let!  GO!”[/fae][/p]

[p]With a surprising display of physical prowess from a tiny winged girl, she manages to wrench it out of the dog’s jaws and flies high up in the air, hiding up in a cloud until the dog loses interest and wanders away.  You’re about to do the same when you see the frisbee zooming straight at you.  Instinct kicks in and you just manage to clutch it out of the air before it smacks you in the face. [/p]

[p] [fae]“Oh hey!  You’re not bad!”[/fae] she zips over to you and lands on your shoulder, her skin sweaty and showing through a tear in her dress about the size of a canine tooth.  [fae]“Real dogs are dumb and smelly.  I like playing with people-dogs instead, much smarter and they don’t pee on the floor.  As much.  Hey, I don’t suppose you wanna play dog with me?  I’ll be the biggie and you the doggy girl… how about a Bitch in Heat?”[/fae][/p]</IntroText>
  <CorrectFormText>[p]Jewdewfae squeals, clapping her hands as she sees you approach, crawling on your hands and needs as your six breasts jiggle below you.  [fae]“Good girl!  I like you!  Now go fetch!”[/fae]  She winds her arm and throws the frisbee as hard as she can, spinning in circles a few times to build up speed before she releases it.  Instinct takes over and you bark, chasing it in your clumsy half-human half-dog body.  When you find the frisbee and start to trot back with it in your teeth, Jewdewfae is gone, but instead you find a large black labrador in his place with Jewdewfae’s familiar scent..  Your sharp nose detects his lust, the pheromones causing your own body to begin to crave a good humping and release your own, a self-reinforcing feedback loop that can only end one way.[/p]

[p]The two of you begin to circle around, sniffing one another’s sexes until the two of you can take it no longer.  You bend down, wet womanhood raised invitingly up, as Jewdewfae in her male dog body mounts you and begins to hump excitedly.  You yelp and bark as you are lost to pleasure.  When he finally rolls off of you, you collapse and take a nap as Jewdewfae licks the sweat off of your face.[/p]

[p]When you wake up you see Jewdewfae back in her normal fairy body, petting your soft fur.  When she sees that you are awake she giggles and scratches your head by your ears.  “So I might have lied a little about what game I wanted to play,” she teases.  [fae]“You’re quite a naughty bitch, you know that?  I just couldn’t pass that up.  Anyway, thanks for the fun!  Catch you later!”[/fae]  She zaps you, gifting with some of her fairy magic, and flies off.[/p]</CorrectFormText>
  <FailureText>[p][fae]“I can play frisbee with any one of you biggies or any old dumb canine mutt.  Right now I want to play catch with a nice, cute and loyal bitch.  Can you do that for me?”[/fae][/p]</FailureText>
  <RequiredForm>form_Brainwashed_Bitch_LexamTheGemFox</RequiredForm>
</FairyChallengeBag>




<FairyChallengeBag>
  <dbLocationName>college_track</dbLocationName>
  <IntroText>[p]As you step lightly on the rubberized athletics track, you hear a strange whistling sound.  You turn and see a strange, light-blue blur zooming around the track, sailing a few feet off the ground, circling the track over and over well over a hundred miles an hour.  Curious, you sit down on a bleacher and watch, trying to figure out just what in the world you are looking at.  It seems the thing is slowing down over time, its path becoming a little more erratic and uneven until it shoots out of its way entirely, tumbling straight at you! [/p]

 [p]Something clangs underneath you as it strikes metal.  [fae]“Owwwww...”[/fae] you hear Jewdewfae moan.  You peek down to see her lying dizzy and exhausted on a lost cheerleader pom-pom.  [fae]“Oh no, I dropped the pocketwatch again, dangit dangit dangit!  You dummy,”[/fae] she sighs to herself.[/p]

[p]The bleachers creak as you begin to stand up.  Jewdewfae hears it and flies up, landing on your shoulder and mopping some sweat off of her face with the hem of her dress.  [fae]“Oh, hey there.  Can you help me with something?  I’m trying to learn how to fly faster, so I’ve been going around this track as fast as I can.  I think I can do a lap in under four seconds, but it’s just so frustrating taking a quarter second too long, you know?  I think I need something to cheer me on so I can get my time down to three seconds.  Oh!  You should be a cheerleader and dance while you yell stuff at me!  But you gotta do it right, like one of those Chatty Cheerleaders around here...”[/fae][/p]</IntroText>
  <CorrectFormText>[p][fae]“Perfect!  I feel inspired already!  Can you sing something like ‘Go go fairy girl, you can do it!’  Nah, that just sounds dumb.  ‘Maybe ‘Go Go Jewdewfae, this is your day!’  Nah, that doesn’t work either.  Um.  Just jump up and down a lot and cheer, okay?”[/fae]  Jewdewfae hands you a stopwatch and takes her position at the start line.  [fae]“Okay, three, two, one... go!  Oops, false start.  On the count of three.  Go!”[/fae][/p]

[p]A gust of wind blows against your clothes as the fairy launches off, beginning her lap.  Once you recover from your disbelief at how fast she can fly when she puts her mind to it, you do what your own current body does best--cheer!  You scream out to Jewdewfae with all the chants, songs and cheers of encouragement that have been seared into your mind from your semesters in Saint Circe’s (or rather the magic that has gives you the memories of such).  It’s a shame hardly anyone is around to see you, and you wonder if Jewdewfae can even see or hear you when she zooms by.[/p]

[p]Finally the dizzy fairy flutters to a halt and collapses against you, nestled between your breasts.  [fae]“Thanks!  You’re the bestest cheerleader I’ve ever seen!”[/fae] she gasps.  [fae]“But I’m so tired now, lemme take a quick nap…”[/fae] she falls silent and for a moment you wonder if she has collapsed in exhaustion right there in your shirt, but she lazily climbs out and flutters back to the bleachers.  [fae]“I’m gonna rest a while and try again later.  Thanks for the help though!  Here, have this.”[/fae]  She zaps you, filling you with some fairy magic in reward as she flies off.[/p]</CorrectFormText>
  <FailureText>[p][fae]“Hm.  No, you don’t look very inspiring right now.  Cheerleading is a sport, you know. Not just anyone can do it.  I need you to be the real thing.”[/fae][/p]</FailureText>
  <RequiredForm>form_Chatty_Cheerleader_Haretia</RequiredForm>
</FairyChallengeBag>





<FairyChallengeBag>
  <dbLocationName>ranch_pasture</dbLocationName>
  <IntroText>[p]As you step out into the pasture, you catch sight of Jewdewfae sitting on a wooden picket fence, chugging down the last drops from a plastic bottle of milk.  Finishing it off, she holds it up as if trying to see if there is a single drop left that she can coax out.  Sighing, she tosses it down to the grass, letting it roll a few feet away in the wind.  She notices you and flies over, landing on your shoulder.[/p]

[p][fae]“Hey there, biggie,”[/fae] she greets you.  [fae]“I love being out here on the farm.  So much more organic and fresh and close to nature.  Well, except for the forest.  And the mountains.  And out in the middle of a lake.  Or the ocean I suppose.  But the ocean doesn’t have any cows!  Well, they do have sea cows, but those don’t really count now do they, you silly biggie?  You know what?  I’m still thirsty, and that milk wasn’t very fresh anyway.  Probably been sitting in a truck for weeks.  I don’t suppose you could help out?  I want some fresh milk, straight from the udder, from a nice, fine, mature cowgirl. Specifically one of those adorable Milk Maids.”[/fae][/p]</IntroText>
  <CorrectFormText>[p]Jewdewfae licks her lips, staring at your four large breasts, sloshing with milk and the udders jutting out of a pink bulge below.  [fae]“Mmmm, perfect. Just what the good doctor ordered.  Follow me!”[/fae]  She leads you into the barn and sits you down on the hay while she drags a metal tin pail under you.  She grabs ahold of one of your nipples, tugging at it gently, though her small fairy hands have some difficulty coaxing your nurturing milk out.  Frustrated, she flies sideways and puts her tiny, bare feet against your skin, clutching the udder and pulling away with all of her strength.[/p]

[p]You moan and moo as a spurt of milk splashes out, striking her in the face and knocking her out of the air.  She tumbles into the straw, her tiny dress soaked and her body dripping with your white warmth.  Giggling, she pulls herself to her feet and shakes free of the straw clinging to her damp body.  [fae]“Yum!  Wow!  Delicious!  Gimme more!”[/fae][/p]

[p]Being the obedient and loyal maid that you are, you follow Jewdewfae’s command and lift her up to a different udder, holding her up to your chest and gently rubbing it with your free hand, allowing the milk to flow out.  It still comes out too fast for the tiny fairy to keep up with and most of it ends up running down and off your bodies, pooling on the wooden ground and making a pale mud from the dust below.  When it seems as if Jewdewfae will explode if she takes another gulp, she backs away with a content grin on her face, which quickly turns into a wince. [fae]“Ooh, I gotta go take a leak.  Be right back.  Actually, have this first.  Catch you later!  Byyye...”[/fae]  Her voice trails away as she flies off, but not before sending a zap your way and enhancing your magic with a bit of her own.[/p]</CorrectFormText>
  <FailureText>[p][fae]“Eeeeeew, no, I don’t want to drink your milk, silly biggie!  Not with you looking like that.  Come back later, when you have some nice Milk Maid udders.”[/fae][/p]</FailureText>
  <RequiredForm>form_Milk_Maid_Rayner</RequiredForm>
</FairyChallengeBag>





<FairyChallengeBag>
  <dbLocationName>concert_hall_stage</dbLocationName>
  <IntroText>[p][fae]“Oh Romeo, oh Romeo, where’s your art, my Romeo, deny thy mother and refuse your name!  Or, if your flowers wilt... no, that’s not right...”[/fae]  As you peek around and take a look at the stage, you see Jewdewfae the fairy flying back and forth above the stage, rubbing her chin and dragging the last few inches of a theatrical gown across the wooden stage.  [fae]“Romeo, oh Romeo, wherefore thou art? Deny thy father and...  Shoot, no.  Where is that script?  I put it around here somewhere...  Why is it so hot in here?  How can those stupid biggies ever do anything on this stage?  Oh--hey there, stupid biggie!  Um, I mean, not stupid biggie!  Can you help out a fellow poet?”[/fae][/p]

[p]Jewdewfae shrugs off the robe and flutters over to you, carrying some torn pages of a script and muttering to herself, clearly trying to memorize the lines on them before settling down to rest on a folding chair in front of you. A paper slides out of the stack and flutters to the ground without her noticing. [/p]

[p][fae]“Ugh, I don’t get your biggie art.  One of my friends said I should read Spearshakes guy because... I forget.  But it’s too hot in here, those stage lights are killer for anyone in costume.  I need someone to help cool this place down... one of those Ice Queens would do nicely, I think.  All you have to do is stand near me and hold my drink while I practice.  Perfectly simple job for a biggie like you, eh?  Whattaya say?”[/fae][/p]</IntroText>
  <CorrectFormText>[p][fae]“Ooh, awesome!”[/fae]  Jewdewfae giggles as she rubs against your chilled flesh, sighing in relief as she slides her body against yours.  [fae]“Can you hold this, please?  Oh, and this.  And this ice cream sandwich I found in the bar.  And this towel.  And--hey, you dropped everything!  Ugh, nevermind.  Just... stand around, mkay?  Okay, here goes.  Ahem.  ‘My royal lord, you do not give the chair.  Cheer.  You do not give the cheer…’”[/fae][/p]

[p]Sighing to yourself, you do as Jewdewfae asks and stand on the stage, facing out to the nonexistent audience, shifting your weight as your fairy companion settles into a comfortable nest between your icy breasts, shuffling her papers about and doing her best to decipher the text on them.  You offer some words of support and pronounce some of the more archaic words, but Jewdewfae only pouts, offended that a plebeian like you would dare offer such a master thespian such obvious advice.[/p]

[p][fae]“You know what, biggie? Poetry is dumb and makes no sense.  I’m outta here.”[/fae]  She buzzes her wings but remains attached to you no matter how fiercely she tries to break free.  Eventually you come to realize that her tiny dress, previously damp with sweat, has become frozen to your skin.  Eventually she struggles so hard that the dress tears down the front and she tumbles straight out of it, ending up in the nude.  When she regains her composure, she glances down at her naked body and shrugs.  [fae]“Eh, I’ll get another one,”[/fae] she sighs.  [fae]“Thanks, dearie.  I’d kiss you but uh... here, just have this instead.”[/fae]  She sends a bolt of her fairy magic at you, gifting you with some of her knowledge as she drifts away to find an art more fitting to her talents.[/p]</CorrectFormText>
  <FailureText>[p]Jewdewfae presses her tiny hand against your cheek.  [fae]“Nope, too warm. Way too warm.  I want to feel like I’m in Antarctica.  It’s cold there, right?  I’ve never been that far north.  South.  Whatever, you know what I mean.”[/fae][/p]</FailureText>
  <RequiredForm>form_Ice_Queen_Alessandro_Stamegna</RequiredForm>
</FairyChallengeBag>

	
  </FairyChallengeBags>
</FairyChallengeViewModel>