<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<FairyChallengeViewModel xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <FairyChallengeBags>
    <FairyChallengeBag>
      <dbLocationName>candystore_shelves</dbLocationName>
	  <RequiredForm>form_Massively_Obese_Woman_Aethar</RequiredForm>
      <IntroText>
        You turn the corner to find Jewdewfae the fairy trying to unscrew the lid from a jar of gummy bear candies.  She is too small and light to twist it off, but she seems to be having too much fun just trying to do it by herself.  She giggles and turns to you.

        “Heya there, big buddy,” she giggles.  She begins zipping around various candy jars and boxes, pulling out chocolates and other types of sweets and throwing them generally in your direction.  Most fall at your feet.  “Want some candy?  This kind here is my favorite!  No, wait!  This kind!  Or this one!  I love them all!  Wanna eat some candy with me?  But I mean a LOT of candy, I don’t want to leave here without trying a little bit of everything...”
      </IntroText>
      <CorrectFormText>Before you can respond, Jewfewfae zips over to your mouth and tosses what is to her an entire armful of different kinds of candy--chocolates, gummies, jawbreakers, bubble gum, licorice, and plenty others you cannot distinguish by taste mixed in with all the others.  Surprised, you gulp and swallow it all down in a single swallow, but all it does is get your stomach growling for more.  You look up to see Jewdewfae growing into an equally plump sister, pulling jars off the shelves and pouring half of its contents into her mouth at once, throwing handfuls more at you, pelting your open mouth and body with sugary goodness.

The two of you pig out for some time.  When you are both finally satisfied--and most of the candy appears to be gone, though somehow jars that you thought were empty seem to be back on the shelves and full as ever--you slumber over side by side in a food-coma nap.

“Mmm, that was fun,” Jewfewfae sighs contently as she shrinks back down to her regular fairy body and perches on your belly.  “Thanks for playing with me.  here, have this…” she zaps you, fueling your arcane knowledge with fairy magic before zipping off to find another partner to play with.</CorrectFormText>
      <FailureText>Jewfewfae giggles.  “No, I don’t think you have the right body right now for this.  I want to play with someone who won’t mind packing on a dozen pounds in an hour or two, say, maybe a Massively Obese Woman…”</FailureText>
    </FairyChallengeBag>
    <FairyChallengeBag>
      <dbLocationName>medclinic_lobby</dbLocationName>
	  <RequiredForm>form_Slutty_Nurse_Ashley_Maid</RequiredForm>
      <IntroText>You walk inside to find Jewdewfae perched on the counter of the payee window, trying to reach into the jar of lollipops and pulling one out.  When she notices you standing there she giggles and abandons her task, letting the glass lid fall back down with a clink.  However, she doesn’t move her tiny fingers away fast enough and some of them get struck with the lid on the way down.

“Owwwww,” she moans, zipping over to you, leaving behind a trail of fairy dust lingering in the air, her flight instead.  She lands on your shoulder and holds her fingers over to your lips as you turn your head to look.  “Are you a nurse?  I want someone to kiss my fingers and make them feel better.  And then kiss me on the lips, and then kiss me between my thighs…”
</IntroText>
      <CorrectFormText>“Oh good, you’re just what the doctor ordered!” Jewdewfae sticks her fingers between your lipstick-red lips.  Just as she promised, she then plants her tiny lips against your plump bottom lip, kissing you passionately as her body grows from nine inches tall to a voluptuous five foot woman without her fairy wings.  “Come here, you!  I need you to come and check out this strange little pain I’ve been having down here...”  She pulls you toward the emergency room and leaps onto a rolling gurney, rubbing her inner thigh.

You oblige, rubbing some lotion along her legs and thighs as she directs you along her “boo-boos” closer and closer to her clitoris.  She stares with you with a wide grin and you focus your attention on her steaming womanhood, pleasuring her with your fingers as she writhes on the gurney in lust.  She gasps loudly and collapses down, sweaty and satisfied.  “You’re the bestest nurse ever!  Let me pay you back… Here, have this…” she zaps you, fueling your arcane knowledge with a bit of fairy magic before returning to her regular body and zipping off to find another partner to play with.</CorrectFormText>
      <FailureText>“You don’t look like you’re qualified to treat my ouchie fingers,” Jewdewfae giggles.  “I need a nurse.  Not just any nurse though, one who really wants to help me through the recovery process… a Slutty Nurse…”</FailureText>
    </FairyChallengeBag>
	
	<FairyChallengeBag>
      <dbLocationName>mansion_bedroom</dbLocationName>
      <IntroText>As you carefully step into the room you see Jewdewfae the fairy perched at the top of the headboard in the bedroom’s canopy bed.  She hangs off of it with one hand, poised to leap down onto the mattress below.  You watch as she pushes off into the air, giggling and twirling around as she plummets down onto the sheets below.  But when she lands she is greeted by a cloud of dust rising off of every nearby surface, causing her to quickly fly up into the air covering her eyes and wheezing.

Blindly, Jewdewfae collides with you and clutches onto your neck as she hacks the last bit of dust out of her tiny lungs.  “That was so much fun, if only this place were a little bit cleaner…” she looks up at you, recoiling in mock surprise that she just-so-happened to have flown right into someone.  “Oh heya!  Are you the new Mincing Maid I ordered?  Would you help me clean out this bed so I can play on it without getting dirty?  Well, at least not dirty from dirt...”</IntroText>
      <CorrectFormText>“Oh!  Perfect!  Hola, madamoiselle!  Did I get that right?  Oh, it doesn’t matter.  Come here!” Jewdewfae sends a bolt of energy at you, striking your body and making you gasp and strike a sexy pose against your will.  You find yourself blushing as Jewdewfae eyes your body, whistling in approval as she grows into a full-sized woman wearing fine velvet robes, clearly someone rich and powerful.

“Okay, now, go change those bedsheets, dust the mirror, vacuum the floor, mop up the kitchen, mend up this little tear in my dress, paint the walls a slightly lighter shade of blue, and have my dinner all ready for me in half an hour!  Heehee!  Oh, isn’t this fun, me bossing you around like that?  But maybe you need a sister to help you?” in the blink of an eye Jewdewfae’s clothes vanish, replaced instantly by a dress just like yours.  “Oui, oui, let’s get to cleaning!”

Cleaning begins and ends with you and Jewdewfae changing the bedsheets but somehow tripping and becoming entangled in them with your clothing mysteriously slipping away.  Ultimately the bed remains as dirty as ever, perhaps with a few more fluids drying on them.  “Bestest maids ever,” Jewdewfae sighs.  “Time for your paycheck!”  She zaps you, filling you with some fairy magic in reward as she flies off.</CorrectFormText>
      <FailureText>“Where’s your outfit?” Jewdewfae giggles.  “Where’s your sexy sweet French accent?  Where’s your feather duster?  This whole bedroom is messy, messy, messy, and I need a real veteran cleaning lady here, not… whatever you are!”</FailureText>
	  <RequiredForm>form_Mincing_Maid_Ellipsis</RequiredForm>
</FairyChallengeBag>
	
  </FairyChallengeBags>
</FairyChallengeViewModel>