<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<Description>This obviously-demonic woman isn't acting quite like the other succubi inhabiting the city - though she seems just as lustful as the other demonesses, she is also ... more aggressive, more haughty.  You suspect you may be seeing a demon in full control, rather than simply a polymorphed magus - though it would be far too dangerous to gaze closely into her glowing red eyes to judge the truth of the matter.  And then there are the differences in her physical form - some minor, some severe.  Long purple hair.  Pointed ears.  Skin more pink than red.  Humanoid feet in place of hooves.  A particularly phallic-looking tail.  Movements suggesting unholy strength and agility, despite the lack of any visible muscles.  And between her legs, the most obvious difference of all ... a huge demonic cock, jutting forth above her feminine equipment.  So, not a succubus then, but an incubus?  Looking at her exaggerated feminine curves ... especially her enormous, milk-leaking breasts ... 'incubus' is obviously inappropriate.  Perhaps another word ...?</Description>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>From somewhere nearby, you hear what sounds like a deranged cultist chanting.   "Exeunt omnes!" the voice cries out,   "Exeunt omnes spiritae corpus!  Possidete est formae de semimarem duodecim daemonum!"  Looking up, you see a circle of fire form in front of the mage, an attractive-looking, but insubstantial demoness stepping out of it, no doubt to devour the amateur magi's soul.  But what are you going to do?  It's just another day in the big city.  Paying the scene no mind, you return to what you were doing, as you hear a piercing shriek from the cultist's direction.  "No!  Him!  Take him instead of me!"  And you look to the two of them with a dawning horror, as you see the cultist's finger pointed squarely at *you*.  Too stunned to move, you see the demoness - if that's even the correct word, as she is now sporting an enormous phallus - run towards you, leap within your own body.  You hear her voice within you:  "HELLO LITTLE MAGE ... YOU AND I ARE GOING TO BE VERY CLOSE FROM NOW ON.  VERY CLOSE INDEED."  You try to run - as if it would do any good with her inside you - and find you cannot.  "THAT'S RIGHT, PET - I CONTROL THIS BODY NOW - IT BENDS TO MY WILL.  YOU CANNOT EVEN MOVE, UNLESS I ALLOW IT.  IF I WANT TO SAY ... PLEASURE MYSELF RIGHT HERE IN THE OPEN" - with that, you look on in terror as your hands unzip your pants, and begin to play with your cock, right out in broad daylight - "THEN THAT IS WHAT 'WE' WILL DO.  UNDERSTAND?"  You try to meekly nod, and find you cannot even do that.  "GOOD."</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>"NOW, LITTLE MAGE - I THINK IT'S TIME WE DO SOMETHING ABOUT THAT PLAIN BODY OF YOURS.  SO UNREMARKABLE."  You try to open your mouth to protest, and find that you cannot; the demoness has again taken full control of your body.  So you think back angrily:  {it is NOT - do you have any idea how hard it is to keep a male body in *this* city?}  - but even your protesting thoughts are cut off as she screams: "SILENCE!".  She continues: "MY BODY ON THIS PLANE MUST LOOK MORE ... EXOTIC.  OUR SKIN TONE ... THAT WON'T DO AT ALL ..." - you look down at your hands, finding them turning a dark shade of pink - "OUR HAIR - IT MUST BE LONGER, MORE VIBRANT..."  - flowing purple locks cascade down your back - "AND OUR FACE.  IT MUST BE MUCH MORE APPROPRIATE ...".  It will be some time until you can look in a mirror; but when you finally can you see your new, oddly angular looking face framed by the long purple hair; eyes that are simply *wrong* looking out from the dark pink skin, between a set of long, pointed ears.  Your face doesn't look male anymore ... it doesn't even look human.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>"LITTLE MAGE" - the demoness inside you again freezes you in place - "YOUR BODY, IT IS NOT THE RIGHT SHAPE FOR A DEMONESS OF MY STATURE.  LOOK AT IT - I LIKE THE MUSCLES, BUT IT IS FAR, FAR TOO MALE.  LET US SEE WHAT CAN BE DONE ABOUT THAT ..."  Even as she says it, you can feel the changes begin.  You lose several inches of height; your shoulders narrow, your hips widen, your legs lengthen in proportion to your body.  The muscles beneath your pink skin, if anything, actually grow - though as your skin softens and your whole body takes on a curvier, rounder look, their appearance winds up minimized.  {What have you done, demon?  I look like a woman!} you think in protest.  There is only mocking laughter within you.  "A GIRL PERHAPS, THOUGH VERY UNDEVELOPED.  WHERE ARE THE TITS?  THE ROUNDED ASS?  THE WET PUSSY? THOUGH, IF YOU INSIST ..."   Eep.  Though, fortunately(?), she does not force any more changes on you just yet, although it is likely only a matter of time ...</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>"LITTLE MAGE" she calls, and your body instantly stops moving again.  More laughter: "I SEE YOU ARE ALREADY ADAPTING - I DID NOT EXERT MYSELF TO STOP YOUR MOTION."  And it's true - you start moving again, wiggling your fingers, taking a few tentative steps, when her will halts you again in earnest.  "NOW - NONE OF THAT.  IT DOES PLEASE ME TO SEE THAT YOUR WILL IS STRONG - THOUGH FALLING BEFORE ME."  {"Just what do you have planned this time, demon?"} you think to her.  "OH, NOTHING MUCH.  I JUST THINK THAT *I* ... OR OF COURSE, YOU ... COULD STAND TO BE A WHOLE LOT SEXIER.  DON'T YOU?"  You gasp as the changes start hitting.  Your proportions become unmistakably feminine - wide hips, huge ass, long legs, tiny waist ... and a growing weight on your chest, stopping at ... what, C-cups?  You've never needed a bra before ... {"What, you're finally making me into a woman?  You ... you bitch!"}  "SILENCE, LITTLE MAGE!"  she practically roars within you.  "JUST FOR THAT ..."  Your breasts (breasts!) immediately feel like they are on fire - they start growing, and growing, expanding beyond that of any natural woman you've ever seen, ending large enough that you can no longer see your feet, and have difficulty balancing.  "ANY *FURTHER* COMPLAINTS THEN?"  You remain silent, fearful of what else she might do.  At least you still have your dick ...</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>"OH ... LITTLE MAGE ..." the voice inside you calls out; you stand quiet, obediently, of your own accord.  "THE TIME HAS COME TO POSSESS YOU FULLY, I THINK ..."  Frightened, but at the same time feeling an unnaturally lustful anticipation, your try to watch the changes to your body - though all you can truly see below your enormous breasts are the tips of your fingernails lengthening, forming into claws.  Though you're pretty sure what other -orgasmic!- sensations coming from your warping body mean.  The feeling of your spine ejaculating outward must be a long demon tail coming forth, likely with the demoness's own heart-shaped tip.  The feeling of your shoulder blades ripping open, feeling as if two new limbs were issuing forth must be your new pair of leathery, bat like wings.  And the intense, throbbing headache, complete with the sensation of two large points of bone erupting through your forehead must be your new horns.  What you do not yet realize are the changes to your eyes ... they are now glowing an orangeish-red, appearing almost as portals to some infernal plane.  {Are ... are we complete now?} you hesitantly ask, your defiance starting to fade away.  "NO ... JUST TWO MORE CHANGES, LITTLE MAGE - AND THEN YOU WILL *TRULY* BE MINE."  Hmm.  But you already have the perfect demonic shemale body//doesn't the pussy form later?; what more could she possibly improve on?  "ONE NOW, AND ONE SOON ..."  The pleasure of the first is like nothing you have ever felt before, as your pathetic human cock absorbs the demonic energy around it, swelling to well over a foot in length, always hard, hugely thick, capped off with a giant swinging sack - it cums almost instantly, and immediately gets hard again.  Fuck - if that change felt so good, a final one would be even better, right?  Even worth the cost of your soul?</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>"IT IS OVER, LITTLE MAGE.  I HAVE WON.  I AM IN FULL CONTROL."  And it's true - other than a small corner of awareness in the back of your mind, you find you have no other existence, no link to your body at all, except to feel it, experience its intense sensations.  "OH, I DID PROMISE YOU ONE LAST CHANGE, DID I NOT?  I ASSUME THERE ARE NO OBJECTIONS?"  You are too stunned at the complete loss of control to even answer.  "GOOD.  WHILE YOUR COCK IS NICE, I AM REALLY A SUCCUBUS AT HEART - AND ANY BODY I INHABIT JUST NEEDS TO HAVE A LOVELY, STEAMING CUNT ..."  And it is so - skin parts beneath your heavy nutsack, thick, bright red lips splitting open, revealing your new burning, steaming, tight horny sex.  "MMMM ... I HOPE YOU LIKE IT - BUT HONESTLY,  I COULDN'T CARE LESS IF YOU DO.  TIME TO GO OUT THERE AND GET IT FILLED - OR..." she strokes your giant demonic cock - "DO THE FILLING.  PERHAPS OF THAT NICE CULTIST THAT SUMMONED ME FIRST?"  And - even from your tiny corner of awareness, you agree - you just know that fucking and being fucked in this body will feel amazing.  You doubt you could ever bring yourself to change it ... though, just perhaps, if an outsider took the initiative ... maybe you could work at helping the exorcism?  </TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>From  somewhere nearby, you hear what sounds like a deranged cultist  chanting.   "Exeunt omnes!" the voice cries out,   "Exeunt omnes  spiritae corpus!  Possidete est formae de semimarem duodecim daemonum!"   Looking up, you see a circle of fire form in front of the mage, an  attractive-looking, but insubstantial demoness stepping out of it, no  doubt to devour the amateur magi's soul.  But what are you going to do?   It's just another day in the big city.  Paying the scene no mind, you  return to what you were doing, as you hear a piercing shriek from the  cultist's direction.  "No!  Her!  Take her instead of me!"  And you look  to the two of them with a dawning horror, as you see the cultist's  finger pointed squarely at *you*.  Too stunned to move, you see the  demoness - if that's even the correct word, as she is now sporting an  enormous phallus - run towards you, leap within your own body.  You hear  her voice within you:  "HELLO LITTLE MAGE ... YOU AND I ARE GOING TO BE  VERY CLOSE FROM NOW ON.  VERY CLOSE INDEED."  You try to run - as if it  would do any good with her inside you - and find you cannot.  "THAT'S  RIGHT, PET - I CONTROL THIS BODY NOW - IT BENDS TO MY WILL.  YOU CANNOT  EVEN MOVE, UNLESS I ALLOW IT.  IF I WANT TO SAY ... PLEASURE MYSELF  RIGHT HERE IN THE OPEN" - with that, you look on in terror as your hands  unzip your pants, and begin to plunge in and out of your sex, right out in broad  daylight - "THEN THAT IS WHAT 'WE' WILL DO.  UNDERSTAND?" You try to meekly nod, and find you cannot even do that.  "GOOD."</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>"NOW, LITTLE  MAGE - I THINK IT'S TIME WE DO SOMETHING ABOUT THAT PLAIN BODY OF  YOURS.  SO UNREMARKABLE."  You try to open your mouth to protest, and  find that you cannot; the demoness has again taken full control of your  body.  So you think back angrily:  {It is not!  I've worked hard to look as good as I do!}  - but even your  protesting thoughts are cut off as she screams: "SILENCE!".  She  continues: "MY  BODY ON THIS PLANE MUST LOOK MORE ... EXOTIC.  OUR SKIN TONE ... THAT  WON'T DO AT ALL ..." - you look down at your hands, finding them turning  a dark shade of pink - "OUR HAIR - IT MUST BE LONGER, MORE VIBRANT..."   - flowing purple locks cascade down your back - "AND OUR FACE.  IT MUST  BE MUCH MORE APPROPRIATE ...".  It will be some time until you can look  in a mirror; but when you finally can you see your new, oddly angular  looking face framed by the long purple hair; eyes that are simply  *wrong* looking out from the dark pink skin, between a set of long,  pointed ears.  Your face doesn't look at all human anymore - though you have to admit, it does have a certain exotic beauty ..</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>"LITTLE MAGE" -  the demoness inside you again freezes you in place - "YOUR BODY, IT IS  NOT THE RIGHT SHAPE FOR A DEMONESS OF MY STATURE.  LOOK AT IT - SO WEAK, SO FRAIL.  WE MUST ATTEND TO IT."  Even as she says it, you can feel the changes begin.   You gain several inches of height, even as you feel your shoulders broaden considerably, reaching out past the curve of your hips.  Your body instantly gains quite a bit of weight - nearly all of it muscle - though mostly hidden by your soft pink skin.  Flexing your arm now reveals powerful biceps, and your taut abdomen shows quite a bit of musculature as well.  Your mind cries out: {what ... what are you doing to me, demon?  Are you trying to make me into a man?}  There is only mocking laughter within you.  "A MAN?  WOULD A MAN STILL HAVE THOSE TINY TITS OF YOURS?  WOULDN'T A MAN HAVE A BIT MORE BETWEEN 'HIS' LEGS?  STILL ... IF YOU INSIST ..."  Eep.  Though, fortunately(?), she does not force any more changes on you just yet, it is likely only a matter of time ...</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>"LITTLE MAGE"  she calls, and your body instantly stops moving again.  More laughter:  "I SEE YOU ARE ALREADY ADAPTING - I DID NOT EXERT MYSELF TO STOP YOUR  MOTION."  And it's true - you start moving again, wiggling your fingers,  taking a few tentative steps, when her will halts you again in  earnest.  "NOW - NONE OF THAT.  IT DOES PLEASE ME TO SEE THAT YOUR WILL  IS STRONG - THOUGH FALLING BEFORE ME."  {"Just what do you have planned  this time, demon?"} you think to her.  "OH, NOTHING MUCH.  I JUST THINK  THAT *I* ... OR OF COURSE, YOU ... COULD STAND TO BE A WHOLE LOT  SEXIER.  DON'T YOU?"  You gasp as the changes start hitting.  Your already feminine proportions become exaggerated - wider hips, larger ass, longer legs, tinoer waist ... and a weight on your chest suggests you've gone up a cup-size or three. {"What, you're making me into some sort of over-sexed whore?  You ... you bich!"}  "SILENCE, LITTLE  MAGE!"  she practically roars within you.  "JUST FOR THAT ..."  Your  breasts immediately feel like they are on fire - they start  growing, and growing, expanding beyond that of any natural woman you've  ever seen, ending large enough that you can no longer see your feet, and  have difficulty balancing.  "ANY *FURTHER* COMPLAINTS THEN?"  You  remain silent, fearful of what else she might do.  At least she stopped trying to make you more masculine ... didn't she?</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>"OH ... LITTLE  MAGE ..." the voice inside you calls out; you stand quiet, obediently,  of your own accord.  "THE TIME HAS COME TO POSSESS YOU FULLY, I THINK  ..."  Frightened, but at the same time feeling an unnaturally lustful  anticipation, your try to watch the changes to your body - though all you  can truly see below your enormous breasts are the tips of your  fingernails lengthening, forming into claws.  Though you're pretty sure  what other -orgasmic!- sensations coming from your warping body mean.   The feeling of your spine ejaculating outward must be a long demon tail  coming forth, likely with the demoness's own heart-shaped tip.  The  feeling of your shoulder blades ripping open, feeling as if two new limbs  were issuing forth must be your new pair of leathery, bat like wings.   And the intense, throbbing headache, complete with the sensation of two  large points of bone erupting through your forehead must be your new  horns.  What you do not yet realize are the changes to your eyes ...  they are now glowing an orangeish-red, appearing almost as portals to  some infernal plane.  {Are ... are we complete now?} you hesitantly ask,  your defiance starting to fade away.  "NO ... JUST TWO MORE CHANGES,  LITTLE MAGE - AND THEN YOU WILL *TRULY* BE MINE."  Hmm.  But you already  have the perfect succubus body; what more could she possibly  improve on?  "ONE NOW, AND ONE SOON ..."  The pleasure of the first is  like nothing you have ever felt before, as your pathetic human cunt absorbs the demonic energy around it.  As the pubic hair around it reforms into a demonic rune, you inner folds instantly begin to heat to near boiling; fluids begin to drip forth, constantly, even at the few odd moments you aren't aroused.  After a brief session of forced frigging, still feeling a gaping void within, needing to be filled, you remember her words - that a final change is coming.  But - fuck - if that change felt so good, a final one would be even better, right?  Even worth the cost of your soul?</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>"IT IS OVER,  LITTLE MAGE.  I HAVE WON.  I AM IN FULL CONTROL."  And it's true - other  than a small corner of awareness in the back of your mind, you find you  have no other existence, no link to your body at all, except to feel  it, experience its intense sensations.  "OH, I DID PROMISE YOU ONE LAST  CHANGE, DID I NOT?  I ASSUME THERE ARE NO OBJECTIONS?"  You are too  stunned at the complete loss of control to even answer.  "GOOD.  WHILE YOU MAKE A BEAUTIFUL SUCCUBUS, I FEEL LIKE WE COULD BE SO MUCH MORE ..."  And it is so -  from right above your groin, a bit of skin begins to press out, forming into a long, rigid, fleshy tube; soon you are sporting an enormous demon cock, over a foot long, throbbing, rigid, with two giant balls to match.  "MMMM ... I  HOPE YOU LIKE IT - BUT HONESTLY,  I COULDN'T CARE LESS IF YOU DO.  TIME  TO GO OUT THERE AND FUCK EVERYBODY.  OR PERHAPS ..." as she fingers your sulfurous pussy - "GET FUCKED OURSELF.  PERHAPS OF THAT NICE CULTIST THAT  SUMMONED ME FIRST?"  And - even from your tiny corner of awareness, you  agree - you just know that fucking and being fucked in this body will  feel amazing.  You doubt you could ever bring yourself to change it ...  though, just perhaps, if an outsider took the initiative ... maybe you  could work at helping the exorcism?  </TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>You intone the words of the spell: "Exeunt omnes!" - the lights around you flicker at just the first syllables, when pronounced by a powerful mage.  "Exeunt omnes spiritae corpus!  Possidete est formae de semimarem duodecim daemonum!"  The lights go dark, and a circle of flame erupts from the ground; a rather attractive, but insubstantial looking demoness emerges from it.  "SO, MAGUS" she addresses you in a deep resonant voice, "YOU HAVE SUMMONED ME - EXACTLY HOW DO YOU PLAN ON KEEPING ME FROM POSSESSING YOUR BODY NOW?  JUST WHAT DO YOU HAVE TO OFFER ME?"  Her wispy form then moves up ... to kiss you?  No ... she's trying to flow into your open mouth.  "Stop!"  you cry, thinking quickly.  "I, ah ... I have prepared another body for you to inhabit!"  Picking someone at random, you point at a startled man nearbly.  "Him!  Take him instead of me!"  She grins wickedly at you:  "SO WILLING TO SELL OUT A FELLOW WIZARD TO COVER YOUR MISTAKE, MAGUS?  HELL WILL HAVE YOUR SOUL  EVENTUALLY THEN, THERE IS NO NEED FOR MY HELP.  YOUR 'FRIEND' THOUGH ..."  she sizes him up.  "A MAN?  SURELY, IN *THIS* TOWN, YOU COULD HAVE FOUND ME AN ATTRACTIVE FEMALE TO INHABIT?  NO MATTER, I CAN ADAPT."  Slowly, horrifyingly, two feet of ridged demon cock erupts from her loins.  She smirks at you "EMPOWER MY POSSESSION OF YOUR ENEMY, MAGUS ... OR YOU'LL BECOME *VERY* FAMILIAR WITH THIS."  And then she is off, running towards your enemy, practically leaping inside him. He looks around startled, having not really been paying attention to the exchange ... perhaps listening now to the evil voice within him...</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>The demoness calls to you, from inside the man you cowardly sent her into in place of yourself.  "MAGUS - YOU *WILL* LEND ME YOUR POWER TO CONSUME YOUR RIVAL'S SOUL - UNLESS YOU'D RATHER OFFER YOURSELF UP TO ME INSTEAD?"  You stand there trembling, and begin to channel mana into the man's body.  "'NO'?  I THOUGHT NOT ..."  Stunned, you watch as your victim's body begins to shift.  His skin, from head to toe, turns a dark shade of pink.  Purple hair erupts from his scalp in waves, full, voluminous, reaching down to his ass.  Their face begins to simply melt, re-shifting; when it is over it looks - angular, exotic.  The eyes are simply *wrong*, and the ears are pointed; not only does your victim not look male from the neck up anymore, they don't even look human!  "REMEMBER MAGUS, THIS COULD *STILL* BE YOU INSTEAD..." she calls, as you quickly flee the scene.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>Again, you see your victim.  "MAGUS - MORE MANA IF YOU PLEASE ..."  You hesitate.   "IF YOU'D RATHER, THERE IS STILL TIME FOR ME TO POSSESS YOUR SHELL OF A BODY INSTEAD."  Quickly, you channel into your sacrifice's changing body.  The demoness is really working him over this time - though it's getting hard to think of the poor soul as 'him'.  He loses several  inches of height; his shoulders narrow, his hips widen, his legs lengthening in proportion to his body.  The muscles beneath his pink skin,  if anything, actually grow - though as his skin softens and his whole  body takes on a curvier, rounder look, their appearance winds up  minimized.  When all is said and done, he resembles nothing so much as a pink-skinned, purple-haired amazon - you look on, almost admiring the demoness's craftsmanship.  "LIKE WHAT YOU SEE MAGUS?  THIS COULD STILL BE YOU..."  Eep.  </TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>The changing man walks up to you, and you hear the demoness's voice from within him  "YOU KNOW THE DRILL, MAGUS - MORE MANA.  NOW."  You quickly begin to channel.  This time, nearly all traces of your victim's masculinity vanish.   Wide hips, huge ass, long legs, tiny waist ... 'he' gets them all, concluding with two growing bulges on his chest, resolving into C-cup breasts.  'His' eyes glaze over briefly - perhaps an internal argument with the demon?  You almost wish you could hear ... but if it was indeed an argument, 'he' clearly lost.  His breasts suddenly balloon outward, Ds, Es, Fs, onward far past your ability to judge, far past the ability of nature unassisted by magic or cosmetic surgery.  "LOVELY, AREN'T THEY" the demoness calls after you as you again take the coward's way out, running.  "THEY COULD STILL BE YOURS..."</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>The changing ... man(?) approaches you again - this time, the command is in his own, high-pitched voice: "Please, continue - the demon, she commands it!"  Obliging, still afraid of the consequences if you do not, you channel yet more magic into him - this time causing him to rapidly gain demonic features.  Long curved horns from their head; claws on their fingers; thick, leathery bat wings on their back; a long, sinuous, heart-shaped tail erupting from their rear.  And their eyes - god, their eyes! - like to orange-red portals to Hell ...  "WHAT IS THE MATTER MAGUS?  FRIGHTENED?"  the demoness gloats.  "WATCH, YOU'LL JUST LOVE THIS THEN."  So saying, your eyes are drawn to the man's crotch - the small human dick there the main remnant of his masculinity - as you watch it turn red, and begin to swell, and swell, and swell, the sack beneath it following suit.  It even cums on the spot, fountaining almost a liter of thick black cum; and in mere seconds afterwards, it is hard again.  "WHAT'S WRONG MAGUS, AFRAID I'LL USE THIS ON YOU?"  You flee, yet again.  "THAT'S RIGHT ... YOU HAD BETTER RUN ... BUT I KNOW YOU CAN'T STAY AWAY.  YOU *WILL* BE BACK TO FINISH THIS."</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>The demoness walks up to you - or you suppose, your former victim, though there is essentially none of him left; possibly a slight twinkle in her infernal eyes, though you don't dare to look for long.  "WELL MAGUS - DO YOU LIKE OUR WORK?  IS MY FORM NOT BEAUTIFUL TO YOU?  COME NOW - ONE MORE JOLT OF MAGIC, AND IT WILL BE COMPLETE!"  You do not resist.  Though you can barely see it behind the huge cock and swinging nutsack, a tight, steaming, sulfurous cleft opens in the demoness's groin; pushing her sack aside, her clawed fingers plunge in and out of the bright-red hole as she continues to address you.  "SURELY YOU WISH TO FUCK OR BE FUCKED BY THIS PERFECT BODY, MAGUS?  AFTER WE'RE DONE, MAYBE I'LL MAKE ONE FOR YOU TOO..."  You flee, the new omnibus laughing all the while.  She looks extremely powerful - dangerous - but at least one thought cheers you - you are SURE you saw a glimmer of your old rival's soul inside her as you ran.  Perhaps he will be able to assist you somehow, should you ever gather the courage to exorcise this infernal horror?</TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>You  intone the words of the spell: "Exeunt omnes!" - the lights around you  flicker at just the first syllables, when pronounced by a powerful  mage.  "Exeunt omnes spiritae corpus!  Possidete est formae de semimarem  duodecim daemonum!"  The lights go dark, and a circle of flame erupts  from the ground; a rather attractive, but insubstantial looking demoness  emerges from it.  "SO, MAGUS" she addresses you in a deep resonant  voice, "YOU HAVE SUMMONED ME - EXACTLY HOW DO YOU PLAN ON KEEPING ME  FROM POSSESSING YOUR BODY NOW?  JUST WHAT DO YOU HAVE TO OFFER ME?"  Her  wispy form then moves up ... to kiss you?  No ... she's trying to flow  into your open mouth.  "Stop!"  you cry, thinking quickly.  "I, ah ... I  have prepared another body for you to inhabit!"  Picking someone at  random, you point at a startled woman nearbly.  "Her!  Take her instead of  me!"  She grins wickedly at you:  "SO WILLING TO SELL OUT A FELLOW WIZARD TO COVER YOUR MISTAKE, MAGUS?  HELL WILL HAVE YOUR SOUL EVENTUALLY THEN, THERE IS NO NEED FOR  MY HELP.  YOUR 'FRIEND' THOUGH ..."  she sizes her up.  "OOH, SHE IS QUITE THE COMELY ONE, IS SHE NOT.  STILL, SHE COULD BE MORE ... MUCH MORE"  Slowly, horrifyingly, two feet of  ridged demon cock erupts from her loins.  She smirks at you "EMPOWER MY  POSSESSION OF YOUR ENEMY, MAGUS ... OR YOU'LL BECOME *VERY* FAMILIAR  WITH THIS."  And then she is off, running towards your enemy,  practically leaping inside her.   Your victim looks around startled, having not  really been paying attention to the exchange ... perhaps listening now  to the evil voice within her...</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>The demoness  calls to you, from inside the woman you cowardly sent her into in place of  yourself.  "MAGUS - YOU *WILL* LEND ME YOUR POWER TO CONSUME YOUR  RIVAL'S SOUL - UNLESS YOU'D RATHER OFFER YOURSELF UP TO ME INSTEAD?"   You stand there trembling, and begin to channel mana into the woman's  body.  "'NO'?  I THOUGHT NOT ..."  Stunned, you watch as your victim's  body begins to shift.  Her skin, from head to toe, turns a dark shade  of pink.  Purple hair erupts from her scalp in waves, full,  voluminous, reaching down to her ass.  Her face begins to simply  melt, re-shifting; when it is over it looks - angular, exotic.  The eyes  are simply *wrong*, and the ears are pointed; she no longer even looks human!  Though she does seem to possess a terrible beauty ...  "REMEMBER MAGUS, THIS COULD *STILL* BE YOU INSTEAD..." she calls, as you  quickly flee the scene.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>Again, you see  your victim.  "MAGUS - MORE MANA IF YOU PLEASE ..."  You hesitate.   "IF  YOU'D RATHER, THERE IS STILL TIME FOR ME TO POSSESS YOUR SHELL OF A  BODY INSTEAD."  Quickly, you channel into your sacrifice's changing  body.  The demoness is really working her over this time - though the demoness is making it a bit harder to fully think of your victim as a 'her'.  She gains several  inches of height, even as her shoulders broaden considerably,  reaching out past the curve of her hips.  Her body instantly gains  quite a bit of weight - nearly all of it muscle - though mostly hidden  by her still soft soft pink skin.  You see her flex her arms, revealing powerful biceps,  and her exposed, taut abdomen shows quite a bit of musculature as well.  When all is said and done, she resembles nothing so much as a  pink-skinned, purple-haired amazon - you look on, almost admiring the  demoness's craftsmanship.  "LIKE WHAT YOU SEE MAGUS?  THIS COULD STILL  BE YOU..."  Eep.  </TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>The changing woman  walks up to you, and you hear the demoness's voice from within her   "YOU KNOW THE DRILL, MAGUS - MORE MANA.  NOW."  You quickly begin to channel.  While the prior round made your victim more muscular, this seems to only be enhancing her femininity.   Wider hips, a larger ass, longer legs, a tinier waist ... she gets them  all, concluding with a wobbling from her chest, as her two already-substantial breasts swell a cup size or three.  Her eyes glaze over briefly - perhaps an internal  argument with the demon?  You almost wish you could hear ... but if it  was indeed an argument, 'your victim clearly lost.  Her breasts suddenly balloon  outward, onward, far past your ability to judge, far past  the ability of nature unassisted by magic or cosmetic surgery.  "LOVELY,  AREN'T THEY" the demoness calls after you as you again take the coward's  way out, running.  "THEY COULD STILL BE YOURS..."</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>The changing woman approaches you again - this time, the command is in her own,  strangely low-pitched voice: "Please, continue - the demon, she commands it!"   Obliging, still afraid of the consequences if you do not, you channel  yet more magic into her - this time causing her to rapidly gain demonic  features.  Long curved horns from their head; claws on their fingers;  thick, leathery bat wings on their back; a long, sinuous, heart-shaped  tail erupting from their rear.  And their eyes - god, their eyes! - like  to orange-red portals to Hell ...  "WHAT IS THE MATTER MAGUS?   FRIGHTENED?"  the demoness gloats.  "WATCH, YOU'LL JUST LOVE THIS  THEN."  So saying, your eyes are drawn to the woman's crotch - as you watch her folds turn bright red, and begin to constantly seep steaming feminine juices, even as her pubic hair reforms into a demonic rune.   "WHAT'S WRONG MAGUS, AFRAID TO FUCK ME?  THINK IT MIGHT COST YOU YOUR SOUL?"  You flee, yet  again.  "THAT'S RIGHT ... YOU HAD BETTER RUN ... BUT I KNOW YOU CAN'T  STAY AWAY.  YOU *WILL* BE BACK TO FINISH THIS."</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>The demoness  walks up to you - or you suppose, your former victim, though there is  essentially none of her left; possibly a slight twinkle in her infernal  eyes, though you don't dare to look for long.  "WELL MAGUS - DO YOU LIKE  OUR WORK?  IS MY FORM NOT BEAUTIFUL TO YOU?  COME NOW - ONE MORE JOLT  OF MAGIC, AND IT WILL BE COMPLETE!"  You do not resist.  From above her sulfurous sex, you see a long fleshy tube emerge, then swell into immensity - she is soon sporting over a foot of thick, rigid demon cock, with heavy balls to match swinging over her feminine folds.  "SURELY YOU WISH TO FUCK OR BE FUCKED  BY THIS PERFECT BODY, MAGUS?  AFTER WE'RE DONE, MAYBE I'LL MAKE ONE FOR  YOU TOO..."  You flee, the new omnibus laughing all the while.  She  looks extremely powerful - dangerous - but at least one thought cheers  you - you are SURE you saw a glimmer of your old rival's soul inside her  as you ran.  Perhaps he will be able to assist you somehow, should you  ever gather the courage to exorcise this infernal horror?</TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>

</Form>
