<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>As the black bolt of energy is about to hit you, you try to block it with your hands. It doesn't seem to do much except changing your fingernails into black claws. You don't think much of it and quickly reverse the change. </TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>You almost manage to dodge the spell your opponent throws at you but it manages to graze your shoulder, the changes are bigger this time around as your arm slowly changes and twists assuming the form of a bear's front leg complete with paw and claws, the white fur sprouting tells you that it must be a polar bears.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>The black bolt hits your weakened body square in the chest this time. Your muscles bulge as you slowly change to a quadrupedal form and fur sprouts over your body. Your opponent seem to be hell bend on changing you into a Polar bear for some reason. As you concentrate on halting the changes before they affect your head or mind they move in closer trying to take advantage of the distraction only to be greeted by your claw as you swipe at em. They managed to dodge your claw all though it barely missed em. Surely that little experience will make them reconsider their foolish attempt to turn you into a wild beast.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>You've had enough, this time you get hit on purpose, If they want to turn you into a Polar bear, then they will pay for their stupidity. Intent on mauling them to death as soon as the spell changes your form. You let it change you willingly, your muscles bulge, the fur spreads and claws form as your face twists and contorts into a the bear muzzle. Something seems to be wrong though. No matter how hard you bear down on em, your movements are sluggish and slow, and it seems to be getting worse.... it dawns on you that the spell might not really be changing you into a simple bear and you quickly try reverse the changes before they can overpower and lock you into place although it takes a lot out of you.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>Your previous mistake costs you dearly, the exhaustion left you winded and a easy target, your opponent seems to be smiling fondly at you as they once again hit you with the black energy of their spell. The changes come swiftly due to its energy saturating your form. Within moments you become a polar bear, but something is wrong, you can't seem to bring yourself to harm your captor, quite the opposite you catch yourself smiling at them fondly. Your body locks up and starts to shrink and stiffen, this radical change is enough to jolt you out of your revere and you manage to fight off the spell, slowly but steadily you turn back. That progress seem to be met with a frown and a hint of sadness in their eyes.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>The final bolt that hits you seals your fate, nearly instantly you turn into a polar bear before you start to shrink. One of the last things you see are how your arms lock into place as if your going to give a hug. Your insides change as your being filled with fluff and spice and everything nice. Your sight is slightly impaired as a strand of Silvery hair grows over your eye and it dawns on you that you've been turned into a cuddly little teddy bear. Your captor coos and smiles at you, quickly picking you up and snuggling you tight, it doesn't feel bad at all, You can't help but feel loved and save in the embrace of your beloved, after all some day they will manage to break the curse allowing you to finally embrace em again.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>You fire the spell in the form of a black bolt of energy at your enemy. As it is about to hit them they try to deflect it with their hands. The spell doesn't seem to do much except turn their fingernails into black claws and they quickly reverse the change.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>Your opponent is better prepared now but your spell is to quick, they almost manage to dodge it but it grazes their shoulder, changing and twisting their arm into the front leg of a bear. The white fur sprouting confirms that they are changing into a polar bear before they manage to halt and reverse the changes.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>Your black bolt hits em square in their chest this time. You can see their muscles bulge as they slowly change to a quadrupedal form and white fur sprouts all over their body.  You sense A chance as their concentrate on reversing the changes before it can affect their head and mind but as you close in they notice you and bear their claws down on you. Startled you jump back as the claw flies past your face. Maybe turning em into a wild beast before the final changes wasn't the best idea for your spell.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>You strike your opponent easily this time. But something is wrong they are .. smiling. They got hit on purpose and you soon find out why, as the unhindered changes wrack their body, quickly changing them into a polar bear, muscles bulging, joints twisting while fur sprouts everywhere and their face contorts into a polar bears muzzle  they approach you quickly.  They are in no real danger now that the physical form is complete as the spell further changes em, diminishing their size and making it harder and harder to move, Despite their frustration they seem to have noticed that too and quickly work to rework your spell before it's too late, huffing and wheezing. In their panic it seems to have taken a lot more out of em as a calm reversal could have. Lucky!
</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>You press forward and hit them again before they are able to catch their breath. Unable to suppress a smile you stare at em as the changes happen swiftly due to the previous spells energy still lingering in their body. Even though they have become a true Beast of a polar bear they can't seem to find the will to attack you, The mental portion of the spell seem to finally affect em. Their muzzle contorts slightly into something that could be called a smile even. Their body shrinks and stiffens as they are about to change into a adorable plush bear, unfortunately that seem to have shocked em out of the revere and they quickly shake of the mental manipulation and they slowly return to normal. You can't help but feel an intense sadness as you were so close to getting your beloved plush bear.

</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>As your final bolt hits them their fate is sealed. They change into a polar bear within the blink of an eye before they start to shrink. Their arms lock into place as if they wanted to give you a hug. Their insides seem to change as the movements ebb down and the cutest little outfits forms on their body, Their muzzle becomes only hinted at with black thread replacing their lips And Silvery hair strands block the view of one  their red glass eyes. You pick up your little price and squeeze them gently, knowing that the spell made sure that they think of you as their lover rather then captor. Willing to give you all they have to help you in your "quest to save them".</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
