<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<Description>This one time human is now a gorgeous unicorn mare. A slight light glows from their pure white fur, shimmering brighter around their silver horn and silver hooves. They swish their flowing white tail to give a slight flash of their animalistic sex, but they are a creature of purity and they suppress those feral desires of the flesh. Her presence is calming to those who are innocent and horrifying to those who practice greedy and lustful magics. They are the essence of purity and compassion and she now lives to protect the innocent from losing their minds, bodies, and souls.</Description>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>You feel a wave of white magic wash over your body. You turn to watch as globs of black and pink magic are slowly blown down the white tunnel that is surrounding you. As you watch the manifestation of your perverted desires and sins blow away you fail to notice your body changing. Your old identity was blown away and soon you collapse to the ground, feeling reborn and very weak. Your body feels alien to you as you look down at your slender fingers and hands. Your eyes widen as you slowly follow up your silk smooth skin of your arms to your chest, now sporting a pair of petite breasts. Using your hands you feel down your taut belly and over your rounded hips and rump, exploring the unfamiliar curves. You even feel a strange wetness grown between your legs but you ignore the sensation, for lust is wrong. You blink at that thought and begin to remember your old self. You stand shakily to your feet and wonder if your opponent was only trying to change you into a slender young woman, but as a strand of your now snow white hair fall in front of your crystal blue eyes does a sense of panic settle into your heart. You can't help but wonder just what they are planning to do to you or whether or not you should fight back or flee.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>You gasp as the tunnel of white magic surrounds you again, this time much less globs of pink and black are blown out of your body and soul. Your slender body drops to your knees, a sharp pinch forming in the center of your forehead. You feel the spot with your fingers, gasping as you find something cool and smooth slowly sprouting from the point. You whimper as another pinching sensation forms right above your backside, a small numb growing from your tailbone. With a powerful shudder the nub bursts forth with thousands of white strands of hair that form into a flowing tail, reaching down to your ankles if you were standing. You run your slender fingers through your new tail before feeling the small horn in the center of your forehead. Somewhere deep in your mind you feel a small bubble of anger form, thinking about how you should change that annoying opponent into a lovely horse cock dildo or something. But the thought of creating such a perverted item makes you a little sick to your stomach and you cast the thought aside and focus on the innocent laughter of children to regain your composure. But this to causes you great confusion, just what the hell are they doing to you!?</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>You lift your face towards the blinding light, welcoming the cleansing energies the flood into and over your nubile form. Your tail swishes in a mixture of pleasure and discomfort as an itching sensation spreads across your form. Fine silken white fur begins to sprout across your body, soon covering your entire form in a downy coat of snow white fur. You smile gently at your attacker, wishing no harm on them as your horn grew even longer and took on a brilliant silver color. Your back begins to ache and you feel wobbly on your feet. Somewhere in your mind you can hear a small voice telling you that this is wrong, that you sin is a part of being a person. You simply smile and ignore that whispering plead, loving the purity of your existence and your chaste habits.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>The tunnel of light surrounds you once more, blowing your hair and tail in a majestic manner. Your face begins to ache, but you accept this pain and discomfort because in your mind you are simply accepting your role as a symbol of purity. As your nostrils flare, your eyes taking on a glowing silver coloration, you find your fingers and toes becoming oddly stiff. You raise your hand to your face, perplexed at the sight of your equine snout but you become even more confused to see solid lumps of silver on the ends of your fingers. You falter at the sigh, as a bit of residual fear dips into your heart. The material on your fingers looks like that of a horses hoof and you aren't an animal....are you? You toss your mane and try to remember who you really are.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>You feel your back pop suddenly as you fall forward onto all fours, your hands touching the ground and shimmering into silver hooves with white tassels on your ankles. Your rump expands to a mare-like size, your tail flitting down to hide your unmentionable parts from the view of those who are corrupt and wicked. You smile and admire your new yet very familiar body. You begin to prance around, testing out your slender yet powerful body as a purification magic begins to radiate from your core. But deep inside your mind is that little voice, begging you to stop before it's to late.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>You shudder as the tunnel appears around you one last time. Something grips tightly in your mind, sobbing and crying as it tries to stay inside you.....inside their old body. You smile and appear before them, gently loosening their grip for them. "Let go my little one....you and I are one now....accept the purity of our existence." You speak and the dark little blob quivers, the last of your lust, wickedness, and humanity slipping away into the oblivion of purity. You smile and jump out of the tunnel and looks around, your mind expanding to sense those who need your help. You gallop off to protect the crying children who are suffering from this war of erotic fire, greed, and desire!</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>Your opponent falters as they feel a wave of white magic wash over their body. All they can do is turn to watch as globs of black and pink magic are slowly blown down the white tunnel that is surrounding them. As they watch the manifestation of your perverted desires and sins blow away, they fail to notice their body changing. They collapse to the ground as their body changes, the magic weakening them considerably. They look down as their body as it is a stranger to them, taking note of their slender fingers and hands. Their eyes widen as they slowly follow up their silk smooth skin of your arms to their chest, now sporting a pair of petite breasts, indicating that this new body of theirs is very definitely female. Using her hands, she feels down her taut belly and over her rounded hips and rump, exploring the unfamiliar curves. You grin as you notice a wetness between her legs, but she seems to, interestingly, blatantly ignore it, as if trying to deny its pleasures. She blinks at that thought and, to your dismay, seems to begin to remember her old self. She stand shakily to her feet, looking at you in confusion, before her eyes settle on the hair that drifts in front of her, which causes the confusion to turn to panic as she unfortunately turns back. However, your opponent still seems rather confused as to what you were trying to do. Best to make sure you keep him/her off his/her guard, so better to let the spell set in…</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>They gasp as the tunnel of white magic surrounds them again, this time much less globs of pink and black are blown out of their body and soul. Their slender body drops to their knees, a small lump forming in the center of their forehead. They feel the spot with their fingers, gasping as they find something cool and smooth slowly sprouting from the point. They whimper as another lump forms right above your backside, a small numb growing from their tailbone. With a powerful shudder the nub bursts forth with thousands of white strands of hair that form into a flowing tail, reaching down to their ankles if they were standing. They run their slender fingers through their new tail before feeling the small horn in the center of their forehead. They look at you with a hint of anger and confusion as you continue to change them further.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>They lift their face towards the blinding light, welcoming the cleansing energies the flood into and over their nubile form. Their tail swishes in a mixture of pleasure and discomfort as goosebumps spreads across their form. Fine silken white fur begins to sprout across their body, soon covering their entire form in a downy coat of snow white fur. They smile gently at you, seemingly wishing no harm on you as their horn grew even longer and took on a brilliant silver color. Their back arches and they look wobbly on their feet. </TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>The tunnel of light surrounds them once more, blowing their hair and tail in a majestic manner. Their face begins to lengthen, but they accept this pain and discomfort because in their mind they are simply accepting their role as a symbol of purity. As their nostrils flare, their eyes taking on a glowing silver coloration, they find their fingers and toes becoming oddly stiff. They raise their hand to their face, perplexed at the sight of their equine snout but they become even more confused to see solid lumps of silver on the ends of their fingers. They falter at the sigh, as a bit of residual fear appears in their eyes. The material on their fingers looks like that of a horses hoof. They toss their mane in annoyance, trying to figure out who they are.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>You hear their back pop suddenly as they fall forward onto all fours, their hands touching the ground and shimmering into silver hooves with white tassels on their ankles. Their rump expands to a mare-like size, their tail flitting down to hide your unmentionable parts from the view of those who are corrupt and wicked. They smile and admire their new yet very familiar body. They begin to prance around, testing out their slender yet powerful body as a purification magic begins to radiate from their core. But deep inside their mind is that little voice, begging them to stop before it's to late.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>They shudder as the tunnel appears around them one last time. Something grips tightly in front of their face, sobbing and crying as it tries to stay inside them.....inside their old body. They smile and gently blow against the creature, gently loosening their grip for them. "Let go my little one....you and I are one now....accept the purity of our existence." They speak and the dark little blob quivers, the last of their lust, wickedness, and humanity slipping away into the oblivion of purity. They smile and jump out of the tunnel and looks around, their mind expanding to sense those who need their help. They gallop off to protect the crying children who are suffering from this war of erotic fire, greed, and desire!</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
