<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>You watch as your foe prepares an elaborate spell. They raise their hand as if to cast… and the spell simply fizzles out at their fingertips.  You hurt yourself laughing at them more than their magic ever could.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>You raise an eyebrow as your opponent slowly creeps closer.  You barely bother to react as they dive forward and manage to slap you on the ass.  You gasp as a ripple of magic forces your hips out and pulls your waist in.  You still dispel it easily, though.  This opponent really is pathetic.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>Your opponent begins to circle.  Their magic is poor, but you still don’t want to let them touch you again if you can help it.  You carelessly stumble as you turn and they strike. Their fingertips running across your belly with an electric tingle.  You freeze as your waist shrinks down, and your crotch… oh, what’s happening to your crotch!?  You barely register as your opponent’s other hand brushes through your hair causing it to grow long and rich.  The sharp pain of your ears elongating snaps you out of it, and you change back.  Quickly.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>You are starting to realize that your opponent isn't the pushover you thought, but mocking them is still too fun for you to leave just yet.  A sudden lunge and they have your wrists. Your body spasms as a huge wave of magic washes over you.  Your muscles vanish, your shoulders lose their manliness, while your chest balloons out, forming two very distinct breasts.  You stare down as the magic reshapes your waist, and your hips flare out.  A surge flows through your crotch, and a reactive grab confirms your new womanhood.  The magic continues down your athletic legs and you look back up to your captor.  With a laugh you realize how easily your new body could break free, and you quickly do.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>Knowing how strong your opponent’s magic is up close, you are ready for anything.  Except when they dive straight at you and knock you to the ground.  You feel your body flow back into the beautiful elf before you hit the ground. You land with your opponent straddling you and sending wave upon wave of magic through your body.  Squirming you manage to wrap your legs around them your new breasts pushed firmly into their chest.  You breathe heavily from the struggle and look up to see your opponent is star-struck.  Flushed, they slowly lean in and you realize they are trying to kiss you.  You shove them off and twirl back to your feet, changing back to your male self as you do.  But you can’t quite get the image of their lips out of your mind…</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>The constant onslaught of magic and touch is getting to be too much for you.  The feeling of that elf body wrapped around your opponent is SO distracting.  So much that you react far too slowly to stop them jumping forward and wrapping their arms around your waist.  By the time you bring your arms up to try and fight back they are already toned and feminine. You can feel your breasts pushing out against their chest as a pleasant warmth spring into life in your new female sex.  You try to break free when the second wave of magic hits, this time attacking your mind.  An emotional onslaught smashes your mental defenses, as feelings of responsibility, dignity, and obligations overwrite your desire to fight back, and something else... something that has been denied from you since your royal birth… something someone of a lesser station could give in to with no repercussions. An overwhelming lust to use your body for nothing but sex fills you.  As you give in to this desire you feel a tiny diamond tiara appear in your hair.  As your lips touch the magic sparks, and you know it is over.  You’re an elf.  You’re a princess.  And you’re very, very horny.</TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>You watch as your foe prepares an elaborate spell. They raise their hand as if to cast… and the spell simply fizzles out at their fingertips.  You hurt yourself laughing at them more than their magic ever could.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>You raise one eyebrow as your opponent slowly creeps closer.  You barely bother to react as they dive forward and manage to grab your wrist.  Magic courses up your arm, turning it pale and athletic.  With a shake, the changes vanish.  This opponent really is pathetic.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>Your opponent begins to circle.  Their magic is poor, but you still don’t want to let them touch you again if you can help it.  You carelessly stumble as you turn and they strike. Their fingertips running across your belly with an electric tingle.  You freeze as your waist becomes toned and athletic, easily seen as your clothing becomes transparent.  Your opponent’s other hand reaches up, creating a ring of flowers that binds your rich brown hair.  A pain in your ears brings you back to your senses, and you quickly dispel the magic.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>You are starting to realize that your opponent isn't the pushover you thought, but mocking them is still too fun for you to leave just yet.  A sudden lunge and they have your wrists. Your body spasms as a huge wave of magic washes over you.  Your arms become toned and athletic, while still maintaining their softness.  Your breasts shrink slightly as your skin becomes pale and flawless.  You feel your face shift slightly, as your ears lengthen.  As your eyes shift to green they look back at your captor.  With a laugh you realize how easily your new body could break free, and you quickly do.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>Knowing how strong your opponent’s magic is up close, you are ready for anything.  Except when they dive straight at you and knock you to the ground.  You feel your body flow back into the beautiful elf before you hit the ground. You land with your opponent straddling you and sending wave upon wave of magic through your body.  Squirming you manage to wrap your legs around them, your perkier breasts pushed firmly into their chest.  You breathe heavily from the struggle and look up to see your opponent is star-struck.  Flushed, they slowly lean in and you realize they are trying to kiss you.  You shove them off and twirl back to your feet, changing back to your old self as you do.  But you can’t quite get the image of their lips out of your mind…</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>The constant onslaught of magic and touch is getting to be too much for you.  The feeling of that elf body wrapped around your opponent is SO distracting.  So much that you react far too slowly to stop them jumping forward and wrapping their arms around your waist.  By the time you bring your arms up to try and fight back they are already toned and feminine. You can feel your breasts pushing out against their chest as a pleasant warmth springs into life in your sex.  You try to break free when the second wave of magic hits, this time attacking your mind.  An emotional onslaught smashes your mental defenses, as feelings of responsibility, dignity, and obligations overwrite your desire to fight back, and something else... something that has been denied from you since your royal birth… something someone of a lesser station could give in to with no repercussions. An overwhelming lust to use your body for nothing but sex fills you.  As you give in to this desire you feel a tiny diamond tiara appear in your hair.  As your lips touch the magic sparks, and you know it is over.  You’re an elf.  You’re a princess.  And you’re very, very horny.</TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>You cast the spell with an elaborate twirl and fling the magic at your opponent.  The magic crackles across your fingertips... And then fades as soon as you send it at your, now laughing, antagonist.  You are going to have to get a LOT closer to wipe that smirk off their face...</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>Your opponent, still mocking your abilities, laughs as you approach.  He barely reacts as you dive to the side and slap him across the ass, sending magic coursing through him.  From behind you see his waist shrink, as his hips swell.  You hear a gasp but, by the time they turn to face you, they have returned to normal.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>You circle your opponent, looking for an opening.  They misstep and stumble, and you dart forward to run your fingertips across their waist.  Again their belly shrinks and becomes toned and feminine.  He freezes in shock as his hips begin to expand, and you use the opportunity to bring your other hand behind his head.  Immediately the magic lengthens his hair, turning it a rich brown.  Your opponent pushes you away and returns to normal, but not before you see very distinct and very pointy ears.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>Your opponent is starting to be wary around you, but he is still too confident to back away to safety.  You lunge and grab his wrists, sending magic arcing through him.  He spasms as the energy transforms him, first melting away the muscles of his arms, then shrinking his shoulders and torso down as his chest balloons out.  You both stare at his small and perky breasts as the energy continues unabated down past his reducing waist, across her expanding hips, and eventually grounded through her toned and athletic legs.  She looks back up and you lock eyes with a beautiful elf maiden, her pointy ears rising to the braids in her long brown hair.  With a quick twist she is free and dances back, laughing at how easily she escaped and returns to normal.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>You don't wait for an opening, you simply dive on your opponent, knocking him to the ground.  The magic of your touch rapidly changes him back into the beautiful elf, but you continue to send waves of magic through her and you watch as her top turns into a tight blue corset and her pants merge into a dress that becomes transparent with a touch of your finger.  She squirms under you, her legs wrapping around yours as her breasts push against your chest.  She stops as you lock eyes and you truly realise how beautiful a woman you have created.  She raises her head, her lips parting slightly as she bring her mouth to yours.  You lean in... and she shoves you off with a laugh that sounds like bells chiming a dedication to your failure.  By the time you get to your feet, your opponent is back to their arrogant male self.  They do seem to be looking at you strangely, though...</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>You notice your opponent, over-stimulated from the constant magical onslaught, distractedly looks you up and down.  He blushes slightly, his thoughts of you betraying him, and you realise it is time to strike.  Your smile takes them off guard, and he doesn't react until your arms are around his waist and your magic is already well on the way to finishing his transformation.  In seconds his body flows into the beautiful elf, who tries to use her agility to break free.  You are prepared this time, and send waves of emotional memories into her - a tiresome adolescence learning responsibility, constant reminders to remain dignified, strict adherence to obligations of her station... and years upon years of repressed lust forced upon her by her station.  If they're going to act like a princess, you are going to make them into one.  As the new feelings merge with her old, she stops struggling against you and begins to fight her growing needs.  As she opens her eyes and stares into yours you realise that her old self lost and the beautiful - and very horny - princess is here to stay.  She leans in, her eyes closing again as you change her clothing and a diamond tiara appears perched above her flushed face.  As she kisses you the magic finalises, sealing her into this form for good.  As you kiss her back you wonder... when she makes love, does she leave the crown on?</TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>You cast the spell with an elaborate twirl and fling the magic at your opponent.  The magic crackles across your fingertips... And then fades as soon as you send it at your, now laughing, antagonist.  You are going to have to get a LOT closer to wipe that smirk off their face...

</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>Your opponent, still mocking your abilities, laughs as you approach.  She doesn't even bother with any defensive spells as you get within striking distance.  Quick as a flash you take her hand, sending magic coursing up her arm.  She pulls back as her arm becomes pale and thin, yet toned.  With a shake she is back to normal, but she doesn't look as confident.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>You circle your opponent, looking for an opening.  They misstep and stumble, and you dart forward to run your fingertips across their waist.  The clothes there vanish, and you see her skin lighten and become athletic and toned.  The magic crackles down her clothes, turning it transparent.  She backs away in surprise, but not before you step forward and bring you other hand up behind her head.  The magic flows through your fingers, her hair turning light brown as flowers bloom and wrap her hair in place.  She pushes you away and dispels the magic, but not before you see her very distinct and very pointy ears.

</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>Your opponent is starting to be wary around you, but she is still too confident to back away to safety.  She taunts you by dancing forward, and you manage to catch her wrists, sending magic coursing through her.  She spasms, as her arms become toned and thin, her skin become pale and flawless.  Her breasts shrink, but lift slightly, as subtle changes wrack her body.  Her neck becomes longer and delicate, her facial features become refined and dignified as light brown hair cascades down her back.  You stare as her ears form high points and her eyes flash to green.  The elf maiden stares at you and laughs, and with a quick twist she is free.  She returns to normal with a smirk at how easy she escaped your grasp.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>You don't wait for an opening, you simply dive on your opponent, knocking her to the ground.  The magic of your touch rapidly changes her back into the beautiful elf, but you continue to send waves of magic through her and watch as her top changes into a tight blue corset and her dress becomes transparent with a touch of your fingers.  She squirms under you, her legs wrapping around your waist as her breasts push against yours.  She stops as you lock eyes and you truly realise how beautiful a creature you have created.  She raises her head to yours, her lips parting as she brings her mouth to yours.  You lean in... and she shoves you off with a laugh that sounds like bells chiming a dedication to your failure.  By the time you get to your feet, your opponent is back to their arrogant self.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>You notice your opponent, over-stimulated from the constant magical onslaught, distractedly looks you up and down.  She blushes slightly and you realise it is time to strike.  Your smile takes them off guard, and she doesn't react until your arms are around her waist and your magic is already well on the way to finishing her transformation.  In seconds her body flows into the beautiful elf, who tries to use her agility to break free.  You are prepared this time, and send waves of emotional memories into her - a tiresome adolescence learning responsibility, constant reminders to remain dignified, strict adherence to the obligations of her station... and years upon years of repressed lust forced upon her by her station.  If they're going to act like a princess, you are going to make them into one.  As the new feelings merge with her old, she stops struggling against you and begins to fight her growing needs.  As she opens her eyes and stares into yours you realise that her old self lost and the beautiful - and very horny - princess is here to stay.  She leans in, her eyes closing again as you change her clothing and a diamond tiara appears perched above her flushed face.  As she kisses you the magic finalises, sealing her into this form for good.  As you kiss her back you wonder... when she makes love, does she leave the crown on?</TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>

</Form>
