<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>For a moment your head reels as something tries to force itself inside. Even as you recover from the mental assault you realize something has made you shorter. With a word you reverse the spell.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>Again your head feels the intrusion of another mind, trying to bend you to its will. You throw off the intrusion, and realize that once again you are shorter. Your head and ass feel different and a quick pat reveals your ears have become catlike and shifted to the top of your head and a tail extends from your behind. With an annoyed spat you reverse the spell.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>Once more you feel that presence of another mind probing and melding into yours. A dominant mind which you want to serve. Gathering your will you push them back, finding yourself biting your lip. Your body has shrunk once more and is now covered with glossy black fur. The light seems brighter, and you can feel whiskers on your face. With an annoyed hiss you manage to reverse the spell, but it is more difficult than before.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>That mind presses against yours once again, and you can feel its presence reshaping your own. Suddenly everything seems new and mysterious, and you find a part of you wants to explore it all, and maybe pull a few pranks while you're at it. With what feels like all your resolve you manage to push back this invading presence, and find that your hands have become paws and you're having difficulty remaining on your legs. A desire for fish crosses your mind, but you push it away, hissing as you reverse the spell.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>You wonder if master will give you fish, or let you go cause some chaos with some bunny girls, as you begin to prance about on your four legs. Your glossy black fur almost gleams in the light, and your green eyes seem to produce light all their own. You remain this way for a few moments before it dawns on you that something is wrong. With your master stroking you behind your metaphysical ears it's all you can do to reverse the spell. Even then it was so nice, and you know it wouldn't have been so bad especially if they gave you fish.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>This time you don't even try to resist master's mind. Why would you? It's so much better with them here. You find yourself purring, as you feel your body take its proper quadrupedal shape. Rubbing against your master's legs, you feel a little red collar, complete with bell, form around your throat. Looking up you utter a feline yowl begging your master for some wonderfully delicious fish.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>Narrowing your eyes at your target you release your magic. For a moment you feel their mind, but they resist your attempt to bind them to you. Even the physical change only lasts a moment as you see them shrink down and almost immediately resume their former stature.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>You recite your incantation once more. To your delight their physical change is deeper this time, momentarily giving them cat ears and a tail even as they shrink down to a more fitting size for a pet. Even so they resist the mental bonds and you find yourself scowling a bit as they reverse the changes.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>To your delight it takes them longer to resist your mental invasion this time, and when you are done they look just like a miniature catgirl. As they reverse the spell they even give out a feline hiss, as opposed to a more articulate spell.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>You feel their mind begin to bend to yours, accepting a little piece of you into it, but they manage to force you out. They stand no taller than a cat on its hind legs, and they wobble, their legs halfway between those of a biped and a quadruped as they hiss a counter spell to return to their previous form.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>For a moment they are yours, an extension of your mind residing within them as their master. You can feel their desires, their hungers, and their wants, and you can control them. They're nothing but a little black cat, your pet, and your familiar, but then you feel it resistance stirring, a part which remains their own. Their purring stops as they barely reverse your spell. Perhaps next time?</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>At last you feel them succumb, becoming nothing but your pet. Their body shrinks, fur growing across it as they transform into a svelte, glossy, black cat, a red collar with a silent bell forming around their neck. You reach down to scratch them as you mentally reach out to feel how they are truly yours now. They let out a little yowl, begging for fish, maybe you ought to oblige?</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
