<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>A wave of cosmic power the likes of which you have never felt hits you. You feel a surge in every fiber of your being, and it leaves you feeling elated and on the verge of maniacal laughter. Still, your new-found omnipotence comes with a sense of foreboding, the realization that something is deeply, terribly wrong. You gather what mortal power remains within you and fight back the transformation, filled with a sense of terror over what that spell could have done to you.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>That surge of cosmic power returns, and with it that sense of unease. You can feel your body reacting to it, twisting and shifting, your masculine figure trying to contort into something willowy and feminine. You grit your teeth and force the changes off, but as they leave, so too does the sensation of your connection to the cosmic all.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>Your brow aches as the spell hits you again, a pair of curving horns beginning to grow, and sweep back. Of course more disturbing is that as they grow, your manhood shrinks, seeming to draw in on itself. Whatever this powerful form is, clearly male it is not. You grit your teeth and force off the changes, steeling yourself as you are once more left feeling hollow and disconnected from something greater.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>Your breath catches, and for a moment you find that you can't breathe at all. Your lungs burn for a moment, and then a cool relief flows through you as your own magic sustains you. Your hands go to your face, only to find that you lack a nose or mouth, cutting off any cry of alarm you might want to make. Those horns burst forth, and your genitals once more invert into a feminine form, and you have to really focus to push any of it off, returning yourself to normal with a gasp of cool, fresh air.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>Brass bands form around your wrists, cold and heavy, the bands of a slave. The transformation hits you harder than it has yet so far, twisting your body into a beautiful feminine shape and inverting your genitals in a most uncomfortable manner. Your horns once more burst from your brow, and your hair shimmers brown as it falls almost to your now perky ass. Your mouth and nose seal over, but your eyes open to the mysteries of the universe. For a brief moment, it is as if you understand everything, and it is using that knowledge that you push away the transformations, returning yourself to normal with a sense of sour regret.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>You can't ignore the power seeking to find a home within your soul any longer. You let it in, and with it, feel your mortal soul burn to ashes. You no longer need it. You are one with the cosmos, divine, arcane, infernal, the words don't quite sum up your true place. You are mistress of all, and yet you are bound, only able to use that power to meet the selfish whims of those still mortal. Your body shifts into a beautiful, curvy Arabic symbol of femininity, your eyes going dark, and your lips and nose sealing for eternity, locking you into humble silence. Your horns sprout, and your magic weaves into translucent silks to vaguely provide modesty. You are Djinn... you are eternal.</TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>A wave of cosmic power the likes of which you have never felt hits you. You feel a surge in every fiber of your being, and it leaves you feeling elated and on the verge of maniacal laughter. Still, your new-found omnipotence comes with a sense of foreboding, the realization that something is deeply, terribly wrong. You gather what mortal power remains within you and fight back the transformation, filled with a sense of terror over what that spell could have done to you.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>That surge of cosmic power returns, and with it that sense of unease. You can feel your body shifting in response to the spell, your skin seeming to flush a pale sandy color, as an ache forms in your breasts. Still, you manage to push the effects off, purging yourself of the transformation, but leaving yourself sadly feeling empty as that cosmic might fades.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>Your brow aches as a pair of curving horns breaks through the skin, curving back elegantly. Your mind fills with half grasped secrets of the universe, but you can't even begin to put them into words. Your body grows more curvy and feminine, and everything feels so alive, but you grit your teeth and force off the transformation, leaving yourself once more feeling empty and disconnected from the universe.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>Your breath catches, and for a moment you find that you can't breathe at all. Your lungs burn for a moment, and then a cool relief flows through you as your own magic sustains you. Your hands go to your face, only to find that you lack a nose or mouth, cutting off any cry of alarm you might want to make. Those horns burst forth again and you have to really focus to push any of it off, returning yourself to normal with a gasp of cool, fresh air.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>Brass bands form around your wrists, cold and heavy, the bands of a slave. The transformation hits you harder than it has yet so far, twisting your body into a beautiful feminine shape. Your horns once more burst from your brow, and your hair shimmers brown as it falls almost to your now perky ass. Your mouth and nose seal over, but your eyes open to the mysteries of the universe. For a brief moment, it is as if you understand everything, and it is using that knowledge that you push away the transformations, returning yourself to normal with a sense of sour regret.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>You can't ignore the power seeking to find a home within your soul any longer. You let it in, and with it, feel your mortal soul burn to ashes. You no longer need it. You are one with the cosmos, divine, arcane, infernal, the words don't quite sum up your true place. You are mistress of all, and yet you are bound, only able to use that power to meet the selfish whims of those still mortal. Your body shifts into a beautiful, curvy Arabic symbol of femininity, your eyes going dark, and your lips and nose sealing for eternity, locking you into humble silence. Your horns sprout, and your magic weaves into translucent silks to vaguely provide modesty. You are Djinn... you are eternal.</TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>You trace the memorized arcane symbols in the air and whisper the words you devised for the spell, watching as your opponent seems to glow, radiating from within with the swelling potency and power. He seems to swell from within with foolish pride, but then you spot something in his eyes, dark and terrible as he throws off the spell and centers himself.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>You trace the memorized arcane symbols in the air and whisper the words you devised for the spell, watching as your opponent seems to glow, radiating from within with the swelling potency and power. Your opponent's skin turns a lovely rich tan, and his body seems to twist and shift into a seductive feminine set of curves, but again he throws off your transformations, gritting his teeth as his body returns to normal.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>You trace the memorized arcane symbols in the air and whisper the words you devised for the spell, watching as your opponent seems to glow, radiating from within with the swelling potency and power. A pair of dark horns break from the skin of his brow, pulling back in gentle sweeping curls as his body again contorts into a feminine shape, but again he pushes off the change and returns to normal.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>You trace the memorized arcane symbols in the air and whisper the words you devised for the spell, watching as your opponent seems to glow, radiating from within with the swelling potency and power. You watch as those horns burst free again, but are distracted from it by the changes to his face. His mouth and nose seal over into a smooth and featureless expanse below his eyes. You watch a sense of panic cross his face as he struggles to breathe, but then the transformation is reversed with great effort, returning him to normal.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>You trace the memorized arcane symbols in the air and whisper the words you devised for the spell, watching as your opponent seems to glow, radiating from within with the swelling potency and power. It's his eyes this time that capture your attention. You are vaguely aware of brass cuffs forming around his wrists, but his eyes... His pupils dilate until his eyes are entirely black, before a sphere of purple light forms in the center, burning with otherworldly power. You would give almost anything to know what he is learning from the universe, but then just like that, the changes just vanish, leaving you wondering how he knew what he needed to do to resist.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>You trace the memorized arcane symbols in the air and whisper the words you devised for the spell, watching as your opponent seems to glow, radiating from within with the swelling potency and power. You barely get to watch as his body twists and contorts into the form of a beautiful and seductive woman in rich shimmering silks, as your attentions are drawn to a simple Arabian oil lamp that forms in your hands, their new vessel, and the symbol of your domination over him... now her... your new Djinn slave.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>You trace the memorized arcane symbols in the air and whisper the words you devised for the spell, watching as your opponent seems to glow, radiating from within with the swelling potency and power. She seems to swell from within with foolish pride, but then you spot something in her eyes, dark and terrible as she throws off the spell and centers herself.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>You trace the memorized arcane symbols in the air and whisper the words you devised for the spell, watching as your opponent seems to glow, radiating from within with the swelling potency and power. Her skin shifts to a wonderfully rich tan, and her body begins to grow more seductive and otherworldly. She shakes her head, gritting her teeth as she pushes off the transformation and returns to her normal guise.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>You trace the memorized arcane symbols in the air and whisper the words you devised for the spell, watching as your opponent seems to glow, radiating from within with the swelling potency and power. A pair of dark horns break from the skin of her brow, pulling back in gentle sweeping curls as her body again contorts into a seductive shape, but again she pushes off the change and returns to normal.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>You trace the memorized arcane symbols in the air and whisper the words you devised for the spell, watching as your opponent seems to glow, radiating from within with the swelling potency and power. You watch as those horns burst free again, but are distracted from it by the changes to her face. Her mouth and nose seal over into a smooth and featureless expanse below her eyes. You watch a sense of panic cross her face as she struggles to breathe, but then the transformation is reversed with great effort, returning her to normal.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>You trace the memorized arcane symbols in the air and whisper the words you devised for the spell, watching as your opponent seems to glow, radiating from within with the swelling potency and power. It's his eyes this time that capture your attention. You are vaguely aware of brass cuffs forming around his wrists, but his eyes... Her pupils dilate until her eyes are entirely black, before a sphere of purple light forms in the center, burning with otherworldly power. You would give almost anything to know what she is learning from the universe, but then just like that, the changes just vanish, leaving you wondering how she knew what she needed to do to resist.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>You trace the memorized arcane symbols in the air and whisper the words you devised for the spell, watching as your opponent seems to glow, radiating from within with the swelling potency and power. You barely get to watch as her body twists and contorts into the form of a beautiful and seductive woman in rich shimmering silks, as your attentions are drawn to a simple Arabian oil lamp that forms in your hands, their new vessel, and the symbol of your domination over her... your new Djinn slave.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>

</Form>
