<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>The spell seems to strike straight at your heart and leaves you with a feeling of emptiness inside.  Fortunately it passes after a few moments.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>The empty feeling caused by your opponent's magic seems to linger longer and is increasingly pervasive.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>After being struck again in the heart you feel more than ever that you are nothing more than a placeholder--an empty shirt just going through the motions expected of one in your position.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>In addition to your ongoing feeling of emptiness you begin to notice that your skin has become oddly soft and silky.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>Your skin has begun to take on a much darker tone thanks to the increasing amounts of magic flowing through you, and while your skin remains soft and silky, the flesh beneath seems increasingly insubstantial.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>Where once you were a mighty mage, full of life, you have now been reduced to nothing more than an empty silk suit.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>Your target may not look any different yet, but you know this magic begins by making them feel empty before actually making them empty.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>Your victim's facial expression makes the emptiness they now feel obvious, even if there still aren't any physical effects.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>Your target's posture makes it seem almost like they've actually started to deflate, even if you know that actual deflation is one of the last steps in the process.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Any blemishes and hair on your target's skin have melted away, leaving behind a smooth, silky surface.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Your victim's complexion darkens toward black as their skin seems to flutter in the breeze--the flesh underneath no longer any more substantial than a bit of cloth around some bones.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>Your victim's features melt away, leaving behind an empty silk suit that flutters to the ground along with anything they were carrying.  Your feeling of accomplishment switches to one of annoyance when you realize that the suit now probably needs to be dry-cleaned and ironed out.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
