<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>Your opponent doesn't seem to be that strong, sure you were hit, but looking at your body nothing is amiss. Well time for payback. You fling a spell back that nearly knocks over your enemy. As you move closer you notice that your foe dropped something: a finely crafted masquerade ball mask, a red one with black and red feathers at one side and with small gemstones all over it. The voice of your enemy interrupts your examination by saying: “Done gawking? Give it back and then we can settle this.' Well a worthless trinket anyways.  You put it aside and taunt your enemy: “If you want it back come and get it.'</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>Your opponent attacks you again and even manages to hit you. Not that it matters. The amount of transformation-energy is so low that you don't even feel the need to cleanse. “Give it back and I will go. No harm done yet.' offers your enemy. You pick up the mask again, wondering why this item means so much to your enemy. Sure it's a fine piece of craftsmanship, but to continue fighting over it? Your foe must be desperate. You place it back down and answer: “But the fun just started.'</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>Your opponent screams at you “Give it back! Don't you wear it!' and their magic bolt hits you. Again so weak you just shake it off. But how rude your foe is. “Don't yell at me and don't tell me what to do.' you say. Casually you walk over to the mask and in one fluid motion you put it on your head. Well it limits your vision a little but besides that, it somehow makes you feel really sexy. But it's not just that. It makes you feel devious, mysterious and a little bit aroused. “Maybe this mask isn't so worthless after all.' you taunt your enemy as you slip it off and place it down behind you again.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>Again your enemy attacks you, this time with a spray of magic bolts. Many got past your guard, not that you really care. Those bolts are really weak. You don't even bother with attacking your enemy. You know a better way to hurt you foe. Once again you slip the mask over your head.  You are however not prepared for what comes next as the mask touches your face. You are suddenly somewhere else. Music, twirling and waltzing bodies and the sound of laughter. You don't know why but you are at a masquerade ball. Looking down you notice with a dreamlike detachment that you are in the body of a young lady. A hand appears within your view and you hear the words: “Would you care for a dance milady?' You look up to a handsome man, masked like you, as you accept his hand unable to deny his wish. As you dance, your partner asks:'That is a beautiful mask. Surely the face behind it must be equally beautiful.'  You tear the mask from your face, feeling like someone has just punched you in the stomach. “No it isn't' The thought runs through your head over and over again. As you calm your nerves you notice that you are back in your reality.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>Your enemy attacks again, much to your annoyance. You raise a shield and don't even bother if one or two bolts manage to slip through. Your mind returns to the mask. Will wearing it make you feel this beautiful again?Will you have a vision again? You decide that there is only one way to find out. You close your eyes and slip the mask on your face again. As your eyes open you find yourself at the masquerade ball once more. You are offered a dance again, this time without words, and a moment later you find yourself back on the dance floor.  As you spin and twirl you can feel the eyes of the crowd on you. How they envy you. How they admire you. You take it all in and wish that this would never end. But it does, as you are suddenly back in your world. You blink, confused, and then notice that your enemy has taken your mask. You grab at your foe's arm with one hand and twist your precious mask out from your enemy's hand. You snarl “This is mine!'. Your attacker quickly retreats to a safer distance.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>You prepare for a new attack from your opponent but nothing happens. Your foe breaks the silence by asking:“Why do you even want my mask?' The question catches you off guard, but you answer, “It makes me feel beautiful.' “But isn't that just an illusion? No matter how long you wear it you will always be just yourself. You will never be as breathtaking and you know it.' As you hear those words, a cold feeling of unease penetrates your guts. You want to scream in denial, but you know it is and tears start to build in your eyes. “I can help you. Make you just as fantastic as this mask. Don't you want that?' Your mind races as conflicting thoughts clash inside your head. In the end, a small consenting nod shows that you give in. Your opponent circles you and places their hands on your shoulder. “Put on the mask and then just concentrate on it. Pour all your feelings into it.' As you try to follow the instructions you feel a cold sensation rise from your feet upwards yet at the same time your face feels caressed and warm. As you pour more and more of your feelings into the mask, you notice that you not only feel the mask at your skin. You can feel the mask itself. You don't even mind the fact that you can't feel anything below your hips anymore. You need more. With all of your will, you force everything you are into the mask and finally it's done. You understand now. You are not as beautiful as the mask: you have become the mask. And you feel like a big weight has been lifted off your heart. Your new owner gently slips you off your old body, a statue made of ugly stone. You can't believe that this was once you. But not anymore: you are the mask now and the mask is you. You know now that you are gorgeous. Forever.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>You spot a worthy target to be your mask. Sure you have the mask made but what mask is complete without adding a little bit personality? But to transfer a soul to the mask you have to be tricky. You decide to run with a little mind bending and acting. You start off with flinging some spell that rise the curiosity until you finally hit. Time for some acting: as your enemy attacks you feign to get hit and drop the mask. Your curiosity-spell takes effect and your victim picks up the mask to examine it.  You interrupt your target by saying: “Done gawking? Give it back and then we can settle this.' Your target puts the mask aside and replies: “If you want it back come and get it.'  
</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>You manage again to hit your enemy and raising their curiosity again. Steering your victim's focus back to the mask, you state: “Give it back and I will go. No harm done yet.' As intended your foe picks the mask up and examines it closer. A moment later they state: “But the fun just started.'</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>It is time that your victim wears the mask, so you decide to step up your game by yelling: 'Give it back! Don't you wear it!' You even cast some spells, not really expecting them to hit, but they do.  Does your enemy underestimate you? Well if they do it works in your favor. Your yelling worked as intended and your foe picks the mask up and says: “Don't yell at me and don't tell me what to do.' Your victim slides the mask on their hand and poses a little. You know that the hook was swallowed as your target comments: “Maybe this mask isn't so worthless after all.' Now you just have to reel them in.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Time to make your victim to not just wear the mask but to love it. You prepare some spells that give visions and fling them at your target. Most of those go through and you have a hard time to not smirk. They clearly underestimate you. Well, not that you mind. Your victim gives you a strange smile and slides the mask over their head. As they do they suddenly freeze. The vision must have kicked in. You wait patiently for the moment when suddenly your victim tears the mask from their head. Your victim looks shaken and a bit afraid.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Well the visions didn't work as intended last time but you have to try again. Your foe has absent-mindedly put up a shield but you easily out maneuver it. Your opponent doesn't even notice, as they are enthralled by the mask. They slip it on and freeze up once more as the vision takes over. And so you wait, a lot longer this time. Thinking that something is wrong you go to your victim and slip the mask off. Their dazed look vanishes quickly as they grab your arm and twist the mask free from your hand. You know that you are more successful than you initially thought as they snarl: “This is mine!' You quickly retreat and plan how to use this to your advantage.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>After a moment of consideration, you know how to proceed. You ask your victim:'“Why do you even want my mask?' They blush and and reply with:“It makes me feel beautiful.' Perfect, you can use that to your advantage. You taunt your foe with:“But isn't that just an illusion? No matter how long you wear it you will always be just yourself. You will never be as breathtaking and you know it.' With head hung low and tears in their eyes your enemy makes for a pathetic sight. Time to end this. You offer:'“I can help you. Make you just as fantastic as this mask. Don't you want that?' For a while your victim just trembles until a small consenting nod marks their surrender. You slowly circle your now broken enemy and place your hands on their shoulder. You whisper in their ear: “Put on the mask and then just concentrate on it. Pour all your feelings into it.' You gather your magic and slowly turn your victim to lifeless stone. At the same time, you force the soul of your target into the mask. It's all done in a matter of heartbeats. You slide the mask of the stone and examine your prize,  a finely crafted red masquerade ball mask with black and red feathers at the right side. Its surface decorated with gems that reflect and break the light.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>