<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<Description>Once a powerful mage, you are now a tennis racket.  With a tough leather grip, a sturdy red handle and a blue wire net, you have become a professional piece of magic sports gear that can help your owner hit back any attack that is thrown at them.  All they need to do is hold you in their fleshy warm palm and let you soak up some of the magic.  And should they decide to play a simple game of tennis with you, there's nothing quite so orgasmic as the vibration of bouncing back a fuzzy yellow ball...</Description>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>All of a sudden you and your opponent are whisked to the Sunnyglade Park tennis court, or at least some pocket dimension that looks exactly like it.  Your opponent throws the ball at you and you are certain that you can hit it back, but you stumble on someone else's tennis racket and it snaps. You don't remember seeing it there before, but you observe that it has a red handle with a rubber grip and a blue wire net, it has a sticker on it that says "WizardBall© High-quality tennis rackets". You feel a tingling in your lower body, as it gets thinner and melts together. As your opponent hits their next serve, you change back to normal and reappear where you last came from.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>Once again you and your opponent are whisked to the Sunnyglade Park tennis court, or at least some pocket dimension that looks exactly like it.  As you once again miss the serve, you hear your opponent's buzzer, and with it feel the tingling return... This time, the sensation goes from your feet up to your chest. Your body slowly becomes a cylinder shape, larger below your knees. Your lower legs seem soft and squishy, while everything else seems hard and cold. Quickly, the sensations go away as a wave of change sweeps your body, returning you to normal, just in time for the next serve.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>Once again you and your opponent are whisked to the Sunnyglade Park tennis court, or at least some pocket dimension that looks exactly like it.  Groaning in disbelief, you miss the shot again. Hearing the opponent's point buzzer, the now familiar sensation quickly returns; spreading up your body, fusing your arms and legs into your body. Stiffening, your body becomes a shiny red while your lower legs seem to become a comfortable rubber grip... Losing your balance from the sudden changes, your body reverts while falling to the ground.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>Once again you and your opponent are whisked to the Sunnyglade Park tennis court, or at least some pocket dimension that looks exactly like it.  This time, you finally hit the ball... out of bounds... In a fury of rage, you throw your racket in the air.  You know what they say, "What goes up must come down". Hitting your head, you feel an immediate swelling. Expanding from side to side and up and down, your head becomes more tennis racket shaped. Flattening out, you feel your face disappearing, leaving only a strong, grid-like structure. You feel a sudden jolt, and your head morphs back to it's normal, round shape.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>Once again you and your opponent are whisked to the Sunnyglade Park tennis court, or at least some pocket dimension that looks exactly like it.  Disoriented from the last change, you clumsily trip over your own feet and hit the net with your racket as your opponent serves. Failing to score a point, you feel the odd sensation return. You feel a wave of cold wash over your body as it thins and becomes red painted metal. Your lower legs bulge, becoming a smooth yet sturdy rubber grip. Your torso expands in length, to form a full handle Your head bulges left and right, becoming a fine, blue, wire net. Realising there's still one point before the opponent wins, you snap out of it and slowly regain your living body.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>Once again you and your opponent are whisked to the Sunnyglade Park tennis court, or at least some pocket dimension that looks exactly like it.  The referee calls the final point, announcing your defeat. Your face turns red in embarrassment, but soon it won't matter anyway. For the final time, you feel your body melting together and being extruded into a long, shiny, red cylinder. Your lower legs bulge, becoming  a soft yet strong rubber grip. Your head expands to your left and right, as well as up. Your face fades away in squares, leaving only a blue net surrounded by a red frame. Just as you begin to wonder what the point of an oversized tennis racket is, your entire body shrinks until you are only twenty-seven inches tall. </TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>You cast a spell that whisks yourself and your target into a pocket dimension that closely resembles the Sunnyglade Park tennis court.  You serve the ball to your novice opponent, certain that they will miss. Luckily, not only do they miss, but they stumble on someone else's tennis racket, causing it to snap. It has a red handle with a rubber grip and a blue wire net, and it has a sticker on it that says "WizardBall© High-quality tennis rackets". They look toward their lower body, as it gets thinner and melts together. Hitting your next serve, they get back into the game.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>You cast a spell that whisks yourself and your target into a pocket dimension that closely resembles the Sunnyglade Park tennis court.  Once again, they miss. Hearing your buzzer, they look strangely from their legs up to their torso as it narrows and melts together into a cylinder, bulging below their knees. Their lower legs turn dark grey in a wave-like manner, and their body becomes a brilliant red. With another wave, their body changes back to normal from their feet going up; just in time for your next serve.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>You cast a spell that whisks yourself and your target into a pocket dimension that closely resembles the Sunnyglade Park tennis court.  As you watch your opponent miss the serve once more, you hear the soothing sound of your point buzzer. In awe, your opponent quickly checks over their body as an invisible force fuses their arms and legs into their now cylindrical body. Becoming stiff their body becomes a shiny red while their lower legs bulge, becoming a grey handgrip. They fall, losing their balance and the changes reverse as they fall backwards.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>You cast a spell that whisks yourself and your target into a pocket dimension that closely resembles the Sunnyglade Park tennis court.  You stand surprised that your opponent actually hit the ball. You become worried that they might actually win... until the ball lands out of bounds. Raging, they throw their racket into the air. Falling back to the ground, it hits their head. Their head swells from the left, right and up. Their head deflates as their face disappears leaving only a thin, yet strong, grid-like structure. With a sudden jolt, their head reforms to its normal shape.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>You cast a spell that whisks yourself and your target into a pocket dimension that closely resembles the Sunnyglade Park tennis court.  Your opponent trips over their own feet and accidentally hits the racket while trying to hit your serve. Their body morphs into a perfect cylinder, expanding in length, making them almost seven feet tall. With a wave of colour, their body becomes coated in a red metal finish. Their lower legs - or what used to be their lower legs - bulge, becoming a comfortable, grey rubber grip. Their head bulges left and right, their face disappearing, and leaving only a blue wire net. Realizing that you still have one point before you can win, they use their remaining mind to force the changes to halt. Returning to normal, they prepare for one more serve...</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>You cast a spell that whisks yourself and your target into a pocket dimension that closely resembles the Sunnyglade Park tennis court.  The referee calls the final point, announcing your opponent's defeat. Their face turns red in embarrassment, but soon it won't matter anyway. For a final time, their body is extruded into a long, shiny, red cylinder. Their lower body bulges, becoming a soft yet strong rubber grip. Their head inflates, their face fading away in squares, leaving only a blue net surrounded by a red frame. You begin to wonder what the point of an oversized tennis racket is, at almost seven feet tall, but that interest goes away as their body shrinks to a size of only twenty-seven inches.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
