<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<Description>You are a smooth, one-piece Latex Swimsuit, having been transformed by a rival spellcaster into your new form. Your new form feels permanently damp, the spell keeping a constant, dripping sheen of water on your new 'body'. You can still move around ever so slightly- not enough to move around on your own, but enough to perhaps play with your owners body, distracting them, considering how tightly you're clinging to it...</Description>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>You feel an unexpected spell strike your body. You quickly look around, seeing an enemy mage focused upon you, their hand still pointed toward at you. It doesn't seem to do anything other than make you sweat a bit and give you a warm feeling, though you shake it off easily enough. What was the point of that?</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>The enemy mage gestures at you once more, casting another spell upon you. You feel its energy coursing through you as your body drips with sweat from the sudden and unexpected heat. You reach up to wipe some of the perspiration off your forehead and you hear a squeak as you notice your body taking on a black, rubbery sheen. You quickly cleanse yourself, now worried about what your opponent has planned...</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>As another spell strikes you, the rubbery sheen returns, your body dripping once more with perspiration from the heat of the spell swelling up inside of you. But now you see that you're beginning to shrink as well, going down to two-thirds your previous height before you are able to reverse the spell. The strange warmth seems to be interfering with your attempts at cleansing. Are they trying to turn you into some kind of doll?</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>As you feel the spell strike your body once more, you notice yourself shrinking again, your skin changing to a black, rubbery texture before your limbs start to decrease in size, attempting to meld into your body, and you have the strangest sensation of emptiness inside of your chest. You suddenly realize that your opponent is trying to turn you into a swimsuit! You reverse the spell again with some trouble, that heat clouding your mind as your counterspell seems to be getting harder and harder to perform...</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>The spell wracks your body once more, your arms and legs shrink and merge into your torso. Your body is flattening, hollowing out as holes form where your limbs previously were! Your head is halfway gone before you manage to cleanse yourself again, the hazy heat and lack of limbs interfering with the process. Even after you turn back, your limbs still feel somewhat stiff and unresponsive, and you're unsure if you can come back from another hit...</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>As the spell strikes you, your mind immediately clouds over; you can still vaguely feel your body shrinking down, your arms and legs melding into your hollowed out torso as arm and leg holes open up once more. Your head melts into the rest of your body, the hot haze that clouds your mind only now begins to dissipate as you feel your body go past the point of no return. You try, but you can barely move, giving nothing but a slight, almost aimless tug over your empty new form...</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>Your spell hits the target and you see their body begin to sweat profusely before they quickly cleanse themselves and dispel the effect. They seem to be somewhat confused as to what you're trying to do.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>Your spell strikes them, the energy coursing through their body as they begin sweating again... Their skin starts turning a shiny, rubbery black as they reach up to wipe some of the sweat off of their face. You hear their skin squeak, and let out a little grin of amusement at the shocked look that crosses their face when they notice the changes. They quickly cleanse themselves, turning back to normal once more.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>You fire the spell at your opponent again, causing their body to return to a rubbery sheen and begin to shrink! Their body rapidly reduces to a third of their size, their limbs shrinking faster than the rest of them, but they are able to quickly perform a counterspell to negate the effects! Returning to normal takes them visibly more effort than before though, and as they pant from the increasing heat in their body, it's clear they still don't fully understand what you have planned for them...</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>You blast your opponent with another spell, quickly returning the rubbery, wet sheen to their skin. As they begin to shrink and their limbs recede into their body once more, they appear to finally realize what you've planned for them! In spite of the shrinking limbs and intense heat, they manage to perform a counter-spell and return their body to its normal form.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Your spell hits its mark again. As your opponent quickly shrinks and their limbs meld into their body, holes open up in their former torso, leaving room to stick your own limbs through. Without legs to support them, they collapse on the ground, looking like a simple swimsuit with a deflating human head. As you step forward to pick them up they surprise you by managing to revert all the changes in a sudden burst, recollecting their normal form. Though they've regained their normal form, they're visibly tired, weakened from the exertion. You doubt they'll be able to resist your efforts much longer.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>Your spell wracks the target's body one last time, quickly turning their body back to latex. They fall over as their limbs fail them and disappear, merging into their upper body. Their head flattens and melts away into the rest of the swimsuit, their neck widening and leaving behind a large hole for you to stretch out and slip through. You step forward to claim the spoils of your victory.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
