<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>A rival mages approaches you, an intent look in their eyes - they appear to be reading directly from a spellbook.  "Psh, what an amateur" you think to yourself ... just as your body is transformed into a puff of smoke, which is quickly drawn into the book itself.  "Listen!" you hear a high pitched voice from somewhere slightly above you.  "You, yeah ... Hey!" she says, as you realize a tiny, flying faerie is speaking to you.  Looking down at yourself - a young, elvish looking male in a green tunic, you hesitantly ask: "W-what happened?" you ask, and she responds:  "Listen!  You need to escape, to flee!  You're trapped!  Hey!  You need to get out!  Listen! you're inside a copy of Practical Transformations and the Metaphysical blahblah ..."  she continues in that vein for quite some time, long after you have completely tuned her out, searching for egress on your own.  Suddenly feel something wrapping around your leg, and look down to see a tentacled monstrosity holding you tight, starting to force off your tunic.  "HEY!" says the fairy, in a much more menacing tone, her still nude body growing to near human size with spectacular proportions - though your lust is overcome by the evil look in her eyes, and whip in her hand.  "YOU SHOULD HAVE LISTENED!"  And while the beast holds you down, she begins to have her way with you ... though fortunately, after a subjective eternity, the magic binding you to the book breaks, returning your body to the shape, time, and place it was in before your rival invoked this magic; you will not underestimate them so easily again.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>The rival mage again approaches with their spellbook, and again you are sucked into a copy of Practical Transformations and the Metaphysical Realm.  This time, you find yourself in the body of a young, red-haired schoolgirl, whose actions are not entirely under your control.  You are currently checking your makeup in the mirror, critically looking at your blouse ... and deciding to undo another two buttons.  You then find yourself walking over to an oak-framed door labelled "Alfred Wayne, PhD"; hiking up the hem of your skirt, you timidly knock on it.  "Professor Wayne?" you find yourself asking, in a young voice trying to sound sultry: "I'm here to ask you about some extra credit for Psych 101?"  "Oh?" the middle-aged man answers in a deep voice, "come in, I've been expecting you." After some more chit-chat, he springs it on you: "Now Miss Wallace, I'll overlook your frequent absences and abysmal test scores, if you can answer a single question for me: 'What things are best in life?'"  You find yourself hesitantly responding: "Well, uh, like the Cimmerian warrior-poets say it's to like, crush your enemies, and, uh, something about lammy-tations?"  He laughs.  "That may be - but what do YOU think, Miss Wallace?"  As he slowly moves behind you, closing the door, unzipping his pants, you find yourself practically screaming - loud enough to be heard on the rooftops, if his office were not soundproof: "TO SUCK YOUR FABULOUS HORSECOCK!"  And, as you get down on your knees before his desk, he takes his customary place in his high-backed leather chair before you - and you get to the business of earning another easy A.  You find yourself still moving your lips, swirling your tongue around a cock that is no longer - nor ever truly was - there, for quite some time after your body and spirit return to the real world ...</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>You again find yourself trapped inside the book; a young man, likely an actor, given that you seem to be backstage in some kind of a theater?  A harried looking woman, sporting cat ears and a tail, though otherwise looking like a typical director comes running up to you.  "What? You aren't dressed nya? This is a cat-astrophe!  Quick, nya, get into wardrobe!"  Hurriedly, she foists a crop-top tie-dye shirt on you, and a pair of woman's bell-bottom jeans.  "But ... these aren't going to fit me?" you say, in a voice already cracking as the cat-girl channels some magic into you; soon enough, you're brushing long blonde hair out of your eyes, as you quickly dress, pulling the tight articles of clothing over your suddenly tattooed skin, leaving your taut midriff bare.  "Ok, wow, like, flower power man" you say, getting into your hippie character, "do I look like a groovy enough chick to go onstage yet?"  You walk to the door, but the catgirl shrieks "Don't furget!  Your character is pregnant, nya!"  Putting on a pair of gloves so as not to touch it herself, she tosses you a stone idol, in the shape of a heavily pregnant woman; as you touch it, your breasts begin to swell against the tie-dye top, your exposed belly bloating enormously above your bell-bottoms.  "Great, you look purrfect now, nya!" she whispers, shoving you out to the stage, "hope you're ready for the orgy scene!"  You blink in the bright stage lights, as you see dozens of actors in various states of undress already getting it on, several beckoning you over ... you waddle over to them, taking your place, getting down to business before the audience.  You still feel your phantom swollen breasts and belly shaking from your actor/lover's ministrations, as you return to the real world ...</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>This time, you find yourself in the body of a tanned, athletic girl; given your location in a barn, you are quite likely a farmer.  Your eyes go wide as you survey the animals before you, many of them suddenly anthropomorphic, or at least speaking in human voices.  "Why kiss my grits!" you say, in an American southern drawl, "all y'all done turned into people!"  From the mud-filled corner, a pig-girl quietly lets out what can only be described as a gigglesnort at your surprise, while a cowgirl quickly headbutts you, knocking you to the ground. A particularly dominant-looking donkey quickly binding you in chains before you can recover.  "Do you know why I have bound yoou?" moos the cowgirl. "Hog-tied you mean" snorts the pig.  "N-no, sure as sugah I don't" you plead.  "Every day you've come into this barn and taken from us ... mmilk from mme, eggs from the chickens, even lead some of us to the slaughter ..."  "Four legs good, two legs bad!" squeals the pig.  "Ah ... ah didn't mean it" you begin, as the donkey whips you.  "Silence!" she moos, "no, starting today, you are going to give back.  Look at me - I'mm all skin and bones fromm your neglect, hardly a proper cowgirl at all ... do you know what I'mm going to turn you into?"  "A nice pile of slop?" suggests the pig.  "Another cute fennec like me, Mistress?  I'm urs" suggests the fox.  "Someone to fuck you, and maybe me?" whines the farm's hound, rubbing her legs together, obviously in heat.  "A nice horsec-" suggests the stallion, before being cut off by the bovine. "No, we all know what YOU think, and I quite like being female."  "Sorry Moocy" he neighs; it looks like the barnyard isn't going to let you get a word in edgewise.  "No" - continues the cow - "your fate is to give back what you have taken from mme over the years!"  Her hooflike hands begin weaving a spell, and you find your breasts multiplying; the four of them growing into immensity, absorbing the rest of your flesh as they go - an udderly horrible fate.  The cowgirl moves over to you, taking you, attaching you above her groin, as you begin to fill with milk, pulsing against her.  Somewhere outside your fleshy prison, you hear the bitch ask the pig: "Hey, how come Moocy isn't sharing her with us?"  The reply: "Well ... all us animals are equal ... " - a gigglesnort as she watches the cowgirl pull on her/your new teats, milk fountaining forth - "but the way Moocy sees it, some are more equal than others."  And with that, the scene fades; though you still feel your whole body pulsing, as if you were just about to erupt with milk ...</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>This time you find yourself outdoors, dressed only in brief swimtrunks, a heavily muscled man cruising the beach with your best bud. "Hey, Broseph?" you ask him.  "Yeah Matt?"  "Don't it seem to you that all the girls out here kind of ... look the same?"  "Oh, I know what you mean" the dude with muscles for brains nods, clearly incorrect: "One pussy's pretty much the same as another bro!"  "No, I mean ... like REALLY all the same, bra" - you point at what appear to be three identical triplets across the way.  "Man, you're harshing my vibe" he says - "I'll catch ya on the flip side"; Jo never was much up on modern slang.  Still, having a severe case of blue balls, you can't help but approach the three identical women.  "Like, what have we here?" says one.  "A, like total hunk!" says another.  "We should like, totes fuck him fer sure!" says the third, or possibly the first again.  It's not long at all before the three bimbos are all over you, smothering you with kisses.  Suddenly, in unison, one sticks her tongue down your throat, a second takes of her top, rubs her breasts against you as she pulls down your trunks, just in time for the last bimbo to pull off her own bikini bottom, and impale herself on your member!  You're briefly in heaven before your body starts tingling; but soon it, like, feels too good ta care, ya know?  Your nipples are hard, your girlfriend is totes grinding on your clit, while another is totally frenchin ya; it's, like, so kewl, even though you'd rather be suckin a dick!  The other three speak:  "Oh, it like happened again"  "Why do all the hawt ones, like, turn so easy?"  "Where are we gonna find a dick ta suck now?"  You suddenly have the greatest idea ever; who says you aren't totally smart?  "Like, I know where we can go girlfriends; my BFF Jo is like, totes over that way!"  Your brainless adventures continue for quite some time in this vein, the four, but soon five identical bimbos slowly making their way through the city, spreading their happiness to all around them ... you shudder slightly, as your mental faculties finally return, back outside the book.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>Now THIS is more like it - the spell has left you in the body of an angel; you should be powerful, able to defend yourself, and most of all, given your past experiences with the book, chaste.  "Should be" being the operative word, as she finds herself encased in a glass ball, a fifty foot tall demoness looking down at her, laughing evilly.  No ... not fifty feet tall ... she herself seems to have been shrunken, placed inside a crystalline sphere.  "Unhand me demon!" you shout - "let me free and face justice!"  She can only laugh at you, your relative sizes making the ominous cackle even more sinister.  "No Bectheriel ... you have tormented me for FAR too long ... I hope you ... ENJOY ... your stay inside my magic slut ball ... I've been told it's quite the experience."  She grins wickedly, as her lustful magic permeates your prison; you feel your resolve fading as your clothes vanish; your breasts swelling greatly, filling with milk; your pussy alight with infernal heat, causing you to want ... no NEED ... to plunge your fingers in, over and over and over... "N-no ... let me out ... aaaaaaah!" you cry, as the first orgasm hits you.  "Certainly Becky" the demoness gloats, her face a mask of misplaced sympathy.  "Just tell me, HONESTLY, that you're not enjoying this, and I will let you leave your sphere, and the book as well."  "I, ungggh ... more, I need to be fucked, please!" you cry out, suddenly realizing that you DON'T want to leave, that you want to be in here, forever.  "Good, good - but let us, 'turn a page', shall we say, on your new life?"  And suddenly - as unbeknownst to you, back in the real world the enemy mage is idly leafing through the book - your situation changes again and again.  Back in the forest, the school, the theater, the barn, the beach ... and countless other places and bodies as well; in each, filled with the same burning lust you felt within the demon's ball.  It's going to be an interesting life, at least ...</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>You approach a rival mage, holding your copy of Practical Transformations and the Metaphysical Realm aloft, attempting to begin the process of ensnaring your rival's soul. The ritual of capture works even more quickly than you could have imagined - not only is their body instantly transformed into a puff of smoke, which is quickly drawn into the book - but your own mind is drawn in as well.  You do not resist, as you know that while the scene which plays out may subjectively take hours, it will be over in mere seconds in the real world.  You arrive to see a small faerie addressing your rival, who has been transformed into a young, elvish looking man in a green tunic.  "Listen!" she says, addressing the 'elf'  "You, yeah ... Hey!".  Realizes she is speaking to him, your rival hesitantly asks: "W-what happened?" She responds:  "Listen!  You need to escape, to flee!  You're trapped!  Hey!  You need to get out!  Listen! You're inside a copy of Practical Transformations and the Metaphysical blahblah ..."  she continues in that vein for quite some time, long after you AND your rival have completely tuned her out.  But suddenly, while he is searching for egress on his own, you see something wrapping around his leg; he looks down to see a tentacled monstrosity holding him tight, starting to force off his tunic.  "HEY!" says the fairy, in a much more menacing tone, her still nude body growing to near human size with spectacular proportions - though your rival's lust is overcome by the evil look in the faerie's eyes, and the whip in her hand.  "YOU SHOULD HAVE LISTENED!"  And while the tentacled beast holds him down, the faerie begins to have her way with him ... though after a subjective eternity for your rival the magic breaks, returning you both to the real world, things apparently unchanged.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>You again approach your rival, copy of Practical Transformations and the Metaphysical Realm in hand, and send their spirit to temporarily inhabit another of its pages; your own mind follows in to watch.  This time, they find themself in the body of a young, red-haired schoolgirl, whose actions are quite obviously not under their control.  Currently, your rival is checking her makeup in the mirror, critically looking at her blouse ... and deciding to undo another two buttons.  She then finds herself walking over to an oak-framed door labelled "Alfred Wayne, PhD"; hiking up the hem of her skirt, she timidly knock on it.  "Professor Wayne?" she finds herself asking, in a young voice trying to sound sultry: "I'm here to ask you about some extra credit for Psych 101?"  "Oh?" the middle-aged man answers in a deep voice, "come in, I've been expecting you." After some more chit-chat, he springs it on your rival: "Now Miss Wallace, I'll overlook your frequent absences and abysmal test scores, if you can answer a single question for me: 'What things are best in life?'"  She finds yourself hesitantly responding: "Well, uh, like the Cimmerian warrior-poets say it's to like, crush your enemies, and, uh, something about lammy-tations?"  He laughs.  "That may be - but what do YOU think, Miss Wallace?"  As he slowly moves behind your rival trapped in that schoolgirl body, he closes the door, unzipping his pants - you see your rival practically screaming - loud enough to be heard on the rooftops, if this professor's office were not suspiciously soundproof: "TO SUCK YOUR FABULOUS HORSECOCK!"  And, as she gets down on her knees before the desk, the professor takes a seat in the high-backed leather chair before her- and your rival gets down to the business of "earning another easy A".  Suddenly, you both snap back to reality; but you see your rival still moving their lips, swirling their tongue around a cock that is no longer - nor ever truly was - there, for quite some time ...</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>Your rival again finds themselves trapped inside the book; a young man this time, likely an actor, given that you seem to be viewing the backstage area of a theater?  A harried looking woman, sporting cat ears and a tail, though otherwise looking like a typical director comes running up to him.  "What? You aren't dressed nya? This is a cat-astrophe!  Quick, nya, get into wardrobe!"  Hurriedly, she foists a crop-top tie-dye shirt on him, and a pair of woman's bell-bottom jeans.  "But ... these aren't going to fit me?" he says, in a voice already cracking as the cat-girl channels some magic into 'him'; soon enough, your rival brushing long blonde hair out of her eyes. She quickly dresses, pulling the tight articles of clothing over her suddenly tattooed skin, leaving her taut midriff bare.  "OK, wow, like, flower power man" the new actress says, getting into her hippie character, "do I look like a groovy enough chick to go onstage yet?"  She tries to walk to the door, but the catgirl shrieks "Don't furget!  Your character is pregnant, nya!"  Putting on a pair of gloves so as not to touch it herself, the catgirl director tosses your rival a stone idol, in the shape of a heavily pregnant woman; as she touch it, her breasts begin to swell against the tie-dye top, her exposed belly bloating enormously above her bell-bottoms.  "Great, you look purrfect now, nya!" the director whispers, shoving your rival out to the stage, "hope you're ready for the orgy scene!"  The heavily-pregnant actress blinks in the bright stage lights, as she see dozens of actors in various states of undress already getting it on, several beckoning her over ... she waddles over to them, taking her place, getting down to business as both you and the phantom audience watch.  Eventually, of course, the magic fades, though you find your spellbook to be a bit thicker ...</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>This time, your rival finds themselves in the body of a tanned, athletic girl; given the location in a barn, she is quite likely a farmer.  Her eyes go wide as she surveys the animals before her, many of them suddenly anthropomorphic, or at least speaking in human voices.  "Why kiss my grits!" she says, in an American southern drawl, "all ya'll done turned into people!"  From the mud-filled corner, a pig-girl quietly lets out what can only be described as a gigglesnort at your rival's surprise, while a cowgirl quickly headbutts her, knocking you to the ground. A particularly dominant-looking donkey quickly binds her in chains before you can recover.  "Do you know why I have bound yoou?" moos the cowgirl. "Hog-tied you mean" snorts the pig.  "N-no, sure as sugah I don't" your rival pleads.  "Every day you've come into this barn and taken from us ... mmilk from mme, eggs from the chickens, even lead some of us to the slaughter ..."  "Four legs good, two legs bad!" squeals the pig.  "Ah ... ah didn't mean it" you begin, as the donkey whips you.  "Silence!" she moos, "no, starting today, you are going to give back.  Look at me - I'mm all skin and bones fromm your neglect, hardly a proper cowgirl at all ... do you know what I'mm going to turn you into?"  "A nice pile of slop?" suggests the pig.  "Another cute fennec like me, Mistress?  I'm urs" suggests the fox.  "Someone to fuck you, and maybe me?" whines the farm's hound, rubbing her legs together, obviously in heat.  "A nice horsec-" suggests the stallion, before being cut off by the bovine. "No, we all know what YOU think, and I quite like being female."  "Sorry Moocy" he neighs; it looks like the barnyard isn't going to let the farmgirl get a word in edgewise.  "No" - continues the cow - "your fate is to give back what you have taken from mme over the years!"  Her hooflike hands begin weaving a spell, and your rival finds her breasts multiplying; the four of them growing into immensity, absorbing the rest of her flesh as they go - an udderly horrible fate.  The cowgirl moves over to the pile of flesh, taking your rival in her hooves, attaching the udder above her bovine groin, as your transformed rival begin to fill with milk, pulsing against the cow.  The bitch asks the pig: "Hey, how come Moocy isn't sharing her with us?"  The reply: "Well ... all us animals are equal ... " - a gigglesnort as she watches the cowgirl pull on her new teats, milk fountaining forth - "but the way Moocy sees it, some are more equal than others."  And with that, the scene fades; your rival's body still pulsing and quaking a bit afterwards ...</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>This time you find yourself outdoors, looking at your rival dressed only in brief swimtrunks, a heavily muscled man cruising the beach with his best bud. "Hey, Broseph?" your rival asks his buddy.  "Yeah Matt?"  "Don't it seem to you that all the girls out here kind of ... look the same?"  "Oh, I know what you mean" the (other) dude with muscles for brains nods, clearly incorrect: "One pussy's pretty much the same as another bro!"  "No, I mean ... like REALLY all the same, bra" - your rival points at what appear to be three identical triplets across the way.  "Man, you're harshing my vibe" his bud says - "I'll catch ya on the flip side"; looks like the old book isn't much up on modern slang.  While he senses something wrong, your rival must be having a severe case of blue balls, as he can't help but approach the three identical women.  "Like, what have we here?" says one.  "A, like total hunk!" says another.  "We should like, totes fuck him fer sure!" says the third, or possibly the first again.  It's not long at all before the three bimbos are all over him, smothering him with kisses.  Suddenly, in unison, one sticks her tongue down his throat, a second takes of her top, rubs her breasts against him as she pulls down his trunks, just in time for the last bimbo to pull off her own bikini bottom, and impale herself on his member!  He seems to be briefly in heaven before his body starts shaking, blurring; but soon he - now she - doesn't seem to care.  Her nipples are hard, her girlfriends is totes grinding on her clit, while another has her tongue down your rival's throat; she seems blissful, though empty, as if she'd much rather have a dick around to suck.  The other three bimbos speak:  "Oh, it like happened again"  "Why do all the hawt ones, like, turn so easy?"  "Where are we gonna find a dick ta suck now?"  Your rival - after what appears to be intense concentration among her few remaining brain cells, has what for her must be a genius level idea: "Like, I know where we can go girlfriends; my BFF Jo is like, totes over that way!"  Their brainless adventures continue for quite some time in this vein, the four, but soon five identical bimbos slowly making their way through the city, spreading their happiness to all around them ... your rival's expression even looks vapid, air-headed yet lustful, after the spell finally fades.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>This time, your rival is sucked inside the book, but you aren't immediately; you see her in the body of an angel, but tiny, trapped inside a crystalline sphere, watched over by a looming demoness ... who directly addresses you - speaking with the voice of the book itself?  "Congratulations magus - you have fully given your rival's soul over to me; in exchange for that, I will unlock the book's true power for you.  No strings attached ... unless you'd consider another offer?  But first, come - enjoy the final scene ..."  Again, your consciousness is sucked into the book, just in time to see the 'angel' aware of her predicament, the same demoness standing above her crystal prison - and winking at you.  "Unhand me demon!" your rival shouts - "let me free and face justice!"  The demoness can only laugh: "No Bectheriel ... you have tormented me for FAR too long ... I hope you ... ENJOY ... your stay inside my magic slut ball ... I've been told it's quite the experience."  She grins wickedly, her lustful magic permeates the prison; your rival's resolve fading - permanently -  as her clothes vanish; her breasts swelling greatly, filling with milk; her pussy alight with infernal heat, causing her to want ... no NEED ... to plunge her fingers in, over and over and over... "N-no ... let me out ... aaaaaaah!" she cries, as the first orgasm hits her.  "Certainly Becky" the demoness gloats, her face a mask of misplaced sympathy.  "Just tell me, HONESTLY, that you're not enjoying this, and I will let you leave your sphere, and the book as well."  "I, ungggh ... more, I need to be fucked, please!" she screams, her fate sealed as your mind's eye leaves the scene; your opponent's body is simply missing from the outside world, leaving nothing more than a pile of clothing in its place.  The book-demon again addresses you: "I can give you so much more, if only you are willing to join your victim in here ... such power, such pleasure ..."  You cut her off, rapidly turning the book's pages, her infernal laughter echoing in your ears as you do.  As you see your rival on each illustrated page -  the forest, school, stage, barn, and beach, as well as countless others - you feel a new knowledge of the transformative arts welling up within you.  This book will be VERY useful, even if you never open it to torment your former rival again.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
