<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<Description>These panties are soft and comfortable, and a little frilly. They cling nicely to a woman and soul inside wishes nothing more to protect and support young mothers and their babies. Of course there is little they can do but hug the woman's hips. Even those not yet expecting will find them self with a little baby bump of their own if they wear these.</Description>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>You are hit with a spell and are nearly knocked over, but when you get your balance you realized that nothing even happened. Though you suddenly realize you have not talked to your mother in a while, maybe you should give her a call?</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>You are hit again and you nearly fall over as as your body tingles with a strange feeling. You look down and your arms and legs become soft as strange frilly images appear on your skin. Your body starts to cave in becoming more soft and flat but then you focus and reverse the spell before it is too late!</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>You are hit and knocked off your feet and your head hits the ground. You awaken to find yourself in bed. How did you get here? You slowly sit up and the sheets slide down, exposing your heavy milk swollen tits. You stroke your fingers down your soft breasts, before tracing your fingers across your swollen belly.  Your fingers start to slide a little lower when you realize you are not a pregnant woman and snap out of it! You find your self laying on the ground and back to your normal self.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>You are hit in the back and the world goes dark once more. You wake up, pregnant once more. Your smile as your hands reach for your soft milk tits, and you rub and stroke them. Your fingers tease down over your large swollen belly, before dipping down to your sex. Your fingers stop however as they find the pair of frilly white panties, with little flowers on it. The panties are snug against your sex, and hips, and feel so nice against your skin. You wouldn't mind being a pair of panties just like them...Suddenly you awake back on the ground, panting heavily at the strange dream you were having.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>Before you know it you are in that strange bed once again. A woman smiles as she wakes up and her fingers slide down to lightly touch your body. You cling to her hips, holding her tightly as her fingers trace along your frilly waistband. Her belly is so fully and round, and it stretches you a little, but you do not mind. You want to protect her, and the baby inside of her. That is your new job. You cling her as your mind drifts away but then suddenly you snap out of it, finding yourself alone on the ground.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>You drift off into that wonderful dream once more, being the nice soft, protective panties. You cling to the woman happily as she slides out of bed. Your dream is ruined however as you feel someone touching you and your mind is brought back to reality. You are on the ground, a pair of soft frilly panties. You feel yourself sliding up their legs, and soon you are hugging tightly to their body. Something is off though...That is right you are not panties... You are maternity panties! You hug at their form as your magic starts to reshape, filling out their ass and hips, and filling their stomach with a small little baby bump. You let out a happy sigh in your mind as you snuggle close to the new mother, happy to protect her and the baby.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>You hit them with a spell and they nearly fall over. However they recover a moment later and look off, as if thinking about something besides the fight.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>You nail them with a spell and they nearly fall over once again. This time you notice frilly lace patterns start to spread over their body as their skin soften and changes. Yes, soon they will be a nice pair of panties! Sadly they begin to change back a moment later.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>You hit them hard and knock them clear off their feet and they fall over. You expect a sickening crunch when their head slams into the ground but instead their head seems to land softly and their head caves in, growing softer and flatter as they become a roll of person shaped fabric. They start to shrink and wrap, taking on the shape of a nice pair of panties but then suddenly the spell spots and they start to retake their normal form.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>You hit them hard once again and they are a pair of frilly panties before they hit the ground. Soft panties with delicate flower images on them, and a frilly waist band. Perfect, just what you wanted! You walk over towards the panties and reach down to pick them up and when your fingers touch them an image flashes through your mind, the image of being a pregnant woman, waking in bed with these panties on. You shake your head slightly and notice they are returning to normal already and run off.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Once more they turn into a pair of panties and fall to the ground. Quickly you race over and grab them but once again strange images fill your mind. You find your self laying in bed. You yawn and stretch before your hand slides down to cup your swollen milk filled tits. Then your fingers trace lower, over your round belly, and then down to your warm sex. There you find the frilly underwear, clinging to you. They make you feel so safe and secure and are so comfortable. You snap back to reality and notice the panties swinging around, wiggling in your hands as hand starts to push out. "No! I was so close!"</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>This time you hit them and they fall to the ground, and you make sure to complete the spell. You lock them in the form of panties forever! You laugh as you walk over and carefully pick them up and can't resist the urge to slide them up your legs, just to give them a test drive. They cling nicely to your hips, fitting just perfectly. Your hips swell slightly and your belly grumbles before pushing out, swelling to look as if you were a few months pregnant. You smile as your fingers trace across the soft fabric of your new panties before you walk off.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
