<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>You blush as a wave or erotic magic flows into you from an enemy spell caster. You begin to speak a counter spell but your lips begin to feel odd. You blink a few time and reach up, rubbing your lips and moaning out in sudden orgasmic bliss. With a bright blush you change yourself back to normal, praying that no one saw you like that.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>You feel your whole body tingle with pleasure as your lips begin to change again, this time they actually move, taking on the form of a woman's sex right in the middle of your face. You want to panic or call for help, but no sound escapes your new "lips" You reach up to feel the damage, but only manage to make yourself become lost in pleasure as you rub your fingers against your new pussy, eagerly taking your finger into your warm wetness even as your skin begin to take on a soft texture and pink coloration. You force yourself to stop your freakish masturbation and change yourself back to normal, but a musky taste of female pleasure sticks to your tongue.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>When the spell hit you again you felt your mouth changing into a fully functional pussy once again. This time you notice your skin changing into a girly pink color as a sensation of softness begins to flow through your body. You feel your arms and legs beginning to shrivel into your body, your eyes widening in panic and humiliation before you manages to gurgle out the counter spell. You pant once you are returned to normal, licking your lips and moaning softly in pleasure.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>Your whole body becomes weak as you gurgle out of your face pussy as you flop to the ground, your whole body becoming made of pink silicone. Your body begins to shrink as your eyes and nose begin to flatten into a smooth surface as your pussy becomes the single noticable part of your face. Your hair falls to the ground and soon you are  looking like an over sized onahole. You quiver and change yourself back, rubbing your fingers over your lips and moaning, orgasming from simply touching your changed back lips.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>You quiver as you rapidly shrink once again, quickly becoming a silicone onahole. As your body reverts to that of a sex toy your mind is the thing that suffers from this cast is your mind. You gurgle some lube from your pussy as your mind begins to craze something nice and hard pumping in and out of your body, spreading you wide like a proper toy. As you lose yourself to the fantasies you can feel a hand grabbing you and lifting you up. The sudden touch of human skin causes your pussy to spasm as you manages to suppress the lust after your orgasm and change yourself back.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>You flop to the ground, eager to return to your proper and desired form. You settle into your life as a sex toy, eager to have someone eat you out, or pump their cock in and out of your 10 inch long silicone body. You quiver as you are picked up and tucked away into someone's backpack for them to use later. You quiver and wriggle alone in the darkness of the pack, your pussy dripping and glistening with lust. Your mind, where a small spark of your humanity remained, begged and cried out in lust. You wanted sex, pleasure, and attention! Your whole soul revolved around that one though, and almost nothing of your old self remained. You were pussy, and pussy wants pleasure.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>You weave a spell and focus it at your enemy. You notice your opponent rub begin to rub their lips and moan with passion before a bright blush takes their cheeks. They quickly change themselves back with a counter spell.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>As your spell hits them, your enemy’s face begins to change. Their once human lips now take the form of a woman’s sex right in front of you. They start to panic until they reach up and touch their new found lips. Rubbing their newly formed lips they begin to relax and pleasure themselves right in front of you. You notice as wetness spills forth from their new pussy that a pink hue has taken hold on their fingers. They quickly stop masturbating and change back.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>When your spell lands on your target, their mouth once again turns into a functioning pussy. This time, their skin changes into a girly pink color. Their arms and legs begin to retract back into their body. Panic sprawls across your victims face, eyes wide in terror and panicking. With a gurgle through their pussy lips, they manage to utter a counter spell and reverse the changes.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Your enemy’s body falls to ground becoming a shaft made of pink silicone. Their eyes and nose begin to flatten into a smooth surface as their pussy for a mouth becomes the single noticeable part of your enemies face. Their hair starts falling out and they have just the appearance of an oversized onahole. You notice the onahole quiver and change itself back into its former self.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Your spell forces your enemy back into being an onahole, the perfect form for them. You notice that their once agitation within this form is replaced by calm. Their pussy begins to ooze forth fluids. You reach down to pick up the onahole, but it manages to once again counter your spell and revert back to its form life.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>The onahole flops to the ground, transforming fully into its new position in life. You walk over to it and pick It up, rubbing the toys lips for a bit realizing how much fun this thing will be when you’re in the mood. You put the toy into your backpack and head off onto your next adventure.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
