<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>You see an enemy caster preparing some sort of odd ritual that confuses you at first. The maneuvers look like no form of magic you have seen before but the immense pain you feel shortly afterward say otherwise. You focus your mind on breaking the spell cast on you though are left panting afterward. What were they trying to do to you?</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st> Again they make the same odd dance as before and this time instead of just pain wracking your body you feel as though something is being pulled from you. You manage to finish your counter spell even as it becomes hard to breathe, eyes watering as you collapse to your knee's panting. Looking at your skin you still seem pale even though your sure you countered the spell, thinking back to the feeling from before you realize the other mage must have been draining you!</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st> You try to strike back as the mage begins chanting and dancing again, but still weakened from before they easily finish the casting bringing back that horrible pain. It feels as though your body is losing all heat while you gasp for breath, feeling as though your life itself is being pulled towards the mage who attacked you. You clear your mind channeling a counter for the spell faster this time due to understanding it's nature and break the link between you, but the damage has still been done and that other accursed mage has take more from you. You feel anger at this other mage for using such horrifying magic and vow that you will make them pay for it.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st> The mage starts to laugh this time as they once again cast the spell or curse as it seems more appropriate on you. The curse has already drained so much from you that you are barely able to stay standing, gasping desperately for air from lungs that refuse to work makes this no easier as you try to focus on the mage casting on you. You know that you need to stop this now before it takes so much that you won't even be able to fight it and with a strong force of will you break the hold the other mage has over you. Panting you realize you must have fallen to your knee's at some point and hearing the mage's manic laughter you look up to meet they're eyes, glaring at you with a crazed look. You start to worry as with that last spell you were already barely able to break free, you wonder for how much longer you can pull it off.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>You panic as the mage begins that same horrifying curse once again trying to brace yourself but screaming even as the draining starts anew. Every cell of your body screams in agony at once, blinding pain everywhere. You've fallen over at some point and are laying on your side, you try to muster any will to breathe but it will not come, the curse seems to be working on everything that's left of you as you feel your entire body becoming empty. You feel tempted to give in out of some hope the pain will end after they take everything from you, but then you feel it. Your memories themselves seem to be fading, being converted to yet more energy for the curse and you feel a new strength come from you with it. You put everything you have from those fond memories repelling the curse and breathing once more. You feel that your body had been changing but you cannot tell what had happened entirely. You look at the mage who seems entirely shocked you managed to break free and realize this may be your opportunity to run. If they should cast that curse on you again...</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st> You try to beg the mage for mercy even as they start up the motions of the spell, but looking in their eyes you see only a giddy joy breaking your will. You don't even resist as you fall over, all strength being pulled from you. Everything that you ever were is just more fuel for the curse, but it doesn't even matter does it? You stopped breathing at some point but you know it would do no good, your memories are being destroyed but you've already lost too many to even remember why they were important. Your body feels different but at the same time the curse drains away even your sense of self, something does remain though. Burning inside of you....hate... you feel an all consuming hate inside of you, for the pain you have endured you want revenge though you no longer remember the target for your revenge. You want to make everything pay and feel this agony that rages inside your small form and seek to bring it to all, even if you must use another as your tool for such...</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd> You almost reconsider casting this spell on your opponent thinking back to the source you learned it from, but curiosity gets the better of you and you start channeling your magic into the curse. Immediately the energy you put into casting it returns and you feel amazing as more comes behind it! Your opponent breaks the spell but you know you came out better for it.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>Channeling the spell again you can't wait for that same wonderful sensation, energy filling your body making you feel as though you could run forever. Your target on the other hand seems to be having a much harder time, they look to you with their eyes watering in bewilderment. The poor fool doesn't even seem to realize what your doing yet as they break your grasp again.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>Eagerly this time you chant the cursed words and funnel your energy cursing them once again, draining every part of them it grasps as you feel an urge to moan in delight. All too soon they break your grasp much to your disappoint, seems like they've finally caught onto your game if the look of anger in their eyes is any indication, they're now pale skin and drained look let's you know you have the upper hand now though.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd> You can't help but laugh as you channel the curse once again. It was just so easy to drain your opponents life away and it felt so good! Watching as their strength fades and they fall to their knees, their weak counter spell only makes you laugh harder knowing they still have more energy for you to take.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd> Knowing your opponent is still weak you almost debate whether to continue for now or let them recover for another helping later, but the temptation is just too strong and you channel the curse once again. They fall over almost immediately worrying you that they already were done, but then you feel the energy flow start anew as they're form seems to shrink! You giggle as even they're remaining essence itself was being turned into more energy for your body and eagerly worked away at anything you could get, sensing a particularly delicious mass inside their mind you started to go to work on even turning their memories into more fuel but suddenly felt yourself forced back. Apparently they still had enough left in them to resist if you tried going that far but you know how much you've taken already, and doubt they can resist you again.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>The poor mage tries begging you for mercy this time, as if you actually care. The thought alone almost sends you into fits of laughter again but hold yourself together as you channel the curse, and from the dead look in their eye you doubt this will even be a challenge. Sucking up every last bit of their essence you find you don't even receive any resistance as you turn all those little memories into more delicious food. After you felt the curse complete you opened your eyes sighing happily at the wonderful feelings you now had until you felt another presence nearby, looking down you see a small straw doll in the remaining clothes your target was wearing, emanating such a deep hatred. It was as if it wanted you to help it hurt everything around it, with a smirk you left the little abomination there. A testament to your victory.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
