<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>You begin to feel odd, your mind becoming fuzzy and disorientated. You look down at your hand, seeing them slim down and the skin beginning to darken to a deep mocha color. You blush brightly and shake your hands, your magic welling up and changing yourself back to normal. Funny you think, your magic felt more wild and powerful than before.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>You feel your opponents spell sink into your skin. Your hair begins to darken and tangle, becoming somewhat unkempt. Your skin gains goosebumps as the tingling of magic causes your skin to darken all over into a deep and sexy mocha color. Your eyes begin to darken into a brown and you giggle softly. You gather your magic and change yourself back to normal, feeling your magic becoming wild and free again right before you regained control</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>Your opponent's spell hits you again, you open your mouth to curse at them "Wa mitta naa chu!" You shout at them in a completely foreign language, your voice becoming higher in pitch and cutesy sounding. Your skin becomes a dark mocha again, your eyes growing rounder and your eyes a bright brown. Your hair lengthens and turns a dark black in color. Your pants feel strange as they begin to break apart into a short grass skirt. When you feel your underwear disappear you realize you need to stop the magic before it was to late. You try to focus your magic and only just manage to get a grip on your power so you can change yourself back to normal.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>You gasp as your clothing unravels, becoming a thin top that barely covers your nipples and your pants becoming a dried grass skirt. You blush when you feel the cool air touching your freshly transformed cunny lips, realizing your panties had completely vanished. "Mii nataa mannu ku!" You shout in embarrassment in your native language. Wasn't English your native language? As you wonder this your body changes once again, regaining your darker skin, feminine body and adorably curious expression. But soon you shake off your new found wonder and curiosity when you remember who you were supposed to be. You try to change yourself back with your magic, but you can't find your magic anymore. You blink and panic, quickly noticing a new pouch of pink powder on your skirt's belt. You beam and open the pouch and toss a handful of powder into your own face and are soon blinking, back to your normal self.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>You gasp and begin running your hands over your slimming form, letting out small gasps of pleasure as your skin becomes a beautiful shade of mocha again. You stare at your attacker with her bright brown eyes, giggling as your clothing changes back to the skimpy outfit of a proper tribal girl. You continue to stroke down your body, over your hips and finally reaching behind you to squeeze your perfectly round bubble butt and letting out a low moan as you do. You love the feeling of being a sexy huntress of the jungle, even though you feel very out of place in this cold grey stone city. You lick your lips as an idea begins to form inside your head, but while you were thinking you faintly recall that you are not supposed to think and look like this. You reach into your trusty magic powder pouch and toss some of the pink dust into the air, showering it over you again and causing you to shudder as you change back to your previous form. You pant and know one or two more of that spell and you will be stuck as a sexy little tribal girl. But would it really be that bad?</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>You gasp and begin running your hands over your slimming form, letting out small gasps of pleasure as your skin becomes a beautiful shade of mocha again. You stare at your attacker with your bright brown eyes, giggling as your clothing changes back to the skimpy outfit of a proper tribal girl. You continue to stroke down your body, over your hips and finally reaching behind you to squeeze your perfectly round bubble butt and letting out a low moan as you do. You love the feeling of being a sexy huntress of the jungle, even though you feel very out of place in this cold grey stone city. You lick your lips as an idea begins to form inside your head, if you are no longer in the jungle or with your tribe, maybe you should make this place into a jungle and turn these strange white people into fellow tribal girls! You giggle in glee as you accept your new body and your plan all at once, ready to face the world again.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>You watch as your spell strikes your opponent. Their cheeks flush as they shiver a little, looking down at their hands to see their fingers becoming slim and girly, while their skin began to darken to a sexy mocha hue. They shake their hands and quickly change themselves back to normal.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>You smile as your spell sink into your your opponent's skin. Their hair begins to darken and tangle, becoming somewhat unkempt. Their skin gains goosebumps as the tingling of magic causes their skin to darken all over into a deep and sexy mocha color. Their eyes begin to darken into a brown and they giggle softly from the pleasant innocence of the changes. But before the spell could change them any further, they summon the power and manage to change back.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>You hit your opponent with your spell again, they open their mouth to curse at you "Wa mitta naa chu!" They shout at you in a completely foreign language, their voice becoming higher in pitch and cutesy sounding. Their skin becomes a dark mocha again, their eyes growing rounder and changing eyes a bright brown color filled with wonder and curiosity. Their hair lengthens and turns a dark black in color once again. Their pants begin to look strange strange as they begin to break apart into a short grass skirt. Clearly the sudden exposure of their privates cause them to quickly snap to, casting the counter spell and standing their, blushing furiously. </TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Your opponent gasps as their clothing unravels, becoming a thin top that barely covers their nipples and their pants becoming a dried grass skirt. They blush when they feel the cool air touching your freshly transformed cunny lips, realizing their panties had completely vanished. "Mii nataa mannu ku!" They shout in embarrassment in their new native language. They look confused for a moment, not noticing as their body changes once again, regaining their darker skin, feminine body and adorably curious expression. But soon they shake off their new found wonder and curiosity when they remember who they were supposed to be. They try to change themself back with their magic, but they seem that they can't find their magic anymore. They blink and panic, quickly noticing a new pouch of pink powder on their skirt's belt. They beam and open the pouch and toss a handful of powder into their own face and are soon blinking, back to their normal self.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>They gasp and begin running their hands over their slimming form, letting out small gasps of pleasure as their skin becomes a beautiful shade of mocha again. They stare at you with her bright brown eyes, giggling as their clothing changes back to the skimpy outfit of a proper tribal girl. They continue to stroke down their taut belly, over their hips and finally reaching behind their back to squeeze their perfectly round bubble butt and letting out a low moan as they do. They seem to love the feeling of being a sexy huntress of the jungle, even though they seemed very out of place in this cold grey stone city. They lick their lips before shaking their head and waking up once again. They reach into their trusty magic powder pouch and toss some of the pink dust into the air, showering it over their body again and shuddering as they change back to their previous form. They pant and you know one or two more of that spell and they will be stuck as a sexy little tribal girl.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>They gasp and begin running their hands over their slimming form, letting out small gasps of pleasure as their skin becomes a beautiful shade of mocha again. They stare at you with her bright brown eyes, giggling as their clothing changes back to the skimpy outfit of a proper tribal girl. They continue to stroke down their taut belly, over their hips and finally reaching behind their back to squeeze their perfectly round bubble butt and letting out a low moan as they do. They seem to love the feeling of being a sexy huntress of the jungle, even though they seemed very out of place in this cold grey stone city. They lick their lips and slide a hand between their legs, trying to seduce you and bring you over. You take a step forward but she quickly tosses a handful of pink powder at you. However she throws it into the wind and succeeds in blowing it back into her own face. She sneezes cutely, but doesn't change back to normal, showing that she is now stuck as this adorable little mocha colored tribal girl.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>You begin to feel odd, your mind becoming fuzzy and disorientated. You look down at your hand, seeing them slim down and the skin beginning to darken to a deep mocha color. You blush brightly and shake your hands, your magic welling up and changing yourself back to normal. Funny you think, your magic felt more wild and powerful than before.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>You feel your opponents spell sink into your skin. Your hair begins to darken and tangle, becoming somewhat unkempt. Your skin gains goosebumps as the tingling of magic causes your skin to darken all over into a deep and sexy mocha color. Your eyes begin to darken into a brown and you giggle softly. You gather your magic and change yourself back to normal, feeling your magic becoming wild and free again right before you regained control</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>Your opponent's spell hits you again, you open your mouth to curse at them "Wa mitta naa chu!" You shout at them in a completely foreign language, your voice becoming higher in pitch and cutesy sounding. Your skin becomes a dark mocha again, your eyes growing rounder and your eyes a bright brown. Your hair lengthens and turns a dark black in color. Your pants feel strange as they begin to break apart into a short grass skirt. When you feel your underwear disappear you realize you need to stop the magic before it was to late. You try to focus your magic and only just manage to get a grip on your power so you can change yourself back to normal.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>You gasp as your clothing unravels, becoming a thin top that barely covers your nipples and your pants becoming a dried grass skirt. You blush when you feel the cool air touching your freshly transformed cunny lips, realizing your panties had completely vanished. "Mii nataa mannu ku!" You shout in embarrassment in your native language. Wasn't English your native language? As you wonder this your body changes once again, regaining your darker skin, feminine body and adorably curious expression. But soon you shake off your new found wonder and curiosity when you remember who you were supposed to be. You try to change yourself back with your magic, but you can't find your magic anymore. You blink and panic, quickly noticing a new pouch of pink powder on your skirt's belt. You beam and open the pouch and toss a handful of powder into your own face and are soon blinking, back to your normal self.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>You gasp and begin running your hands over your slimming form, letting out small gasps of pleasure as your skin becomes a beautiful shade of mocha again. You stare at your attacker with her bright brown eyes, giggling as your clothing changes back to the skimpy outfit of a proper tribal girl. You continue to stroke down your body, over your hips and finally reaching behind you to squeeze your perfectly round bubble butt and letting out a low moan as you do. You love the feeling of being a sexy huntress of the jungle, even though you feel very out of place in this cold grey stone city. You lick your lips as an idea begins to form inside your head, but while you were thinking you faintly recall that you are not supposed to think and look like this. You reach into your trusty magic powder pouch and toss some of the pink dust into the air, showering it over you again and causing you to shudder as you change back to your previous form. You pant and know one or two more of that spell and you will be stuck as a sexy little tribal girl. But would it really be that bad?</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>You gasp and begin running your hands over your slimming form, letting out small gasps of pleasure as your skin becomes a beautiful shade of mocha again. You stare at your attacker with your bright brown eyes, giggling as your clothing changes back to the skimpy outfit of a proper tribal girl. You continue to stroke down your body, over your hips and finally reaching behind you to squeeze your perfectly round bubble butt and letting out a low moan as you do. You love the feeling of being a sexy huntress of the jungle, even though you feel very out of place in this cold grey stone city. You lick your lips as an idea begins to form inside your head, if you are no longer in the jungle or with your tribe, mabye you should make this place into a jungle and turn these strange white people into fellow tribal girls! You giggle in glee as you accept your new body and your plan all at once, ready to face the world again.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>You watch as your spell strikes your opponent. Their cheeks flush as they shiver a little, looking down at their hands to see their fingers becoming slim and girly, while their skin began to darken to a sexy mocha hue. They shake their hands and quickly change themselves back to normal.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>You smile as your spell sink into your your opponent's skin. Their hair begins to darken and tangle, becoming somewhat unkempt. Their skin gains goosebumps as the tingling of magic causes their skin to darken all over into a deep and sexy mocha color. Their eyes begin to darken into a brown and they giggle softly from the pleasant innocence of the changes. But before the spell could change them any further, they summon the power and manage to change back.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>You hit your opponent with your spell again, they open their mouth to curse at you "Wa mitta naa chu!" They shout at you in a completely foreign language, their voice becoming higher in pitch and cutesy sounding. Their skin becomes a dark mocha again, their eyes growing rounder and changing eyes a bright brown color filled with wonder and curiosity. Their hair lengthens and turns a dark black in color once again. Their pants begin to look strange strange as they begin to break apart into a short grass skirt. Clearly the sudden exposure of their privates cause them to quickly snap to, casting the counter spell and standing their, blushing furiously. </TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Your opponent gasps as their clothing unravels, becoming a thin top that barely covers their nipples and their pants becoming a dried grass skirt. They blush when they feel the cool air touching your freshly transformed cunny lips, realizing their panties had completely vanished. "Mii nataa mannu ku!" They shout in embarrassment in their new native language. They look confused for a moment, not noticing as their body changes once again, regaining their darker skin, feminine body and adorably curious expression. But soon they shake off their new found wonder and curiosity when they remember who they were supposed to be. They try to change themself back with their magic, but they seem that they can't find their magic anymore. They blink and panic, quickly noticing a new pouch of pink powder on their skirt's belt. They beam and open the pouch and toss a handful of powder into their own face and are soon blinking, back to their normal self.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>They gasp and begin running their hands over their slimming form, letting out small gasps of pleasure as their skin becomes a beautiful shade of mocha again. They stare at you with her bright brown eyes, giggling as their clothing changes back to the skimpy outfit of a proper tribal girl. They continue to stroke down their taut belly, over their hips and finally reaching behind their back to squeeze their perfectly round bubble butt and letting out a low moan as they do. They seem to love the feeling of being a sexy huntress of the jungle, even though they seemed very out of place in this cold grey stone city. They lick their lips before shaking their head and waking up once again. They reach into their trusty magic powder pouch and toss some of the pink dust into the air, showering it over their body again and shuddering as they change back to their previous form. They pant and you know one or two more of that spell and they will be stuck as a sexy little tribal girl.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>They gasp and begin running their hands over their slimming form, letting out small gasps of pleasure as their skin becomes a beautiful shade of mocha again. They stare at you with her bright brown eyes, giggling as their clothing changes back to the skimpy outfit of a proper tribal girl. They continue to stroke down their taut belly, over their hips and finally reaching behind their back to squeeze their perfectly round bubble butt and letting out a low moan as they do. They seem to love the feeling of being a sexy huntress of the jungle, even though they seemed very out of place in this cold grey stone city. They lick their lips and slide a hand between their legs, trying to seduce you and bring you over. You take a step forward but she quickly tosses a handful of pink powder at you. However she throws it into the wind and succeeds in blowing it back into her own face. She sneezes cutely, but doesn't change back to normal, showing that she is now stuck as this adorable little mocha colored tribal girl.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
