<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>You are hit by the spell and feel no different. In fact you could swear you actually feel calmer... You quickly snap out of the trance.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>You are hit by the spell and immediately feel a pressure around your nipples. You formerly flat pectorals begin to bulge and billow until you have small tennis ball sized breasts. You think to yourself oh it's just a simple gender spell. You reverse the changes easily, but regret it as soon as you are back to your male self. Odd... You felt calmer, more rested in your previous form.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>You are hit again with that presumed gender change spell. Again your chest explodes out. It is much quicker this time, and far more violent, with your breasts growing to beach ball sized orbs. You tumble over your now massive boobs as you feel your manhood wither away. You begin to feel a tingling underneath your growing melons. You reach down under your knockers (which is quite difficult now) to find yet another budding pair of tits erupting from your chest. Even though you feel a hypnotic peace come over you, you manage to stop the spell and revert to your previous self.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>The spell strikes you once again, hitting you with the same force of a speeding train. You are pushed backwards until you fall on your now massive rump. Your chest expands until you have breasts the size of bean bag chairs. You feel your second pair of breasts exploding outward until they are roughly the same size as your original rack. You feel a crack in your lower back and soon you realize you are growing a tail. Tan fur starts to accumulate on your body as it develops dark brown patches. Your body starts to reform itself, but you refocus your willpower and reverse the spell.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>This is it, you think to yourself. You close your eyes as your relentless opponent dominates your body. The changes occur even faster than before. Both sets of breasts grow to gigantic proportions, and you nipples, more like teats now, hang lazily from your now light pink udders. They are huge you think to yourself! They are bigger than your forearm now. You find that you are now completely covered in tan and brown fur. You sprout a tail, and swish it around subconsciously. Your bones cracks as it realigns and your fat and muscle grows as you very quickly turn into a cow. You are mentally accepting the role until you hear your opponent say "No that won't do... You need more fat on you..." You snap out of your pathetic surrender and revert to normal. You don't think you can survive another attack.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>This is it, you think to yourself. You close your eyes as your relentless opponent dominates your body. The changes occur even faster than before. Both sets of breasts grow to gigantic proportions, and you nipples, more like teats now, hang lazily from your now light pink udders. They are huge you think to yourself! They are bigger than your forearm now. You find that you are now completely covered in tan and brown fur. You sprout a tail, and swish it around subconsciously. Your bones cracks as it realigns and your fat and muscle grows as you very quickly turn into a cow. Your opponent then whispers a spell that you don't understand. Suddenly you feel yourself bulking up, getting fatter and fatter until you can't move easily. You try to think straight but all you can do is moo. You see your master walk up to you and say something. You can't understand her, but that doesn't bother you for long. You soon begin to think of your increasing hunger and your need to be milked.</TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>You are hit by the spell and feel no different. In fact you could swear you actually feel calmer... You quickly snap out of the trance.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>You are hit by the spell and immediately feel a pressure around your nipples. Your breasts expand to beachball size and start leaking milk. You think to yourself oh it's just a simple breast expansion spell. You reverse the changes easily, but regret it as soon as you are back to your previous body proportions. Odd... You felt calmer, more rested in your previous form.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>You are hit again with that presumed breast expansion spell. Again your chest explodes out. It is much quicker this time, and far more violent, with your breasts growing to beanbag chair sized orbs. You tumble over your now massive boobs as you begin to feel a tingling underneath your growing melons. You reach down under your knockers (which is quite difficult now) to find yet another budding pair of tits erupting from your chest. Even though you feel a hypnotic peace come over you, you manage to stop the spell and revert to your previous self.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>The spell strikes you once again, hitting you with the same force of a speeding train. You are pushed backwards until you fall on your now massive rump. Your chest expands until you have breasts the size of bean bag chairs. You feel your second pair of breasts exploding outward until they are roughly the same size as your original rack. You feel a crack in your lower back and soon you realize you are growing a tail. Tan fur starts to accumulate on your body as it develops dark brown patches. Your body starts to reform itself, but you refocus your willpower and reverse the spell.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>This is it, you think to yourself. You close your eyes as your relentless opponent dominates your body. The changes occur even faster than before. Both sets of breasts grow to gigantic proportions, and you nipples, more like teats now, hang lazily from your now light pink udders. They are huge you think to yourself! They are bigger than your forearm now. You find that you are now completely covered in tan and brown fur. You sprout a tail, and swish it around subconsciously. Your bones cracks as it realigns and your fat and muscle grows as you very quickly turn into a cow. You are mentally accepting the role until you hear your opponent say "No that won't do... You need more fat on you..." You snap out of your pathetic surrender and revert to normal. You don't think you can survive another attack.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>This is it, you think to yourself. You close your eyes as your relentless opponent dominates your body. The changes occur even faster than before. Both sets of breasts grow to gigantic proportions, and you nipples, more like teats now, hang lazily from your now light pink udders. They are huge you think to yourself! They are bigger than your forearm now. You find that you are now completely covered in tan and brown fur. You sprout a tail, and swish it around subconsciously. Your bones cracks as it realigns and your fat and muscle grows as you very quickly turn into a cow. Your opponent then whispers a spell that you don't understand. Suddenly you feel yourself bulking up, getting fatter and fatter until you can't move easily. You try to think straight but all you can do is moo. You see your master walk up to you and say something. You can't understand her, but that doesn't bother you for long. You soon begin to think of your increasing hunger and your need to be milked.</TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd> </TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>You hit your target with the spell. You are disappointed to see that his body is left unchanged. You realize you must hit him a few more times for your diabolical magic to set it.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>He is hit by the spell and immediately is flat chest swells out. He now has tennis ball sized breasts. He looks panicked but suddenly regains composure. He reverses the spell quickly.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>He is struck yet again by your spell. His chest expands until he has fleshy orbs the size of beach balls. Another pair sprouts beneath his 'original rack'. He looks down startled as his manhood becomes his womanhood. 'She screams and falls flat on her outrageously large breasts. It comical to watch the spectical. 'She' reverses the spell and abruptly becomes a 'he' again. </TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>He is hit once again by your spell. He turns into a 'she' and 'she' now has two pairs of breasts both growing very rapidly until all four tits are the size of bean bag chairs. The newly christened breast lady falls on her now gigantic rump forcing milk to spurt out of her salami sized nipples. Her four breasts each supply a steady stream of milk for the floor. She sprouts a tail and is beginning to grow fur when she manages to utter the counter spell. 'He' returns to normal looking dazed and dull.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>You hit him yet again. Your opponent's body begins to change.  He turns into a woman as her breasts explode out from his body as her teats begin to shoot small nearly invisible streams of milk. Her body is now covered completely in tan and brown fur. With each passing second her mind and body are becoming more cow like. Within moments he has gone from a man into a woman, and then into an average sized milk cow, with an oversized udder. You look at the former man, and say " No that won't do... You need more fat on you..." You grin and prepare to further humiliate the milk cow. Your victim seems to have found a way out of your spells hypnotic trance, and reverts back to their regular male body.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>The spell hits him! You know that there is no escape for this poor man. He transforms into a woman and her  breasts explode from her chest, just as another pair grows just under her original pair. They quickly merge to form a gigantic udder easily three times her size. Her body begins to change. You can hear bones cracking and bowels rearranging. A tail hurts out of her back at the same time that fur begins to cover her body. She soon looks like an ordinary cow with an extra ordinary udder. You smile as you whisper another spell. Her body becomes plump and fat. You smile and say "Now we have to put you to work". You smile as you imagine all of the humiliating things you can do to this former male.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>You hit your target with the spell. You are disappointed to see that her body is left unchanged. You realize you must hit her a few more times for your diabolical magic to set it.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>You hit her with your spell and this time you are fortunate enough to see her body begin to change. She squeals as her breasts grow until they are the size of beach balls. She gasps as her hands run over her elongated nipples and milk spurts out. She reverses the effects and changes back to normal.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>You hit her again, and your poor unwitting victim's breasts expand until they are the size of bean bag chairs. She falls forward in utter shock. Milk erupts from her salami sized nipples. She reaches down only to find another pair of tits growing under her now monstrous breasts. Panicked she reverses the spell.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>She is hit once again by your spell. Your victim now has two pairs of breasts both growing very rapidly until all four tits are the size of bean bag chairs. They each supply a steady stream of milk for the floor. She sprouts a tail and is beginning to grow fur when she manages to utter the counter spell. She returns to normal looking dazed and slow minded.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>Your spell hits her. This is it! She will now be your mindless dim-witted milk cow. Her gigantic breasts merge into equally gigantic udders, that are twice the size of her now bulky form. Her body shifts and changes until it looks like a cow's. " No that won't do... You need more fat on you..." You grin and prepare to further humiliate the milk cow. Your victim seems to have found a way out of your spells hypnotic trance, and reverts back to their regular female body.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>The spell hits her! You know that there is no escape for this poor woman. She existing breasts explode from her chest, just as another pair grows just under her original pair. They quickly merge to form a gigantic udder easily three times her size. Her body begins to change. You can hear bones cracking and bowels rearranging. A tail hurts out of her back at the same time that fur begins to cover her body. She soon looks like an ordinary cow with an extra ordinary udder. You smile as you whisper another spell. Her body becomes plump and fat. You smile and say "Now we have to put you to work".</TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>

</Form>
