<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>You feel the spell glance your body, and a strange sense of power surges through you. It almost feels as though your muscles are just stronger. It feels wonderful just to be, so effortless. Your mind idly wanders to working out at the gym or, even better, running a course! So you can show everyone that you a prime example of your breed. Wait, that's not right at all! How strange, your clothes don't seem to fit quite right either. As you cast the counterspell and the changes reverse, you wonder what the caster could possibly have in mind.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>As the spell hits your body, the surge of power returns with greater intensity this time, and you snort through your nostrils, reveling in the feeling of your tense muscles, your strong flanks. You can hear the sound of the seams of your clothes bursting, your skin stretching like taught hide while your bones and muscles grow. You can almost perceive a hypnotic music in your ears, like some deranged delusion. You want more than anything to dance to it. You flick your developing tail which has started to peak out of the bottom of your spine. 

Suddenly, you regain focus like a startled waking from a dream, realizing how far gone you were. You quickly cast the counterspell (and feel a twinge of regret as your body weakens). Now, you're a bit worried as evinced by the beads of sweat forming on your brow.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>The spell hits you directly in the chest, and this time your body wastes no time blossoming into a beautiful, muscular paragon. You hedonistic revelry in your musculature and power distracts you from the very inhuman shape your body is taking. A tail blooms from your spine into a hairy whisk. Even as your fingers and toes fuse together into solid hooves, your face presses outwards into a muzzle and your spine and pelvis rearrange, forcing you to collapse to all fours, you can only admire your huge rear end and your proudly arched neck. 

The hypnotic music returns in your mind, louder, more frantic. You feel as though you are one with it. And as it takes you, you feel a curious lethargy. You just don't want to move. You feel yourself drifting off until a wrenching pain, like being impaled, centers on your chest and back and you feel something pushing through the surface of your skin from the inside. You choke as your throat seizes up. You are shocked out of your empty bliss, and manage to croak the counterspell. Even as you resume your human form, you are visibly panicking.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>The spell hits you fully, and it's getting hard and hard to think about avoiding it when your brain is shrinking in your skull. You know what is happening is bad, but you just can't place your finger, or rather, hoof on it. Your body burgeons into a form of a beautiful horse. Your growing chest, back and rear shred your garments, and you cry out in fear only to have your voice crack into a register you could never achieve as a human. 

Now you can sense another presence invading your mind; the deranged music floods your thoughts and becomes a roar above all else. A roar that threatens to erase your very consciousness. All that power you enjoyed is being taken from you. Your four legs freeze with sickening creaks. They develop an inorganic sheen. You just can't move much at all, no matter how much you desire to. Your flicking tale becomes too heavy to even twitch, and a pole starts growing from your back and chest, skewering you.

The music rings so loud in your mind that you wish to just stop hearing. Stop feeling. Stop thinking. Just as you feel yourself slipping you regain the faintest sense of control, and you reverse the spell. You can still hear that carousel music in your head, and there is a strong longing just to pose in a running form and stop being. You shake your head in a very horselike fashion, trying to clear it. You look at your assailant with pleading eyes.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>Again, the spell strikes you, and you just can't resist as the changes wash over you like a tidal force. You body explodes into the form of a horse. And, for a brief moment you feel powerful and majestic. And then, the music. It screams in your mind like a delirious siren, sweeping your thoughts and senses in a wake of change. The brass pole shoots from your back and chest with a numbing force. And your horse form creaks and cracks as it solidifies into wood and plastic. You feel hollow and empty in side. You start to suffocate, possessing no lungs with which to breath. The sculpted wood progresses through your legs as you strike a dramatic running pose; your immobile legs feel ice cold. 

The paint and wood spills into your spine, and you stop feeling your body entirely. And as it creeps up into your neck you scream out a neigh in terror; the cold touches your mind and everything starts to dim into nothingness. Clinging desperately to life, and with your last ounce of human thoughts, you will the transformations to cease. You conscious mind momentarily blinks out of existence.

With jolt you awaken as a human, completely unaware of how you got here. You are completely exhausted and don't want to think or do anything. As the realization slowly dawns upon you, all you can do is tell yourself you will get through this over and over again. The music in your mind threatens to drown all thought.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>There is no hope of resisting now as the spell strikes its final blow. The changes are so fast, you barely have time to register them, especially as your awareness of everything is turning into an unconscious dream. Your spirit, mind and body relinquishes itself to the form of a horse and then to an inanimate amusement park fixture. There is something peaceful about the inevitability of the changes now. No more worrying about fighting and winning. There is just the music and the silent dream of nothingness.

You whinny as your back and legs solidify into a dramatic pose. You don't even notice as the brass pole glides out of your wooden hide. Your neck pistons your head away from your body and then bends into a permanent arch with a solid mane adorning it. Your eyes stretch to the sides of your head, your ears force their way upwards. The cold touches your mind. Your ears harden, and then all sound rings into silence. Your eyes glaze over into shiny black paint, and the world dims into nothing. You bare your teeth and try to scream, but no sound comes out. You feel empty-headed. Finally the wood rushes over your horse-face, and you blink out of existence. All that is left is your horrified yet goofy expression, indistinguishable from those of the other restive steeds often found at carnivals.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>Your spell glances the victim’s body, and you watch their strange delighted expression. You can see their biceps, chest and legs surge with newfound muscle, and the target starts to develop the chiseled form of a body-builder (some muscles appear to be a bit disproportionate and wrongly placed, but never mind that). At least, your victim seems to be enjoying it as they flex into poses like they were made for doing this sort of thing, showing off their body. Your victim, however, starts acting a bit weird. They prance in place and toss their head. It's almost as if they think they're something other creature than they are. 

Suddenly, they look mortified as if realizing their peculiar behavior, and, much to your dismay, utter the counterspell before the show could get really good. Fortunately, they don't seem to have it figured out yet, by the determined look in their eyes.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>
This time the spell hits more squarely, and you watch as the victim's skin creaks taught with obscenely large muscles. They snort through their flared nostrils, drenched with power, and their butt muscles twitch and spasm until they've got flanks. You can hear the sound of splitting clothing as their upper legs surge into a massive rump, and their arms fuse to their chest, losing mobility and looking ridiculous on a human. They seem a bit absent minded though. And you can hear your victim humming to themselves a strange sort of music, as they paw the air and act like they are crouched over onto all fours. 

They snap out of it, bolt awake, and quickly chime the counterspell. While their body shrinks, you can see them sweating now, though you don’t know if it is just consequent of those horsey sweat-glands they are developing.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>Your spell hits your victim directly in the chest, and the full force of it impacts their body. Their muscles and bones pulse and pump, growing to ridiculous proportions. It sounds like stretching meat and leather. They seem too absorbed in their own strength, however, to notice as a tail starts growing from above their butt, sprouting long, whisking hairs. Now, it is clear they won't be pumping any iron at the gym, as you watch their hands and feet collapse into unwieldy hooves made for running and prancing. Their face starts to stretch into a horse's muzzle and you hear pops and cracks as their spine lengthens, and the hips rotate into a permanently quadrupedal stance. And yet, your victim seems to only want to show off their horselike ass.

Suddenly, their expression goes completely blank like someone just turned off the lights. They stop moving entirely. They even stop breathing! You think you see patches of hair growing, but on closer inspection, you realize their skin is turning into a shiny, smooth surface. Then, you flinch as you see a golden pole start bursting out of their chest and back, growing grotesquely out of the spine. They seem to have noticed this too, since they are now screaming in pain. Well, screaming as much as their are able. It looks like your victims throat becoming solid wood with a glossy finish. They quickly grunt the counterspell before it can progress much further. You can smell the scent of a panicked horse in the air, and you can see the strain in your victims face.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>You channel extra force into your spell; it strikes your victim fully. You watch as their skull collapses while their face pushes outward into a long muzzle. You can only imagine what’s happening to the brain. With the cumulative effects of your previous curses, it doesn’t take long for their expanding body to start resembling a horse fully. You watch the chest and rear balloon with muscle and shred the target’s garments. They cry out in fear, and their voice cracks into an inhuman register.

Their legs freeze up with sickening creaks and develop an inorganic sheen. They can’t seem to move much at all. You watch them strain just to raise an arm - now foreleg - an inch or so. The flicking tail fills with a graceful flash into immaculately sculpted wood. And the brass pole returns, this time spearing the helpless victim through. You can almost witness the anima slipping from that dull, motionless face, interrupted only when your target regains control enough to reverse the spell.

Once they resume their human visage, they shake their head in a horselike fashion and look at you with pleading eyes. They know they are powerless to stop is about to happen. Your spells are definitely taking their toll.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>You’re sure you’ve got them now; your victim looks like they’ve just about given up as the changes wash over them like a tidal force. Their body explodes into the form of a horse. Their face is an expression of unfiltered terror. The golden pole shoots from your targets back and chest with incredible force, and their horse form creaks and cracks as it solidifies into wood and plastic. You see their flesh gradually stop its autonomic twitches and their breathing cease. The sculpted wood progresses through their legs, and they strike a dramatic running pose. Their spine arches and freezes solid, and they seem to be gasping for air as their chest hollows out into an empty wooden cavity. The paint and wood spills across their body and up their neck, and they scream out a terrified neigh that is quickly cut off. Even, those gasps cease as their throat expands to fill their neck and all muscles solidify into inanimate matter. So soon now, their body is a heavy mass of wood and the paint is gliding over their horse muzzle.

But just as it completes, it starts to reverse itself - quite the letdown. Your victim must have asserted their will at the last possible moment and thought the counterspell. As their body cracks and groans, shrinking to human once again, they seem completely absent of thought and action. Only once they are fully human, do they jolt awake like a body brought back from the verge. They crawl on their hands and knees, panting and retching and begging for your mercy.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>There is no hope of your victim resisting now, as the spell strikes its final blow. The changes are very quick, from all the buildup of transformative energies in the target’s body. They seem to just give up as their body relinquishes itself to the form of a horse and then to an inanimate amusement park fixture. The lifeforce has simply caved under the pressure of the transformations.

It produces a garbled whinny as their back and forelegs solidify into a permanent, dramatic pose. It doesn’t even seem to notice as the brass pole glides smoothly out of it’s wooden hide. It’s neck pistons it’s head away from it’s hollowed horse body, and then bends into a permanent arch, adorned with a solid mane. You eagerly watch as it’s eyes stretch to the sides of it’s expanding muzzles, and it’s ears force their way upwards. So sad it won’t get to behold it’s beautiful final moments and its excellent workmanship, you think. The ears harden. The eyes glaze over into shiny black paint, as a tear runs down. It bares its teeth in an attempt to scream, but no sound comes out. A few decorative elements rise from the wood, along with a saddle and bridle. Finally the wood washes over the wooden horse’s face and it’s over. 

All that is left is a horrified yet goofy expression, akin to those of other restive steeds often found at carnivals. You give a few experimental taps on its body and hear a hollow thud. The carousel horse just stands there, not responding at all.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
