<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<Description>You are a beautiful cloak, bound to this world through as an unwitting host, your soul trapped within the fabric.  Your new form draws others' attention, and as they stare into your gently pulsing form they can see the night sky, dazed by shifting stars you can manipulate to distract them.  You pull mana from the bare ether and boost your wearer's magic powers noticeably, albeit unpredictably. However, in addition to your heavy bulk, your shifting form is somewhat distracting and may cause your owner to hurt themselves with magic more often.</Description>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>You are surprised when your opponent focuses on not you, but the ground under your feet. You are surprised again when nothing seems to happen, except perhaps some nearby shadows moving in the corner of your eye.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>Your opponent focuses on the ground under your feet again, but this time, the shadows around you come alive, sending tentacle-like feelers up to sensually brush against your legs. You can't deny that it's pleasurable, and your crotch feels a little stiff as you faintly blush from arousal, before banishing them back to the darkness. You banish them back to the darkness, but the experience leaves you wanting more.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>Your opponent focuses not on the ground, you realize, but on the shadows around you. Shadowy tentacles come forth, wrapping your legs, before slowly and erotically coursing up your body. Your dick hardens when they rub against it, and while they travel steadily upwards, you move your hand to cover your crotch. When they reach your chest you moan loudly before you regain your senses and banish the shadows, but the experience definitely leaves you wanting.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>Once again, your opponent calls forth shadows from around you, and this time they embrace your entire body bringing you again to the brink of orgasm. But this time, they bring you past the brink as they writhe across your skin, wrapping themselves around your dick as it grows harder and harder. You collapse to your knees with a loud grunt. As you fall backward onto the ground in ecstasy, the shadows seem to pull you down into it. You banish the shadows in a moment of clarity, and you lie on the ground panting for a moment before standing back up.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>Once again, your opponent calls forth shadows from around you, and they embrace your entire body, bringing you to orgasm. They writhe across your skin, wrapping themselves around your dick as it grows harder and harder. You collapse to your knees, grunting and ready to come. As you fall backward onto the ground in ecstasy, the shadows pull you down, down into the warm earth. You feel them pushing on your skin, shaping it into something, but all you care about is your mounting pleasure. In a instant of blind panic, you recall the banishing spell, and once more send the shadows away. But as you lie on the ground panting, you both doubt you will be able to resist much longer.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>Your opponent calls forth shadows from around you for what you feel will be the last time, and they quickly embrace your entire body, wrapping it in pure pleasure, bringing you to a final orgasm. They writhe across your skin, wrapping themselves tightly around your erect dick as it grows even harder. You collapse to your knees, accepting their dark embrace. As you fall backward onto the ground in ecstasy, the shadows pull you deep, deep into not the earth, but themselves. They push on your skin, shaping it, and join you in becoming a beautiful black cloak, but you no longer care about anything but your pleasure, a pleasure you feel will be as eternal as the cosmos itself.</TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>You are surprised when your opponent focuses on not you, but the ground under your feet. You are surprised again when nothing seems to happen, except perhaps some nearby shadows moving in the corner of your eye.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>Your opponent focuses on the ground under your feet again, but this time, the shadows around you come alive, sending tentacle-like feelers up to sensually brush against your shapely legs. You can't deny that it's pleasurable, and your crotch feels slightly moist as you faintly blush from arousal. You banish them back to the darkness, but the experience leaves you wanting more.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>Your opponent focuses not on the ground, you realize, but on the shadows around you. Shadowy tentacles come forth, wrapping your legs, before slowly and erotically coursing up your body. You blush crimson from arousal and suppress a moan when they rub against your crotch as they travel steadily upwards. When they reach your breasts, the moan softly escapes your lips. You quickly regain your senses and banish the shadows, but the experience definitely leaves you wanting.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>Once again your opponent calls forth shadows from around you, and this time they embrace your entire body, bringing you again to the brink of orgasm. But this time, they bring you past the brink as they writhe across your sensitive skin, probing your moist crotch and caressing your breasts. You collapse to the ground in moaning ecstasy, and after a minute of this, the shadows seem to pull you down into the earth. You banish the shadows in a moment of clarity, and you lie on the ground panting for a moment before standing back up.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>Once again, your opponent calls forth shadows from around you, and they embrace your entire body bringing you to orgasm. They writhe across your sensitive skin, probing your moist crotch and caressing your breasts. You collapse to the ground in moaning ecstasy as you approach climax, and soon the shadows pull you down into the warm earth. You feel them pushing on your soft skin, shaping it into something, but all you care about is your mounting pleasure. In a instant of blind panic, you recall the banishing spell, and once more send the shadows away. But as you lie on the ground panting, you both doubt you will be able to resist much longer.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>Your opponent calls forth shadows from around you for what you feel will be the last time, and they quickly embrace your entire body, wrapping it in pure pleasure, bringing you to a final orgasm. They writhe across your skin, deeply probing your moist slit and caressing your breasts. You collapse to the ground in ecstasy, accepting their dark embrace. As you lie on the ground in writhing pleasure, the shadows pull you deep, into not the earth, but themselves. They push on your skin, shaping it, and join you in becoming a beautiful black cloak, but you no longer care about anything but your pleasure, a pleasure you feel will be as eternal as the cosmos itself.</TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>You concentrate on the shadows around your target as you recall the summoning spell. He seems surprised that nothing seems to happen, but you see the darkness around him shift ominously in preparation for what's supposedly to come.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>You again concentrate on the shadows around your target, and the shadows around him come alive, sending tentacle-like feelers up out of the ground. As they sensually brush against his legs, you see his crotch start to bulge as he blushes before he somehow banishes them back to the darkness.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>You call forth the shadow creature again, and your opponent seems to notice the true target of your spell is the shadows around him. Shadowy tentacles come forth, wrapping his legs before slowly making their way up his body. His dick hardens noticeably when they rub against it, and while they travel steadily upwards, he moves to cover it. When they reach his chest, a load moan escapes his lips. He quickly regains his senses, however, and again banishes the shadow creatures, but you can tell the experience definitely leaves him wanting.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>Once again you call forth shadow creature from around your target, and this time they embrace his entire body, bringing him again to the brink of orgasm. But the creature continues, and he goes past the brink as its feelers work their way across his skin, before wrapping around his rapidly hardening dick as he collapses to the his knees with a loud grunt. He falls backwards in pleasure and the creature seems to slowly pull him into itself. He banishes it in a moment of clarity, and lies on the ground panting for a moment before standing back up.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>Once again, you call forth the creature from the shadows around your target, and they embrace his entire body, bringing him to orgasm. Its feelers work their way across his skin, wrapping themselves around his ever-hardening dick and he collapses to his knees with a loud grunt. He falls backwards onto the ground, obviously ready to come and soon the shadows pull him deep into itself. You see it pulse, pushing on his softening skin, shaping the two of them into a pile of black starry fabric as the moans continue from within. Surprisingly, he recalls the banishing spell, and once more sends the creature away. But as he lies on the ground panting, you both doubt he will be able to resist much longer.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>You call forth the creature from the shadows around your target for the final time, and they quickly embrace his entire body, wrapping him in pleasure, bringing him to a final orgasm. Its feelers work their way across his skin, wrapping themselves around his ever-hardening dick and he collapses to him knees, accepting the creature's dark embrace. He falls backwards onto the ground as the shadows pull him deep into itself. You see it pulse, pushing on his softening skin, shaping the two of them into a pile of black starry fabric as the moans continue from within. Soon all that lies on the ground is a beautiful starry cloak, the two trapped within for what will likely be an eternity</TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>You concentrate on the shadows around your target as you recall the summoning spell. She seems surprised that nothing seems to happen, but you see the darkness around him shift ominously in preparation for what's supposedly to come.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>You again concentrate on the shadows around your target, and the shadows around her come alive, sending tentacle-like feelers up out of the ground. As they sensually brush against her gorgeous legs, she faintly blushes from arousal before somehow banishing them back to the darkness.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>You call forth the shadow creature again, and your opponent seems to note the true target of your spell. Shadowy tentacles come forth, wrapping her legs before slowly making their way up her body. She blushes crimson from arousal as they rub against her crotch, traveling steadily upwards. When they reach her breasts, a soft moan escapes her lips. She quickly regains her senses, however, and again banishes the shadow creatures, but you can tell the experience definitely leaves her wanting.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>Once again you call forth shadow creature from around your target, and this time they embrace her entire body, bringing her again to the brink of orgasm. But the creature continues, and she goes past the brink as its feelers work their way across her sensitive skin, probing her crotch and caressing her shapely breasts. She collapses to the ground, moaning loudly, and after a minute of this, the creature seems to slowly pull her into itself. She banishes the shadows in a moment of clarity, and lies on the ground panting for a moment before standing back up.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>Once again, you call forth the creature from the shadows around your target, and they embrace her entire body, bringing her to orgasm. Its feelers work their way across her sensitive skin, probing her crotch and caressing her shapely breasts. She collapse to the ground, moaning loudly, obviously approaching climax, and soon the shadows pull her deep into itself. You see it pulse, pushing on her soft skin, shaping the two of them into a pile of black starry fabric as the moans continue from within. Surprisingly, she recalls the banishing spell, and once more sends the creature away. But as she lies on the ground panting, you both doubt she will be able to resist much longer.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>You call forth the creature from the shadows around your target for the final time, and they quickly embrace her entire body, wrapping him in pleasure, bringing her to a final orgasm. They writhe across her skin, diving into her moist slit and caressing her breasts. She collapses to the ground in ecstasy, accepting its dark embrace. As she lies on the ground in writhing pleasure, the creature pulls her deep into itself. You see it pulse, pushing on her soft skin, shaping the two of them into a pile of black starry fabric as the moans continue from within. Soon all that lies on the ground is a beautiful starry cloak, the two trapped within for what will likely be an eternity.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>

</Form>
