<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<Description>As a pair of sunglasses, some may consider your view of the world rather dim, gloomy over your fate and your blackened view. This could not be further from the truth however, as your master saw fit to create a pair of rose tinted glasses. Through your "eyes", the world is bright and shining, full of happy couples and nary a trouble in the world. Whether this causes your owner to miss a naughty school girl and turned into a pair of cute shoes, well, that's hardly your fault now, is it?</Description>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>A red mist seems to fill the air, the taste of cherry in your mouth. It appears to be harmless, but ever cautious you wave your arms, attempting to waft it away from you. It isn’t thick enough so that you cannot see through it, but the sight still strikes you as odd; everything just looks.. better. Lighter. Funnier. Disturbed by these unusually light hearted feelings, you banish the fog with a blast of magic.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>The mist returns with a greater level of speed, accompanied by that unusual giddy feeling of confidence and optimism. You just can’t help but shake it, but everything just seems to be coming up roses for you; your opponent looks frightened and weak, their efforts having no effect upon you whilst you unleash spell after spell, knocking them off their feet with such force that your vision blurs for a moment, strange reflections and angles in your vision, but it quickly fades. You want to gloat to your would be attacker, but you can barely see in this blasted fog. Once again, it dissipates beneath your magical wave. </TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>A sunny smile breaks out across your face as your opponent falls to the floor, cowering and gibbering before your mighty form. The red mist did not return, instead replaced by a strange red tinge across your vision, reflections and bright lights casting unusual images, brief flashes of something indistinct. You feel light on your feet, not only chirpy but downright portable; it feels like you could simply jump into the air and soar away, you’re that elated. One of those reflections appear again, this time rather strong, the image of you laying upon the floor, arms and legs rigid and stiff, bending unnaturally at the ends. It is enough to shake you out of your current almost certainly magical mood, forcing you to slap yourself to dissipate the red tint and happiness. </TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>The world fills with a bright light, far too bright for you to see anything without damaging your eyesight. Fortunately, the red tint re-establishes itself, not so much darkening the scene but making improving your vision and mood to match that level of brightness. Everything just seems so... light. So good. You can barely comprehend your previous mood before the battle, the possibility of feeling anything but this completely beyond you. You dance upon the spot, a merry jig accompanied by hearty laughter, though it doesn’t sound like your own. It seems distant, as if your opponent has moved a great distance away. Speaking of which, where have they gone? All you can see is the red glow, strange sensations of stiffness and something brushing against the sides of your head disturbing you greatly, forcing the magic to waver and shatter. </TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>Your opponent is gone, leaving you in this hollow place, devoid of anything beyond that red glare. You shouldn’t be this happy, but you just can’t help but smile as wide as possible, the sensations of pleasure confusing you greatly, but not enough to break the spell again. Those alien sensations have become stronger, sights and visions of a pair of malformed sunglasses on the floor, writhing in its transformation. Something brushes against and ear and you reach up to touch it, finding the stiff limb of a pair of sunglasses you had not put on. Grasping both sides, you pull with a great deal of effort to no avail, the sunglasses remaining in place, its rosy red lenses obscuring your vision. In a last desperate attempt, you strike yourself across the face, the stinging pain blocking the happiness long enough to dispel it, but it may not work for much longer.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>The sensations of duplicity are too much for you, one light and buoyant and bouncing around, the other solid and unresponsive, lying upon the floor, paralyzed. You can feel the sunglasses, but no matter how much you attempt to hurt yourself, you just can’t seem to cause an impact beyond the briefest of sensations. You would be sweating at this point if you could as you grasp the sunglasses again, this time wrenching them away without resistance, the lack of which catches you by surprise. At the same time, the duplicity collapses and you see yourself for the first time, a pair of heart shaped glasses in the vaguest outline of a human hand. The rest of your form is little more than a spectre, held in place by your true form. Now that it is no longer in position, you begin to dissipate, the last of your spirit sucked into those dark lenses.
Blackness, broken by two bright windows of light in the shape of two hearts. You can see the bright and happy world beyond it, shining lights and pleasant people, not a care in the world, especially for you...</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>A beautiful spell, really. Practically self perpetuating with as little effort as possible on your part. You whisper the spell into the air, as if speaking to a close friend or lover. A red mist surrounds your foe, light enough to provide a tinge to the air but not affect vision. Your opponent seems to think otherwise, as they are flailing their arms around as if it were a thick fog, dissipating the concentration enough to banish the spell.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>The fog or mist appears more quickly this time, the words barely out of your mouth before the air becomes red again. Your opponent is smiling, waving their arms as if they were throwing spells, ducking to avoid imaginary projectiles. You simply stand there, watching their arms begin to stiffen, an unnatural shade of pink replacing their current tone. They seem to be happy however, laughing at something only they can see off to your left before a brief look of annoyance flashes across their face. They wave their arms again, forcing the spell away.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>Your opponent is smiling with glee, standing over their hallucination in triumph. They must believe that they have defeated you, though the truth is a far more unpleasant reality. They stand legs outstretched, arms at their hips in the classic victory pose, spoiled only by the fact that their arms and legs have flattened and curved, now resembling the arms on a pair of glasses. Their body is rather similar, an outline of bright pink on the edges whilst the middle portions have begun to flatten and darken into the lenses. You can still see their head, eyes covered with two bright red squares, a wide smile fixed in place. Something disturbs their revelry however, forcing your victim to slap themselves to remove the fantasy. </TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Two bright red lights appear in front of your victim’s eyes, easily enough to blind them. They do not seem to mind this sudden act however, sunny smile and bouncing on the balls of their feet. They perform a merry jig, the dichotomy of this act enough to cause you to burst into laughter. The pink colouring moves quickly from the extremities inwards, leaving solid plastic arms in its wake. Their legs begin to melt, lowering them to the floor as they begin to wrap around what was once a torso, now nothing more than two black lenses. The outline of their original body seems to hang in the air however, a form of spectre connected with these malformed sunglasses. The head remains, resting in such a position it looks as if they are wearing themselves. The spirit jerks at the sound of your voice, their body flowing back into place as the magic is shattered. </TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>The bright lights return, small red suns hanging in place as their body begins to shrink once again, heart shaped sunglasses fully forming upon the spirit’s face this time. They float in the air around what remains of your opponent, merely a spirit of the victim, as their body is nothing more than sunglasses now. The lights are gone, but a dull red glow remains on the lenses covering their face. Your opponent’s hallucinations seem to be fading, as they are struggling with the sunglasses, hardly a surprise when they cannot muster the strength to remove something more solid than them. Instead, they punch themselves across the jaw, a very solid impact for such an insubstantial being. The spell is weakened by this unexpected turn, allowing their body to once more flow into the outline, though not for much longer by the looks of things. </TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>Your victim transforms so quickly you can barely see it, a pink blur until the spirit and the sunglasses remain. They seem to be attempting to strike themselves again, but more of their spirit has been absorbed into the sunglasses with the last spell, now so insubstantial they cannot grasp anything beyond their new body. Without any option other than to fade away, your victim grimly grasps the sunglasses and pulls them away with a great deal of force, expecting resistance as before but meeting none. In those brief moments of lucidity, your victim clearly understands what has happened to them before the sunglasses fall to the floor, the remaining spirit absorbed into its form.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
