<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>Your enemy attacks you with by casting two black orbs at your feet. You feel like ants are crawling all around your toes, but shrug off the sensation by shaking your feet.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>Your opponent hits you once again with magical black orbs at your feet. As they get all numb, you look down at your feet and watch them taking a black matte hue and shrinking slowly into your legs. Standing on two stumps you struggle to keep your balance when suddenly, your feet simply turn back to normal.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>Now, your opponent throws even more black orbs at your feet, eager to dispose of you. Your feet turn into black stumps, but this time, the magic also spreads to your knees. You feel like you are standing up on two wooden legs. It’s getting even harder now to keep your balance.  With a little cleansing spell, you stop your transformation and return back to normal.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>Your enemy’s spell hits you once more. This time, your whole legs turn into straight black sticks. You are unable to hold your balance and fall on your butt. Your legs slowly open up while curling inside. You touch your former thighs your hands and recognize the feeling of velvet. You also notice a while layer of lace growing on your arms, from your hands to your shoulders. Once again, you come up with a counterspell and revert back to normal. As you stand up, you can't help but notice how dusty this floor is. </TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>Your opponent sprays you with tiny black orbs, each one hitting your body at different places. Your legs turn into black velvet sticks once again, but this time, your legs get pulled open so hard your crotch splits in half. You fall hard on your back, hitting your head on the floor. Stunned, you lift your head up to see your torso has also been split in haft, up to your neck. Now, each half of your body starts to flatten and curl in to form an arch. Your arms get glued to each side of the arch and transform into white laces. Panicked, you look all over the place, looking for help, but your mind keeps focusing on objects out of place, debris to be picked up and dirt to be cleaned. As you start shrinking, you decide to take a deep breath and concentrate on a reversal spell once again and return to your former being, maybe for one last time.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>This time, your opponent cast a single black orb right to your face. Everything goes black and you fall on the ground, stunned. You don't even need to lift your head to watch your transformation. You can feel your body splitting in two for one last time, your legs forming a velvet black headband and your arms decorative white laces. Your head also sinks into the headband and you start to shrink. Meanwhile, the spell tweaks your senses and adapts them to your new form. Even though you can't see, you can feel this place requires a good clean up. If only someone could put you on their head, you could telepathically tell them what chores need to be done to take care of all this filth that sickens you so much</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>You cast two black orbs at your opponent’s feet. You eagerly wait for the transformation to proceed, but your target simply shakes each foot to get rid of your magic.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>Once again, you attack your opponent with your black orbs, but this time, you can see your target’s feet darkening and shrinking into their legs, forming two small black stumps. Sadly, your spell lacks strength and your victim’s feet revert to normal by themselves.   </TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>By casting even more orbs, you accelerate your opponent’s transformation. Now, you can see the blackness crawling up to your target’s knee, turning their lower legs into two black sticks. You can’t help but chuckle as you watch your opponent trying to keep their balance, but your enemy easily stops the transformation with a cleansing spell.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>This time, your spell hits you enemy with more strength. Each of your victim’s leg turns into a straight black stick. Hence, your opponent cannot hold their balance and falls flat on their butt. The transformation works slowly on the crotch by opening your target’s leg, also curving them inside. You recognize the tips of the headpiece. Unfortunately, your enemy once again stops the transformation as you could perceive white layer of frills growing on their arms.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Like a machine gun, you spray your opponent with dozen of black orbs, each one hitting bull's-eye.  Your victim's legs turn into black velvet sticks once again, but this time, they get pulled apart by a strong invisible strength which split your target’s torso in half, sending shivers down your own spine. Your enemy falls on the floor while each stick flattens and curls in together to form an arch, arms turning into white laces on each side of the arch. Your victim now looks like a huge headband with a human head on top. The headband now starts shrinking into an appropriate size, but your target finds residual strength to break your spell and return to normal.
</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>You grin at your feeble victim, knowing it is coming to an end. You channel all your energy and cast one big black orb right into your opponent's face. It stuns them and throws them on the floor. Your victim's body quickly turns into a headband following the same process as before, but this time, it also shrinks during the transformation. You also think you just saw the head disappear into the velvet headband. You walk over to the frilly maid headband and pick it up. Suddenly, you notice how dirty this place is. Many objects are misplaced and covered in dust, plus there is filth all over the floor! You have a strange feeling this headband has something to do with it and you should be careful.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
