<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<Description>This player is a nurse.  Of course, as the vast majority of this town's inhabitants, she is way to sexy and willing to help you not only with your injuries, but also satisfy your carnal needs. She is wearing nurse attire, although it looks like a costume from a sex-shop rather than an actual thing. She is knowledgeable of human body anatomy, thus she can quickly recover herself and knows just where to hit you with her spells. Although she exists to cure people, not to hurt them, so she is much more willing to help rather then fight.</Description>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>Your attacker shoots out a bolt of energy, oddly shaped similar to a medical syringe. And ouch, it did sting like a needle! Too distracted by the pain you don't notice that the projectile seems to inject some sort of magic into you before disappearing. Wave of warmth rushes through your veins, making you calm and relaxed. Your scalp tingles, but you don't notice anything change about yourself, and look on your opponent in confusion.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>The opponent whispers something, which causes your entire body to shiver. Quickly you realize that they have planted some sort of spell within you and now they are manipulating it to change you! You start to scan your body to find your opponent's magic, and expel it, but your thoughts are increasingly distracted by the fact, that your body shifts around here and there. You notice long polished nails on your arms, your hair starts to grow out, soon tickling your neck. You look at your arms - much thinner and smoother than before and think that it actually looks rather pretty. But wait, you don't have time to waste, you need to cure yourself!</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>You keep searching for the virus-spell inside yourself, but this gets tougher and tougher with every passing moment, as you feel your legs changing into shapely womanly form, hips expand, and waist contracts. Your shoulders begin to narrow and you seem to have lost some height. You long, raven-black hair keeps getting into your eyes, and you regret not fastening your hair as you always do in the hospital. Speaking of which, you suddenly remember that hot guy that was recovering after breaking his leg while snowboarding. You really got along with him... in more ways than one. Thinking about his hot, juicy cock starts to arouse you greatly... Wait, this is not right. That never happened - the spell must be messing with your mind now! Angry at yourself, you continue your efforts to reverse what is happening to you, but your thoughts keep refocusing on sucking a cock, which causes your lips to plump up, accenting your now feminine features well.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>As the changes progress, you almost lose track of your own, native thoughts. New memories and feeling overwhelm you, and while you still think about finding the spell, reversing the changes, fighting it... you don't actually DO those things, losing yourself in the changes. You moan slightly when changes focus on your chest, causing shivers all over your hourglass figure your clothes feel tighter and tighter as two mounds of flesh form on your chest. They are two small... you sigh in disappointment and press your hands against your newly formed breasts. The magic affecting you seems to agree, as your tits start to swell larger as soon as you touched them. You can't help but to rub your hands over them as they grow, and it seems like not only they grow in size - they are becoming more and more sensitive too. You let out a silent moan, imagining what an amazing feeling it would be to give a titjob with these things.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>In a brief moment of clarity you look at the cause of your current condition, and immediately notice that his posture is incorrect - their back seems tired of carrying around their belongings. That is too much pressure on the shoulders. Luckily, you know that a good back massage therapy can fix that in no time. And after you are done, you can massage something else... with your butt. That thought felt really good and your mind wandered off, filling with images of your new gorgeous body taking a cock in the ass, moaning in ecstasy. These thoughts seem to serve as an additional catalyst for the changes, as your ass quickly swelled into a perfect round shape to accommodate those desires better.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>Mmm... You moan slightly, still incredibly aroused by your transformations. You did not even notice when did your clothes change into an incredibly sexy and revealing nurse outfit. The only thing left from the old you - the boring you, who you don't want to be any more - is your male genitalia. It looks like the spell inside you have exhausted itself and vanished, leaving you like this. No, i don't want this stupid thing! - you think to yourself. You focus your mind on a simple spell that should fix your predicament. And fix it did! Your legs give in from a rush of sensations as you fall down on your butt, spreading you legs wide and watching the changes. You balls quickly shrank down into nothing, leaving a smooth patch of skin behind. Soon after it was not so smooth any more as an easily identifiable opening formed right underneath you member, which started shrinking, and the lips in between your legs started moistening, showing your arousal. In mere moments your cock almost vanished - leaving nothing but female clit behind. As soon as your transformation finished, your body quivered in a short, but intense orgasm. Breathing heavily, you get up and look at your opponent, smiling gratefully. "Thank you so much for this! You look tired and stressed... i can help you with that." - you wink playfully, hinting how exactly you are going to do it by licking your lips sensually.</TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>Your attacker shoots out a bolt of energy, oddly shaped similar to a medical syringe. And ouch, it did sting like a needle! Too distracted by the pain you don't notice that the projectile seems to inject some sort of magic into you before disappearing. A wave of warmth rushes through your veins, making you calm and relaxed. Your scalp tingles, but you don't notice anything change about yourself, and look on your opponent in confusion.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>The opponent whispers something, which causes your entire body to shiver. Quickly you realize that they have planted some sort of spell within you and now they are manipulating it to change you! You start to scan your body to find your opponent's magic, and expel it, but your thoughts are increasingly distracted by the fact that your body shifts around here and there. You notice very long polished nails on your arms, your hair starts to change - soon becoming a gorgeous mane of raven-black hair reaching just below your neck. You look at your arms - your skin seems so nice, smooth and clear, and think that it actually looks very pretty. But wait, you don't have time to waste, you need to cure yourself!</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>You keep searching for the virus-spell inside yourself, but this gets tougher and tougher with every passing moment, as you feel your legs lengthen, hips expand, and waist contracts. Your clothes change at even faster pace than your body, and soon you find yourself wearing a skimpy nurse outfit - much more suited for a mannequin in a sex-shop, rather than for an actual nurse. You blush in embarrassment, trying to cover yourself a bit more, but that soon becomes quite difficult as your ass swells up, making sure that if you bend even slightly, everyone around you will see your butt in all its beauty, along with the complete absence of underwear.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>Your long, raven-black hair keeps getting into your eyes, and you regret not fastening your hair as you always do in the hospital. Speaking of which, you suddenly remember that hot guy that was recovering after breaking his leg while snowboarding. You really got along with him... in more ways than one. Thinking about his hot, juicy cock starts to arouse you greatly... Wait, this is not right. That never happened - the spell must be messing with your mind now! Angry at yourself, you continue your efforts to reverse what is happening to you, but your thoughts keep refocusing on sucking a cock, which causes your lips to plump up, accenting your feminine features well.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>In a brief moment of clarity you look at the cause of your current condition, and immediately notice that his posture is incorrect - their back seems tired of carrying around their belongings. That is too much pressure on the shoulders. Luckily, you know that a good back massage therapy can fix that in no time. And after you are done, you can massage something else... with your tits. This thought brings a wave of embarrassment - or arousal? You had a hard time distinguishing the two in the last few minutes. You gaze down on your chest and see that this damn outfit makes your hard nipples clearly visible. You try not to think about rubbing them over someone's cock, but it feels too good. Your breasts start to swell under your slutty outfit to make you look even more provocative. Unable to resist, you undo the top button on your outfit - making the already generous cleavage show even more of your breast flesh - and start rubbing them with your hands, admiring the sensitivity of your big titties.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>Mmm... You moan slightly, still incredibly aroused by your transformations. You look at yourself - incredibly sexy nurse in a skimpy outfit - and can't help but think about how arousing you must be for all your male patients. But you enjoy the attention, truly believing that a healthy dose of hot sex only helps people. And you like to help people. You look at your "opponent", smiling gratefully. "Thank you so much for this! You look tired and stressed... maybe i can help you with that?" - you wink playfully, hinting how exactly you are going to do it by licking your lips sensually.</TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>Smiling, you conjure up your spell, eyes locked on target. A magic projectile that looks a lot like a medical syringe forms in your hand, and you feel it with potent magical energy. Before your victim notices your presence, you throw the spell into them like a dart, and it finds it's mark! He is caught off-guard and the painful sting distracts him long enough for the actual spell contained within the projectile to be injected in his body. He effortlessly dispels the projectile that hit him, but the virus-like spell inside him starts to take effect, filling him with warmth and a sense of false security, while it's busy burrowing itself inside their body and hiding.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>When your spell hides itself deep within your opponent's body, you whisper the activation phrase, and it begins to transform his body. He looks at you in confusion, as he did not understand why he was affected by your magic when you did not even cast anything? You watch his arms become thinner, hair lengthen, facial features started to shift into an androgynous shape. Unfortunately for you, he seems to realize what's happening and starts scanning his body in an attempt to find your tricky spell inside himself.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>Feeling that your opponent is getting dangerously close to finding the transformative spell, you whisper another command, giving the virus orders to start working on it's victim's mind. And so it does. You don't know what exactly is happening in his head, but he seems to lose his focus, and a lump on his crotch tells you that he is really aroused. Taking more power in his arousal, the transformation picks up the pace, shifting him towards hourglass figure quickly. To accommodate this change, his clothes change as well, quickly transforming into a skimpy nurse outfit that would look much better on a porn star rather than actual nurse. Your opponent, however, snaps out of his visions relatively soon, and resumes his scan. You curse silently - you cannot allow him to find the transformation source!</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>Trying to distract you victim from fighting the changes, you chant a simple arousal incantation - which takes effect immediately, provoking more changes - this time, his chest sprouts two distinctively feminine breasts. Too small for this outfit and its generous cleavage... Your opponent seems to get to the same conclusion, rubbing his - or perhaps, at this point, her - tits, which causes them to grow, straining the fabric of her outfit, which causes her hard nipples to be clearly seen. Smirking, you wait until the transformation will finish, now feeling confident that you've won.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>Your victim is coming along nicely - her form now definitely female, aside from genitalia. With each passing moment her body seemed to develop more gorgeous curves. Her mind seemed to be completely elsewhere, perhaps daydreaming about letting some guy fuck her in the ass, as her posture was constantly trying to instinctively bend down, presenting her ass to whoever wants to take her. Which only caused her rear asset to become even more pronounced, nice and shapely. Just a few more moments...</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>And then your plan failed. too distracted by you victims sexy body you completely forgot to check up on the transformation spell status - and it exhausted itself and disappeared before it was able to complete the changes. You started to panic as your opponent seemed to gather her own magic - she is going to reverse the effect, or strike you back! Either one is bad news... while you were trying to decide, whether you need to ready your defences or conjure up another offensive spell to finish the deal, she finishes up her own spell that she casts... on herself. You watch, surprised, and she spreads her legs, sitting on the ground, and her male genitalia shifts and shrinks, quickly transforming into female pussy. The finish of the changes caused her to orgasm, moaning out loud in pleasure. As she gets up, she smiles at you and speaks in a pleasant soft tone: "Thank you so much for this! You look tired and stressed... maybe i can help you with that?"</TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>Smiling, you conjure up your spell, eyes locked on target. A magic projectile that looks a lot like a medical syringe forms in your hand, and you feel it with potent magical energy. Before your victim notices your presence, you throw the spell into them like a dart, and it finds it's mark! She is caught off-guard and the painful sting distracts her long enough for the actual spell contained within the projectile to be injected in her body. She effortlessly dispels the projectile that hit her, but the virus-like spell inside her starts to take effect, filling her with warmth and a sense of false security, while it's busy burrowing itself inside their body and hiding.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>When your spell hides itself deep within your opponent's body, you whisper the activation phrase, and it begins to transform her body. She looks at you in confusion, as she did not understand why she was affected by your magic when you did not even cast anything. You watch her skin become visibly smoother and softer, hair lengthen, facial features started to shift into a sexier shape. Unfortunately for you, he seems to realize what's happening and starts scanning his body in an attempt to find your tricky spell inside himself.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>Feeling that your opponent is getting dangerously close to finding the transformative spell, you whisper another command, giving the virus orders to start working on it's victim's mind. And so it does. You don't know what exactly is happening in her head, but she seems to lose her focus, and spot of wetness on her crotch tells you that she is really aroused. Taking more power in her arousal, the transformation picks up the pace, shifting her towards a perfect hourglass figure quickly. To accommodate this change, her clothes change as well, quickly transforming into a skimpy nurse outfit that would look much better on a porn star rather than actual nurse. Your opponent, however, snaps out of her visions relatively soon, and resumes her scan. You curse silently - you cannot allow her to find the transformation source!</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>Trying to distract you victim from fighting the changes, you chant a simple arousal incantation - which takes effect immediately, provoking more changes - this time, her chest bursts outward, growing about one cup size. Still, feels too small for this outfit and its generous cleavage... Your opponent seems to get to the same conclusion, rubbing her tits, which causes them to grow further, straining the fabric of her outfit, which causes her hard nipples to be clearly seen. Smirking, you wait until the transformation will finish, now feeling confident that you've won.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>Your victim is coming along nicely - her form now jaw-droppingly sexy. With each passing moment her body seems to develop more gorgeous curves. Her mind seemed to be completely elsewhere, perhaps daydreaming about letting some guy fuck her in the ass, as her posture was constantly trying to instinctively bend down, presenting her ass to whoever wants to take her. Which only caused her rear asset to become even more pronounced, nice and shapely. Just a few more moments...</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>And soon the spell is complete and the girl standing in front of you can definitely be described only as "slutty nurse". Her outfit is barely concealing any of her gorgeous curves, but she seems to like to show off her hot body. To confirm that, she undoes the top button of her outfit, showing even more skin in her cleavage. She then smiles at you and speaks in a pleasant soft tone: "Thank you so much for this! You look tired and stressed... maybe i can help you with that?"</TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>

</Form>
