<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<Description>A cute, sexy, and sassy cat girl. She is dressed in skimpy clothes that barely cover her lithe and graceful body. She is constantly dancing and happy, her glow sticks and pink dyed fur showing off that she is clearly all about the party and nothing else. She smiles and beckons others close with her charms and sexy form, eager to have a partner to dance with all night and cuddle with during the day. Her mind is filled with living in the moment, and not preparing at all for things to come, making her an easy target to change if you can find it in your heart to transform such a sexy kitty dancer. With her tail flicking about, this slave to the music continue to dance for you and everyone else.</Description>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>You begin to tingle all over, a strange urge to move and dance settling into you. You shake your head to clear these thoughts from your mind. When you open your eyes again the world seems bigger some how, but you quickly realize that you shank by a few inches. You quickly cast a counter spell and change back, wondering what that spell was trying to do to you.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>The tingling returns this time, but is stronger than before. You begin to subconsciously sway your hips and gyrate to music that is beginning to play inside your mind. You giggle cutely as you shrink a bit more than last time. Your ears begin to feel oddly warm as they migrate to the top of your head, becoming triangular and covered in pink fur. They twitch to pick up soft sounds and the sudden increase of noise around you makes you snap out of your trance, quickly gathering your wits and changing yourself back to normal.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>They visable shiver in excitement and begin to sway, gyrating their hips as they run their hands through their hair, which begins to take on a glossy sheen, as well as grow longer and stylish. They quickly shrink to about five feet tall, their ears returning to triangular cat ears, covered in pink fur. They let out a happy purr as their hips become narrow and their breasts become small A cups, giving them a sexy lithe figure perfectly built for dancing. But when they begin to rub their thighs together lustily they groggily let their rational self regain control, gathering up their magic and transforming back to normal.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>You meow loudly as your body begin to change back once again, your ears flicking happily as the beat of music returns to your mind. The sound of the music starts to drown out your rational mind as you begins to dance once again, feeling so sexy and carefree. You suddenly find glow stick hanging of bracelets on your wrists and ankles. You purr and pull your pants down a little, letting your growing tail slide free. You run your hands over your small breasts, taut belly, tight hips, and then happily grope your bubble butt, giggling happily at how cute and sexy you are. A strong sensation grows between your legs, letting you know your getting horny from showing off so much and that you should probably.....change....yourself back. With that though shouting through the music inside your head you begrudgingly summon the counter spell and change back to a boring old human.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>You eagerly begin dancing before the spell even fully grips you, the music blaring in your head as you almost willingly loose yourself to the beat. Your ears and tail return, covered in that wonderful pink fur, your hair lengthening and changing colors to a dyed rainbow style. Your body slims down again, leaving your small, but perky breasts, tight hips, and prominant bubble butt. You look down at your pink colored finger nails, as the variously colored glow sticks appears around your wrists again, held on by a sexy little bracelet, ankles bangles holding the glow sticks on around your legs. You purr deeply, feeling so sexy, so carefree, so eager for another dancer to rock your world after the club closes for the day. You begin to look around for a suitable partner when a faint voice pleads with you inside your music filled mind. With a defeated sigh you let yourself be changed back once more, but you know that next time the bouncer will throw that annoying voice out on the curb</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>You eagerly begin dancing before the spell even fully grips you, the music blaring in your head as you almost willingly loose yourself to the beat. Your ears and tail return, covered in that wonderful pink fur, your hair lengthening and changing colors to a dyed rainbow style. Your body slims down again, leaving your small, but perky breasts, tight hips, and prominant bubble butt. You look down at your pink colored finger nails, as the variously colored glow sticks appears around your wrists again, held on by a sexy little bracelet, ankles bangles holding the glow sticks on around your legs. You purr deeply, feeling so sexy, so carefree, so eager for another dancer to rock your world after the club closes for the day. You smile and blow a kiss at the one who changed you, thanking them for making you into a sultry little cat girl who lives to party, but you giggle to yourself and plan on repaying the favor.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>Your target begins to shiver all over. They shake their head, seemingly to clear their mind of something. You notice them as they begin to get shorter. When they open their eyes again they seem to figure is out as well and quickly change themselves back to normal.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>They shiver visably again , but it is stronger than before. They begin to sway their hips and gyrate to music that you can't hear. You giggle as they shrink again, a bit more than last time. Their ears begin to migrate to the top of their head, becoming triangular and covered in pink fur. They twitch to pick up new sounds, but the sudden increase of noise around them appears to make them snap out of their trance, quickly gathering their wits and changing their self back to normal.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>Your target shivers in excitement and begin to sway, gyrating their hips as they run their hands through their hair.  They quickly shrink to about five feet tall, ears returning to triangular cat ears, covered in pink fur. Your target lets out a happy purr as their hips narrow and breast become small A cups, giving them a sexy lithe figure perfectly built for dancing. But when your target begins to grow wet between their legs they groggily let their rational self regain control, gathering up their magic and transforming yourself back to normal.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>They meow loudly as their body begin to change back once again, their ears flicking happily as the beat of music returns inside their mind. They begin to dance once again, looking so sexy and carefree. They suddenly find glow sticks hanging of bracelets on their wrists and ankles. They purr and pull their pants down a little, letting their growing tail slide free. They run their hands over their small breasts, taut belly, tight hips, and then happily grope their swelling bubble butt, giggling happily at how cute and sexy they felt. The constant rubbing together of their thighs betrayed what a horny kitty they were becoming. They blink a few times before the sigh in annoyance, changing them self back to normal, looking as if they were depressed to ground the sexy kitty dancer inside their mind.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>They eagerly begin dancing before your spell even fully grips them, the music blaring inside their head seeming to become so loud, you think you can almost hear it yourself. Their ears and tail return, covered in that wonderful pink fur, Their hair lengthening and changing colors to a dyed rainbow style. their body slims down again, leaving their small, but perky breasts, tight hips, and prominent bubble butt looking as sexy as ever. They look down at their pink colored finger nails, as the variously colored glow sticks appears around their wrists again, held on by a sexy little bracelet, ankles bangles holding the glow sticks on around their legs. They purr deeply, feeling so sexy, so carefree, so eager for another dancer to rock their world after the club closes for the day. They begin to look around for a suitable partner when a small glint of resistance appear in their eyes. They pout as they begin to change back, but you know one or two more spells will free that sexy kitty for good.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>They eagerly begin dancing before your spell even fully grips them, the music blaring inside their head seeming to become so loud, you think you can almost hear it yourself. Their ears and tail return, covered in that wonderful pink fur, Their hair lengthening and changing colors to a dyed rainbow style. their body slims down again, leaving their small, but perky breasts, tight hips, and prominent bubble butt looking as sexy as ever. They look down at their pink colored finger nails, as the variously colored glow sticks appears around their wrists again, held on by a sexy little bracelet, ankles bangles holding the glow sticks on around their legs. They purr deeply, feeling so sexy, so carefree, so eager for another dancer to rock their world after the club closes for the day. They spot you and smile, blowing a kiss at you. They seem to be thanking you for freeing them from their old self, so they can dance all night, and get it on every day.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
