<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>As their spell falls over you, you can feel a deathly chill running through your body. For a moment it seems like your heart has stopped, but it quickly resumes its beat.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>You feel the deathly chill of their spell fall over you once more, your heart slowing to a gradual halt, as your entire body goes cold. Your face begins to shift, as you grow slightly taller and more imposing, and you feel your canine cut your lip a slow trickle of blood leaking from the wound. Even so the chill passes and your heart starts again.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>The cold enters your body again and you see broken flashes as you feel your heart stop. The image of a person holding your head to their bleeding chest fills your mind, near black blood filling your mouth in the hallucination. You snap yourself out of it, only to find yourself, bleeding from two holes in your lower lip, eagerly lapping up your own slowly trickling blood. Your teeth are longer now, and you feel taller, your face subtly different, but the greatest change is this need, this craving that fills you. Your heart starts beating once more and you let out a sigh of relief as the effects of the spell fade.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>The cold pervades your body once more, and the visions are clearer now. Your attacker seems to be holding your head to their bleeding breast, their blackish blood pouring into your mouth. They hold your head there, forcing you to drink it, and as you drink you feel your body grow cold, and your hunger for it grow, soon they are no longer holding your head, but you are lapping from their chest with a wanton gluttony. The image ends and you feel yourself more powerful, more ancient, your heart is stilled, your body lacking life's warmth, but you have the power and beauty of the grave which attracts so many like moths to the flame. Then your heart starts once more, and you can feel your lifeblood's warmth push back the magic affecting you.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>The cold fills you once more, your heart stopping. You see the same vision as before, but this time you never struggle, kneeling to drink from their blood and become what you must be. Your teeth stretch out, your bearing becomes aristocratic and powerful, and your now blood-red eyes gaze forth from beneath your heavy brow, like a hawk's eager and waiting. You feel the call of the night, of the shadows, somewhere deep inside you, a desire to dance from one to the next, eternally hunting. The power coursing through you, the never dying strength of an immortal lord of the night, fills you with exhilaration, but then it starts again, the pounding of your heart, the cleansing pulse of life's blood flowing through you and you find yourself returning to your previous form.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>Your heart stops, the cold filling you, and with a laugh you know this time it is forever. The music of the night calls to you, the thrill of the hunt, the power of the undead. Your blood-colored eyes scan the crowds for someone to make your lunch, or your thrall. For a moment it's hard to determine which is more delightful. You look at your foe, or unsuspected savior, and throw back your head and laugh. Your reign of shadows has begun.</TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>You feel a chill come over you as your opponent casts their spell. Your heart seems to slow as you feel an itching sensation in your groin and chest. You dismiss the smell with hardly a thought.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>The chill comes over your body again as your opponent's spell slows your heart to a stop. Your whole body tingles as your shoulders grow broader, your body thicker and taller. You can feel your breasts begin to shrink, your pussy merging shut. You manage to dismiss the magic with a sigh of relief.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>The deathly chill creeps over you once again, as your heart stops. You feel your breasts shrink down until they're little, aa-cup bumps, your pussy merging shut as your clit extends into a micropenis. Your torso grows broader, as you become taller, your arms and legs thickening. You can feel a hunger stirring inside you, as your teeth extend almost cutting your lip. As your tongue explores your new fangs, you can feel your lip is flatter and more masculine, and imagine the same is true of your face. With irritation you dismiss the spell affecting you.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>The chill returns once more, freezing your heart in your tracks. You can feel your breasts flatten, leaving you with first a smooth chest and then the muscle hardens and powerful pecs form. Your pussy fuses shut, as your clit extends outward into a powerful cock. You can feel your shoulders widen as you grow taller. Even as your body changes so does your mind. You feel a growing hunger stirring in you, a thirst for blood. You look about, hungry, but a beam of sunlight touches you and as you hiss in pain your mind clears and you dismiss the spell.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>Your blood freezes as your heart stops. Your once full breasts dwindle to nothing, your feminine waist expanding even as your rounded hips shift into a more masculine configuration. Your face hardens, becoming the harsh face of a traditional lord, your brow deepening, even as your eyes turn a deep red. Your pussy is gone, a large cock growing from where your clit once was, full balls hanging beneath it. You feel your teeth expanding, the hunger of the vampire growing within you. You are a king, a lord of the shadows, and you feel yourself in your domain. It is only a bit of sunlight which reminds you of what you were, and that you ought to fight this. With all the will you can muster you manage to break the spell, but it was difficult and next time might not be enough.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>Your heart stops as your breasts shrink away once more, and a cock grows between your legs. Your body quickly becomes that of an ancient aristocrat once more, and with it comes the hunger. You smile, showing pristine white fangs, you will find prey, and perhaps lovers. Yes, that might be good, a bride for the vampire lord. Your former opponent catches your eye and you chuckle, a thick, lordly chuckle, wondering if they might do nicely.</TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>You watch as your target's face pales, they brow deepening, and cheeks become more distinct. The spell cannot stop their heart completely, though, and their coursing blood soon reverses it.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>You feel his heart stop, the spell slowly changing his blood into the dark ichor of the nosferatu. His face takes on a traditionally noble visage, even as his presence seems to grow. Even so his pallor soon fades as his heart beats again driving out the spellwrought ichor and returning him to his previous state.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>Your spell seems to stop his heart as deathly pallor sets in once more. They seem somehow more, even as the shadows welcome and conceal his body. His noble face, breaks into a grin as his canines extend into fangs, and then his eyes open, red as blood. You see the first look of hunger on his face, and then the blood begins to pump again, driving out your curse.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>You watch as his flesh grows pale and cold once more, his features growing aristocratic and defined. He seems in a trance pleading for you to stop, begging for no more, but then his voice changes, growing deeper, and more commanding. "Yes," he says, "More, give me more." Fangs show in his mouth as he speaks and his eyes open, red as crimson, and then he seems to awaken, a rosy flush returning to his face as your spell fades.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>His heart stops, his blood slowing, and you can see the physical changes happening quicker this time. He stands, regal, domineering, a lord of the night, and he whispers, then his eyes open. They gaze forth with power, command, and a predatory hunger. He takes a step forward and you feel fear through your body. His smile, showing his pearly fangs only worsens it, even as it stirs desire within you, then he blinks his eyes returning to their former hue. His skin grows ruddy with blood once more and you know the spell was only barely reversed. Next time it might not be, and you aren't sure if that scares you or delights you.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>You watch as his heart stops once more, his visage growing noble and proud yet again. His eyes open, red as blood, and he smiles, lips red against his deathly pallor. "Yes, yes," he says. He steps forward, the shadows flowing behind him like a cape, and his smile widens, as his predatory gaze passes over you. You feel fear, and also desire for him, as he looks at you, and find yourself worrying what would happen if he beckoned you. You may have created a monster.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>You watch as your target's face pales, her shirt growing a little looser around her chest. She quickly dismisses it with an offhand gesture.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>You watch your target's face grow pale as your magic takes hold of her. Her breasts shrink down more than a cup size, as her shoulders grow broad and mannish, her face becoming harsh and angular. They seem a little distressed as they dismiss the spell.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>Your target pales as your magic slows and stops her heart. She lets out a little gasp as her canine teeth become fangs, and her breasts shrink down to tiny bumps. Her torso widens, as she begins to look almost like a dashing gentleman from a noble lineage. She stands, a look of hunger playing across her face, obviously wrestling with your magic for several moments before they finally dismiss the spell affecting them.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>You watch as your spell stops her heart, causing her flesh to take on an inhuman pallor. Her breasts slowly shrink back into her chest, even as a bulge forms in her, now his, pants, as his former pussy vanishes and a cock grows in its place. His shoulders widen, as his hips and waist shift towards a masculine configuration. He opens blood red eyes, a look of hunger on his handsome face, a hunger both for food and sex. You shiver for a moment as you meet that gaze, and are actually a little relieved when they dismiss the spell.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>You watch the spell stop her heart, her body becoming male once more. Shadows wrap around him like a cloak, his cock rigid despite the lack of blood flow. He moves forward, his face like an eagle's, noble but predatory, and somehow you feel like a mouse under its gaze despite being the one to cause this. He takes a step forward, and leaving you feeling frozen, but the sun scorches him and he lets out an animalistic hiss as he counters your spell. You find yourself trembling, realizing that she is that close to being completely transformed, but that in so doing you may create a monster.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>Resolved to finish this you cast your spell again and her face immediately pales. Fangs extending from her lips, as her body transforms. Breasts and curves vanish, as her softness leaves her, replaced with a harsh, angular strength, broad shouldered, and powerful. He strides forward, cock partially hard, his red eyes meeting yours. Something about that gaze is hypnotic pulling you in, and you can hear his deep voice speaking to you, stirring a need within you. As the shadows sweep around them, you realize that this might very well have been a mistake.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>

</Form>
