<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<Description>This sly fox of a man stalks the town looking for prey, to steal money, items, and perhaps things more precious. His body is slim and agile and his mind is sharp, his red and white fur does well, mostly, to hide a strong body underneath. His every move seems calculated and precise, and he's always one step ahead of his target, some might even suspect he is toying with them. Should his stealthy approach be broke however he is quick to take off and try again later, he is not one to engage in a direct fight. </Description>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>A warm tingle spreads across your body as the spell hits. You feel tiny pricks across your skin and a tightness in your muscles before it dissipates. </TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>The tingle spreads over you once more as your chest begins to grow a patch of white fur. Your body begins to feel tighter, stronger, more agile as the warmth spreads. The last thing you feel before the magic ends is a movement as your ears grow and move a bit up. </TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>The warmth hits you again and your body is a light with the prickly tingle of before. Your chest is full of white fur as it spreads outwards in all directions becoming a reddish color as it reached your sides. Your body once again becomes taught and firm as the fur spreads across you, you feel more agile then ever before and you feel a desire to use that flexibility and skill... Your face continues to reshape slowly your jaw extending into the beginnings of a muzzle as your ears find a new home atop your head becoming more animalistic and black in color as they too gain fur. </TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>Your body is almost instantly returned to a semi-furred state as the prickling tingle returns and spreads to your upper arms and down into your upper thighs. You feel a tickling tingle as it passes through your cock and balls transforming them agonizingly slowly and pleasurably into something more animal then they used to be. A pressure from behind you draws you attention as you grunt with the change and slowly a tiny tail begins to form just furred enough not to show skin. Your face is more pronounced and covered in fur now as your jaw continues to push into its final form. Your eyes become that of the predator you are and your short hair becomes the color of your fur. </TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>Oh you can feel it once again, so close, your body bursts back into a fur covered half beast again, the tingle spreading down your arms and legs into your hands and feet. Your hands become furred and claws extend from your finger nails to help with traction and your feat follow much the same way. Your tail grow in behind you full and fluffy a perfect aid to your balancing acts. </TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>Once more fur bursts across your body changing everything as it goes. Upon your head now sit two black ears and your face has pushed out into a muzzle of sharp teeth which you check with your tongue and a smirk. Your body is taught, spry, agile and covered by a red fur. You feel as though you could slip into and away from anywhere you pleased with ease in this form. Your tail to help with balance in the most acrobatic of feats, your claws on both your hands and feet to help you with traction and grip, and your mind sly and cunning to outwit who ever or whatever becomes the target of your new desires. </TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>A warm tingle spreads across your body as the spell hits. You feel tiny pricks across your skin and a tightness in your muscles before it dissipates. </TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>The tingle spreads over you once more as your chest begins to grow a patch of white fur. Your body begins to feel tighter, stronger, more agile as the warmth spreads. The last thing you feel before the magic ends is a movement as your ears grow and move a bit up. </TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>The warmth hits you again and your body is a light with the prickly tingle of before. Your chest is full of white fur as it spreads outwards in all directions becoming a reddish color as it reached your sides while your beasts start to deflate on your chest, the fur tickling your nipples lessening as they become smaller and less sensitive. Your body once again becomes taught and firm as the fur spreads across you, you feel more agile then ever before and you feel a desire to use that flexibility and skill and you grow in height as your figure becomes more angular and masculine. Your face continues to reshape slowly your jaw extending into the beginnings of a muzzle as your ears find a new home atop your head becoming more animalistic and black in color as they too gain fur. </TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>Your body is almost instantly returned to a semi-furred state as the prickling tingle returns and spreads to your upper arms and down into your upper thighs. Your breasts have all but vanished against your tight chest, nipples following suit as they become their male equivalents. You feel a tickling tingle spreading in your hot pussy as your clit grows and grows. Slowly it grows thicker and longer in its new sheath until you have a very real very animal set of cock and balls. A pressure from behind you draws you attention as you grunt with the change and slowly a tiny tail begins to form just furred enough not to show skin. Your face is more pronounced and covered in fur now as your jaw continues to push into its final form. Your eyes become that of the predator you are and your short hair becomes the color of your fur. </TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>Oh you can feel it once again, so close, your body bursts back into a fur covered half beast again, the tingle spreading down your arms and legs into your hands and feet. Your hands become furred and claws extend from your finger nails to help with traction and your feat follow much the same way. Your tail grow in behind you full and fluffy a perfect aid to your balancing acts.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>Once more fur bursts across your body changing everything as it goes. Upon your head now sit two black ears and your face has pushed out into a muzzle of sharp teeth which you check with your tongue and a smirk. Your body is taught, spry, agile and covered by a red fur. You feel as though you could slip into and away from anywhere you pleased with ease in this form. Your tail to help with balance in the most acrobatic of feats, your claws on both your hands and feet to help you with traction and grip, and your mind sly and cunning to outwit who ever or whatever becomes the target of your new desires. </TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>You watch, your magic cast as the man before you squirms slightly at its touch. </TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>Once more your magic hits him, white fur spreads upon his chest and you notice his ears start to change and move atop his head. His body seems more pronounced as the magic takes hold, his form more lean and a hint of an animal strength or agility. </TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>The white fur on his chest starts to spread across his body, meeting red fur on the sides. His ears have settled upon his changing head growing larger and black while his face pushes out into a muzzle more fitting his coming form. You watch his posture change some as animal instincts and new thoughts are surely probing his mind. </TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>The fur continues its steady march across his body, into his upper arms and lower legs now. His face takes on more of a fox like appearance with his muzzle pushing further out, his face covered in fur and his eyes a predatory yellow. Below his cock begins to change into a more animalistic counterpart settling nicely in its sheath. Finally a tail begins to form, slowly and about half its length. </TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>The fur continues and this time his hands and feet are changed, both gaining claws which will help him in his feats of crime. behind him his tail grows out long and proud now with all its fluffy fur. Slowly he is coming together to be the prefect criminal, the power of his animal form and the sly mind of a fox.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>Finally he stands before you changed, a fox man. His tongue licks at his sharp teeth with a smirk as his predatory eyes are already looking you up and down for a potential mark. His body is taught and agile covered in red fur and he stands already in a way more fitting him, ready to spring to action, ears twitching atop his head at the slightest sound. </TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>You watch, your magic cast as the woman before you squirms slightly at its touch. </TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>Once more your magic hits her, white fur spreads upon his chest and you notice her ears start to change and move atop her head. Her body seems more pronounced as the magic takes hold, her form more lean and a hint of an animal strength or agility. </TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>The white fur on her chest starts to spread across her body, meeting red fur on the sides, while her breasts slowly start to deflate. Her ears have settled upon her changing head growing larger and black while her face pushes out into a muzzle more fitting her coming form. You watch her posture change some as animal instincts and new thoughts are surely probing her mind. </TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>The fur continues its steady march across her body, into his upper arms and lower legs now. Her face takes on more of a fox like appearance with his muzzle pushing further out, her face covered in fur and her eyes a predatory yellow. Her chests shrinks into its new manly form while below she grabs at her crotch new sensations forming. From her pussy her clit extends and changes as a sheath forms around her new anatomy.Finally a tail begins to form, slowly and about half its length. </TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>The fur continues and this time her hands and feet are changed, both gaining claws which will help him in her feats of crime. behind her, her tail grows out long and proud now with all its fluffy fur. Slowly she is coming together to be the prefect criminal, the power of her animal form and the sly mind of a fox.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>Finally he stands before you changed, a fox man. His tongue licks at his sharp teeth with a smirk as his predatory eyes are already looking you up and down for a potential mark. His body is taught and agile covered in red fur and he stands already in a way more fitting him, ready to spring to action, ears twitching atop his head at the slightest sound. </TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>

</Form>
