<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>You try to shift out of the way of the flashy spell sent at you, but misjudge where it's going. It doesn't seem directed at your body, but your legs. They tingle a moment, feeling a little itchy, but otherwise just fine. Just to be safe though, you cast a reversal spell.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>Some deft hand-motions by your opponent catches you off guard as the spell strikes you. The magic hits your legs and a strong tingling travels up them, encompassing your entire body. You feel light headed for a moment, and glancing down, you see a criss-crossing type of pattern on your legs. Quickly you counter the spell, but the sensation takes a while to fade away.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>Quicker than your eyes can follow, your opponent unleashes a spell that strikes you right at your feet. You watch in stunned horror as a criss-crossing pattern literally etches its way up your legs and body. You feel lighter as well, and seem to be falling. Wait, not exactly, you're upper body is falling into your legs, while your legs seem to become some type of material. You summon your will and reverse the spell, returning to normal and panting slightly, disoriented from the experience.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>One moment your opponent's hand is over there, the next it's here casting a spell you aren't able to dodge in time. An intense tingling suffuses you as your upper body seems to simply fall into your legs, which have become some type of material. They are hollow inside and almost look like a net of some sort. They still hold their leg shape, but they seem so empty. Maybe you can have someone slide them over their legs. They would look so sexy with you on them. Suddenly you realize you shouldn't be thinking like that and quickly cast a counter spell, your body returning to normal.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>A spell hits you again; you're not even sure where it came from. You get a sensation of falling in slow motion, but the real reason is because you're much lighter. Your legs have become some sort of material, forming the shape of fishnet tights, and your upper body falls into it, merging with the fabric. Soon you're merely an empty pair of tights standing upright and swaying slightly. You feel so empty and incomplete. A nice pair of legs would fix that. Your fabric stretched taut over them would draw everyone's eye as they walked around in you. You imagine it would feel wonderful. That is, until you remember you aren't fishnet tights and snap out of it. You cast the reversal spell and change back, unsure if you can survive another hit.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>A bright flash, a sudden lightness, and you can tell that it is over. Your body rapidly reforms, your upper body merging with your legs as they become fabric patterned like a net. As you fall to the ground as a pair of fishnet tights, you can't help but feel a sense of loss. Not at being defeated like this, no, at the feeling of being so empty. You wish someone would slip you on, fill you with their legs so you can encase them with your provocative design. They would look so sexy wearing you. Sexy and magical....</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>Using a bit of misdirection you sling this spell, watching as they dodge the wrong way. You grin to yourself as you see it hit their legs and a wave of magic suffuses them. You think you may see a pattern on them, but it might be the light. They hardly notice however, casting a reversal spell out of reflex, though they give their legs a scratch before they do.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>With a feint you hit them with the spell. You clearly see a criss-cross pattern forming upon their legs where the spell lands. And they seem to lose weight. Perhaps they're shrinking? It lasts only for a bit though, as they quickly counter the spell. They look a little unnerved however.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>You catch your opponent with the spell, watching as it quickly takes effect. Their legs seem to become some kind of material, a net-like pattern forming as they hollow out. Their upper body falls into their legs, merging with the material, almost leaving them as nothing but a pair of legs standing there. But suddenly they seem to gather their wits and counter your spell, returning to normal, though a bit worse for wear.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Your hands are a blur as you cast the spell. Confused, your opponent merely stands there as you hit them dead center. Quickly their upper body shrinks and falls into their lower body, merging with their legs as they take on the pattern of fishnet tights. They begin to hollow out, creating a space to slide your long legs into. Soon they're nothing but a standing pair of tights and you think the spell has finished, when they begin to change back, having somehow cast a reversal spell.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Your victim is distracted as you hit them with this spell full blast, their upper body merging with their lower torso as their legs change into fabric, hollowing out to become fishnet tights for you. In a matter of seconds, they have completely changed into the clothing and are falling to the ground. You're about to reach out and grab them when they suddenly twitch and snap back into their previous state, apparently somehow managing to reverse the change. So close....</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>Before they can even react, you hit your victim with the spell. They seem to fall backwards, but it is merely the top half of their body merging with the fabric that their legs have become, the fishnet design having completely overridden what their legs normally look like. It's over in a blink of an eye. One moment they're standing there, the next a pair of fishnet tights are falling to the ground. You pick them up and run the material between your fingers. You definitely can feel some magic in these tights...</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
