<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>Your assailant shoot a black sphere to you pin pointing your chest, immediately after being hit you felt your body temperature lowering, sending shivers down your whole body. Your skin turn paler, but before it get farther you cast a counter spell and turn back to normal. Whatever that was it couldn't be good.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>Your opponent manage to hit you again with the black sphere, like last time your body temperature lower greatly and your chest start to hurt. You felt your heartbeat getting more and more rare, was they trying to kill you?! You hurry and undo the effect before feeling too weak to stand up and the warmth come back to your body. </TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>You get hit once again and feel the warmth leaving your body, but it wasn't as scary as it was before, it felt more natural, more relaxed, like a liberation. You felt your skin turning white and more delicate and your vision turn sharp you noticed you could now look at the darker place as well then the lighten area, you rapidly shake your head and turn back to normal, noticing the spell was starting to affect you mentally.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>Yet again your opponent shoot the spell directly on you, but it was different, it didn't felt like you were dying you knew it for sure now it was rather a reborn. Your human body was frail and weak but this one was better, faster and let face it sexier. Your curves your perfectly shaped breasts, but right when you were examination your new body a ray of light reach your eyes and blind you, it was momentary enough for your old mind to come back and for you to cancel the change before it was too late.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>This time your body do not even try to move when the opponent launch the attack. You stand there desiring to be turned, to feel reborn to drink the essence of death itself. You body turn perfect, your skin turn perfect, even your teeth turn perfect, perfect to drain the life out of your helpless prey. You giggle thinking on how you could easily fool those mortal to do whatever you wish by only lifting a single finger. But yet again the sun shine bright and blind you, shaking your old mind, with all the willpower that you had left you managed to undo the change unsure if you could realize something of this feat again.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>Your opponent shoot the orb in you for one last time causing your body to change faster you could even blink, the sweet cold of death the perfect desirable body, the desire to control all mortal around you, all this assault you all at the same time and you loved it. You were simply perfect you pass over the frontier of death to reach a point that little people could have ever reached. A point where you were now perfect in both life and death. It is sure the sun was a bit harsh on your delicate pure white skin, but you could easily dismiss it, after all even this big orb of fire was not strong enough to stop the new you.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>You cast the spell on your opponent that took the form of a black sphere, hit on the chest they back off a bit, holding it shivering when their skin turn paler and paler. At the look you could tell their body temperature was dropping greatly, but sadly they undo the spell before anything else happen.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>This time your opponent  flinch backing off and put a hand on their chest, they probably felt their heartbeat slowly getting rarer. You smirk at the idea that the person right before you was dying, but naturally you knew they weren't truly dying, you aren't monster... or maybe you actually are... anyway before it go farther your victim undo the change getting some  color back and in addition a face showing total fear.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>The spell hit your victim again turning their skin pure white and more soft, this time they seem less shaken by the cold, their hair slowly lengthen into a beautiful silver waterfall. The poor soul close their eyes for a bit and re-open them, but they were different, the iris was an exotic red when their pupil took a slit like for like cats in middle of the day. They glance at their surrounding for a bit, but a few second later they undo the spell at your great deception.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>You pin point hit your opponent again, but this time all the previous change happen in the first second letting your opponent body to reshape and take a sexier form, the form you imagined when you casted the spell. Snow white skin, long silver hair, sharp but awfully inviting red eyes and a smile that could seal most of the men heart in a few seconds. The victim seem to observe herself too, passing her slender hands on her curvy and elegant form, but in middle of her (and yours) contemplation she shield her eyes from the sun and undo the change. Like it wasn't hard enough even the sky is against you on this one, but you are sure only a few more time will be enough to finalize the change. </TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>This time you easily hit your opponent, like they didn't even try to avoid the spell at all, but you don't really mind it is only making your job easier. Once again your opponent took the form of a sublime night creature, a beautiful vampire woman was standing in front of you and you could see it in her eyes that she loved it. The way she was smiling was for sure unsettling, but you knew her mind was completely changed. Well it is what you thought until Mr. sun help the poor soul to retrieve their way to the light, but without leaving a strong strain, just one more little push and you are sure they will break completely.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>You shoot a final black sphere in your victim body, causing them to instantly turn into the sexy vampire woman you lung to see, but something was different this time, you do not know if it was their eyes or their gesture, but you feel like you didn't stand in front of the same person. She clearly had a aura she didn't had before a dangerous yet attractive one. Mesmerized you stay there looking at the new creature that had took the place of your opponent, turning to the sun, remembering the effect of it you ready another barrage of sphere in case she turn back, but she simply smirks showing her pointy teeth before turning her back to you and walk further. You couldn't stop thinking it was probably not a good idea to make her solar resistant.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
