<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>The other mage stands for a moment, weaving his arms in an unusual pattern. You are light upon your feet, ready to dive out of a spell. He does not fire at you however, simply creating a flash of light from their hands and in front of you. Your eyes dart around, searching for any changes or attacks but you cannot seem to find any. The air feels muggy and humid however, shimmering and waving in a strange fashion. This waving only increases until it forms a mirror image of you, standing there looking at the mirror. You step forward to touch it, only to see your duplicate does not do the same. The shock runs through your system, the sudden burst of adrenaline allowing you to dive out of the way of the incoming spell instinctively. You curse yourself for being distracted and gaze at your opponent again, though you are finding it difficult with the mirror hanging just on the edge of vision.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>Your opponent performs a feint, forcing you to side step into the actual spell. Your skin begins to darken, becoming a reflective black, strangely resilient to the touch. The changes focus upon your legs however, forcing them together and melding into one solid lump, squaring off in shape. You wobble, attempting to maintain your balance on this strange new appendage. Once again the mirrored world catches your eye and you see your duplicate suffering the same fate, though they seem to be worse off. Their torso is beginning to warp and flatten, but you tear your eyes away and dispel the effects before you begin to suffer the same fate.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>Your movements feel sluggish and limited, making it difficult to dodge the balls of energy being thrown at you. The mirror has resettled halfway over your vision now, and you can't turn away from it, the mirror following your gaze. Your legs feel stiff and surprisingly sturdy, allowing you to balance upon them despite your knees and feet being locked in position. One of the balls catches you on the side and winds you, allowing the second to strike you directly in the chest. Your legs once again form the strange black pillar, this time losing your balance. You catch yourself on your arms, but the pose is not very comfortable due to the length of the pillar. This does not last long however, as your back begins to languidly stretch, arching forward, causing you to rest on your elbows in a surprisingly comfortable manner. It warps and shifts, becoming flatter in the middle whilst the sides rise upwards. Desperately, you scream the dispelling incantation and collapse to the floor, sweating.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>The mirror dominates your entire vision now, blinding you to any incoming spells, but not preventing them. Your duplicate is struggling too, staring at both you and their own mirror, trying to dodge the spells flying through its opaque surface. You are both struck at the same time in the chest once again, mirroring the effects of the first stage, forming the pillar once again. You topple forward as your back arches in preparation, sides folding upwards. Your arms melt into your chest, forming another solid black mass like before. You catch a glimpse at your duplicate and you finally realize what is happening to you. You're becoming a pair of shoes! The front of you shapes itself, smoothing the sides. Your mouth opens wider as your head stretches, becoming the front end with a peep toe. You aren't complete however, and you desperately grasp at your humanity, restoring your form.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>You do not even attempt to dodge the spell now. Thoughts permeate through your mind of shoes, sexy high heels and women wearing them. You fall into the position naturally, quickly shifting into a sexy pair of platform heels. Something is still missing however. You realize with a start that the back of the shoe is not there, leaving only the bottom. The mirror world appears to be dealing with that, however. Your duplicate is struck by the spell, their legs blending into a high heel and their torso flattening outwards. Their arms also become flat, hands a silvery color. They join in a circle, forming the strap. The mirror begins to waver again, collapsing suddenly with a clap of thunder. It is only now you realize you're fully formed! Your back and strap are now a part of you, but the spell hasn't finished yet, even now. The magic dissipates on its own, leaving you awkwardly bent in its pose.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>Your opponent doesn't even bother to use the mirror world to distract you, simply firing a ball into your unresisting form. You sigh, enjoying the feeling of becoming such a sexy piece of footwear. The mirror flashes briefly and disappears, returning you to your full form; A five inch platform heel. Your opponent smiles over you, then frowns for a second. They cast another mirror spell and another version of you appears! You feel complete now, a sexy shoe for a sexy person. You can't wait to be worn!</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>Your target looks ready to move, and you know the spell is quite slow. You won't hit them if you can't distract them somehow, and you still need to create a second shoe too! A thought comes to mind on how to kill two birds with one stone. You concentrate your mind, creating a magical mirror, a duplicate of sorts, to be affected by your spells as well. The air shimmers around your target as this forms, blocking their vision partially. They look confused for a moment, distracted, so you quickly fling a ball of energy. Too slow unfortunately, as they dive to the left. The mirror is functioning, however, so it isn't all bad.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>You fling a hand forward but do not cast the spell, waiting for your opponent to dive before you unleash the energy. The ball clips them in the side, causing their skin to darken in tone into a deep black. It's an almost reflective surface, the perfect shiny leather for your new shoes. Their legs fuse into one mass, the high heel, though they haven't appeared to have worked this out yet. They quickly dispel the enchantment.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>They appear to be struggling with movement somewhat, their skin remaining a black leather and their legs incapable of moving. You quickly throw a ball as they wobble a tad and watch as the magic takes hold. Their legs form the high heel once again and this time, they lose balance. The heel grows as they do so without their notice, as they are too busy attempting to balance themselves on their overly long bottom half to their short arms. The spell quickly fixes this issue however, flattening their torso as it naturally curves, becoming the base of the shoe. Their sides stretch and round themselves, ready to take some soft feet. Your revelry in their defeat is cut short however, when they suddenly scream the counter spell and get back to their feet, visibly shaken.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>The mirror spell almost seems to have a mind of its own, positioning itself in front of your opponent. Your spells travel through its surface however and you can see him, whilst they appear to be distracted by what's inside the mirror. You do not even attempt to aim them properly, merely flinging balls of magic haphazardly, knowing full well that their chance of dodging is low. One of the orbs strikes them again and the changes occur more rapidly as their body acclimatises itself to being a pair of platform heels. Their back transforms into the base before they have even lost their balance this time, forcing them to collapse to their elbows instead. This quickly proves a mistake as the target's arms melt into a solid mass, their head becoming the top strap whilst the front of the shoe curves itself, almost finished. The mirror needs to perform its part however, allowing your target time to restore themselves.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>The target simply stands there, blissfully gazing as the magic travels towards them. The mind controlling aspects must have kicked in earlier than anticipated, but no matter. At least you do not need to waste effort. The spell has hardly touched them before they take up the position, quickly transforming into a platform high heel. The mirror spell is complete now, collapsing with a loud clap as the second half appears on the shoe. They are finished, physically at least. You're quite pleased with yourself before you realise you did not seal the form, cursing yourself as they suddenly shift back into their original form, looking confused and saddened. </TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>You vow not to make the same mistake, lazily casting the spell knowing full well your target won't attempt to dodge. Heck, they practically jump onto it. The transformation is over in a matter of seconds, the mirror flashing once, leaving a fully formed five inch platform heel. One shoe isn't enough however, and you cast a brief duplication spell, the air shifting for a moment as a second shoe appears in place. Their consciousness is in both shoes, spread across them. You quickly stride forward and collect your new shoes; you can't wait to wear them!</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
