<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<Description>This player is a small, elven femboy. Even from a distance it is difficult to tell just what gender he is, though the cute, tight bulge in the front of his lower clothes is a good clue. His hair is shoulder length, worked into a cute bob with his long, pointed ears poking through, framing a soft, feminine face with a button nose and lightly pouted lips. His eyes, while usually looking down submissively, will occasionally flit up, looking around to make sure there are no threats to him as he shifts his wide, sharply flared hips and large, bubbly, rotund ass from side to side, his hands adjusting the clothes that he wears over his slim, deliciously flat chest and torso, his skin fair to the point of almost being pale. Despite his weariness, however, you can see that need in his eyes, that craving to bow and submit to a master and mistress to be a good boi....

While the boi himself looks physically weak, and very likely is, his sharp ears and sharper eyes denote that he is not completely helpless. You've no doubt that an agile, fleet-footed creature such as this elf would be a terror with ranged weapons, and it is very likely this marksmanship extends to his spell casting as well. </Description>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>With a sudden burst of light, your attacker hits you square in the chest with a spell bolt. You feel your ears tingle, and upon feeling them, realize they became slightly pointed, but you shrug and reverse the changes. </TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>Again, you are hit by the spell bolt. This time, the whole top of your head tingles, and you can feel your hair lengthen slightly, your ears becoming even more pointed than before, actually poking through your lengthened hair. The world seems to become bigger, though you are aware this likely means you just became smaller...and weaker. With a gasp, you see the muscles on your arms and legs shrink, though your thighs and hips seem to widen a little. You growl, and reverse the changes, looking warily at your attacker. </TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>The spell hits you once more, even more powerful than last. You shrink, while at the same time your hips and ass grow, your face softening as your hair lengthens, your elven ears poking out once more. You yipe lightly as you feel your ass tighten under your clothes, growing rounder and wider even as your muscle mass shrinks. And yet....you feel very light on your feet, as if you could run for miles. Even moreso, your sight and hearing become more acute, the smallest sound and movement so much more apparent. And with this acuteness comes a sensitivity...your skin becoming paler and warming at even the lightest brush of your clothes shifting. You find yourself blushing, and manage to muster the willpower to change back.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>This time the spell knocks you off your feet, sending you flying into a nearby wall. You cry out as the wind is knocked out of you, your voice notably softer, more...feminine. You gasp for air as you try to stand, your body shifting once more, your muscle mass draining, your ass expanding and rounding out, your cock and balls shrinking into a cute, femboi package. Your now shoulder-length hair drifts in front of your face, and you comb it out of the way, patting it back into the short bob of your hair. You manage to somehow get to your feet, but as you try to get off your knees, you feel a....longing to stay down there, kneeling in front of Master...or Mistress....reluctantly, though, you push to your feet, somehow managing to reverse the changes....but you know for certain this battle is not going well for you. </TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>Try as you might, you cannot avoid the spell's blast. You cry out, stumbling and almost falling again, but you manage to stand up. However, the damage is already done; even as you turn to face your attacker again, your body (and package) shrinks, your ass grows, and your face softens as your hair lengthens around it to frame it, the tips of your now pointed elven ears poking out of them by a few inches. Your senses are very acute now, every movement and sound magnified tenfold....but so is your sense of touch, and the spell's residue makes it even moreso. Because of this, you cannot use your new-found abilities effectively, since every movement you make makes you blush, requiring effort to hold back your moans. With your last ounce of willpower, you manage to reverse the changes....but for how long? </TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>This fight is over, you think as the last spell makes contact. With no willpower left, all you can do is yelp and watch helplessly as the spell transforms you, making you shorter, sapping your hard-earned muscles away while blowing up your butt and flaring your hips, slimming your torso and chest down as it does so. You glare daggers at the victor as your face softens and rounds out, your grimace becoming a pout when your lips plump up. You blow a loose strand of hair from your eyes, tucking it back into the bob that is your new hairstyle, your fingers lingering on your long, pointed ears. The spell's sensation fades away, thankfully sparing you from moaning with every movement of your clothes, but the change is irreversibly done by this point. Oh well, you think as you pout at the victor, trying to resist the urge to get on your knees in front of them and beg to be claimed. Things could be worse...right?</TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>With a sudden burst of light, your attacker hits you square in the chest with a spell bolt. You feel your ears tingle, and upon feeling them, realize they became slightly pointed, but you shrug and reverse the changes. </TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>Again, you are hit by the spell bolt. This time, the whole top of your head tingles and you can feel your hair shorten slightly, your ears becoming even more pointed than before, actually poking through your hair. The world seems to become bigger, though you are aware this likely means you just became smaller...and weaker. With a gasp, you see your breasts begin to shrink, though your thighs and hips seem to widen a little. You growl, and reverse the changes, looking warily at your attacker. </TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>The spell hits you once more, even more powerful than last. Your breasts again shrink, while at the same time your hips and ass grow, your face softening as your hair shortens to a bob, your elven ears poking out once more. You yipe lightly as you feel your ass tighten under your clothes, growing rounder and wider even as your breasts shrink. And yet....you feel very light on your feet, as if you could run for miles. Even moreso, your sight and hearing become more acute, the smallest sound and movement so much more apparent. And with this acuteness comes a sensitivity...your skin becoming paler and warming at even the lightest brush of your clothes shifting. You find yourself blushing, and manage to muster the willpower to change back.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>This time the spell knocks you off your feet, sending you flying into a nearby wall. You cry out as the wind is knocked out of you, your voice feminine, but with a notable male edge to it, as if signifying the middle ground you are becoming. You gasp for air as you try to stand, your body shifting once more, your breasts deflating like punctured balloons into your flat, slim chest, your ass expanding and rounding out, and, you notice with a cry of dismay, your vagina disappearing and being replaced with a cute femboy package. Your now shoulder-length hair drifts in front of your face, and you comb it out of the way, patting it back into the short bob of your hair. You manage to somehow get to your feet, but as you try to get off your knees, you feel a....longing to stay down there, kneeling in front of Master...or Mistress....reluctantly, though, you push to your feet, somehow managing to reverse the changes....but you know for certain this battle is not going well for you. </TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>Try as you might, you cannot avoid the spell's blast. You cry out, stumbling and almost falling again, but you manage to stand up. However, the damage is already done; even as you turn to face your attacker again, your body (and breasts) shrinks, your ass grows, your precious pussy is replaced with a femboy clitty, and your face softens as your hair lengthens around it to frame it, the tips of your now pointed elven ears poking out of them by a few inches. Your senses are very acute now, every movement and sound magnified tenfold....but so is your sense of touch, and the spell's residue makes it even moreso. Because of this, you cannot use your new-found abilities effectively, since every movement you make makes you blush, requiring effort to hold back your moans. With your last ounce of willpower, you manage to reverse the changes....but for how long? </TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>This fight is over, you think as the last spell makes contact. With no willpower left, all you can do is yelp and watch helplessly as the spell transforms you, making you shorter, sapping your hard-earned breasts and vagina away while replacing it with a femboy cockette and balls, blowing up your butt and flaring your hips, slimming your torso and chest down as it does so. You glare daggers at the victor as your face softens and rounds out, your grimace becoming a pout when your lips plump up. You blow a loose strand of hair from your eyes, tucking it back into the bob that is your new hairstyle, your fingers lingering on your long, pointed ears. The spell's sensation fades away, thankfully sparing you from moaning with every movement of your clothes, but the change is irreversibly done by this point. Oh well, you think as you pout at the victor, trying to resist the urge to get on your knees in front of them and beg to be claimed. Things could be worse...right?</TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>With a sudden burst of light, you hit your target square in the chest with a spell bolt. He blinks, trailing his hand along his ears as he realizes they became slightly pointed, but he shrugs and reverses the changes. </TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>You grin as you score another direct hit. This time, his hair lengthens slightly, his ears becoming even more pointed than before, actually poking through his lengthened hair. He gasps, shrinking by a couple inches, his his muscles on his arms and legs shrink, though at the same time, his thighs and hips seem to widen a little. Your target growls and casts a wary look your way as he reverses the changes.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>Once more you score a direct hit on your hapless target.  He shrinks, while at the same time his hips and ass grow, his face softening as his hair lengthens, his elven ears poking out once more. He gives a light yipe, his hands going to his inflating ass, tightening the clothes as it balloons out into a nice round bubble butt even as his muscle mass shrinks. He seems very light on his feet now, and you are sure like this he could run for miles. He looks up, his eyes seeming more focused and sharp than before, but at the same time, a blush crawls across his face; you grin as you realize this is because the residue from your spell is playing havoc on his soft, sensitive skin....However, to your dismay, the boi finds it in him to change back to his original form.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>This time the spell knocks your target off his feet, sending him flying into a nearby wall. You cries out as the wind is knocked out of him, his voice notably softer, more...feminine. He gasps for air as you try to stand, his body shifting once more, his muscle mass draining and his your ass expanding and rounding out, his cock and balls shrinking into a cute, femboi package. His now shoulder-length hair drifts in front of his face, and he combs it out of the way, patting it back into the short bob of his hair. He manages to get to his  feet, but he seems to be hesitant to get of his knees, as if he wants to submit....the longing expression only lasts for a moment, however, and he gets to his feet, reversing the changes....but you know that things are not going well for him... </TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>Your target makes an effort to avoid your attack, but it is no use. He cries out, stumbling and almost falling again, but he manages to stand up. However, the damage is already done; even as he turns to face you again, his body (and package) shrinks, his ass grows and balloons out, and his face softens as his hair lengthens around it to frame it, the tips of his now pointed elven ears poking out of them by a few inches.  He seems focused and intent on you for a moment, but then the magic's sensation kicks in, leaving him biting his lip and suppressing a moan. With his last ounce of willpower, he manages to reverse the changes....but for how long? </TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>This fight is over, you think as the last spell makes contact. With no willpower left, all your victim can do is yelp and watch helplessly as the spell transforms him for the last time, making him shorter, sapping his hard-earned muscles away while blowing up his butt and flaring his hips, slimming his torso and chest down as it does so. He glares daggers at you as his face softens and rounds out, his grimace becoming a pout when his lips plump up. He sighs and blows a loose strand of hair from his eyes, tucking it back into the bob that is his new hairstyle, his fingers lingering on your long, pointed ears. The spell finishes up its changes, irreversible now as the magic leaves the newly made elf boi as he is. He seems to be taking it rather well, you think. And he is rather cute. </TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>With a sudden burst of light, you hit your target square in the chest with a spell bolt. She blinks, trailing her hand along her ears as she realizes they became slightly pointed, but she shrugs and reverses the changes. </TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>You grin as you score another direct hit. This time, her hair shortens slightly, her ears becoming even more pointed than before, actually poking through her shorter hair. She gasps, shrinking by a couple inches, her breasts and vagina shrinking, though at the same time, her thighs and hips seem to widen a little. Your target growls and casts a wary look your way as she reverses the changes.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>Once more you score a direct hit on your hapless target.  Her body and breasts shrink, while at the same time her hips and ass grow, her hair shortening, her elven ears poking out once more. She gives a light yipe, her hands going to between her legs as her vagina shrinks away and replaced by a small, cute femboy cock and balls, and then with another yipe her hands go to her inflating ass, tightening the clothes as it balloons out into a nice round bubble butt even as her breasts and hair shrinks. She, or rather he, you think as you correct yourself,  seems very light on his feet now, and you are sure like this she could run for miles. He looks up, his eyes seeming more focused and sharp than before, but at the same time, a blush crawls across his face; you grin as you realize this is because the residue from your spell is playing havoc on his soft, sensitive skin....However, to your dismay, the boi finds it in him to change back to his original, unfortunately female form.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>This time the spell knocks your target off her feet, sending her flying into a nearby wall. She cries out as the wind is knocked out of her, her voice still feminine, with a light trace of a male edge. She gasps for air as you try to stand, her body shifting once more, her breasts deflating and and her ass expanding and rounding out, her vagina turning into a cute, femboi package. Her now shoulder-length hair drifts in front of her face, and she combs it out of the way, patting it back into the short bob of her, or rather his, hair. He manages to get to his  feet, but he seems to be hesitant to get of his knees, as if he wants to submit....the longing expression only lasts for a moment, however, and he gets to his feet, reversing the changes....but you know that things are not going well for her... </TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>Your target makes an effort to avoid your attack, but it is no use. She cries out, stumbling and almost falling again, but she manages to stand up. However, the damage is already done; even as she turns to face you again, her body (and breasts) shrinks, her ass grows and balloons out as her vagina is absorbed into her and she grows a femboy package once again, her hair shortens around her soft face to frame it, the tips of her now pointed elven ears poking out of them by a few inches as she turns into a femboy again.  He seems focused and intent on you for a moment, but then the magic's sensation kicks in, leaving him biting his lip and suppressing a moan. With his last ounce of willpower, he manages to reverse the changes back into a woman....but for how long? </TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>This fight is over, you think as the last spell makes contact. With no willpower left, all your victim can do is yelp and watch helplessly as the spell transforms her for the last time, making her shorter, sapping her precious vagina and breasts away while blowing up her butt and flaring her hips, slimming her torso and chest down as it does so. She glares daggers at you as her vagina fades away, permanently replaced by a small, cute femboy cock and balls, its only use to look cute. He sighs and blows a loose strand of hair from his eyes, tucking it back into the bob that is his new hairstyle, his fingers lingering on your long, pointed ears. The spell finishes up its changes, irreversible now as the magic leaves the newly made elf boi as he is. He seems to be taking it rather well, you think. And he is rather cute. </TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>

</Form>
