<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>You watch as your opponent does some type of cheer routine and then suddenly throws a spell at you. It hits you, but it barely causes a tingle, the spell is so weak. Very weak. How can they survive against others with that kind of spell casting? Maybe you should help them out. Maybe you could protect-Wait what? You shake your head and cast a counter spell as you realize there was more to that spell than the tingle you felt...</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>The energy of your rival mage is a bit infectious and you find yourself responding to their cheering prompts. Just as you shout "C" they throw another spell at you. You feel the magic pass through you as you stare at the mage. The spell feels strong, but the one casting it seems so fragile to you. With the cheering they did, they'll obviously be seen by others. A giant walking target. You should help them, keep them safe. You could even shield them-Hold on. Are you shrinking? Snapping out of your train of thought, you reverse the changes and let out a sigh of relief. That was close...</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>You're wondering where you can find a good pair of Pom Poms when suddenly you're hit by a spell. You can't help but feel anger at them for that! After all, don't they know the risk they're taking attacking people?! Especially with their chest so wide open like that?! Anybody could hit them with a powerful spell easily there! You really need to help them, someone has to do it. You'll just have to wrap yourself around them. Protect them. You just need to better fit them to do that. Maybe something that shows your team spirit while you're at it? Sure the colors are a little bright, but you'll protect them no matter how noticeable they are. As you think that, you've noticed that you've started shrinking, your skin having changed into some type of fabric. The shock derails your thought process and you reflexively cast a counter spell to reverse the changes. You still can't help feeling worried about that mage though...</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>As you contemplate the many benefits of the color pink, you feel yourself hit by a spell. The spell feels exceptionally strong, but one look at the caster and you can tell they need help. You just feel it. A knight wouldn't go into battle without their armor, right? And you can be their armor! Well, not all metal and clunky, but you're a mage. You can change your form so you not only look fashionable but are functional too. Though, you guess a uniform is like an armor for some. Like what the St. Circe Cheerleaders wear. That sleeveless sweater of theirs is kind of like a breastplate, if a bit snug on them. Just as you imagine yourself wrapped around a cheerleader's chest, you snap back to reality and find yourself laying on the ground, the exact vest you were daydreaming about. Shocked at this turn of events, you use a bit of will to reverse the changes, returning to an upright form.  You feel maybe you were a bit hasty in doing so though...</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>You see a fellow mage taking unnecessary risk, but before you can warn them, they hit you with a spell. It's alright though, they probably just don't know better. But you can help, you can protect them. Encircle their torso, their chest and shield them. Like armor. Like a shell. That's what you can do, that's what you were made to do! Not just to make cheerleaders look great, but also to protect them. They just need to pick you up and wear you. ...Pick you up? Why would they- You snap out of it, you're aren't part of a cheerleader outfit! You shouldn't be on the ground! You reverse the changes your body went through, returning to your previous form. Because this is who you are. Not something that protects cheerleaders...right?</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>You see the spell coming and merely stand there taking it. That's your purpose after all, to take the hits for your owner so they aren't hurt. You barely even notice as your body reforms, it just feels normal. Normal to be a sleeveless vest for someone. You'll cover them and protect them and they'll look good while you do! You fall to the ground, currently empty, but knowing soon someone will pick you up and you can start helping and sheltering them...</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>In a good mood, you try out some cheers you've seen the St. Circe Cheerleaders do. During it, you notice a rival mage watching. And not paying attention. So you quickly lob a spell at them. You didn't put much strength in it, and they actually seem to give you a pitying look after it hits them. Then they snap out of the sympathy they seemed to be feeling and counter it, starting to glower at you...</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>You shout "Gimme a 'C'!" and surprisingly enough, your target does so! So you reward with them with a spell. A concerned look sets upon their face as the magic works on them. Concern that seems directed to you, as if worried you're in danger. You notice they seem to be shrinking, but they don't seem to realize it's happening.  It almost seems like they're about to interpose themselves between you and some imaginary 'bullet' when they finally notice their size decrease and quickly reverse your spell...</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>Noticing another mage lost in thought, you sling a spell at them, getting past their defenses. They glare at you, but it's not very harsh. More like a parent gives a child when they think they're doing something risky. Their body starts to collapse in on itself, their skin seeming to change to a fabric and taking on the color scheme of the St. Circe Community College cheer squad. They don't seem to notice the changes, almost welcoming them. But suddenly they seem to think something is wrong and cast a reversal spell that cancels the changes. They've changed back, but a look of concern creases their face. For themselves or for you, it's hard to tell...</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Before they can notice, you hit your target with a spell. You expect them to give you a look of anger like most mages do when hit with spells, but instead they gaze at you with nothing but concern and worry. You can see they're contemplating something, something that must be important as they don't notice their body shrinking. Their skin seems to become fabric like as it changes to a color scheme of black and pink. Their arms pull into their torso along with the rest of their lower body and soon the sleeveless vest worn by St. Circe Cheerleaders is laying on the ground. You smile and go to pick it up when it suddenly quivers and reforms back into your opponents previous form. Seems you still have a bit to go...</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Your target is merely watching, like they're keeping an eye on you, when you throw another spell at them. In a daze, their body quickly seems collapse in to their torso, their skin turning into fabric and the design of the St. Circe Cheerleaders appearing on them. Soon a sleeveless vest is upon the ground, and you can just feel the intent of it to protect you. It wants you to wear it so it can take the hits for you. You're about to grant its wish when suddenly it jerks and slowly changes back to what they were previously. Though they almost see as shocked as you that they aren't a piece of clothing...</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>Your target stands there with open, accepting arms as the spell connects. It doesn't take long at all for their body to reshape into a simple sleeveless vest. The cheerleading shell you saw in the clothing store. It's in the colors of St. Circe Community College, making it pretty visible, but as you walk over and pick it up you can feel the magical energy imbued in the garment. It will protect you beyond what a normal piece of fabric will do. And it wants to do so now too...</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
