<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<Description>You have been defeated by Donna Milton, and thus have been turned into a mindless doggy. Your body still contains traces of your transformer's magic inside it.  Your pussy is puffed with need and your paws are useless in pleasuring yourself. Your heat and lust has caused your mind to snap, and now you are nothing but a doggy in need of a bone and an owner to care for you. You helplessly crawl behind your master or mistress, tail flagged to show everyone that you challenged the great Donna Milton and lost, becoming nothing more than a slutty beast that lives only to pleasure others.</Description>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>Donna's magic washes over your body, causing a burning sensation in your ears. You blush as they migrate to the top of your head, sprouting golden fur and becoming floppy dog ears. "You made a very big mistake." Donna chuckles, hinting that she's just toying with you for now. You brace yourself to continue the fight, knowing there is no turning back.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>Donna rolls her eyes at your continued attempt to battle against her. With a flick of her fingers her magic begins warping your body again. Your tongue feels heavy and slips out from between your lips, which have now gained a black coloration. You begin to pant like a dog as her magic takes a firm hold on you. "I have lived for thousands of years, sweetie, you cannot beat me at my own game." She grins. You pant and feel your ears, still floppy dog ears from her first attack. You can't help but begin to feel a little intimidated.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>With another flick of her finger, Donna drops you to your knees. Your clothing vanishes, and you watch as your body begins to warp and change. Your breasts become larger, now settling at what are at least DD-cups, while two more pairs of nipples appear down your belly. Your thighs and butt swell as your gender now becomes very female, a puffy pair of feminine lips resting between your legs now.  You begin to reach down towards your sex as a burning need begins to form within you. You hear a cackle and look up, seeing Donna watching you in amusement. You gulp and get back to your feet, ready to face her until the very end.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>Donna's magic slams into you this time. Her face is more cold than amused now as her true strength begins to appear. Your hands and feet cramp as they quickly shift into useless paws, this wouldn't be so bad if the need between your legs didn't burst into a full fledged wildfire of lust and arousal. You whine and whimper, feebly pawing at your sex with your useless paws, not noticing as the large bushy golden tail sprouted from above your sexy backside. Donna whistles and pats her leg, inviting you over to her. You begin to crawl towards her, but stop a few feet away, your human mind screaming to regain control and win this battle!</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>Your body already changed, all that's left is your mind as her magic digs its talons into your brain. You begin to see yourself crawling naked through the streets, letting everyone know that you had lost against Donna Milton. You whimper at the humiliation of showing off your pouting pussy to everyone, begging for some hunk or bimbo to pleasure you to give you a small break from this cursed heat you are suffering from. You whine and pant as your mind goes through various bouts of sex and mates. Everyone from lowly mutts, to minotaurs, to bimbos, to huge horse cocks using you like the good little bitch you are quickly becoming. As the images fade from your mind you are left on all fours, drooling from both your mouth and sex. Only a thin strand of sanity keeps your mind from simply snapping apart.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>Donna reaches out her hand and places it on your head. "Good girl," she purrs, and you feel your mind snap apart. You pant and whimper up at Mistress; she is so wonderful and perfect. You sit there like a loyal pet, tail wagging and pussy dripping. "I am sorry, pet, but I have more important things to do." She points towards the city, "Go find yourself a owner and tell them Donna sent you," she tells you. You let out a bark and crawl towards the city, eager to show everyone what a good bitch you have become.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>X</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>X</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>X</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>X</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>X</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>X</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
