<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<Description>You are a tiny little goo girl, barely able to reach the ankles of an average sized human. Everything is big and new to you now as you struggle to recall who you used to be. Not that your sensitive form gives you much incentive to worry about all that as merely touching something is enough to set off a myriad of distracting sensations: you can literally taste the ground as you slide around! Still, as nice as it feels to crawl around and explore, you'd really like something soft and warm and alive to cuddle up against...</Description>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>Another mage suddenly squirts some pink liquid in your general direction! Having no time to react, you soon find yourself coated in the fluid, giving your skin a glossy pink look.
Feeling tingly all over, you suspect a transformation and quickly use your magic to evaporate the liquid, preventing further changes. However, some damage has already been done: your skin has taken on a pinkish hue. As you run your hands over your new skin, restoring its old coloration with magic, you can't help but note how sensitive it is.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>Your opponent hits you with a splash of pink liquid which is quickly absorbed into your skin before you can evaporate it with your magic. You watch as your skin turns pink once again with a mix of fear and fascination  this time growing softer as the magic penetrates the surface layer. 'Softer' is perhaps understating it, as your body appears to be covered in a thick layer of pink goo by now. You tentatively touch one of your arms, sending ripples of pleasure through your all-to-sensitive new skin-layer. It feels really weird, as if your sense of touch has extended deeper into your body.
Lost in the sensation of waves propagating through your arms, you fail to notice how the changes are affecting your legs until you suddenly collapse as your softened legs are no longer able to bear the load of your weight! Startled to find your lower body a puddle of goo, you put all your heart into reversing the transformation, eventually restoring your old form. </TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>A spray of pink liquid hits you, and your traitorous form immediately begins to change as the goop worms its way into you. In a matter of seconds, your legs collapse and cause you to fall down in a puddle on the floor. Your mind, still not adjusted to your new form, is flooded with strange sensations as your sense of touch expands to encompass all of your body. Whenever you try to move, ripples of pleasure propagate throughout your body, making it difficult to hold onto any train of thought, nevermind reversing the spell! You eventually manage to still your unbearable body, giving you enough peace of mind to focus on reversing the spell. Laying absolutely still so as to not stir up more sensor input, you bring up a mental picture of your old self, which you manage restore with some difficulty. </TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>Your body quickly melts into a pink puddle, your mind being flooding with tactile stimulation as you spread out on the ground. Unable to focus on anything but the overwhelming feeling of touching and being touched at every point in your body, you can do little to resist the transformation. Something slowly shifts inside you on a more microscopic level as your body begins to gelate. For some reason, you think you can taste a hint of dirt and... strawberries? cherries? You can't quite make it out, though you are somehow able to make some sense out of all the stimuli your new body is flooding you with. You take this as an opportunity to reverse the spell. However, you can't seem to forget about that unidentifiable taste.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>You try to evade as your opponent fires a spray of pink goo your way, but instead, you are hit straight in the face, large amounts of the fluid entering your mouth and nose! Your senses are flooded with a peculiar pink taste, which you immediately identify as... your own taste? Confused by this strange realization, you don't even register that you are now a pink puddle. Still instinctively trying to flee from your gigantic opponent, you slide around effortlessly, your sensitive body filling with ectasy as you glide against the ground, which also has its own peculiar taste. Realizing that your opponent is not currently attacking you, you shape yourself into your normal form, preparing to counter with a spell of your own...
Except nothing happens! Looking around in confusion, you realize that the world is suddenly much bigger, or rather, you are much smaller! 
You can't help but wonder what it would be like to stay like this: your body is really sensitive and there are so many new interesting flavors to take in. You begin to slide towards your opponent, curious of what they taste and feel like, when you suddenly realize what you are doing. It dawns on you how far gone you are, and you start to dispel the magic affecting you, a lengthy process since your current form seems to lack most of your magical powers. You eventually manage to restore yourself to your proper size and shape, but you know you probably won't be able to pull that feat off again...
</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>Changes quickly wash over you as your mind and body are permeated by familiar pink goo. You are briefly overwhelmed by the sensation of being touched everywhere inside, while the taste of goo spreads throughout you.
You collapse into a pink puddle, and as you regain control of your body, you quickly reform yourself back into a goo girl. On some level, you know that you should be resisting these changes, but it all seems so distant and irrelevant compared to the wondrous sensations your new body is providing you with. With a giggle, you begin to slide towards your former opponent, hoping that they will let you wrap yourself around them. Your curiosity to see what they taste like is greater than your desire to be a powerful mage, a dream that will soon fade into a distant memory!</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>You try to evade as your opponent fires a spray of pink goo your way, but instead, you are hit straight in the face, large amounts of the fluid entering your mouth and nose! Your senses are flooded with a peculiar pink taste, which you immediately identify as... your own taste? Confused by this strange realization, you don't even register that you are now a pink puddle. Still instinctively trying to flee from your gigantic opponent, you slide around effortlessly, your sensitive body filling with ectasy as you glide against the ground, which also has its own peculiar taste. Realizing that your opponent is not currently attacking you, you shape yourself into your normal form, preparing to counter with a spell of your own...
Except that nothing happens! Looking around in confusion, you realize that the world suddenly is much bigger, or rather, you are much smaller! 
As well, this isn't even your normal form, but instead one of a voluptuous pink goo girl! You try dessperately to redistribute your curves into something more like your old male self, but for some reason it's really difficult to not think of yourself as the gooey girl you now are. What's worse, you can't stop thinking about how good it would feel to rub yourself against and taste your former opponent. Realizing that it's probably very dangerous to fool around  in this form any longer, you start to dispel the magic affecting you, a lengthy process since your current form seems to lack most of your magical powers. You eventually manage to restore yourself to your proper size and shape, but you know you probably won't be able to pull that feat off again...</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>You conjure a blob of pink liquid and launch it at your opponent! You watch in delight as it coats their skin in a sticky, thick goop.
 Your opponent, however, does not seem as happy as they evaporate the fluid with a quick counter-spell. Your efforts were not all in vain though, as your opponent's skin has taken on a nice, pink hue and seems to be quite sensitive, judging by the look on your opponent's face as they try to dispel the magic.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>Encouraged by the previous results, you summon even greater quantities of liquid to coat your opponent in. With a splash, they are once again coated in the pink goop, their body slowly softens as the goo permeates their skin and proceeds further inward. Your victim seems to be distracted as a mere touch is enough to send ripples through their now quite sensitive and deep skin layer. 
Suddenly, your opponent's softened legs collapse, causing them to snap out of their reverie as they fall down into a puddle of goo: all that remains of their lower body. With a frightened look on their face, they quickly begin to work on reverting the changes, which, to your amusement at least takes them a few seconds.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>A spray of pink goo hits your opponent, whose body begins to melt as the goo quickly worms its way inside. In a matter of seconds, their legs have been turned into goo once again, the rest of their body practically melting mid-fall as they collapse into a jiggling pink puddle. You stare attentively at the puddle as it wobbles, certain that you are witnessing some sort of internal struggle. Eventually the goo falls still, and short afterward, your opponent returns to their normal form.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>You fire another salvo of goo against your opponent, who, by now, seem helpless to resist its corroding powers. 
Their body quickly melts, forming a jiggling pink puddle on the ground once again. What's more, the transformation has entered another phase, distinguishable from the previous one by the fact that the puddle is slowly shrinking as it settles down.
Much to your disappointment, however, the puddle does not even stop moving until your target has managed to reverse the spell. Perhaps you're losing your touch or... perhaps their mind is more adjusted to their new body now, making it easier for them to cast the counter-spell? Judging by the thoughtful look on your restored opponent's face, you bet it's the latter!</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Your opponent tries to evade as you fire a beam of pink liquid towards them, but perhaps due to some subconscious desire, or just bad luck, they end up being hit square in the face! The fluid enters their nose and mouth, quickly melting their startled face; the rest of their body not faring much better as they change and shrink into a cute little pink puddle, just the right size to hold in your cupped hands. You never get a chance to try that out, however, as the puddle suddenly starts to slide away from you! 
After having put some distance between you and it, the puddle changes shape, forming a humanoid body: that of a voluptuous pink goo girl, who seems ready to retaliate with a spell of her own! However, nothing happens. The goo girl looks confused as if she suddenly realized that something is off, but some new urge seems to take hold of her as she slowly begins to slide towards you, a curious and hungry look on her cute little face. She halts as she realizes what she is doing, and begins to force herself to change back into her old form with a counter-spell, but from the exhausted look on their face, you doubt they will be able to do that again...</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>The changes wash over your opponent faster than ever as a final splash of pink goo cleans up all that remains of their old form. They collapse into a shrinking puddle of goo once again, and it doesn't take long until a cute little goo girl emerges from that puddle!
The newly created goo girl seems somewhat conflicted at first, but she eventually slides towards you with a giggle and an alarmingly hungry look in her eyes. You'd reckon she'd be quite a threat—if she wasn't so small! Still, with her magic sealed and her mind readjusted, how dangerous could she be to keep around? Not very, you answer your own rhetorical question.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>Your opponent tries to evade as you fire a beam of pink liquid towards them, but perhaps due to some subconscious desire, or just bad luck, they end up being hit square in the face! The fluid enters their nose and mouth, quickly melting their startled face; the rest of their body not faring much better as they change and shrink into a cute little pink puddle, just the right size to hold in your cupped hands. You never get a chance to try that out, however, as the puddle suddenly starts to slide away from you! 
After having put some distance between you and it, the puddle changes shape, forming a humanoid body: that of a voluptuous pink goo girl, who seems ready to retaliate with a spell of her own! However, nothing happens. The goo girl looks confused as if she suddenly realized that something is off, she desperately tries to suppress her curves and return to what you assume is supposed to approximate her old male body, though she doesn't seem to be able to take on any other shape right now. You even catch her giving you curious, hungry looks. However, some part of her still seems to resist and to possess just enough magic to force herself back into her old form with a counter-spell. </TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>

</Form>
