<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>As the spell hits you, your body suddenly feels incredibly heavy and strangely stiff. You drop down to your knees, needing a moment to recover before you can stand and cast a counter spell. The weight and stiffness vanish and you feel it was a miracle you weren't crushed under your own weight!</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>As you're struck by the strange spell again, the weight and stiffness come flooding back, though you feel as if you can handle it better this time. A strange but calming heat radiates from your chest. It's curious, but you quickly stop and remove the spell from yourself.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>The spells strikes you again, completely stiffening your body this time, though you don't really mind. It feels rather calming. Small seams and armored plates form across your body, and large metal breasts seem to weld themselves to your chest.  You hesitantly undo the spell. Could a little protection really hurt?</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>You're struck by your opponent's spell yet again. The familiar effects return, but this time your sight briefly goes out. Just as you begin to panic, you realize it was only your new OS being installed, and your vision comes back online. Looking around, you now see the everything in the world with a faint outline and some statistical numbers. Feeling exhausted, you quickly absord the remaining mana from the spell before you undo its effects. As you become your normal self again, you can't help but feel kind of weak and fragile. Maybe that new form wouldn't be so bad...</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>As the spell comes at you again, you almost leap INTO it! You enjoy being so tough, and all this new information is just too interesting for you to pass up. You find yourself feeling bored and dumb without it.
Your body changes to be almost completely made of metal. Your face is the only exception; it's covered with some kind of very realistic looking silicone. The finishing touchs are some LEDs on your chest and knees that blink in accordance to the workload of your CPU.
It takes all of your willpower to revert the changes. Though you know you can't succumb to these changes, a small part of you thinks you would be pretty much immortal as a machine. That couldn't possibly be a disadvantage.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>You see the spell coming and you want it. A tough body, the ability to think faster and better than any organic being, and immortality. It's simply TOO good. You want this, and you want it to last forever.
The final change to your body is a single LED on your pubic area which begins to glow according to your arousal. You shove your opponent aside, feeling truly powerful. You don't need them anymore. You're a perfect machine. A being of knowledge and reason, and you want to see the one person able to take this away from you</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>As your spell hits your opponent, they pause for a short while before dropping to their knees. They seem to need all of their strength to get back on their feet, though they are able to rise back up and cast a counter spell.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>Again, your spell strikes your opponent. And again, they becomes a little stiff, though they manage to stay on their feet this time. Their chest radiates a strange energy and swells up a little. Rather than panic, they simply look around calmly and revert the spell's effects after a moment.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>Another hit!  Your opponent goes completely stiff this time, and for a brief moment you wonder if you accidentally turned them to stone. Your worries are put aside as small seams begin to form around their joints, returning some level of flexibility to them. Small armored plates form across their body, and a still-growing breast plate seems to weld itself to their chest.  They hesitantly undo the spell, looking a little bit puzzled.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Yet again, your spell strikes its target. The usual changes occur, though their face becomes very feminine and cute this time. You notice their eyes go blank briefly, but return shortly, almost looking like little cameras! They seem to be incredibly exhausted by this change and greedily absorb any left-over mana into them before they change back to their normal form. You wonder if you should stop as you don't know what will happen if the spell finishes their transformation.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>As you cast your spell at your target again, they almost seem eager to take it. Their body looks as if it's made almost entirely of metal; the exception being their face, which seems to have taken on the appearance of very realistic silicon. They look around in awe, appearing to be analysing their surroundings with a calm look on their now-uncannily human face. LEDs form on their chest and knees and seem to blink as they consider their surroundings. They revert the spell, seeming disappointed</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>Your opponent sees your spell coming and doesn't even try to act as if they don't want it. As it makes contact with them, they completely change into the voluptuous robot girl with a shiny metal body you saw before. A little LED forms right above their pubic mound, glowing softly. They appear satisfied and simple shove you aside as if they have no need for you anymore. You've created a robot, but instead of a loyal servant you made a machine with self awareness and its own hidden agenda.  Let's just hope it's not the elimination of all organic beings!</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
