<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>You swivel your ears around as they focus on a noise behind you. Turning around you notice someone grinning at you, and you hear them chuckling to themselves. You blink in surprise, they're at least a block away! How can you hear that before you gasp and reach up touching your new ears. Soft tan fur covers the nearly foot tall ears extending from the top of your head, and you didn't even realize it happened. Shaking your head you return your ears to normal and watch that person carefully.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>Hiding around a corner you can hear that person is still after you. Their footsteps echoing off the walls plain as day for you to hear. Your noses catches their scent as the wind blows from that direction and you prepare to sneak off and find them later before you realize somethings wrong. Letting out a sigh as you check yourself over you see your entire face has changed this time. Prodding certain parts of your dark furred nose lightly, you reverse the changes before they can continue.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>Running lightly on your paws you duck down behind a nearby object before turning around to look at your pursuer. They don't seem that strong.. you could probably take them you decide. Your fast and able to hear the quietest of sounds after all, and they can't run from your nose. Nodding to yourself you get up to confront them before their smile makes you stop. Rolling your eyes you check yourself over again, expecting to see a little more progress, but are shocked to find your almost fully an anthropomorphic fox. Running a hand across your backside you grin, "Still no tail!" you call out playfully as you reverse the changes.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>Thinking back one what you saw of the person following you a smile plays across your face. They didn't seem like a mean person, maybe they could own and take care of you. Your tongue rolls out of your mouth, panting as you turn around to go look for that person again. Spotting them you begin to walk over, but notice that your now looking up at them. In a panic you run from them as they burst out into laughter, your black tipped tail swaying behind you as you focus on reversing the changes.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>Trotting back towards your owner you smile up at them. Your fur covered ears swiveling as they search for any threats that might come along. Before you get to your owner though you stop and sway in place. Why? Why are you not standing on four limbs like a good pet? Your earns turn to focus on the sharp sound of someone approaching you, and looking up you see them holding a collar out to you. As you reach up to grab it you almost fall over and suddenly realize what is wrong! Throwing yourself away from them you reverse the changes as quickly as possible, but it still takes you several minutes and your worried what might happen next time.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>You yip happily as you run over to your owner. Rubbing against their legs while making sure to keep alert for threats. You feel them bend down to pet you for a bit and you sit still enjoying it like a good pet. You feel something clasp around your neck and let out  a small yip of surprise. Realizing your in danger you try to reverse the changes, but the new collar is preventing your magic from working! Slowly your magic fades completely as new instincts take over and replace your old mind. Panting you look up at your owner hoping they will show you plenty of attention today!</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>Casting out your spell towards your unsuspecting prey your rewarded with their ears growing to the top of their head and twitching at all the new sounds. You lean back chuckling to yourself to see if the spell will have anymore changes, but one of the ears picks up on your laugh immediately and they turn to face you. They seem confused about something before reaching up to touch their new ears. They reverse the changes with a shake of their head.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>As your spell rolls over them again they suddenly seem to realize that your still chasing them and they duck around a corner. Not before you can see a fox muzzle push out from their face as their head completely changes into a proper fox head. Walking quickly to get sight on them you notice them touching their new muzzle gently before returning everything to normal.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>This time your spell washes over them fully and the changes are more dramatic. Their heels rising up as they fully shifts into an anthropomorphic fox covered in tan fur, except they have no tail. You lose sight of them for a moment as they duck behind a nearby object, but after a minute they get up and turn towards you allowing you to see the fur at the bridge of their nose deepens to black. As they catch the look on your face they seem to mutter to themselves and look over their body. They playfully taunt you about not having managed to give them a tail as they reverse the changes.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Same as last time your spell rolls across them. The changes returning to their body as they grow a black fur tipped tail this time as they steadily begin to shrink. After losing almost two feet of height they turn and begin walking towards you, their tongue hanging out of their muzzle as they pant happily. Before they get much closer to you panic flickers across their face and they take off running. You get a good laugh at the tail wagging side to side before they reverse the changes.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Your spells changes occur almost instantly now. The fox couldn't be standing more then two feet high anymore as their changing limbs before to slowly adopt a more quadrupedal form. They remain on two legs though and you see them happily moving over to you before confusion takes over and they stop. Deciding now might be the perfect time to press the issue you walk towards them, the sound of your movement causing the confused fox to look at you. Showing them the collar their eyes brighten for a second and they happily reach for it, but trip on their new limbs and struggle to remain standing. Sadly this seems to have jolted their mind into realizing what is going on and they quickly move away from you and change back to normal. Drat, oh well you know their very close to giving in.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>With one final cast they drop to all fours, yipping excitedly as they run to your side. You smile and bend down to scratch them behind their large ears and from their reaction they're enjoying the attention. Taking the collar back out you click it around their neck and they seem to wake up from a daze. Their yipping turns frantic as you feel them trying to reverse the changes, but the collar you just attached to them seems to be holding them in this form. Slowly you feel their magic fade completely and they return to looking up to you panting happily. Looks like you've finally acquired that fox pet you've always wanted!</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
