<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>You feel your scalp tingle slightly as two little pieces of cloth begin to grow out of them just above your eyebrows.  You aren't entirely sure what is supposed to be going on, and you reverse the effects with no difficulty.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>As the two cloth protrusions return, jutting out of your forehead, they grow out a few inches just long enough for them to drape down over your eyes.  What are they, ears?  Bunny ears to be specific, pink and fuzzy, cute and wholly pointless.  You reverse the changes, more embarassed than afraid.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>The two fuzzy pink ears pop our of your forehead in milliseconds this time.  But you pay more heed to the fact that your arms and legs are shrinking, your eyeline descending by several inches as your body shrinks.  You feet the changes and return your body, but it's becoming harder now.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>You shrink down to half your height, fuzzy pink ears popping out of the tip of your head, your skin erupting in fine, fuzzy fibers.  You stumble, fighting the rapidly changing center of gravity as you shrink down to four, three, two feet tall.  The only part of your body that maintains its proportions are your feet, though they become exceptionally pink and fuzzy.  Additionally, you find it harder to stand, as if your feet were turning hollow.  Luckily, with a good amount of effort, you are able to reverse the changes.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>You gasp, shrinking down to just half a foot tall, your skin erupting in strands of fuzzy pink fibers.  Two floppy bunny ears fold down over your eyes, but your nearly non-existant arms can do nothing to move them away.  Your vision begins to darken as your eyes start to transform into two black beads, cute and wholly decorative bunny 'eyes'.  Your face, or whatever is left of it, is where your ankles used to be when you finally, with extreme difficulty, are able to reverse the magic and return to your old form.  Any more of this spell cast against you may well leave you stuck as a pair of fuzzy pink bunny slippers.  You're determined not to let that happen.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>You gasp, shrinking down to just half a foot tall, your skin erupting in strands of fuzzy pink fibers.  Two floppy bunny ears fold down over your eyes, but your nearly non-existant arms can do nothing to move them away.  Your vision begins to darken as your eyes start to transform into two black beads, cute and wholly decorative bunny 'eyes'.  Your face, or whatever is left of it, is where your ankles used to be.  You can no longer fight the changes.  You feel your torso hollowing out, your vision vanishing as your head and neck merge into the fibers, leaving a hole large enough for a foot to comfortable slip inside.  This is it.  You are a pair of fuzzy pink bunny slippers with floppy ears and bead eyes.  Forever.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>Your target feels their forehead as two little pieces of cloth begin to grow out of them just above their eyebrows.  Your target looks confused, not entirely sure what is supposed to be going on, and they reverse the effects with no difficulty.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>As the two cloth protrusions return, jutting out of your target's forehead, they grow out a few inches just long enough for them to drape down over your opponent's eyes.  They are clearly now bunny ears to be specific, pink and fuzzy, cute and wholly pointless.  Your target reverse the changes, more embarassed than afraid.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>The two fuzzy pink ears pop our of your target's forehead in milliseconds this time.  But your opponent pays more heed to the fact that their arms and legs are shrinking, their eyeline descending by several inches as their body shrinks.  They reverse the changes, but it's clear that it's becoming harder now.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Your opponent shrinks down to half their normal height, fuzzy pink ears popping out of the tip of their head, skin erupting in fine, fuzzy fibers.  Your target stumbles, fighting the rapidly changing center of gravity as they shrink down to four, three, two feet tall.  The only part of their body that maintains its proportions are their feet, though they become exceptionally pink and fuzzy.  Additionally, your target seems to find it harder to stand as if their feet were turning hollow.  However, with a good amount of effort, they are able to reverse the changes.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Your target gasps, shrinking down to just half a foot tall, their skin erupting in strands of fuzzy pink fibers.  Two floppy bunny ears fold down over your opponent's eyes, but their nearly non-existant arms can do nothing to move them away.  Your target grimaces as their vision begins to darken, transforming into two black beads, cute yet wholly decorative bunny 'eyes'.  Their face, or whatever is left of it, is where their ankles used to be when they finally, with extreme difficulty, are able to reverse the magic and return to their old form.  Any more of this spell cast against then may well leave you stuck as a pair of fuzzy pink bunny slippers.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>Your target gasps, shrinking down to just half a foot tall, their skin erupting in strands of fuzzy pink fibers.  Two floppy bunny ears fold down over their eyes, but their nearly non-existant arms can do nothing to move them away.  They grimace as their eyes start to transform into two black beads, cute and wholly decorative bunny 'eyes'.  Their face, or whatever is left of it, has descended down where their ankles used to be.  They can no longer fight the changes.  Your target's torso hollows their head and neck merge into the fibers, leaving a hole large enough for a foot to comfortable slip inside. You wait for a moment but nothing happens.  Your target has fully transformed a pair of fuzzy pink bunny slippers with floppy ears and bead eyes.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
