<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>Your opponent fires a red ball of light at you, and it hits you right in your arm. Nothing seems to happen till you notice your hairs turned... reddish? While you wonder what your opponents intentions are, you effortlessly undo the changes.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>Once again the red ball hits you, tho this time in your leg. The hairs around the hit area immediately turn red, but now they also seem to lengthen a bit. You are still confused about the goal of your opponent, maybe he intends to transform you into some sort of animal? You do kinda feel like being stroked. Regardless, you undo the changes with barely an effort.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>This time the spell hits you squarely on the chest. Red fur begins to develop on your chest, yet its much longer than you'd usually find in a regular animal. Suddenly you feel some extra weight on your head, as you hair lengthens and turns red, till it reaches you lower back. You feel like stroking your hair, and combing it but why would you do that, you're in the middle of a fight! You concentrate and return to your previous form.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>Again the spell hit you on middle section, and spreads as never before. Your hair turns red and seems to gain volume and curl a bit, as it lengthens till it reaches you knees, your body hair also turns red and starts lengthening and sprouting all over your body. "Ugh that's gonna take forever to properly wash and curl" you think, but then you notice you're starting to shrink. "Oh no!" It finally hits you, their turning you into a wig! You focus your thoughts and undo the changes, but it's not easy by now.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>The spell hits you straight in the face, and all over your body, red wavy hair starts growing, while you once again, begin to shrink. This time your hair shoots to the ground, and before you can see anything else, more red hair starts growing on your face, preventing you from seeing, and almost blocking your breathing. Tho at this point, few people would actually notice you can breathe, since you look more like a a huge wad of red hair on the floor. Yet you are not defeated, and you slowly return to your previous form, gasping for air.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>The spell hits you straight in the face, and all over your body, red wavy hair starts growing, while you once again, begin to shrink. This time your hair shoots to the ground, and before you can see anything else, more red hair starts growing on your face. As you stop shrinking, you can only think of looking perfect and shiny and wavy and red and long and oh so pretty. Who says blondes have more fun?</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>Your spell hits your opponent on their arm. Drat, it would have more effect on its head, but that will do for now, as you notice their arm hair turned red. Your opponent looks puzzled, but quickly undoes the changes.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>This time around you hit them on their leg, and curse as you are even further away from your target. Once again the changes are minimal, just their leg hair turning red, but this time they seem to grow a bit. Well that's a bit better. You opponent still seems clueless of your intentions, but they undo the changes fast.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>"Finally we're getting somewhere" you think, as your spell blasts your opponent in the chest. Red hair starts sprouting from it, and you notice your opponents hair finally starts being affected, growing till it reaches their waist. Your opponent seems to be distracted with these changes, but suddenly snaps out of it and undoes the changes, tho you can tell they needed to focus this time.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Once again a square hit to the chest, red wavy hair starts sprouting all over their bodies, as they begin to shrink. Their hair gains great volume and length, this time almost reaching the floor. As you observe your opponents reaction, you laugh as you notice their shock, they have only now realized your plans for them, the fool. It takes some time for your opponent to turn back, but at this rate, you'll have your luxurious new hair soon enough.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>A direct hit! At last your spell finds the intended mark, and hits your opponent in the face. In nearly no time, they look like nothing more than a huge pile of luscious red wavy hair, you can't even see their faces anymore. "Is... is it done?" you wonder as your opponent stops moving, but no, you notice they are growing again and slowly changing back to how they were before, while gasping for air. "Soon".</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>A direct hit! At last your spell finds the intended mark, and hits your opponent in the face. In nearly no time, they look like nothing more than a huge pile of luscious red wavy hair, you can't even see their faces anymore. You cheer, as your opponent is now clearly defeated. You marvel at how luscious and shiny your new wig is, thinking with delight, that they will remain beautiful like this forever.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
