<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>You suddenly feel very feminine, and something weird begins happening to your skin. You easily reverse the spell.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>You feel very feminine, and your skin beings to lose its color, becoming transparent. You can see and feel your insides disappearing. You reverse the spell.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>Extreme femininity affects your brain, your skin becomes transparent, your insides poof away, and your torso begins disappearing. Your arms shrink and split into four pieces, as they transform into small white garter straps.  After some mental struggle, you're able to reverse the spell.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>The spell has its way with you once more. Your legs disconnect themselves from your groin and hollow themselves out, leaving behind delicate transparent stocking legs. Your groin suddenly explodes as it melts into your legs, and your sensations of arousal are transferred down to the insides of your stocking feet. With a great deal of mental struggle, you manage to reverse the spell.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>Once again, you fall victim to the spell. Your head suddenly transforms into a small pair of white dotted panties, as your neck disappears. Your four garter strap arms connect your panty head and your stocking legs together. You can feel your nose and mouth settle into the crotch area of the panties. A cute little bow materializes on your waistband. With a tremendous amount of skill, effort, and luck, you manage to reverse the changes. You're going to spending a long time hugging someone's sensitive parts if that spell connects again. .  .</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>The spell connects. Your mind is warped with femininity, your skin becomes transparent, and your insides disappear along with your neck and torso. Your arms split and transform into four garter straps, your legs transform into stockings, your groin disappears, and your sensations of arousal are transferred to your stocking feet. Your head is transformed into a cute little pair of panties, and your garter strap arms link your lingerie body parts together. The spell polishes a few things, and finalizes by locking your soul into this form. Looks like you'd better get used to existing as some ultra feminine intimate lingerie. You're going to be stuck like this for a long time.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>Your victim's mannerisms and poise suddenly change, as they seem to become very feminine. Their skin begins to become transparent. Your victim easily reverses the spell.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd> Your victim appears to become very feminine, and their skin loses its color, becoming transparent. You can sort of see their insides disappearing. They reverse the spell. </TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>Extreme femininity affects your victim's brain, their skin becomes transparent, their insides poof away, and their torso begins disappearing. Their arms shrink and split into four pieces, as they transform into small white garter straps.  After some mental struggle, your victim is able to reverse the spell.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>The spell has its way with your victim once more. Their legs disconnect themselves from their groin and hollow themselves out, leaving behind silky transparent stocking legs. Your victim's groin suddenly explodes as it melts into their legs, and their sensations of arousal are transferred down to the insides of their stocking feet. With a great deal of mental struggle, your victim manages to reverse the spell.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Once again, your victim is taken by the spell. Their head suddenly transforms into a small pair of white dotted panties, as their neck disappears. Their four garter strap arms connect their panty head and their stocking legs together. If you look closely you can see their nose and mouth settle into the crotch area of the panties. A cute little bow materializes on their waistband. With a tremendous amount of skill, effort, and luck, your victim manages to reverse the changes. They're going to spending a long time hugging someone's sensitive parts if that spell connects again. .  .</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>The spell connects. Your victim's mind is warped with femininity, their skin becomes transparent, and their insides disappear along with their neck and torso. Their arms split and transform into four garter straps, their legs transform into stockings, their groin disappears, and their sensations of arousal is transferred to their stocking feet. Their head is transformed into a cute little pair of panties, and their garter strap arms link their lingerie body parts together. The spell polishes a few things, and finalizes by locking your victim's soul into this form. Looks like you've got yourself some new ultra feminine lingerie. They're going to be stuck like this for a long time.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
