<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>With the tingling shock of magic comes a wave of anxiety as a large part of you wants to just curl into a ball and hide. You manage to shrug it off, however, resisting any real transformation.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>Your ears feel hot as the spell surges through you, a blush coloring your cheeks as you bite your lower lip nervously. Are your teeth bigger? You shake yourself and try to steady your nerves, resisting the magic's forceful power.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>Your ears swell and grow, and your skin turns a candy pink as a soft gray pelt forms like a shadow across the majority of your body. You feel a twisting in your gut that makes you want to run and hide, but you swallow it down and shake off the transformation, returning your body to normal.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>A bulge forms in the back of your underwear, threatening to tear your clothing as a tail starts to form this time, further adding to the growing gray pelt, the shell like ears and buck teeth, your body taking on a distinctly mousy and girlish appearance. You grit your teeth and fight back the urge to run, concentrating on reversing the spell.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>Your fur grows in, soft and gray, your hips swelling and your waist drawing in, though your chest stays adamantly flat. Your tail bursts from the back of your clothes and you let out a girlish moan as the transformations rock through you. You can feel your mind changing. You can barely fight off the change, and as it passes, you are left walking a touch more gingerly, with a sway in your step as a reminder that you barely avoided a new fate.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>You can't fight it any longer. You give in to the spell and feel your body shift and change. Your fur grows in gray and silky soft, your body taking an effeminate form, with a flat chest, but girlish hips and a perfect perky little ass, with a long pink tail that sways with your every step. Your ears perk high and alert, ready for any sound of trouble so that you can run and hide. After all, that’s what mice do. They hide. And a cute little sissy mouse like you... well... you hide from everything.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>


<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>With the tingling shock of magic comes a wave of anxiety as a large part of you wants to just curl into a ball and hide. You manage to shrug it off, however, resisting any real transformation.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>Your ears feel hot as the spell surges through you, a blush coloring your cheeks as you bite your lower lip nervously. Are your teeth bigger? You shake yourself and try to steady your nerves, resisting the magic's forceful power.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>Your ears swell and grow, and your skin turns a candy pink as a soft gray pelt forms like a shadow across the majority of your body. You feel a twisting in your gut that makes you want to run and hide, but you swallow it down and shake off the transformation, returning your body to normal.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>A bulge forms in the back of your underwear, as your masculine bulge shrinks in the front, threatening to tear your clothing as a tail starts to form this time, further adding to the growing gray pelt, the shell like ears and buck teeth, your body taking on a distinctly mousy and girlish appearance. You grit your teeth and fight back the urge to run, concentrating on reversing the spell.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>Your fur grows in, soft and gray, your hips swelling and your waist drawing in, though your chest stays adamantly flat. Your cock and balls shrink to a pathetic little sissy package, more cute than masculine. Your tail bursts from the back of your clothes and you let out a girlish moan as the transformations rock through you. You can feel your mind changing. You can barely fight off the change, and as it passes, you are left walking a touch more gingerly, with a sway in your step as a reminder that you barely avoided a new fate.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>You can't fight it any longer. You give in to the spell and feel your body shift and change. Your fur grows in gray and silky soft, your body taking an effeminate form, with a flat chest, but girlish hips and a perfect perky little ass, with a long pink tail that sways with your every step. Your ears perk high and alert, ready for any sound of trouble so that you can run and hide. After all, that’s what mice do. They hide. And a cute little sissy mouse like you... well... you hide from everything.</TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>


<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>With the tingling shock of magic comes a wave of anxiety as a large part of you wants to just curl into a ball and hide. You manage to shrug it off, however, resisting any real transformation.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>Your ears feel hot as the spell surges through you, a blush coloring your cheeks as you bite your lower lip nervously. Are your teeth bigger? You shake yourself and try to steady your nerves, resisting the magic's forceful power.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>Your ears swell and grow, and your skin turns a candy pink as a soft gray pelt forms like a shadow across the majority of your body. You feel a twisting in your gut that makes you want to run and hide, but you swallow it down and shake off the transformation, returning your body to normal.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>A large bulge forms in the back of your underwear, almost hiding the small masculine bulge that swells up front, threatening to tear your clothing as a tail starts to form this time, further adding to the growing gray pelt, the shell like ears and buck teeth, your body taking on a distinctly mousy and girlish appearance. You grit your teeth and fight back the urge to run, concentrating on reversing the spell.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>Your fur grows in, soft and gray, your hips swelling and your waist drawing in, though your chest actually deflates nearly flat. Your pussy inverts, forming a tiny little sissy-dick with a tight coin-purse scrotum. Your tail bursts from the back of your clothes and you let out a girlish moan as the transformations rock through you. You can feel your mind changing. You can barely fight off the change, and as it passes, you are left walking a touch more gingerly, with a sway in your step as a reminder that you barely avoided a new fate.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>You can't fight it any longer. You give in to the spell and feel your body shift and change. Your fur grows in gray and silky soft, your body taking an effeminate form, with a flat chest, but girlish hips and a perfect perky little ass, with a long pink tail that sways with your every step. Your ears perk high and alert, ready for any sound of trouble so that you can run and hide. After all, that’s what mice do. They hide. And a cute little sissy mouse like you... well... you hide from everything.</TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>


<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>You watch as your target gasps and looks around themselves fearfully, seemingly wanting to run and hide, but before any real changes take place, they notice the attack and shake off the spell.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>Your target shudders as their ears seem to grow, a blush crossing their cheeks as they bite their lower lip, full and feminine, and looking glossy as though freshly made up. Then they blink and shake off the attack, frowning.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>Your target's skin turns candy pink, and then starts to gray as a pelt begins to grows in, their face pushing out in a faint hint of a muzzle as they bite their lip again and groan. They look around nervously again before balling their hands into fists and fighting off the change.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>A bulge forms in the back of your target's clothes, as a writhing budding tail threatens to break loose, the gray pelt and shell like ears quickly manifesting, along with a distinctly mousy and girlish appearance. They manage to shake off the effects of the spell, but you can tell that it is a losing battle by this point.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>The target's hips take on a feminine curve, their waist drawing in, but their chest remaining flat and smooth, as a tail finally bursts free behind them, swishing side to side as they take a tentative step forward, arching their back and groaning with the losing effort to resist your magic's toll. When they finally do shake free, you notice a lingering swish in their step that leaves them not quite as they were despite themselves.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>There is just no resisting the spell by this point, their fate sealed. Their body changes with a shuddering rush, taking on a soft, effeminate form with girlish hips and a narrow waist, as well as a deliciously flat chest. Their pelt grows in gray and silky soft, and their tail sways pink and sensual behind their heart shaped perky little ass. Their face takes on a feminine shape, mousy and timid, with full pouty lips that tug at the heart strings of any future attackers.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>


<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>You watch as your target gasps and looks around himself fearfully, seemingly wanting to run and hide, but before any real changes take place, he notices the attack and shake off the spell.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>Your target shudders as his ears seem to grow, a blush crossing his cheeks as he bites his lower lip, full and feminine, and looking glossy as though freshly made up. Then he blinks and shakes off the attack, frowning.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>Your target's skin turns candy pink, and then starts to gray as a pelt begins to grows in, his face pushing out in a faint hint of a muzzle as he bites his lip again and groans. He looks around nervously again before balling his hands into fists and fighting off the change.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>A bulge forms in the back of your target's clothes, as a writhing budding tail threatens to break loose, the gray pelt and shell like ears quickly manifesting, along with a distinctly mousy and girlish appearance. Worse, his manly bulge is looking less manly and more... boyish. He manages to shake off the effects of the spell, but you can tell that it is a losing battle by this point.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>The target's hips take on a feminine curve, his waist drawing in, but his chest remaining flat and smooth, as a tail finally bursts free behind him, swishing side to side as he takes a tentative step forward, arching his back and groaning with the losing effort to resist your magic's toll. When he finally does shake free, you notice a lingering swish in his step that leaves him not quite as he was despite himself.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>There is just no resisting the spell by this point, his fate sealed. His body changes with a shuddering rush, taking on a soft, effeminate form with girlish hips and a narrow waist, as well as a deliciously flat chest. His pelt grows in gray and silky soft, and his tail sways pink and sensual behind his heart shaped perky little ass. His face takes on a feminine shape, mousy and timid, with full pouty lips that tug at the heart strings of any future attackers. His once masculine bulge is now reduced to a tiny sissy parcel, easily hidden within girlish clothing.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>


<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>You watch as your target gasps and looks around herself fearfully, seemingly wanting to run and hide, but before any real changes take place, she notices the attack and shake off the spell.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>Your target shudders as her ears seem to grow, a blush crossing her cheeks as she bites her lower lip, full and feminine, and looking glossy as though freshly made up. Then she blinks and shakes off the attack, frowning.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>Your target's skin turns candy pink, and then starts to gray as a pelt begins to grows in, her face pushing out in a faint hint of a muzzle as she bites her lip again and groans. She looks around nervously again before balling her hands into fists and fighting off the change.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>A bulge forms in the back of your target's clothes, as a writhing budding tail threatens to break loose, the gray pelt and shell like ears quickly manifesting, along with a distinctly mousy and girlish appearance. She blushes as she notices a second bulge forming between her legs, clutching her crotch. She manages to shake off the effects of the spell, but you can tell that it is a losing battle by this point.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>The target's hips take on a feminine curve, her waist drawing in, but her chest deflating until flat and smooth, as a tail finally bursts free behind her, swishing side to side as she takes a tentative step forward, arching her back and groaning with the losing effort to resist your magic's toll. When she finally does shake free, you notice a lingering swish in her step that leaves her not quite as she was despite herself.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>There is just no resisting the spell by this point, her fate sealed. Her body changes with a shuddering rush, taking on a soft, effeminate form with girlish hips and a narrow waist, as well as a deliciously flat chest. Her pelt grows in gray and silky soft, and her tail sways pink and sensual behind her heart shaped perky little ass. Her face takes on a feminine shape, mousy and timid, with full pouty lips that tug at the heart strings of any future attackers. Her once tight slit is now inverted into a tiny sissy-dick parcel, easily hidden within girlish clothing.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>

</Form>