<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>You try to block or possibly even deflect the magic coming at you, but it’s no use. The spell hits you fair on your chest and knocks your breath away. Your body feels funny and tingly, and one look at it confirms your fears; it is covered in a layer of soft white fur! Your muscles have lost a lot of definition, and you feel… shorter somehow? The spell is still easily reversible though, so cancelling the changes is a piece of cake. Hmmm cake… Wait, why does thinking of cake make you feel so damn hungry?</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>You lose your guard for just a second, and that’s enough for one of the spells to hit you again. Instantly your skin starts to get covered in white fur again, sending you scratching and rubbing your soft, newly budding breasts with your… wait, what happened to your hands! Were they always this claw like? Meanwhile your legs are growing shorter and a bit stubby compared to the rest of your body, a body which is becoming slightly plump but oddly agile. Once again you reverse the changes without a problem, but somehow you are left with a very aggressive and nagging craving for fine cheeses.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>The spell misses your head by just a hair’s length, but that alone is enough to awaken the magical energies that the first spells have unleashed inside of you. Fur sprouts all over your body, you lose half of your length, and your ears migrate to the top of your head where they become cute and round. You gasp in a squeaky tone as you suddenly grow breasts, accompanied by multiple new rows of them budging up below the first two. There’s no denying it now, you’re being changed into a tiny mouse girl! You reverse the changes as you spot a cat in the distance, making you involuntarily shiver.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>“Peep!” you shout out before the spell hits you again. Mere seconds after impact you've shrunken down to your previous size and form, now not much bigger than a child, but the changes don’t stop there. Far from it… You shrink even more, and as you do so it starts to feel better and better. You can’t help but moan as your multitude of breasts appear again and a long hairless tail pushes out from above your pudgy mouse butt. You grab it instantly and pull it between your legs, using it to hide your engorged privates in shame with a blush on your cheeks. Shy and embarrassed you are hit with an indescribable feeling to run and hide away from danger in the nearest hole, but you manage to shrug it off. You’re better than that! You’re not really a shy mouse! Firmly focusing your thoughts you manage to turn yourself back just in time to prepare for the next spell.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>The next time your opponent casts the spell you hesitate to move for just a second, and by doing so end up getting hit by the spell. Why did you do that?! D-do you want to be a cute tiny mouse? You have no time to think about your subconscious decision though, as you are rapidly turning into a mouse girl again. And boy does it feel good… The ears puffing out on top of your head, the tail sneaking its way past your mousy butt, your hair lengthening past your shoulders, furry little paws, rows of breasts with little teats forming on your belly that you can’t help but touch and rubbing your thighs together and… WHAT? You don’t want to be a mouse! Or… well maybe you do, but you don’t want to be someone’s pet! You shake off the magic, but it’s very, very hard and leaves you panting, aroused and with a very wet spot between your legs. Even though you are back to your original self, the people around you still look scary and big, and you shyly evade them.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>You somehow manage to dodge your opponent’s spell every time, knowing fully well that you can’t take another hit. But wait a minute… what’s that? You are suddenly distracted by a hypnotizing smell that makes you drool. You don’t have time to investigate though, since that pesky opponent is dangling something suspiciously yellow between two fingers with a big grin on their face. Hey, wait a second… You can’t help but push your nose in the air like a rodent and take a deep whiff. Is… is that… is that some CHEESE?!  Instincts immediately take over and the next thing you know you are once again a mouse girl, reaching just to your opponent’s knees, clinging to their leg while drooling and begging in your squeaky cute voice for a taste of the cheese. Your new owner picks you up with a gentle smile and hands you the treat. Happily you chip away at it with your sharp teeth, your body becoming smaller and smaller in the process, now irreversibly turning into the cute and tiny mouse girl you were meant to be. You don’t care anymore. Master will protect you from the scary big people after all. Oh, and you smell more free nibbles, can’t beat free nibbles.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>You try to block or possibly even deflect the magic coming at you, but it’s no use. The spell hits you fair in the chest and knocks your breath away. Your torso feels funny, and one look at it confirms your fears; it is covered in a layer of soft white fur! Your muscles are losing their definition and you become shorter and more feminine. The spell is easily reversible though, so cancelling the changes is still a piece of cake. Hmmm cake… Wait, why does thinking of little crumbs of cake make you feel so damn hungry?</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>You forget your guard for just a second, and that’s enough for one of the spells to hit you again. Instantly your skin starts to get covered in white fur again, sending you scratching and rubbing your soft, tingling breasts with your… wait, what happened to your hands! Were they always this claw like? And when did you grow breasts?! You softly rub against the nipples on your new additions, and can’t help but moan and get a boner from the sensations. Meanwhile your hips are growing wider compared to the rest of your body, a body which is becoming plump yet oddly agile. But then your penis starts to shrink…. Fuck that! You don’t… you don’t really want to be a girl! You focus on your old body and lose all of the changes, but somehow you are left with a very aggressive and nagging craving for fine cheeses.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>The spell misses your head by just a hair’s length, but that alone is enough to awaken the magical energies that the first spells have unleashed inside of you. Your hair lengthens and becomes girly as it tumbles down your shoulders. White fur sprouts all over your feminine body, you lose half of your length, and your ears migrate to the top of your head where they become cute and round. You gasp in a squeaky tone as your penis is forcefully sucked inside of you, your testes following suit and travelling upwards while reshaping themselves into working ovaries, leaving you completely female down below. Then two tiny breasts budge out on your chest, followed by another row below them, and another, and… Gaahhhh it feels so good that you can hardly take it anymore! You have to find a way to stop this, because there’s no denying it now, you’re being changed into a tiny mouse girl! You reverse the changes as you spot a cat in the distance, making you involuntarily shiver.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>“Peep!” you shout out before the spell hits you again. Mere seconds after impact you've shrunken down to your previous female size and form, now not much bigger than a child, but the changes don’t stop there. Far from it… You shrink even more, and as you do so it starts to feel better and better, even if you have to become a girl. You can’t help but moan as your multitude of breasts appear again and a long hairless tail pushes out from above your pudgy mouse butt. You grab it instantly and pull it up between your legs, using it to hide your engorged privates in shame with a blush on your cheeks. Shy and embarrassed you are hit with an indescribable feeling to run and hide away from danger in the nearest hole, maybe to explore your female body there a bit, but you manage to shrug it off. You’re not really a shy mouse! Heck, you’re not even a girl either! Firmly focusing your thoughts you manage to turn yourself back just in time to prepare for the next spell.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>The next time your opponent casts the spell you hesitate to move for just a second, and by doing so end up getting hit by the spell. Why did you do that?! D-do you want to be a cute tiny mouse girl?? You have no time to think about your subconscious decision though, as you are rapidly turning into a mouse girl again. And boy does it feel good… Your male genitals turning into a wet vagina, the ears puffing out on top of your head, your graceful tail sneaking its way past your mousy butt, hair going girly again, furry little paws, rows of breasts with little teats forming on your belly that you can’t help but touch and rubbing your thighs together to stimulate your new slit and… WHAT? You don’t want to be a mouse! O-or a girl! Or… well maybe you do, but you definitely don’t want to be someone’s pet! You shake off the magic, but it’s very, very hard and leaves you panting, aroused and with a very wet spot between your thighs. Even though you are back to your original self, the people around you still look scary and big, and you shyly evade them.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>You somehow manage to dodge your opponent’s spell every time, knowing fully well that you can’t take another hit. But wait a minute… what’s that? You are suddenly distracted by a hypnotizing smell that makes you drool. You don’t have time to investigate though, since that pesky opponent is dangling something suspiciously yellow between two fingers with a big grin on their face. Hey, wait a second… You can’t help but push your nose in the air like a rodent and take a deep whiff. Is… is that… is that some CHEESE?!  Instincts immediately take over and the next thing you know you are once again a mouse girl, reaching just to your opponent’s knees, clinging to their leg while drooling and begging in your squeaky cute voice for a taste of the cheese. Your new owner picks you up with a gentle smile and hands you the treat. Happily you chip away at it with your sharp teeth, your body becoming smaller and smaller in the process, now irreversibly turning into the cute and tiny mouse girl you were meant to be. You don’t care anymore. Master will protect you from the scary big people after all. Oh, and you smell more free nibbles, can’t beat free nibbles.</TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>You try to block or possibly even deflect the magic coming at you, but it’s no use. The spell hits you fair on your chest and knocks your breath away. Your body feels funny and tingly, and one look at it confirms your fears; your breasts and the rest of your torso are covered in a layer of soft white fur! Your muscles have lost a lot of definition, and you feel… shorter somehow? The spell is still easily reversible though, so cancelling the changes is a piece of cake. Hmmm cake… Wait, why does thinking of little crumbs of cake make you feel so damn hungry?</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>You lose your guard for just a second, and that’s enough for one of the spells to hit you again. Instantly your skin starts to get covered in white fur again, sending you scratching and rubbing your soft, tingling breasts with your… wait, what happened to your hands! Were they always this claw like? Meanwhile your legs are growing shorter and a bit stubby compared to the rest of your body, a body which is becoming slightly plump but oddly agile. Once again you reverse the changes without a problem, but somehow you are left with a very aggressive and nagging craving for fine cheeses.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>The spell misses your head by just a hair’s length, but that alone is enough to awaken the magical energies that the first spells have unleashed inside of you. Fur sprouts all over your body, you lose half of your length, and your ears migrate to the top of your head where they become cute and round. You gasp in a squeaky tone as your full breasts suddenly become a few sizes smaller, accompanied by multiple new rows of them budging up below the first two. There’s no denying it now, you’re being changed into a tiny mouse girl! You reverse the changes as you spot a cat in the distance, making you involuntarily shiver.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>“Peep!” you already shout out before the spell hits you again. Mere seconds after impact you’ve shrunken down to your previous size and form, now not much bigger than a child, but the changes don’t stop there. Far from it… You shrink even more, and as you do so it starts to feel better and better. You can’t help but moan as your multitude of breasts appear again and a long hairless tail pushes out from above your pudgy mouse butt. You grab it instantly and pull it between your legs, using it to hide your engorged privates in shame with a blush on your cheeks. Shy and embarrassed you are hit with an indescribable feeling to run and hide away from danger in the nearest hole, but you manage to shrug it off. You’re better than that! You’re not really a shy mouse! Firmly focusing your thoughts you manage to turn yourself back just in time to prepare for the next spell. </TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>The next time your opponent casts the spell you hesitate to move for just a second, and by doing so end up getting hit by the spell. Why did you do that?! D-do you want to be a cute tiny mouse?? You have no time to think about your subconscious decision though, as you are rapidly turning into a mouse girl again. And boy does it feel good… The ears puffing out on top of your head, the tail sneaking its way past your mousy butt,  furry little paws, rows of breasts with little teats forming on your belly that you can’t help but touch and rubbing your thighs together and… WHAT? You don’t want to be a mouse! Or… well maybe you do, but you don’t want to be someone’s pet! You shake off the magic, but it’s very, very hard and leaves you panting, aroused and with a very wet spot between your legs. Even though you are back to your original self, the people around you still look scary and big, and you shyly evade them.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>You somehow manage to dodge your opponent’s spell every time, knowing fully well that you can’t take another hit. But wait a minute… what’s that? You are suddenly distracted by a hypnotizing smell that makes you drool. You don’t have time to investigate though, since that pesky opponent is dangling something suspiciously yellow between two fingers with a big grin on their face. Hey, wait a second… You can’t help but push your nose in the air like a rodent and take a deep whiff. Is… is that… is that some CHEESE?!  Instincts immediately take over and the next thing you know you are once again a mouse girl, reaching just to your opponent’s knees, clinging to their leg while drooling and begging in your squeaky cute voice for a taste of the cheese. Your new owner picks you up with a gentle smile and hands you the treat. Happily you chip away at it with your sharp teeth, your body becoming smaller and smaller in the process, now irreversibly turning into the cute and tiny mouse girl you were meant to be. You don’t care anymore. Master will protect you from the scary big people after all. Oh, and you smell more free nibbles, can’t beat free nibbles.</TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>You throw your spell square at your victim’s chest and hit the mark perfectly. They immediately bend over, gasping for breath and squeaking slightly. As they do so you notice that their body is getting covered in thin, white fur and that they are shrinking at an alarming rate. Your victim recovers quickly from it all though, but for an instance you think you saw the mousy pet that you unleashed within them, begging you to be freed.  That, or you are just imagining things because you are slightly mad with power.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>You dance around your victim, waiting for the right moment where they drop their guard. When they finally do, you release the spell and hope for the best. You’re not disappointed. This time your victim’s skin bursts out in white fur immediately, and they shrink down to almost half their original size. You smile lewdly as they grow breasts and totally forget about their surroundings, massaging the new additions with not a care in the world. But just when it gets interesting in the downstairs department the mouse girl shakes her head and slowly starts to turn back to her previous form. </TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>Even though your spell misses by a hair’s length, you see that it definitely has an effect on your victim. They immediately shrink to half their length and their ears are being replaced by the round ones of a mouse. Fur covers their feminine body, and then the breasts kick in… You can’t help but gaze in wonder and slight arousal as the small mouse girl starts to moan as she gropes and fondles herself. Lost in a trance one of her hands drifts downstairs over her belly, over her mound… But just before she reaches the slit between her legs she starts to slowly change back. Slightly disappointed you prepare yourself for a new flurry of spells to aim at them.  There’s no stopping this train anymore now.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Your victim lets out a high pitched peep of shock as your spell engulfs them. Instantly they are turned back to a cute and mousy form, one that appears to have a whole lot of other things on her mind than changing back, clearly loving the sensation of being transformed. She’s stroking her breasts and ears like it’s the first time, and you see her crossing her legs and rubbing her thighs together to fight the growing itch between them. Then she suddenly moans in a squeaky voice as her tail comes through for the first time, and you can see her thighs growing a bit damp. Sadly she recovers from her lust though, and quickly slides her tail between her legs to hide her privates. Biting her lip and blushing like mad she shyly looks around for a hiding spot, even as her body reverses back to normal. Good thing that you have a nice comfy pocket or other home waiting for them.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Your victim stays perfectly still as you raise your hands for the last few spells… but wait, isn't that odd? It’s almost like they don’t mind becoming your pet…. You fire away, and the spell hits them square in the chest. The effects are amazing… Your victim actually smiles as “she” reverts back to her tiny mouse form. White fur erupts over her body, her legs turn short and stubby, and the tail shoots out again, accompanied by the same lewd moaning and peeping as before. Row after row after row of tiny breasts pop up on her stomach, and she seems to want to touch them all simultaneously. She sits down, spreading her legs, teasing her pink slit with her tail... and then she starts to grow and turn back again. Your victim looks sad at their hands and body for a second before shaking their head. They are clearly really confused and conflicted on this, and even though they are not a mouse anymore they still evade other people as if they were giants. A bit sad isn't it? You should continue and give this pet in the making a nice and safe home.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>You take aim and charge up time after time, but you can’t get a good lock on your opponent. It seems like the mouse instincts in them are taking over, making it very hard to get a good shot. You prepared for a situation like this though… reaching into your pocket you grab a small cube of incredibly smelly cheese, and dangle it in front of you, blowing the smells their way. The effects are astonishing. Your opponent starts to sniff like an animal, and when they see the cheese dangling between your fingers all their inhibitions towards you seem forgotten. Even though you didn't hit them with a spell you see your victim shrinking, white fur erupting from their skin as she hurries on his little feet to reach you. Once they do, they, or rather she, is a complete mouse girl. She starts clinging to your leg, reaching up with one tiny hand like a child begging for candy. You smile and gently pick her up and offer her the cheese, and as she is happily nibbling away she shrinks and shrinks until she fits snugly in the palm of your hand. With her belly full of cheese your new pet girl lets out a little burp and climbs up on your shoulder, where she sits down, apparently very satisfied with you as her owner, and not even thinking of changing herself back even if she could.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>You throw your spell square at your victim’s chest and hit the mark perfectly. He immediately bends over, gasping for breath and squeaking slightly. As he does so you notice that his body is getting covered in thin, white fur and he’s shrinking at an alarming rate. Your victim recovers quickly from it all though, but for an instance you think you saw the shy mousy pet that you unleashed within him, begging you to be freed.  That, or you are just imagining things because you are slightly mad with power.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>You dance and spin around your victim, waiting for the right moment where he drops his guard. When he finally does, you release the spell and hope for the best. You’re not disappointed. This time his skin bursts out in white fur immediately, and his body shrinks down to almost half of its original size. You smile lewdly as “he” grows breasts and totally forgets about his surroundings, massaging the new additions with not a care in the world. But just when you see his bulge shrinking, indicating that it’s about to get interesting in the downstairs department, the mouse” girl” shakes her head and slowly starts to turn back to her previous form. </TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>Even though your spell misses by a hair’s length, you see that it definitely has an effect on your victim. He immediately shrinks to half his length, and his ears are being replaced by the cute and round ones of a mouse. Fur covers his feminine body, and then the breasts kick in… You can’t help but gaze in wonder and slight arousal as the small mouse girl starts to moan as she gropes and fondles herself. Meanwhile her penis is disappearing completely, getting replaced by a slightly wet female vagina. Totally lost in a trance one of her hands drifts downstairs over her belly, over her mound… But just before she reaches the fresh slit between her legs she starts to slowly change back. Slightly disappointed that the show had to end so suddenly you prepare a new flurry of spells to aim at him. After all, you saw what the spell is capable of… No chance of you stopping this train anymore now.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>Your victim lets out a high pitched peep of shock as your spell engulfs them. Instantly he’s turned back to a cute and mousy form, one that appears to have a whole lot of other things on her dirty mind than changing back, clearly loving the sensation of being transformed. She’s stroking her breasts and ears like it’s the first time, and you see her crossing her legs and rubbing her thighs together to fight the growing itch between them as her genitals warp into that of a girl again. Then she suddenly moans in a squeaky voice as her tail comes through for the first time, and you can see her thighs growing a bit damp. Sadly she recovers from her lust after that though, and quickly slides her tail between her legs to hide her privates. Biting her lip and blushing like mad she shyly looks around for a hiding spot, even as her body reverses back to normal. Good thing that you have a nice comfy pocket or other home waiting for him when you’re done with him…</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>Your victim stays perfectly still and cocks his head as you raise your hands for the last few spells… but wait, isn’t that odd? It’s almost like he doesn’t mind becoming your pet…. You fire away, and the spell hits him square in the chest. The effects are amazing… Your victim actually smiles as “she” reverts back to her tiny mouse form. White fur erupts over her body, her legs turn short and stubby, and the tail shoots out again, accompanied by the same lewd moaning and peeping as before. Row after row after row of tiny breasts pop up on her stomach, and she seems to want to touch them all simultaneously. She sits down, spreading her legs, teasing her pink slit with her tail... and then she starts to grow and turn back again. Your victim looks sad and embarrassed at his hands and penis for a second before shaking his head forcefully. He’s clearly really confused and conflicted on this, and even though he is not a mouse anymore he is still evading other people as if they were giants. A bit sad isn't it? You should continue and give this pet in the making a nice and safe home.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>You take aim and charge up time after time, but you can’t get a good lock on your opponent. It seems like the mouse instincts in him are taking over, making it very hard to hit him. You prepared for a situation like this though… reaching into your pocket you grab a small cube of incredibly smelly cheese, and dangle it in front of you, blowing the smells his way. The effects are astonishing. Your opponent starts to sniff like an animal, and when he sees the cheese dangling between your fingers all his inhibitions towards you seem forgotten. Even though you didn't hit him with a spell you see him shrinking, white fur erupting from his skin as he hurries on his little feet to reach you. Once he does, he, or rather she, is a complete mouse girl. She starts clinging to your leg, reaching up with one tiny hand like a child begging for candy. You smile and gently pick her up and offer her the cheese, and as she is happily nibbling away she shrinks and shrinks until she fits snugly in the palm of your hand. With her belly full of cheese your new pet girl lets out a little burp and climbs up on your shoulder, where she sits down, apparently very satisfied with you as her owner, and not even thinking of changing herself back even if she could.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>You throw your spell square at your victim’s chest and hit the mark perfectly. She immediately bends over, gasping for breath and squeaking slightly. As she does so you notice that her body is getting covered in thin, white fur and that she’s shrinking at an alarming rate. Your victim recovers quickly from it all though, but for an instance you think you saw the shy mousy pet that you unleashed within her, and you could almost hear her begging you to be freed.  That, or you are just imagining things because you are growing slightly mad with power in this crazy world.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>You dance and spin around your victim, waiting for the right moment when she drops her guard. When she finally does, you release the spell and hope for the best. You’re not disappointed. This time her skin bursts out in white fur immediately, and her body shrinks down to almost half of its original size. You smile lewdly as her breasts turn small and firm and she totally forgets about her surroundings, massaging the new additions with not a care in the world. But just when you see new rows of breast appearing below the first two, indicating that it’s about to get, the mouse girl shakes her head and slowly starts to turn back to her previous form.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>Even though your spell misses the girl by a hair’s length, you see that it definitely has an effect on her. SHe immediately shrinks to half her old length and her boring ears are being replaced by the cute and round ones of a mouse. Fur covers her body, and then the rows of breasts kick in… You can’t help but gaze in wonder and slight arousal as the small mouse girl starts to moan as she gropes and fondles herself. She slumps down in a corner, spreading her legs, giving you a good view of her wet pussy. Totally lost in a trance one of her hands drifts downstairs over her belly, over her mound… But just before she reaches the fresh slit between her legs she starts to slowly change back to normal. Slightly disappointed that the show had to end so suddenly you prepare a new flurry of spells to aim at her. After all, you saw what the spell is capable of… No chance of you stopping this train anymore now.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>Your victim lets out a high pitched peep of shock as your spell engulfs her completely. Instantly she’s turned back to her cute and mousy form, one that appears to have a whole lot of other things on her dirty mind than changing back, clearly loving the sensation of her body being transformed. She’s stroking her breasts and ears like it’s the first time, and you see her crossing her legs and rubbing her thighs together to fight the growing itch between them. Then she suddenly starts to moan in a squeaky voice as her tail comes through for the first time, and you can see her thighs growing more than a bit damp. Sadly she recovers from her state of heat after that though, and quickly slides her new tail between her legs to hide her privates. Biting her lip and blushing like mad she shyly looks around for a hiding spot, even as her body reverses back to normal. Good thing that you have a nice comfy pocket or other home waiting for her when you’re done with her…</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>Your victim stays perfectly still and cocks her head as you raise your hands for the last few spells… but wait, isn’t that odd? It’s almost like she doesn't mind becoming your pet…. You fire away, and the spell hits her square in the chest. She doesn’t even flinch away from it! And the effects are amazing… Your victim actually smiles as she reverts back to her tiny mouse form. White fur erupts over her body, her legs turn short and stubby, and the tail shoots out again, accompanied by the same lewd moaning and peeping as before. Row after row after row of tiny breasts pop up on her stomach, and she seems to want to touch them all simultaneously. She sits down, spreading her legs, teasing her pink slit with her tail as she blushes furiously... and then she starts to grow and turn back again. Your victim looks sad and embarrassed at her hands and belly for a second before shaking her head forcefully. She’s clearly really confused and conflicted on this, and even though she is not a mouse anymore she is still evading other people as if they were giants. A bit sad isn't it? You should continue and give this pet in the making a nice and safe home.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>You take aim and charge up the spell time after time to finish this transformation once and for all, but you can’t get a good lock on your opponent. It seems like the mouse instincts in her are taking over, making it very hard to hit her. You prepared for a situation like this though… reaching into your pocket you grab a small cube of incredibly smelly cheese, and dangle it in front of you, blowing the smells her way. The effects are astonishing. Your opponent starts to sniff like an animal, and when she sees the cheese dangling between your fingers all her inhibitions towards you seem forgotten. Even though you didn't even hit the girl with a spell you see her shrinking, white fur erupting from   her skin as she hurries on her little feet to reach you. Once she does, she is a complete mouse girl. She starts clinging to your leg, reaching up with one tiny hand and huge eyes, like a child begging for candy. You smile and gently pick her up and offer her the cheese, and as she is happily nibbling away she shrinks and shrinks until she fits snuggly in the palm of your hand. With her belly full of cheese your new pet girl lets out a little burp and climbs up on your shoulder, where she sits down on her butt. Apparently she’s very satisfied with you as her owner, and not even thinking of changing herself back even if she could.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>

</Form>
