<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>You feel a spell strike you and your body suddenly goes rigid, but only for a moment before you're easily able to undo it.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>You're struck again and once more your body goes rigid, but this time your skin also starts to feel different. Tougher, rougher... You forget about it as you reverse the changes.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>Your arms and legs shoot to your side, causing you to stand like a pole as your body goes rigid again. You feel your skin has changed again and recognizes the texture as feeling like leather. With a bit of effort you manage to change yourself back.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>Once more your body goes rigid, arms at your side, legs locked together, skin like leather. This time, however, your skin changes color, darkening to until it's completely black. You fight it off and reverse the changes.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>Your body rapidly thins and squeezes in on itself as you find yourself turning into something non-human. Your legs feel solid, but the rest of your body is loose. For some reason you long for someone to pick you up and hold your black, leathery body. Fighting these urges, you manage to return to your previous form with a twinge of regret.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>Suddenly your entire body shrinks and changes again. Your legs fuse together into a leather handle and your entire upper body becomes a long, leather whip. Your mind is flooded with desire to be held and used on naughty slaves. You can't even begin to think of changing back, sealing your fate as a leather whip.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>You fire your spell and see it strike your target's body. They suddenly goes rigid, but only for a moment before they're easily able to undo it.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>You strike again and once more their body goes rigid, but this time their skin starts to look different. A little tougher, a little rougher than normal. Unfortunately, they manage to reverse the changes.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>Your spell lands on point and you watch your target's arms and legs shoot to their side, causing them to stand like a pole as their body goes rigid again. You watch their skin change again and recognizes the texture as looking like leather. Though it seems to take some effort, they manage to change themselves back.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>With another strike of your spell, their body goes rigid, arms at their sides, legs locked together, skin like leather. This time, however, the target's skin changes color, darkening to until it's completely black. You can tell that it's a struggle, but they manage to reverse the changes.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Your target's body rapidly thins and squeezes in on itself as they begin turning into something non-human. Their legs stay locked in place, but their upper body seems to hang loosely. Somehow they manage to return to their previous form but you're certain you catch a look of regret in their eyes.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>With another powerful blast, your target's entire body shrinks and changes again. Their legs fuse together into a leather handle and their entire upper body becomes a long, leather whip. This time they don't change back. You pick up your new prize and feel a surge of dominance reverberate through you.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
