<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>The first bolt of gray light connects with you square in the chest. At first you thought the missile to be a dud, but you look at your surroundings and notice they are larger than they once were. You have shrunken by what must have been 4 inches. The world seems to be a bit more vivid as the colors swirl for a moment. Closing your eyes you reverse the changes fairly swift.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>Another bolt strikes you as you fumble about watching for movement to reveal your attacker. Grayish hair sprouts from your chest blossoming outwards in a tidal fashion. It flows in waves beginning slow but reaching a crescendo as it encompasses your chest and back. A feeling of vertigo indicates that you are once again shrinking. The area swirls changing from colors into shades of black and white. Confused on what is happening you focus on reversing the changes managing to restore colors to the scenery. </TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>This time you see the bolt as it leaves the hands of your foe. You move trying to dodge the spell, but it splashes against your legs. Gray fur erupts from where it hits and warmth flows across both your legs you glance down watching as your legs shrink making you fall to the ground. Laying there for a second basking in the sensations of the new power flowing through your legs. Feelings of loneliness spurt through you causing you to tremble. Shaking your head it disperses you reverse the changes adeptly. </TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>Using your legs you launch yourself at your enemy only to get struck with another bolt. Color swims out of your vision as your eyes become pure black. You shrink in size as you skid across the uneven terrain attempting to keep your adversary in sight. Moving forward you feel your hands and feet changing into paws. Your nails now scratch the floor slowing you down with friction. Fur flows up from your hands colliding where your torso fur ends. You reverse the changes slowly because you waste most of your attention focusing on your foe.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>This time you circle your opponent waiting for them to leave an opening. They throw the bolt at you this time you lunge to the side dodging it completely. They smirk at you, "Did you think I wouldn't know you can dodge being this close to being my new pet." You feel the spell collide into your backside. Your tailbone begins to extend covered in grayish fur growing out to a foot long. Your size diminishes once more until you are now smaller than a full grown husky. Loneliness washes over you once more causing you to think, maybe you could work for this person. They might treat you better than how your current situation is going. Growling at these thoughts you open your mouth towards the enemy your mouth completely expands outwards elongating into a snout. Distractedly you reverse some of the mental changes.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>Knowing when you are bested you sit there as they cast the final bolt. Your ears cascade outwards migrating to the top of your head. Sounds ping from all around you. the loneliness hits once more but instead of fighting it off you embrace it and move closer to your once adversary. You nuzzle against them gently looking up with sad eyes. They reach down towards you and scratch you behind your ears and whisper," what a beautiful little cub you have become." You beam up at them and lick their hand lovingly. They stand and say,"well come along, we have people to change and you can help me keep them still." You yip excitedly and follow your new owner.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>You raise your hands and conjure a bolt of grayish light tossing it at your unsuspecting foe. They glance at you curious as you as they begin to shrink before your eyes. They shrink for about 3 seconds not noticing they have lost four inches of their height. You watch their face as their eyes darken briefly and curse as they close them and begin reversing your spell.  </TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>Moving slowly you charge another bolt in your hands focusing on changing them as swiftly as possible knowing they will detect you sooner or later. You flick the bolt at them aiming at their torso. It strikes directly and begins to spread swallowing their entire torso in grayish fur. You watch your victim shrink to almost 2 feet shorter than they used to be. Their eyes begin to darken as your spell takes hold, but then return to almost normal. You bite your tongue to keep from swearing from their prowess.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>This time you charge the bolt a little longer, angry at them for slowing down your progress. They see you unleash the bolt towards them and would have dodged it if you hadn't put so much power into the spell. Hitting the ground near them it splashes against their legs from behind. As the fur begins to encompass their legs they fall to floor as the muscles reshape themselves for speed and stealth over pure strength.  The poor fool's legs shrink in length as they lie there on the ground. They return to a four legged stance and shake their head as if dispelling some parts of your spell.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd> Knowing that you have been seen you quickly charge a bolt in your mind then grant it power as they lunge at you. You unleash your spell into the opponent's face and roll safely out of the way of their attack. You turn as you continue your tumble landing on your feet and noticing their eyes change completely into a pitch black. They begin slowing down as fur slides up their hands even as the nails lengthen on both hand and foot alike. Then their hands and feet morph into paws slowing them down as the nails drag across the uneven street. The fur stops growing as it reaches the torso on your future pet.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>You watch as your mostly changed foe circles you. You realize they are waiting for you to attack them, so you prepare a homing bolt in your mind focusing it on them and nothing else. You fire at them and then smirk after they dodge as expected. "Did you think I wouldn't have prepared for you to dodge being this close to being a pet?" your question distracts them as the bolt returns striking against your enemies backside.  A tail grows a foot in length right out of their behind. They shrink until they are a bit smaller than a fully grown husky, and they begin growling as their mouth extends outwards into a snout, at you or something you are uncertain but you know you haven't won yet and prepare for the final attack.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>They sit there looking defeated glancing directly at you as you fire one last bolt at them. Your new pet's ears cascade outwards moving to the top of their head. After their ears have finished they walk up to slowly staring at you sadly as if you were going to abandon them after all of this. You reach down and scratch your finished work fondly behind the ears. "You have turned out to be a beautiful cub." They lick your hand in what you think to be appreciation. You stand up and say to them,"well come along, we have people to change and you can help me keep them still." As you walk away they follow you closely. </TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
