<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>Your opponent tries to cast a powerful and complex arcane spell, which summons thick grey clouds all over the place, as if you and your opponent were being moved into another dimension. But quickly, the clouds dissolve and you're back on Earth.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>Once again, you are surrounded by grey clouds, leaving you and your opponent alone in another dimension for a private duel. The atmosphere thickens as you wait for your enemy's next move. As thunder starts to roll, a strange metallic gooey pond materializes itself between you two. It solidifies into an oblong metallic wall, then polishes itself so brightly you can see your reflection slowly showing on it. You take no chance and cast a magic missile right in the middle. The wall instantly turns into liquid and splashes onto the floor. The clouds also dissipate.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>Your opponent is getting more experienced at casting this spell. You're quickly back into the clouds and this time, the strange metallic gooey pond floating between you and your opponent changes into a giant oblong mirror with a bright silver frame. You scowl at your own reflection, which scowls back at you as it should. You wait, on guard, for the next twisted move your opponent has in store for you, but nothing happens. You walk closer to the mirror to inspect it, and everything seems normal, except for strange ripples on its surface. You can't resist but touch it with the tip of a finger and suddenly, your reflection vanishes. Surprised, you back off and kick the frame in retaliation, shattering the mirror into thousands of pieces. Superstitions say it's seven years of bad luck, but in this magical world, nobody know's how much it actually is...</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>Things are getting serious now. Your opponent summons the mirror right in your face while thunder rolls and lightning illuminates your surroundings.  This time, you don't see your reflection. Mesmerized, you can't resist and try to touch it the mirror with a finger, but it simply goes through the mirror, crossing a kind of portal. On the other side, you see a manicured finger. You pull your finger back and it reverts to normal. You pull your finger in and out again, amused, then decide to try a complete hand. It turns into a dainty feminine hand. As you push it deeper, long white lace appears, then the tip of a blue sleeve with golden embroidery patterns. It looks like the sleeve of a Victorian dress. Once again, you pull back your arm and it reverts to normal. You try a foot, and it turns into a very feminine one clad in a black slipper. The hem of a blue dress with white laces also appears. Finally, you try the tip of your forehead and see a curly lock of brown hair falling in front of your sight. Although a part of your mind really wants to see how you would look like on the other side of this portal, the most rational side of your brain knows it's probably part of the spell to trick you there. You decide to back off and shatter the portal with a magic missile.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>Now, your opponent tries a different strategy by summoning the mirror back between you two. Once again, you fail to see your reflection in it, but the wind starts to blow strongly against your back and you have a strange sensation of being pushed towards the mirror. You try to resist, but your feet start to slip. You cast a magic missile, but the portal simply swallows it. A strong gust of wind throws you on your back and you quickly slide toward the portal. You get swallowed by your feet, then your torso and as you are about to go through, you grab the frame of the mirror. You can see your arms wrapped in the same blue sleeves with golden embroidery patterns. As you are holding tight, you take a quick look under you. You see two big mount of flesh, breasts, and your body dressed with a blue Victorian dress. With all your strength, you pull yourself out of the portal, reverting to your former state. You drop under the portal where it cannot suck you up and wait for the wind to calm down. </TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>For one last time, your opponent summons a huge portal in front of themselves. You tremble in fear as you realize you won't be able to get out of this one. The wind blows and simply lifts you up in the air. You are thrown into the portal and violently dropped on the floor. You stand up, smooth out your dress instinctively and run back towards the portal, but it won't let you through. You bang on the invisible wall and try to cast spells, but it resists all your attack. You can see clouds dissolving on the other side, but not on yours. You keep banging on the glass again and again. The world now seems to grow bigger around your prison. Once again, you try to hit as hard as you can, but you realize your hands and arms just disappeared! You look down and see your whole body has also dissolved in thin air! You are now just a floating head, unable to move or do anything. You see a giant walking over you, binding down and picking you up like a coin. Then, you see your opponent's giant face, which asks you : "Oh choker, choker, who do you belong to? Who do you vow to serve and protect?" With your new sophisticated girly voice and unable to lie, you answer : "You, o' mighty arcane wizard!"</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>You try to cast this powerful arcane spell, which summons thick grey clouds all over the place, but you fail to connect the next part. Quickly, the clouds dissolves.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>Once again, your spell summons grey clouds, leaving you and your opponent alone in another dimension made for a private duel. The atmosphere thickens as you start the second part of the spell which is much more complex. As thunder starts to roll, a strange metallic gooey pond materializes itself between both of you. It solidifies into an oblong transparent wall. Your opponent casts a magic missile right in the middle of it and instantly, it turns into liquid, splashing onto the floor. The clouds also dissipate. You'll have to be faster if you want to capture your enemy with this spell.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>As you are getting more experienced at casting this spell, you manage to achieve each step which greater speed. You both are quickly back in the clouds and this time, the strange metallic gooey pond floating between you and your opponent materializes itself into a giant oblong window with a bright silver frame. You see your opponent scowling at you and doing funny faces. You think your victim must be facing some kind of one-way mirror. Your target then walks closer to the mirror to inspect it and touches it with the tip of a finger. Your target suddenly backs off and kicks the frame, shattering the glass into thousands of pieces. </TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>This time, you summon the mirror right in front of your target while thunder rolls and lightnings illuminate your surroundings.  You can see your target playing around with the mirror once again, but when your opponent touches it, their finger disappears, and then reappears when pulled back. Your victim then tries a hand, then an arm, then a foot plus both arms, and each time, your enemy seems to be going through some kind of portal. You almost hope your victim will simply walk into their prison and be done with it, but they back off and shatter the portal with a magic missile. Next time, it may be a good idea to try to force your enemy into it.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Now, you summon the glass prison at a good distance and call strong arcane winds to force your victim into the trap. You can see them trying to hold ground while they slip towards the portal. Suddenly, your target loses balance and slides inside the portal, beginning to disappear. You can see your opponent's fingers holding the frame tightly and cursing from inside the portal, but with a slightly different voice. You quickly make a run to kick your victims' grasp, but they are quicker and manage to pull themselves out of the prison. You cut off the spell, not wanting to waste any more energy. </TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>Like a master arcane wizard, you summon a terrifying thunderstorm which strikes fear in the face of your opponent. The glass prison appears, bigger than ever, and a small tornado lifts your victim like a feather and throws them into the trap. Your enemy didn't even have a chance to lift a single finger. The thunderstorm calms down and the clouds vanish, but the glass prison is still standing in midair. It changes from transparent to silver and shrinks slowly. You can hear your target banging and casting spells against the prison, but you know their soul is now trapped forever. The glass prison keeps shrinking until it's no bigger than a coin and falls onto the ground. You bend over and pick it up. You can see the face of a sophisticated woman staring at you, scared. She looks like a cameo. Hence, you make up a black ribbon with a quick spell and tie the cameo to it to make a cute little choker. You look at the woman and ask : "Oh choker, choker, who do you belong to? Who do you vow to serve and protect?" you impatiently await the answer when she says : "You, o' mighty arcane wizard!" </TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
