<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<Description>You are an adorable black and pink crop top, tied in the front for convenience (since buttons can be such a bother when your owner is in a hurry to get naked!). It's your job to make your owner feel sexy, fun, and carefree; providing just enough coverage to keep their assets from being exposed without creating too much in the way of inhibition. You are the perfect combination of girl next door and neighborhood slut!</Description>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>Your opponent conjures a mini-tornado of swirling pink and black energy and hurls it at you. Before you can dodge, the whirlwind engulfs your body and you find yourself trapped within its spinning vortex. You begin to feel a little light-headed as the air whips past your face too quick for you to catch a breath. Raising your hands defensively, you suddenly find yourself weaving your fingers together.  Your hands act quite against your will as they press to your chest and refuse to budge. While you're struggling to pull your fingers apart you notice that your hands are turning hot pink. Startled, you dispel the changes with a counter-spell.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>The whirlwind of color flies from your opponent's hands again, and envelops your body before you have a chance to dodge. Strain as you might, you cannot keep your fingers from weaving together again and pressing against your chest. As you struggle to pull your fingers apart, the tornado of pink and black sparkles spinning around you, a giddy feeling of carefree abandon suddenly occupies your thoughts. "Why bother with buttons?" you say aloud, and then blink in surprise when you realize what you just blurted out. At that point you notice that your hands and forearms have narrowed down to bands of pink fabric, tied in a neat bow! The pink fabric is extending quickly over your elbows. You summon enough concentration to cast a counter spell and reverse the changes.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>Your rival hesitates and starts to turn away, making you wonder if they have given up. It was a ploy to get you to lower your guard! They suddenly spin around and cast the colorful tornado at you again. You groan in frustration as your fingers knot together, quite literally, and your arms again turn into fabric. The pink material moves up to your shoulders and wraps around your back. At the same time, you realize that you are feet have left the ground. As you start to spin within the vortex, your legs start shrinking! These changes should be alarming, but you find it difficult to be worried. In fact, you suddenly feel carefree, with no concern in the world except making someone look cute, sexy, and a little slutty… but not -too- slutty. Groaning, you reverse the changes with a counter spell and drop to the ground as the whirlwind dissipates.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>You brace yourself as your rival hurls the multicolored tornado in your direction again. Even though you are ready for it, the whirlwind effortlessly lifts you bodily off the ground and you start spinning within it. Within seconds, your hands are tied in a pretty bow and your upper body is well on its way to becoming what is clearly some sort of girly top of pink fabric, with a smart black collar and matching short sleeves. How cute! Um… You are getting dizzy with all the spinning around, and… as you think about it, it's so convenient to just tie the ends of a shirt and not worry about buttons! It's such a casual, flirty look. Like, girl next door meets neighborhood slut! Wait… your legs are shriveling up into your body. Is that supposed to happen? Your mind starts to clear and you desperately reverse the changes with a counter spell.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>When your rival casts their spell again, a part of you is actually looking forward to it. The swirling pink-back tornado sweep you off your feet and you find yourself whirling around inside. Within moments, your hands have become slender strips of pink cloth tied in a neat bow, and your upper body quickly forms the rest of the cute pink and black crop top your attacker seems intent on turning you into. As you spin within the vortex, your newly-formed sleeves flapping in the breeze, you dreamily wonder what it would be like to be worn by a beautiful, busty woman, her cleavage practically spilling out of you whenever she bends over. How wonderful it would be for such a woman to wear you! By the time you snap out your reverie, your legs have shriveled up to nothing and your head is vanishing into the collar of the top. With what little concentration you have left, you manage to counter the spell and restore your body to normal.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>You watch with a curious mixture of dread and elation as your opponent summons the magical whirlwind one last time. The tornado of sparkling pink and black energy lifts you off the ground and spins you helplessly as it transforms you fully into a flirty tied crop top. It is over so quickly, you are already garment twirling helplessly in the wind before you realize what has happened. Lightheaded from all the spinning around, you find yourself looking forward to being worn by your opponent… or whoever else picks you up. You want to make your owner look pretty, flirty, and fun… and a little bit slutty, too! The whirlwind finally dissipates, and you flutter to the ground. There you eagerly wait for your new owner to claim you.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>You conjure up a mini-tornado of swirling pink and black energy and hurl it at your opponent. Before they can dodge, the whirlwind engulfs their body and you grin with malicious glee as they are trapped within its spinning vortex. They seem to be struggling to catch their breath as the air whips past their face, and they raise their hands defensively. As you watch, you see their fingers weave together and their hands press to their chest. While they're struggling to pull their fingers apart, they seem to notice that their hands are turning hot pink and panic. They dispel the changes with a counter-spell.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>The whirlwind of color flies from your hands again, and envelops your opponent's body before they have a chance to dodge. You can see the strain in their eyes as they struggle in vain to keep their fingers from weaving together and pressing against their chest. As they struggle to pull their fingers apart, the tornado of pink and black sparkles spinning around them, their expression turns dreamy. "Why bother with buttons?" they say aloud, and then blink in surprise when they realize what they just blurted out. At that point they look down and notice that their hands and forearms have narrowed down to bands of pink fabric, tied in a neat bow. The pink fabric is extending quickly over their elbows. To your disappointment, they summon enough concentration to cast a counter spell and reverse the changes.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>To taunt your rival, you start to turn away as if giving up. Your ploy succeeds in lowering their guard! You quickly spin around and cast the colorful tornado at them again. They groan in frustration as their fingers knot together, quite literally, and their arms again turn into fabric. The pink material moves up to their shoulders and wraps around their back. To your delight, you see that their feet have left the ground, and as they start to spin within the vortex their legs start shrinking! These changes should be alarming, but the expression on your rival's face is carefree, as if they have no concern in the world. Groaning, they break out of their reverie and reverse the changes, dropping to the ground as the whirlwind dissipates.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Focusing your magic, you hurl the multicolored tornado at your target again. The whirlwind effortlessly lifts their bodily off the ground and they start spinning within it as you laugh with glee. Within seconds, their hands are tied in a pretty bow and their upper body is well on its way to becoming what is clearly some sort of girly top of pink fabric, with a smart black collar and matching short sleeves. How cute! A tied crop top is such a casual, flirty look, like girl next door meets neighborhood slut! Your rival is starting to look disoriented, partly from all that spinning around but also due to the mental changes your spell is imposing on their vulnerable mind. Unfortunately, they take notice when their legs start shriveling up into their body and desperately reverse the changes with a counter spell.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>When you cast your spell again, you get the strange feeling that your rival is actually looking forward to it. The swirling pink-back tornado sweep them off their feet and send them whirling around inside. Within moments, their hands have become slender strips of pink cloth tied in a neat bow, and their upper body quickly forms the rest of the cute pink and black crop top you fully intend to turn them into. As they spin within the vortex, their newly-formed sleeves flapping in the breeze, their expression turns dreamy. You imagine they are wondering what it would be like to be worn by a beautiful, busty woman, her cleavage practically spilling out of them whenever she bends over. By the time they snap out their reverie, their legs have shriveled up to nothing and their head is vanishing into the collar of the top. With what little concentration they have left, they manage to counter the spell and restore their body to normal.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>A curious mixture of dread and elation vie for control of your rival's features as you summon the magical whirlwind one last time. The tornado of sparkling pink and black energy lifts them off the ground and spins them helplessly as it transforms them fully into a flirty tied crop top. It is over so quickly, they are already a garment twirling helplessly in the wind before you have a chance to enjoy the changes your magic has wrought. Still, it is with satisfaction that you watch the new top tumbling in the wind, your rival now reduced to mere clothing. The whirlwind finally dissipates, and the cropped shirt flutters to the ground at your feet. You eagerly bend down to pick it up.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
