<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>There’s something happening here, but what it is ain't exactly clear.  There’s someone with a wand over there, telling you that you've got to... got to... what, exactly?  Lay down your spells, quit fighting?  As if!  The wizard doesn't really seem to be doing anything, but paranoia is striking deep; into your mind it creeps.  Thoughts fill your brain, thoughts of renouncing this war, of leaving your fellow humans in the shape you found them, even of buying clothing from the stores instead of making them from your enemies.  You aren't really sure what's going down, but you run off quickly before your opponent can take you away.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>"Good morning, starshine," says the wizard who just walked up to you, "your friend says hello."  You wonder what they're on about this time and try  to leave, but you find that you cannot; you're stuck in place with your opponent above you, yourself trembling below  "If it's hard for me to  free your mind I'll change your body instead," they muse.  Continuing, “First, how about some hair down to... there." You feel your hair grow several inches.  "No, shoulder-length. Longer, gleaming, streaming, flaxen, waxen!"  Your hair explodes outward, becoming long and blonde, moving further and further down your back.  "And some more curves. Let's see...” they think.  Pointing to your chest:  "Here, baby," and it inflates to a full D-cup.  Pointing to your hips:   "There, mama." Your hips expand, your waist contracts, your ass grows to a pleasing feminine shape. Your groin, if not already feminine, becomes so.  Then they gesture wide:  "Everywhere, daddy, daddy!" Your whole body seems to shrink and grow thinner until you take on the appearance of a college age girl.  As you start to actually believe this is your true form, you run off screaming, the changes gradually reverting, though you suspect your opponent can bring them back at any time.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>The enemy mage arrives again, and starts... singing? "Look at yourself, look at yourself, young girl."  You find yourself immediately paralyzed upon hearing this! You follow their suggestion, looking down at yourself and seeing that you’ve regained your thin, college-aged female body, the one with the long, blonde, flower-strewn hair.  They start chanting wordless nonsense, “Gliddy gloop gloopy, nibby nobby nooby, la la la lo lo," are the last words you can make out of their spell as occasions and persuasions begin to clutter your mind.  You feel your good sense under assault, as your mind is crippled with a new innocence.  Thoughts of dead kings, many other things you can't define; peppermints, incense, the color of time.  You've turned out, tuned in, and turned your eyes around, as you  continue to look at yourself even after your opponent has long since  left ...</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>Your assailant is back; subtle waves of magic return you to the same young female form you had before, they start your mind back on track to where it once belonged.  This time it sounds like the enemy mage wants to debate you:  "Imagine there's no Heaven," they begin, though you find that extremely hard to do.  The town is full of succubi, angels, and valkyries, too.  Still, most of them seem just as bad as the other humans; engaging in all sorts of transformative conflicts, wreaking even more carnage than many of their human opponents.  You’re thinking to yourself, "can't we all just get along," when they interrupt you with a query.  "War," they ask, "what is it good for?"   Unhesitatingly, you reply in a high-pitched voice: "Absolutely nothing!"   Perhaps the unusual sounds have you questioning yourself; it's certainly good for acquiring new magical outfits.  So when they ask you to say it again, you don't, instead opting to work on reverting the changes. After all, there is a time for love AND a time for hate, a purpose for all things under Heaven...</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>Away from your assailant, you've been thinking about it and you feel you're more than ready to give peace a chance.  As soon as your body returns, before they can even speak, you begin to question them in song in an attempt to end their war-mongering ways.  "How many roads must a man walk down before she's no longer a man?"  They smile.  "How many lives must be lost to these spells, 'til bras are again sewn by hand?"  Their smile gets wider.  "And how many souls must the bimbo balls claim before they are finally banned?"  They grin from ear to ear.  "The answer, my friend, is..." you hesitate, "the answer is... is..." Their grin breaks as you struggle to think of an answer.  Fifty?  No, maybe a bit over forty?   But a number won't do... and wait. Why are you even thinking about this?  What's happening here?  Instead of finishing, you take a bow before walking off and reverting yourself, though your mind is already trying to think of another protest song...</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>They're back; they transform you again and your peaceful outlook returns. This time you know it will be permanent.  A dying voice suggests you should be quite angry with them, but as of now you can only see them as a supporter of this awful war; you'll need to show them the light.   "Imagine there's no magic," you tell them, "It won't be hard at all.  If you have need of clothing... just go shopping at the mall."  They look unconvinced, though extremely happy about something.  "Imagine Vamp and Kitsu, sharing all the streets..."  At this point they're almost laughing at your efforts. You aren't singing THAT off-key, are you?  You finish:   "You may say I'm a dreamer... I may be the only one.  But I hope someday you'll join me." With this, you pose seductively at them, looking square into their eyes. "We'll have just so much fun!"  You wink at them and their good humor seems to darken just a bit...</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>In this city, there are battle lines being drawn. Nobody's right, everybody's wrong.  Your musing is interrupted - what's that sound?  Oh, yet another mage, quite likely showing up to turn you into a pair of high heels or something. The paranoia is striking deep, the thoughts creeping into your mind.  Barely realizing you're doing it you project a sense of passiveness, of tranquility into your opponent's mind and instead of attacking you, they wander off.  Whew.  If they return, perhaps more drastic measures can be taken?</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>You see the enemy again. This time you are confident that you will stop them from being a threat, perhaps permanently.  "Good morning, starshine," you greet them, "your friend says hello."  They freeze in place as  you stand trembling above them, as they trembling below,  "If it's hard  for me to free your mind, I'll change your body instead," you muse while considering that a weaker body may help in your efforts.  Continuing, “First, how about some hair down to... there," it grows several inches.  "No, shoulder-length, longer ... gleaming, streaming, flaxen, waxen!"  Their hair continues to explode outward, becoming long and blonde, moving further and further down their back.  "And some more curves, let's see,” you think.  Pointing to their chest:  "Here, baby" - and it inflates, to a full D-cup.  Pointing to their hips:   "There, mama," Her hips expand, her waist contracts, her ass grows to a pleasing feminine shape. Her groin, if not already feminine, becomes so.   Then you gesture wide:  "Everywhere, daddy, daddy, her whole body seems to shrink and grow thinner until she takes on the appearance of a college age girl.  Even as she seems to start believing this is her true form, the changes start reverting on their own, though you suspect they will come back if she troubles you again...</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>You find your opponent again and greet... her?  Well, definitely her  after you start chanting:  "Look at yourself, look at yourself, young  girl," she is immediately paralyzed as you continue, indeed looking  down to see her young, thin body and pulling a long blonde strand of  flower-strewn hair from her face.  The spell continues as wordless nonsense, "Gliddy gloop gloopy, nibby nobby nooby, la la la lo lo," as you continue you see her eyes fog up as occasions and persuasions begin to clutter her mind.  You can almost feel her good sense under assault as her mind is crippled with a new innocence.  Thoughts of dead kings and many other things she can't define; glimpses into her psyche of peppermints, incense, and... the color of time?  She's turned out, tuned in, and turned your eyes around; she continues to look at herself, as you slowly walk away...</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>You find her again; subtle waves of magic return her to the same young female form, turning her mind back to where it once belonged.  You decide to change her mind with a simple debate “Imagine there's no Heaven," she begins, though anyone would find that extremely hard to do.   The town is full of succubi, angels, and valkyries, too. Still, it is a thought; all of those supernatural enemies are causing a lot of damage, inflicting great carnage on the town.  "War," you accidentally say aloud as you muse.  Covering yourself, you ask her: "What is it good for?"  Unhesitatingly, in a high-pitched voice she replies: "Absolutely nothing."  Surprised, you ask her to say it again, but you seem to have broken the spell.  As she slowly changes back, you can tell that while she still thinks there is a time for hate, there is also a time for love, a time for peace... you swear that if you encounter her again soon, it may be too late for her to turn back.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>You see her again and think she may well be ready to give peace a chance.   As soon as you give her body and mind back, she begins to question you, practically singing.  "How many roads must a man walk down before she’s no longer a man?"  You smile at the emotion behind her words.   "How many lives must be lost to these spells, 'til bras are again sewn by hand?"  Your smile widens, seeing her commitment.  "And how many souls must the bimbo balls claim before they are finally banned?"  Your grin stretches from ear to ear; she may never lift a finger against you again.  "The answer, my friend, is..." she hesitates, "the answer is...  is..." Your grin breaks as you see her brow furrowed, trying to think  of the answer; even as you see wind blowing through her long hair, you  see her realizing what must have happened.  Though, as she changes back and walks off, you hear her humming a tune, already thinking of a new protest song ...</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>You find her again, and just know that this time, the magic will set in be permanently.  She glares at you, belying your thoughts - but it soon  becomes clear she sees you not as a feared opponent, but merely a  support of the awful war, whose mind must be changed.  "Imagine there’s no magic," she tells you, "It won't be hard at all.  If you have need of clothing... just go shopping at the mall."  Hmm.  Well, at least she’s not going to attack.   "Imagine Vamp and Kitsu sharing all the streets..."  You laugh a bit.  Yes, you'll be fine.   "You may say I'm a dreamer... I may be the only one.  But I hope someday you'll join me." With this, she poses seductively at you, looking square into their eyes, “and we'll have just so much fun!"  She winks at you, darkening your mood just a bit. She's NOT going to be able to make you join her... Is she?</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
