<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>You're hit with a very odd spell. At first you don't notice anything, but slowly a blanket of innocence and curiosity begins to snuggle your brain. You giggle and skip around a little, bending over to look at something on the ground. While your busy observing a very interesting ant, your fail to notice as a short, roppey tail sprout from above your rump. Your new tail sprout short soft grey fur and gains a cute little black tuft at the end of it. Once your interesting ant disappears into a hole you snap out of your mental stupor, quickly changing yourself back, trying to hide your tail from your opponent as it dwindles away.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>Once more the spell hits you, the cuddly blanket of bliss surrounding your mind once again. This time you wiggle in place, your tail quickly regrowing and causing you to giggle as you give it a little tug. When you tug your tail and involuntary bray slips out of your mouth, revealing that your two front teeth have become bucked and cute. You blink a few times and scratch your ears, as they slowly elongate and become covered in the same soft grey fur as on your tail. You giggle as you begin to shrink a little, your clothing hanging off your form as you lose about a fourth of your old height. You groggily force yourself out of this cutsie mindset and change yourself back, feeling a little depressed at how bleak the world seems now.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>Your mind quickly becomes covered in a thick fog of young innocence. You bray cutely and drop to your hands and knees, your tail quickly resprouting and flicking to and fro in excitement. You begin to shrink once again, braying in cute frustration as you begin to wriggle free from your baggy clothes. As you kick your pants and undies off you flash your opponent as your gender quickly becomes apparent as female, your cute little cunny and pucker hiding under your tail. You cringe a little as your face begins to push out into a little snout, covered in soft grey fur. You bray one last time before your human mind regains control. You sit up and cover your nakedness as your change yourself back to normal and quickly redress.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>You shiver, beginning to shrink down to the size of a foal. You bray and wriggle cutely out of your clothes, your tush in the air as you finally wiggle out of your shirt. You sit down on your fuzzy rump, letting out a cute bray as you watch your feet and legs change into proper hind legs. You get wobbly to your hands and new hooves, taking a few careful steps forwardsbefore flopping back onto your rump. You bray in annoyance, wanting front hooves as well. But as soon as you tell yourself you wanted the changes to go further your humanity returned. You change back much slower this time and sit there dazed, not even bothering to redress right away as you try to collect your human life and memories.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>You feel so free as your changed once again, shrinking into a cute little foal. This time getting free from your oversized clothing is easier and you once more sit down on your rump, watching as fur spread over your belly and arms, your hands clenching into hooves. You bray in delight and hop to all fours, beginning to prance and frolic around as your mind is reduced more and more into a happy little jenny. You sniff at things and looks at your opponent with wide curious eyes, wanting them to pet your ears and keep you safe. But that though feels wrong to you somehow. With a final heave of your human self, you find yourself slowly changing back to normal over the course of five minutes. Soon you are laying naked on the ground, looking up at your opponent pleadingly, knowing that one or two more hits and you will be trapped as the adorable little donkey forever.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>You feel your mind almost immediately snuffed out and replaced with the mind of a newborn donkey foal. You bray cutely as you shrink and drop to all fours, wriggling free from those stinky human clothes you were wearing. You feel so free and happy, beginning to prance around again before finally stopping to graze of a patch of grass you found. You bray cutely once more as a butterfly catches your attention and you chase after it a little ways, before bumping into a human, staring down at you with a smug look on their face. You look up at them cutely and they pet your head, quickly causing you to forget what was bothering you and lean into the petting. You love life so much as an adorable little donkey.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>Your spell hits it's mark. At first, it looks like nothing is happening, but then your opponent giggles and skips around a little, bending over to look at something on the ground. While they busy observing a very interesting ant, they fail to notice as a short, roppey tail sprout from above their rump. Their new tail sprout short soft grey fur and gains a cute little black tuft at the end of it. Once their interesting ant disappears into a hole they snap out of their mental stupor, quickly changing back, trying to hide their tail from you as it dwindles away. Either your opponent suffers from ADD or the spell had some mental changes with it.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>Once more the spell hits your opponent. You can only assume the same mental changes return with it. This time they wiggle in place, their tail quickly regrowing and causing them to giggle as they give it a little tug. Definitely not the reaction you'd expect from an enemy. When they tug their tail an involuntary bray slips out of their mouth, revealing that their two front teeth have become bucked and cute. They blink a few times and scratch their ears, as they slowly elongate and become covered in the same soft grey fur as on their tail. They giggle as they begin to shrink a little, their clothing hanging off their form as they lose about a fourth of their old height. They groggily force them-self out of this cutsie mindset and change them-self back, feeling a little depressed at how bleak the world seems now.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>Their brain is quickly affected by your spell again. You. Can see it in your target's eyes. They bray cutely and drop to their hands and knees, their tail quickly resprouting and flicking to and fro in excitement. They begin to shrink once again, braying in cute frustration as they begin to wriggle free from their baggy clothes. As they kick their pants and undies off, they flash you as their gender quickly becomes apparent as female, their cute little cunny and pucker hiding under their tail. They cringe a little as their face begins to push out into a little snout, covered in soft grey fur. They bray one last time before their human mind regains control. They sit up and cover their nakedness as they change back to normal and quickly redress.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>They shiver, beginning to shrink down to the size of a foal. They bray and wriggle cutely out of their clothes, their tush in the air as they finally wiggle out of their shirt. They sit down on their fuzzy rump, letting out a cute bray as they watch their feet and legs change into proper hind legs. They get wobbly to their hands and new hooves, taking a few careful steps forwards before flopping back onto their rump. They bray in annoyance at the difficulty they are having moving. They don't have to deal with it for long since they start changing them-self back. They change back much slower this time and sit there dazed, not even bothering to redress right away as they try to collect their human life and memories.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>You change your opponent once again, shrinking them into a cute little foal. This time getting free from their oversized clothing looks easier and they once more sit down on their rump, watching as fur spread over their belly and arms, their hands clenching into hooves. They bray in delight and hop to all fours, beginning to prance and frolic around as their mind is reduced more and more into a happy little jenny. They sniff at things and looks at their opponent with wide curious eyes. With a final heave of their human self, they find them-self slowly changing back to normal over the course of five minutes. Soon they are laying naked on the ground, looking up at you pleadingly, knowing that one or two more hits and they will be trapped as the adorable little donkey forever.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>You see your opponent's eyes go blank as your spell hits them. They bray cutely as they shrink and drop to all fours, wriggling free from those stinky human clothes they were wearing. They look so free and happy, beginning to prance around again before finally stopping to graze of a patch of grass they found. They bray cutely once more as a butterfly catches their attention and they chase after it a little ways, before bumping into you. You can't help but stare down at them with a smug look on your face. They look up at you cutely and you pet their head, quickly causing them to forget what was bothering them and lean into the petting. They seem to love life so much as an adorable little donkey.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
