<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>With an especially perverse look in their eye, an enemy mage unleashes an incantation on you - the words sound vaguely Japanese, though the inflections sound subtly ... wrong.  You begin to sweat profusely as you feel your arms lengthen, maybe half again their old size ... but that seems to be all.  The spell is easy enough to break; you would have done so instantly, if you weren't momentarily distracted by some of the beautiful women around you ...
</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>Your opponent continues their pseudo-Japanese chanting - though you idly think to yourself that "f'htagn" really sounds out of place for the language as you begin to sweat again, coating your skin in an oily sheen.  (Wait, where did your clothes go?)  Suddenly, you seem to be ... taller?  No ... along with your arms, your legs have grown this time ... but your torso seems to be shrinking.  At least your groin appears to be the same - though it looks extremely aroused; in fact, once you get over the shock and fear, you can't help but feel your mind turn to thoughts of sex.  Particularly with some of those schoolgirls ... Shaking your head, you are able to break free from the spell.
</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>The chant continues, and as the familiar oily sweat resumes - does your skin look PINK under it? - you fall flat on your ass; your whole body shrinking even as your arms and legs grow proportionately. You bend your head down - something quite hard to do as your neck seems to have almost vanished - to look in horror at a completely smooth groin.  "This won't do at all", you think, and with an effort of will, two enormous phalluses burst forth.  Your thoughts turn to using them in all sorts of perverse ways, when it finally hits you - this isn't your true body.  Sheepishly, you gather your will and return to your old form.
</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>Again the chanting starts, and at first you are eager - but soon a wave of fear overtakes you, as your head shrinks into the ball of your torso, leaving you blind to the world.  But soon, eyes blink open - far more than 2 - and you realize you are looking out at many angles from the blob of your main body.  Other than arms and legs - which have lost hands, feet, fingers and toes - there is no distinguishing feature of your body at all - just the pink oily eyeball-studded blob, with quite a few long growths coming out of it, almost like ... tentacles.  Hmm.  Concentrating, you grow a pair of dicks again, letting them be long, flexible, fleshy tubes, just like the remains of your arms and legs ... you can just imagine them extending, binding a nice schoolgirl's legs, reaching up under her short skirt to find ...   And just as suddenly, almost to your disappointment, the magic fades.
</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>You barely even hear the chanting, as your body shrinks again, morphing into the lustful tentacle beast.  You'd be moaning happily, but with your body essentially a gelatinous blob apart from the writhing tentacles, only the expression in your many eyes gives away your lusty state.  Well that, and the fact that most of your tentacles are writhing around, swelling as any humanoid dick would on arousal, growing to many times their resting state in length and girth.  An almost overwhelming desire for them to find a willing (or not-so-willing) partner to mate with, to fill completely, consumes what is left of your mind ... yet something whispers to you that you are not yet whole, not yet fully fertile.  Sighing, you allow the magic to fade from you, knowing you need only another quick boost or two, to finally be complete ... </TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>The chanting reaches its crescendo, and you return to your betentacled body.  You feel - full? - inside, and an outside observer could see through your slightly translucent skin that you have gained what was still missing - a large pile of eggs now sit within you, ready for implantation into new hosts.  Such as the mage chanting at you.  Swiftly, you approach - tentacles extending, ready to tie them down, to force your spawn within them.  Perhaps after a bit of fun they will let you go, to 'lick' the city at will; or perhaps if you do a good job, they will keep you around - 'tame' you, letting you focus your efforts primarily on your new 'owner'.  "Time will tell" passes through the fading remnants of your brain, as your tentacles begin their first act of penetration...</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>You approach a likely-looking victim, eager to create a tentacled monstrosity ... whether to promote chaos by letting it roam free in the city, or for your own personal use ... you have yet to decide.  You begin chanting the words of the spell - they sound vaguely Japanese, but with a bit of an otherworldly inflection.  Your enemy starts to sweat profusely, but other than that and a slight lengthening to their arms, you see little change about them.  Though you do notice them staring at some of the local women, distracted so much as to take their time with the counterspell...
</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>You continue your chanting.  Hmm, how do you pronounce "f'htagn" anyway?  No matter - your guess appeared to be close enough, as your opponent begins to change again.  An oily sheen of sweat coats their skin, as you see both their arms and legs extending far beyond their former, their clothes dissolving away as their torso begins to shrink.  A look at their groin is enough to tell they are obviously very aroused, but this can be seen in their eyes as well - at least until they shake their head and return to their former state.
</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>You continue the chant, watching as the oily slime covers your victim's now pink skin.  They fall flat on their ass, their whole body starting to shrink, even as their limbs grow hugely in proportion to their body.  You notice them looking down at their groin - something hard to do with practically no neck - and look aghast at their current total lack of genitalia.  And then, something you don't think was in the spell happens - you see them concentrate, summoning forth a pair of enormous phalluses ... of their own free will?  You look at them a bit worriedly, but are relieved to see them snap back to themselves, returning to their humanoid form.  Maybe ... maybe this wasn't such a good idea.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Against your better judgement, you resume the chant, watching your opponent shrink down again, this time all the way into an amorphous pink blob.  Their four limbs grow and reshape - hands, feet, fingers and toes all vanish, leaving them with four large ... tentacles.  Just as you are thinking you wished you could see the look on your victim's face, numerous eyes blink open all around the blob of their main body, as they begin to stare lustfully.  At you?  No, just at the world in general; their own magic causes two large phallic-shaped tentacles to burst forth from where their groin should be, and they seem to just be lying there, fantasizing, tentacles pulsing ... until the magic fades away on its own.
</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>The monster you are creating looks like it may be quite dangerous; not only to the town as a whole, but to you in particular.  Nevertheless, you can't seem to stop yourself from continuing the chant; and soon enough, your victim's body returns to that pink, tentacle-covered blob you are coming to know quite well.  It looks at you lasciviously through its many eyes, waving its increasingly phallic looking tentacles about; you watch each grow to many times their resting size in width and girth as it becomes more and more aroused.  However, something still seems to not be completely right ... it is not yet complete ... and the magic fades away, leaving you to let out a sigh of relief.  You realize that if you can't stop yourself soon, that terror will be on the loose...</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>You simply can't stop yourself; you complete the chant, and a tentacle beast stands before you.  You see what was missing through its translucent pink skin ... a large pile of eggs, ready to implant within a willing (or not-so-willing) host.  Such as ... "oh fuck!" you exclaim, as the beast launches itself at you, tying you down with its many lengthening tentacles, some of them already working their way up your legs ...  Perhaps it would be best to flee the scene, let this one go free; though if you are particularly brave (or foolhardy), you suppose you could try to tame the mighty beast...</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
