<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<Description>While this being was once human, now they are a large collection of pink goo. Because they have to concentrate so hard to pool themselves into a humanoid form, movement is rather difficult for them. In addition, they leave a trail of pink goo behind themselves, making it easy for people to follow. Due to various mental changes, they can't seem to pick a form that's anything except for a voluptuous woman. This "body" is translucent pink, including the parts that have the appearance of being hair. Constantly aroused their ability to resist further changes from spell hits has been reduced. On the upside, being in this form seems to have boosted their magic abilities significantly, and their fluid form makes it easier to dodge spells.</Description>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>You see your opponent cast a spell at you, throwing a pink bubble at you! When it hits, it pops! Other than your skin turning slightly pink, nothing seems to happen. Just in case, you cast a reversal spell on yourself.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>Your opponent throws another pink bubble at you, the bubble popping as it hits you! Once again your skin turns pink, but in addition you start sweating a pink liquid. Slightly disturbed by this turn of events, you reverse the changes.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>Your opponent sneaks up behind you and lobs a pink bubble at you. The changes occur more quickly this time, your pink skin still sweating pink liquid. Suddenly, your legs collapse, as your legs start turning into a puddle of goo! Laying in the puddle of goo, you manage to cast a reversal spell and return to your previous form, still feeling a bit unsteady.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>You feel another pink bubble burst against your skin, and you collapse to the ground, turning into a puddle of pink goo! You concentrate, and realize that you can control the puddle's movement. After a few moments of experimenting, you will yourself to form into a humanoid form. While your body is still completely made out of pink goo and your body shape has changed somewhat, at least in this state you're able to cast spells again! You cast a reversal spell on yourself. It takes a little while for your body to return back to normal, and you're still shaken from the experience.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>Yet another pink bubble bursts against your skin! Somewhat expecting it this time, and you collapse into a puddle of pink goo. Knowing what to expect, you control the goo, changing back into a humanoid form capable of casting spells. However as you prepare to cast the reversal spell, a small part of you can't help but wonder what it would be like to have some fun like this. As you slide across the ground looking for someone to have some fun with, you realize what you're doing and force yourself to stop, and cast a reversal spell. You're not sure if you'll be able to resist if you're hit again, even back to normal you're beginning to fantasize what it's like to be a goo girl and wrap yourself around someone.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>Feeling another pink bubble bursts against your skin, you collapse into a puddle of pink goo. Once more  you control the goo, changing back into a goo girl form capable of casting spells. Giggling, you decide that you may as well have some fun before changing back. You know that you should be resisting these mental changes, but as you slide around looking for somebody to wrap yourself around, your last bit of resistance breaks, and you realize that it's not really so bad being made of goo.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>You feel another pink bubble burst against your skin, and you collapse to the ground, turning into a puddle of pink goo! You concentrate, and realize that you can control the puddle's movement. After a few moments of experimenting, you will yourself to form into your normal form. You look down and realize that you didn't turn yourself into a male body, but instead a voluptuous pink goo girl form! Concentrating a little bit more, you force your body to change back into a male form. Now that you're in your normal form, you cast a reversal spell to turn your goo body back into flesh. It takes a little while for your body returns back to normal, and you're still quite shaken from the experience.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>Yet another pink bubble bursts against your skin! Somewhat expecting it this time, and you collapse into a puddle of pink goo. Knowing what to expect, you control the goo, changing back into a human-like form capable of casting spells, deciding to concentrate on being male. However as you are pooling yourself together, a small part of you can't help but wonder what it would be like to have some fun as a goo girl. This breaks your concentration, causing you to fall back to goo girl form. As you slide across the ground looking for someone to have some fun with, you suddenly realize what you're doing and force yourself to stop and cast a reversal spell. You're not sure if you'll be able to resist if you're hit again; even back to normal you're beginning to fantasize what it's like to be a goo girl and wrapping yourself around someone.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>Spotting a potential new victim, you throw a bubble of pink goo at your target! When it hits, it pops! Unfortunately, other than their skin turning slightly pink nothing seems to happen. You see them cast a reversal spell, quickly reverting their skin.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>You throw another bubble of pink goo at your victim, the bubble popping as it hits them. Once again their skin turns pink; in addition, they start sweating a pink liquid. They appear to be slightly disturbed by this turn of events, and reverse the changes.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>You sneak up behind your victim and lob another pink goo bubble at them. The changes occur more quickly this time, their pink skin still sweating pink liquid. Suddenly, their legs collapse as their legs start turning into a puddle of goo! You see them laying in the puddle of goo, managing, with a bit of effort, to cast a reversal spell and returning to their previous form. They look a bit unsteady after this ordeal.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Another pink bubble burst against your victim's skin. You watch as they collapse to the ground, turning into a puddle of pink goo! The puddle remains motionless for a while, but then after few moments it starts to shift into into a form somewhat resembling their previous body, just made completely out of translucent pink goo.  They cast a reversal spell on themselves, which takes some time to take effect. Your victim appears to be visibly shaken by the incident.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Yet another pink bubble bursts against your victim's skin. Once again, they quickly collapse into a puddle of pink goo. This time they seem to have better mastered controlling the goo, and they change back into humanoid form much faster. You can see that the mental changes have began however, as you notice that they have a somewhat dazed look, lusting after some of the other people in the vicinity. Just as they start to slide across the ground towards one of the nearby people, your victim appears to realize what they're doing and forces themselves to stop. Shortly afterwards, they manage to cast a reversal spell. You're pretty sure that the changes will stick permanently after just one or two more casts.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>You throw one more pink goo bubble against your victim, once more causing them to collapse into a puddle of pink goo. A few seconds later, they form back into a goo girl body. You notice them giggling before they start sliding around the room, looking for a target for their new found desires. Your work here appears to be complete, as they make no attempt to revert back to their previous form.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>Another pink bubble bursts against your victim's skin. You watch as they collapse to the ground, turning into a puddle of pink goo! The puddle remains motionless for a while, but then after few moments it starts to shift into into a voluptuous goo girl! They look down in shock, and then close their eyes with a look of intense concentration, forcing their body to change back into male form. Afterwards, they cast a reversal spell to turn their goo body back into flesh. It takes a little while before their body returns back to normal, and they appear to be quite shaken from the experience.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>Yet another pink bubble bursts against your victim's skin. Once again, they quickly collapse into a puddle of pink goo. This time they seem to have better mastered controlling the goo, and they change back into humanoid form much faster. You can see that the mental changes have began however, as you notice that they have a somewhat dazed look, lusting after some of the other people in the area. In addition, they don't seem to notice that they are still in a female goo girl form. Just as they start to slide across the ground towards one of the nearby people, your victim appears to realize what they're doing and forces themselves to stop. Shortly afterwards, they manage to cast a reversal spell. You're pretty sure that the changes will stick permanently after just one or two more casts.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>

</Form>
