<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>Your opponent shouts some nonsense word at you, distracting you just enough to be hit by a spell. A tingle travels over your body as your skin starts to itch. You roll up your sleeves to get ready to show your enemy how it is done when you pause. Are your arms hairier? Deciding to be better safe than sorry, you cast a reversal spell on yourself...</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>Wondering why your opponent is waving their hands around like a fool, you miss when their spell hits you. A strong tingle engulfs your body, and you can feel hair starting to grow. Everywhere. This isn't hair, it's fur! Taking a look at your skin, you can see that indeed you're covered in soft white fur. Is this that rabbit spell again? Running your tongue over your teeth, you find a few more pointed than you recall, throwing out the idea they are trying to turn you into a herbivore. With ease you reverse the spell, though the change back seems to take a bit...</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>Wondering how they pulled a coin out of your ear, your opponent suddenly hits you with a spell! An intense burning sensation runs through your body as the magic washes over you. You notice you're completely covered in white fur now. No, it's not just colored white, there's black stripes there as well. Like a tiger. Yes, a strong and majestic animal. You lash your tail at the thought of stalking prey among the jungle. Wait, tail? Noticing the new appendage snaps you out of your daydream and you quickly counter the spell. Just what is wrong with you?</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>Somehow your opponent just showed you the card you were thinking of! Amazing! And then they hit you with a spell, the jerk. As the magic connects, you feel it hard to stand on two legs anymore, and drop to your hands and knees. Well, not exactly hands and knees anymore, just four legs with paws on the end. You glance back at your body to see the white and black stripe fur covering you and a long tail swaying behind. You feel your strong muscles ripple beneath your fur. And why shouldn't they? You've spent years hunting and capturing prey, so of course you've developed them nicely. But suddenly a voice cries out in your mind that this isn't right and you counter the spell, returning to your previous form. Your ungainly, weak form...</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>Distracted at trying to figure out how those solid rings could link together, you miss when a spell from an opponent strikes you. The bright flash hurts your eyes a moment and you use your foreleg to rub at your face and muzzle, tail lashing angrily. A growl rumbles from your throat as you contemplate showing this pesky human just who is boss, but then you remember that it's them. After all, they're the ones who feed you and take care of you, and even let you help out in their fantastic magic shows. It's actually not a bad life when you get down to it. Maybe the flash in your eyes was just an accident as they try a new trick? But just as you calm down, you suddenly realize what's wrong! You're not some sort of pet show tiger! And with that realization you reverse the spell. It takes a lot of willpower, and you can feel yourself missing that strong form and the cheer of the crowd from the shows...</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>A burst of light and smoke engulfs you, but you don't mind, you've seen it before. Hundreds of times during the stage shows in Vegas or other small venues. After all, as a rare white tiger, people just can't get enough of your mysterious and magical nature. On or off the stage. And even though you've been pampered, you haven't forgotten what you are at your core. A jungle predator, who can stalk and kill with the best of them. As you get a few whiffs of the surrounding area, you can just tell there's a lot of prey out there, and you're eager to hunt...</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>You shout the single word for the spell, distracting your opponent enough to land a hit! The magic washes over them and it seems like they are getting bulkier and a little bit hairier. At first they don't notice, but then they look at their arms in confusion, realizing something is off. They counter the spell, quickly returning to normal...</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>A complex pattern of hand signals confuses your opponent, allowing you to slip the spell past their defenses. A thin layer of fur quickly covers their body, a striped pattern appearing in a few areas. You see them lick their teeth, many of which look quite sharp, before they cast a reversal spell and return their body to normal...</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>"Why what's that behind your ear?" you say as you suddenly produced a palmed coin to your opponent. Surprised, they don't even move as you hit them with the spell. Thick, white fur covers their body, black stripes appearing as well to give their coat a pattern like a tiger. They stare at the hair, seeming to be lost in thought, as a tail grows out just above their rear and starts to swish back and forth. With a look of surprise they finally notice the tail and quickly reverse the changes...</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Using some false shuffles and cuts, you show your opponent a card you forced them to pick to begin with. As they look on in astonishment, you hit them with this spell right in the face. They fall to their hands and knees as the magic works. Or should you say paws? Their body takes on a definite feline appearance as white fur with black stripes covers them, a tail sprouting out from behind them. They stand there a few moments, tail swaying back and forth when suddenly their slitted eyes widen and they start to change back to their former self. It takes longer than you'd expect and they gaze at themselves like their body is all wrong...</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Using a bit of flair and some magic trick rings, you dazzle your opponent and then hit them squarely in the chest with this spell. Their body reforms and shapes as they are suddenly sitting on their hindquarters, completely changed into a magical white tiger. They seem to be rubbing their muzzle with one of their forelegs and then look up at you. You hear a growl starting to form, seeing their tail twitch agitatedly, and you think a moment that turning someone into a large predator might not be a good idea when they suddenly blink their feline eyes and merely stare at you docilely, like any trained pet should. You're about to give them a pat on the head when their eyes widen in shock and they start to change back to their former self. They look greatly confused and sad, as if they didn't really mean to reverse the spell...</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>With some smoke and mirrors (well, mostly just smoke) you hit your opponent with this spell! Their body contorts and changes until sitting before you is a large and majestic white tiger! They lazily swing their tail from side to side, waiting for your command, or next big show in Vegas. But then they begin to sniff the air and get to their feet, looking like they want to do a little hunting first. Hopefully they won't forget who's the boss as you call them to heel. Last thing you need is an angry, or hungry, tiger on your hands.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
