<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>Your opponent forms a little ball of pure white energy and throws it at you at a low speed. You easily dodge the projectile, which strongly looked like a little bunch of white rags.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>Once again, your rival throws you another whitish projectile you easily avoid, but you've been outsmarted as a second projectile hits you right in the belly. It slowly materializes into a white frilly apron and ties itself at your back. You reach behind and simply pull on a ribbon to untie the bow and then it vanishes into thin air. You really have to sharpen those reflexes!</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>Your reflexes fail you as you tire of dodging all those spell projectiles. This time, the apron ties itself strongly at your back and all your clothing get magically torn apart by invisible scissors. Your body darkens at an impressive pace and becomes black and shiny. You touch your torso and feel the cold and soft material forming on you, satin. You take a closer look and see the tips of your fingers caressing your chest flattening and becoming white lace. With a chant of protection, you stop whatever transformation is happening to you, though you have a good idea of what you were becoming...</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>This time, not only the apron ties itself easily around your waist, but it lifts you in the air. Your whole skin turns into jet black satin, while your fingers totally dissolve into a white layer of frills surrounding each wrist. Same thing goes for your legs as your feet turn into white lacy frills. Your tights slowly fuse together at your crotch, forcing you to close your legs together. You can feel your arms and your unique leg slowly hollowing, the skin collapsing on itself and forming sleeves and the hem of a skirt. Your opponent is really trying to turn you into a French maid dress! You quickly cast a counterspell, but can't help being aroused by thoughts of a maid mincing around in a sexy dress...
</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>You let the apron lift you in the air like a rag doll, tired of fighting. The thought of being worn by a maid seems to have settled in your mind. You can't help but smile as you foresee you as the center of attraction of a well-loved fantasy. You're aroused thinking about all those hands that will soon caress your satiny body. Meanwhile, your transformation accelerates even more. Your legs have already merged, flattened and shrunk into a small black skirt with white frills at the hem. Your arms are also shrinking and forming very short cap sleeves. You feel your whole body hollowing out and your head slowly sinking in. A layer of white frills appears over your head, ready to form the collar of the dress, when you suddenly realize you're not quite ready to be part of that fantasy this way. With a last effort, you revert back to normal.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>This is it. You can't take it anymore. You open your arms in resignation and let the apron wrap itself around your waist one last time. Your skin turns in black shiny satin almost instantly. Your legs merge so quickly it looks like they have exploded into a short skirt. Your arms recess into short cap sleeves which will show your new owner's delicate shoulder. A layer of white frills appears over your head, which quickly sinks into your torso, forming a low neck collar. The spell finishes transforming your body by turning your face into a cute white bow in the middle of the collar. You delicately drop on the floor, ready for a maid to claim you.  As you are picked up, you realized how sensitive you are, mostly at each opening of the dress where frills are tickled by the air moving over them. A strong feeling of humility engulfs you as you adjust to your new vocation. You know that after a dirty fight, broken pieces need to be picked up, and you can't think of anybody doing it without you.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>You struggle to cast this complex spell which requires you to focus some of your naughtiest thoughts into a projectile of pure lust energy. After a new moment, you manage to throw the ball of whitish energy to your opponent, but it moves so slowly your opponent dodges it with ease. </TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>You're getting more comfortable at forming those projectiles, but they still move too slowly. Wisely, you think of decoy strategy and throw a second ball. Your opponent dodges the first projectile by jumping in front of the second one. A small white lacy apron materializes around the waist of your target, but they simply untie the bows at the back to make it disappear.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>You can see your opponent is tiring and won't be able to dodge your next projectile, which you are now throwing much faster. The apron materializes itself just in front of your target and wraps itself around their waist. Everything your opponent was wearing gets torn into shreds by invisible scissors, leaving only the apron to hide the secret garden. Your target's skin starts to darken at an impressive pace, becoming all black and shiny. Your opponent starts to caress the satin, and you can almost perceive a smile on their face before returning to normal, well, normal but naked, self....</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>This time, you can feel the apron forming in your hand, ready to catch your opponent as you throw it towards them. Your throw is so fast and strong it lifts your target in the air and holds them in levitation. You can see your opponent's skin turning jet back satin and their hands turning into white laces around their wrists.  Same thing goes for their legs, as you see their feet turning into white lacy frills. The legs also seem to be fusing slowly together to form a long skirt. Your target also starts to loose some mass, while in fact, they are hollowing from the inside out. The transformation is well under way, until your opponent snaps out of trance and reverts back to normal.  </TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>On again, you easily throw a magical apron at your target. Your opponent does not even put up a fight and is lifted up in the air by the apron securing itself around their waist. Black satin spreads from the apron in a fraction of second. Their legs merge together and shrink into a small skirt with a white lace trim. Their hands also turn into white lace trim around their wrists, but this time, their arms crawl back into very short sleeves. A lovely crown of lace appears over your opponent's head and you can't help but notice the arousal on their face. As you start thinking about finding a girl who will be willing to wear such a demeaning dress, your opponent finds the strength to revert to normal.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>You throw one last apron at your victim, who opens their arms wide, forfeiting the fight.  Your opponent's skin turns instantly in a black shiny satin. Their legs merge so quickly they simply explode into a skirt. Their arms shrink into very short cap sleeves, leaving no room for imagination. A crown of white frills appears over your victim's head, which quickly sinks into the torso, forming a very low neck collar. This dress hollows and delicately drops on the ground, and the transformation is finished. You walk to the dress to pick up your prize. You grab the dress and start feeling the satin material with your hand, which slowly arouses you. Suddenly, you realize how dirty this fight has left the area...</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
