<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>A haze appears in the air, sights shifting as a dark corridor forms around you. It isn't there, merely an illusion, but the stone walls and deep shadows seem to strike a chord within you, as if they are somehow familiar...
Your body reacts to these visions, tingling as coarse hair covers you from head to toe. A deep, musky scent catches your nose, nostrils flaring and widening. You quickly shake your head, an action which feels unusually difficult due to the sudden impression of a great weight, dispelling the effects.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>The illusion seems stronger this time, the cold of its crypt like structure causing you to shiver briefly before your fur returns. The changes seem more pronounced this time, in line with the growing strength of the spell. Your body convulses, sensations of thickening and growth across your limbs. You stumble, but do not fall, watching with surprise as the ground moves further away, reaching an impressive seven feet. You take stock of your figure, noticing you have become much larger, now bristling with muscle. Your mind remains unaffected however, merely confused as to why your opponent would cast this. Maybe it has some form of mental effects? You slowly wave your arms and cast the counter spell, momentarily forgetting it, your arms now so large the spell is crudely made, poorly formed by your brutish hands.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>These stone walls now scream home to you, knowing full well that you had not seen them until a short while ago. You grunt with discomfort as the changes occur again, your arm now able to brush against the cold stone roof. The concept of being able to touch the illusion is lost to you, your thoughts slowing into contemplative silence. You sit on the ground, your size easily larger than the average person even now. You can feel the spell, the mental changes and its effects, but the need to prevent it does not seem necessary, so you simply observe. You cross your arms, contemplating upon the structure of the spell used upon you, analysing its structure so you may think about its purpose later on. With a deep sigh, the wind of which almost knocks another man over, you stand and reverse the changes, merely to witness it again more fully. </TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>You rest your head on your fist, unconsciously performing the traditional thinker's pose. You barely notice the effects of the spell upon you, preferring to concentrate upon the spell itself. The structure is clear to you and its purpose, though you have yet to see its end result. Something appears to be off at the end, unusual and at odds with the rest of its use, which has so far only increased your intellectual faculties, if at the cost of your original form. You consider your surroundings, now physically present in some form of corridor. It reminds you of the Labyrinth, briefly causing you to recall the story of the Minotaur. As if on cue, two spikes of pain shoot forth from the sides of your head, the skin hardening and lightening into an off white. A deep crack resounds through your skull as two horns push themselves outward, vicious and sharp. Your passive face reveals nothing of the humour you feel inside at the irony of your previous comment, enough to drive your thoughts towards cleansing yourself once more. </TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>The appearance of the labyrinth is comforting, but its appearance shimmers and wavers as you can see its very weave, the spell no longer capable of fooling a mind so observant and deep in thought. You are mildly interested as the last of the spell takes effect, wishing to see why it was so different from the rest. The dull ache immediately returns, your horns thickening considerably, curving forwards like those of a bull. The labyrinth illusion dispels itself, reforming into images of beautiful women in front of your eyes. Normally, this would have no effect upon you, but some aspect of these visions is enticing, your cold and analytical mind quickly succumbing to lust. Your clothes fall away, a loin cloth covering what is quickly becoming a significant addition to you. It is brushed aside by the rising penis, reaching a full foot in length as it sticks out accusingly at the illusory women. One hand reaches for your member whilst the other moves to grab one of the women, but you hold back at the last minute, dispelling the magic.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>This time the women surround you, stroking and fondling your body. The last element of the spell is clear to you now; it is designed to incite you, such as the rumoured colour red with bulls, now the sight of beautiful women affects you in a similar manner, though not with anger but mad desire. Your mind is easily capable of resisting this until the spell fully takes hold, the sight of women now driving you wild with desire, your normally intelligent mind becoming that of a rutting beast at the sight of such beauties. A ring appears in your nose, symbolising the dominance of the other mage over you, if only with this spell. You ignore it, reaching out and grabbing one of the surprisingly solid illusions, getting to work whilst all thoughts of curing yourself disappear, the other mage laughing in the distance.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>The appearance of the labyrinth is comforting, but its appearance shimmers and wavers as you can see its very weave, the spell no longer capable of fooling a mind so observant and deep in thought. You are mildly interested as the last of the spell takes effect, wishing to see why it was so different from the rest. The dull ache immediately returns, your horns thickening considerably, curving forwards like those of a bull. The labyrinth illusion dispels itself, reforming into images of beautiful women in front of your eyes. Normally, the sight of these women would not affect you, having wandered around this town for so long now, but some aspect of these visions is enticing, your cold and analytical mind quickly succumbing to lust. Your clothes fall away, a loin cloth covering what was your average member, now significantly larger. It is pushed away by your rising penis, reaching a full foot in length as it sticks out accusingly at the illusory women. One hand reaches for your member whilst the other moves to grab one of the women, but you hold back at the last minute, dispelling the magic.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>The illusion seems stronger this time, the cold of its crypt like structure causing you to shiver briefly before your fur returns. The changes seem more pronounced this time, in line with the growing strength of the spell. Your body convulses, sensations of thickening and growth across your limbs. You stumble, but do not fall, watching with surprise as the ground moves further away, reaching an impressive seven feet. You take stock of your figure, realising your femininity has been lost, now bristling with muscle. Your breasts have disappeared, replaced by a wide but flat chest, covered with a coarse brown fur. Your mind remains unaffected however, merely confused as to why your opponent would cast this. Maybe it has some form of mental affects? You slowly wave your arms and cast the counter spell, momentarily struggling with your new limbs, your arms significantly larger, having lost all femininity, replaced by these brutish fists.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>The appearance of the labyrinth is comforting, but its appearance shimmers and wavers as you can see its very weave, the spell no longer capable of fooling a mind so observant and deep in thought. You are mildly interested as the last of the spell takes effect, wishing to see why it was so different from the rest. The dull ache immediately returns, your horns thickening considerably, curving forwards like those of a bull. The labyrinth illusion dispels itself, reforming into images of beautiful women in front of your eyes. Normally, the sight of other women would not attract you, but your days as a woman appear to be over. Your clothes fall away, a loin cloth covering what is quickly becoming a significant addition to you. It is pushed away by the rising penis, reaching a full foot in length as it sticks out accusingly at the illusory women. The shock of the loss of your vagina in exchange for this obscene horse cock is quickly lost when you brush against it. You rub it briefly, proud that if you will be a man it will be an impressive one, but for now you dispel the magic, somewhat disappointed by your smaller and weaker feminine form.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>This spell is not merely a ball of energy to be thrown at your enemy, but rather a complex illusion and partial reality spell. It is quite difficult to cast for a moment, struggling with its potency. Quickly, you raise your arms and begin the illusion, the target's eyes now seeing what should be a labyrinth. This can only be partially seen by you, a vague shimmer in the air, but you only care for its effects, rather than the process. Your target snorts derisively, dispelling the enchantment.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>The spell takes a shorter period of time to cast, allowing you to focus more energy into its structure. The first few steps are merely for physical and mental changes, but the real work is at the end, reducing the danger of this mage to you considerably. You focus upon your opponent again, banishing your day dreaming. Their body shakes as it grows larger, dense muscle becoming apparent against the now dark brown skin. Your victim now resembles a vaguely ox like man, seven feet tall and bristling with muscle, a veritable pillar of masculinity. Their expression looks confused, likely wondering why you have made them so strong, but if only they knew.....</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>The target seems less confused at their surroundings, the illusion now strong enough so that even you are capable of seeing it fully. They reach out and touch some of the walls as if to confirm it before sitting down, a look of mild concentration and thought upon their face. The spell is now quickly moving into the second stage, performing improvements to their mind, at the cost of their mental speed. Creating a great philosopher was not your intention however, but unfortunately came hand in hand with what you really wanted. The Jekyll and Hyde syndrome does please you however, so the spell is mostly a success. </TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Your opponent sits upon an illusory rock and rests his chin against his hand, performing the traditional thinker's pose. You laugh briefly at the effect, but quickly begin to force more energy into the spell. It is growing closer to what you desire, but it still needs to perform its final steps to fulfill the "Minotaur" element. Your opponent does not even flinch when two large horns press forth from their head, nails blackening and skin coarsening into a hard leather. Whomever they were is gone now, no traces left of what they once were, now clearly a bull man. They stand, rising like the sun, slowly and with almost purposeful reverence of the action, as if they only do it occasionally and at great cost. With a flicker of their eyes, the spell is dispelled, though not fully. You can still see the mental changes appear to be active...</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>The labyrinth illusion seems to be losing its effect upon your target, who now gazes through it at you. It is slightly unnerving, so you happily sigh when their horns reappear, thicker and curved outwards like a bull. Finally, that is what you have been waiting for. With a flick of your hand you dispel the labyrinth, replacing it with images of beautiful women. An observer would wonder why you would do so when they appear so cold and calculating, but you are fully aware of what follows next. Their impassive face fractures a little, the wild eyed lust now apparent. The victim's clothes fall to the floor, a loin cloth now covering their crotch. It is quickly pushed aside by the largest penis you have ever seen on a two legged animal, easily a foot in length. Whatever the victim's taste before, their lust for women is readily apparent as they reach forward for one of the solid illusions, before cursing at themselves and dispelling the magic. They seem upset, but who wouldn't after losing such a magnificent tool?</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>To hasten the changes along, you command the illusions to rub against the new minotaur, hoping that it might have the desired effect of pushing them over the edge. Whilst their mind may be a wondrous thing now, the sight of any women will remove all other thought than sex. That is hardly surprising with a tool like theirs, but you will laugh every time you see it. This town is so flooded with women he won't have a chance to use his new found intelligence against you, also serving as a handy distraction to prevent him from dispelling the effects before it was too late. This monologue ends when you feel the tug of your spell, the minotaur grabbing a woman in his massive hands and getting to work. You laugh once again, as now, your work is already done.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>The spell takes a shorter period of time to cast, allowing you to focus more energy into its structure. The first few steps are merely for physical and mental changes, but the real work is at the end, reducing the danger of this mage to you considerably. You focus upon your opponent again, banishing your day dreaming. Their body shakes as it grows larger, dense muscle becoming apparent against the now dark brown skin. Their curves melt away, replaced by this thick muscle, breasts becoming pecs which could serve as the hull of a boat. Her beauty is quickly lost, somewhat to your disappointment, replaced by a heavily masculine face; Square jaw, heavy set eyes and a large nose. Gone is the veritable flower of femininity, replaced by a towering pillar of masculinity, bristling with muscle.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>The labyrinth illusion seems to be losing its effect upon your target, who now gazes through it at you. It is slightly unnerving, so you inwardly sigh in relief when their horns reappear, thicker and curved outwards like a bull. Finally, that is what you have been waiting for. With a flick of your hand you dispel the labyrinth, replacing it with images of beautiful women. An observer would wonder why you would do so when your target appears so cold and calculating, but you are fully aware of what follows next. Their impassive face fractures a little, the wild eyed lust now apparent. The victim's clothes fall to the floor, a loin cloth now covering their crotch. It is quickly pushed aside by the largest penis you have ever seen on a two legged animal, easily a foot in length. Their surprise at its appearance is replaced with lust as they rub it idly, their eyes locked on the women they are now heavily attracted to. Her days as a woman are over. The target dispels the magic once again, but this is clearly the end.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>

</Form>
