<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>You blink. Was that a spell that just hit you? You can feel the tingle of some residual magic, but you detect no other obvious effects. However, while inspecting your mind and memories more closely, you can't help dwelling on all the bad deeds you've done in your time. Suddenly realizing the effects of the spell, you quickly dispel these artificial feelings of regret.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>Without knowing why, you suddenly feel a desperate need to clean yourself. With no other tools available, you attempt to scrape away the dirt from your skin with your bare hands. The rationale part of your mind realizes how ineffectual the whole procedure is, and for now this is enough to make you snap out of it and revert the effect of the spell.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>You are overcome with a strong sense of nausea. You are disgusting. Desperate to clean yourself, you begin to tear at your skin.  You claw at your own chest, as if trying to dig out your own heart. To your surprise, you manage to rip of a patch of your skin, revealing pure white skin underneath your own.
Staring in disbelief at the hole in your chest, you manage to reclaim your senses and revert the effect of the spell. Still, you cannot help smiling. Now you know how to clean yourself.
</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>The hysteria you felt the last time the spell hit you has been replaced by a sense of calm: you know what you have to do. Starting at your shoulder, you dig your nails into your worn flesh. With almost no effort, you are able to peel off a stripe of skin from your chest, all the way down to your waist, revealing luscious pure white skin underneath. There is no pain, as your body is not yours anymore. 
As you continue to peel off your skin, a similar procedure also takes place in your mind. Old memories are discarded, replaced with a new sense of purpose. You suddenly realize that you can't even remember your own name anymore. You hesitate, and in your hesitation, you are able to somehow find strength to reverse the effects of the spell, restoring your old flesh. Still, you can't quite shake of the feeling of ineptitude. You were so close to perfection...</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>As the spell hits you this time, the effects starts to be outwardly visible. Originating from the upper-left part of your chest, your tainted flesh starts to take on a gray, dead hue. Likewise, your stained memories starts to fade from your mind. Without conscious thought, you start to rip off the dead skin from your body, bit by bit revealing the pristine white skin of a young girl. As you shed the last of your old skin, some new part of your mind excitedly expects something to happen...
Yet as it does, some deep rooted survival instinct of yours kick in. There is something foreign inside your mind! Focusing your last ounces of willpower, you manage to expel the invader and revert the changes. However, it may take a while for you to forget the warm echo of the invader's sweet voice. </TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>The spell hits you one last time. You watch expectantly as your skin dries up, the spell allocating everything that is good and healthy about your old self into forming your new body. All bodily and mental impurities are washed away as glowing cracks begin to spread across the dead husk that is your old body. You emerge like a butterfly from its chrysalis, joyously spreading your new angelic wings in flight as your voice joins the chorus of angels in your mind. 
The moment seems to last an eternity. You eventually return to the ground, where your old skin has turned into a beautiful white gown for you to cover your nakedness with: nothing wasted, nothing lost. 
You offer your thanks as prayers to the heavens, praying that the whole earth may be saved; just as you have been saved.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>You focus your transformative magic on the very soul of your target. The target seems somewhat puzzled as the spell takes its course, but otherwise nothing seems to happen.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>You focus more magical power into the soul of your target. Your target is visibly bothered this time, running their hands all over their skin as if trying to scrape of some non-existent filth from their skin. They eventually realize the futility of their actions, and calm down.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>As your spell hits your mark this time, your target seems to get almost hysterical. They tear at their own skin, until they somehow manages to rip out a large piece of flesh just above their heart. Staring in disbelief at the newly exposed white skin underneath their own, your target manages to reclaim their sense and reverse the effect of the spell.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Your target is much calmer this time. In a controlled fashion, they start to peel of their own skin, one stripe at a time, each time revealing pristine white skin underneath. They eventually seem to wake up from their trance and magically restore themselves, but not without a hint of sadness in their face.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Your target yet again starts to peel off their own skin, which has taken on a gray, dead shade. Eventually, all that remains of your opponent is an unnaturally pale girl standing in the midst of her old skin. The girl suddenly seems to panic, and her old self somehow manages to revert the transformation, for now.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>The body of your target seemingly begins to dry up and harden, as glowing cracks starts to appear all over it. The dead husk suddenly breaks open, and a glowing white angel emerges. Singing joyously as she soars through the sky on her new wings, she eventually lands next to her old skin, which has been transformed into a beautiful white gown. After dressing herself in her old skin, she loses herself in prayer. As she prays, you can feel her gratitude radiating off of her.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
