<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>You feel a numbness spreading throughout your body. The sensation is not entirely unpleasant, but it is over too soon for you to even begin to describe it.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>Your entire body tingles as the same pleasant numbness from before returns. Your skin hardens somewhat, making it a bit harder to move! Since you are not too eager to be stuck in place, you quickly reverse the spell before it gets any worse.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>The changes seem to run deeper this time. Your body stiffens; your skin takes on a wooden texture as it hardens.  You notice that your joints seem to have been replaced by ball-joints.   You panic as you try to move them. They are not yours to control anymore! You try to cast a counterspell, but it's surprisingly hard to remember how you usually do it... Stuck in panic mode for an uncomfortably long time, you are eventually able to come up with the appropriate spell and reverse the transformation. You better not let that spell hit you again!</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>You brace yourself as another spell hits you, afraid of what will happen if you forget the counterspell this time around.
Not that your resistance matters...  You can do nothing but cry as you feel your mind slowing down, becoming as rigid as your body. Your reduced mental agility makes it hard to put up any kind of resistance, and you find yourself unable to do anything but stare straight ahead as the transformation continues to run its course.  Once again, your skin hardens, blocking out almost all tactile stimuli.   The only thing you feel is a pleasant tingling on your face as the spell begins to work on it, erasing all your characteristic features.   Your vision starts to fade as the upper part of your face becomes nothing but a smooth surface, leaving nothing to visually distinguish you from a lifeless mannequin.  Not wanting to be cut-off from the outside world, you somehow manage to bring your sluggish mind to panic, giving you the strength needed to reverse the spell.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>The pleasant tingle returns, propagating itself throughout your body as you are once again hit by the spell. You scream internally as your mind stiffens and slows down, rendering you unable to even put up token resistance as the spell remolds you. To your sluggish mind, the world around you now seems unbearably bright and fast.
You are almost relieved as the last window to the outside world close as your eyes and ears disappear in favor of wooden skin. With no external stimuli left to focus on, you soon find yourself drifting away, leaving you little more than an inanimate object to be claimed by an owner.
You are pulled out of your stupor by something touching your 'face'; it feels as if someone is carving something into you, just where your eyes used to be.
This new sensation comes to completely dominate your entire being: you find yourself focusing all of your limited mental resources on trying to understand it. It seems to be some sort of magic symbol, and although you fail to recognize its exact meaning, you feel it at some instinctual level: you'll soon be a loyal servant!
Your body tingles with magic as whoever has come to claim you finishes inscribing the rune.
Suddenly, your body jerks to life! However, it is as if someone else was pulling your strings; someone not quite sane, judging from the way your body spasms around. 
You fall to the floor in a spasming heap, feeling no pain in this body that no longer belongs to you.
 Whoever controls you eventually seems to get the hang of it, and you soon find yourself on your knees.
Next, your mind begins to speed up, but again you are no longer in control! Pleasure overwhelms you as thoughts of serving your Master flood your head, readjusting you to your new purpose: obedience. Nothing would make you happier than to be a useful tool for your master... except you can’t! You are a powerful mage, and while these fantasies make you feel so good, you mustn't let them control you!
Your mind set, you start to reverse the spell. You are so focused on your task that you don't even realize that your mind for some reason has sped up, and that you have full control of your wooden body. You eventually restore your old form, although the vivid fantasies of serving your master will take longer to get rid of... after all, they were carved into your mind by hand.
</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>With so much residual magic left in your body and so little will left in your head, you can do little to fight against the strange urges engraved into your mind.
You completely give in to the magic, eager to let your master reshape you.
Once again, your body stiffens, your mind halts. There is no fear as your senses fail you this time: you have accepted your fate.
You even feel proud as your master carves your new purpose into your face for everyone to see: 'SERVE,' written with a now familiar magical rune.
Your body starts to tingle as your master finishes the rune. Jolts of magic shoot through your body, causing it to spasm all over as the rune is calibrated to take control of your body. Likewise, your mind is being subjugated by the rune, not that it makes much of a difference anymore:  the rune has already been inside your head for a while. 
You seem to regain control of yourself as your mind and body are synced to the master signal of the rune, although 'you' is a matter of definition: the glowing rune on your forehead dictates your every thought. 
You now live to serve those around you. The rune on your forehead is not only nice enough to think for you, and it also provides you with everything you need to know in order to do your job. It allows you to see your surroundings, to hear what your Master is thinking, and even to use telepathy, should your master wish it!  Truly a marvelous thing, you cannot imagine how empty your life must have been before you had the rune. You half expect your Master inscribe even more runes on you, claiming you as a personal servant...
Except, it never happens. Perhaps Master doesn't know the appropriate rune? Of course, you are happy to just serve in general. 

Inspecting yourself to make sure that you are presentable for your Masters, you are delighted to find that whoever crafted your body gave you an artificial vagina, providing you with yet another way to serve your Masters. You somehow know that there is a horsecock-module somewhere, for Masters thus inclined.
</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>You throw a spell at your opponent, intent on turning them into a golem for you to control. Unfortunately, the world does not seem to agree with you, as the spell seemingly has no effect!</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>Not let down by your previous failure to transform your target, you focus even more of your magic into a spell. The spell seems to be more effective this time, as your targets movement somewhat stiffens, and their skin begins to show the hint of a wooden texture. Still, your opponent seems to have little problem reversing the effect, for now...</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>The skin of your victim now has an unmistakably wooden texture. Not content with merely a piece of wood to play with, you begin the next phase of the transformation... You can practically see the panic in your opponent's eyes as their joints are magically replaced by wooden ball-joints. It takes an unusually long time for your opponent to reverse the spell this time, perhaps indicating that your magic is starting to affect their mind.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Your victim quickly stiffens as your spell gives them a smooth wooden complexion. Seemingly petrified, they can do nothing but stare straight ahead as their transformation progresses. You even think you see a tear or two tickling down their chin, oh boy!
Wanting to cheer up your victim, you decide to give them a little gift: with a flick of your finger, you cause their smooth crotch to split open, revealing an artificial vagina. Your victim doesn't even seem to notice, but you are sure they will enjoy it later...

Next, you begin to work on their face, which slowly begins to lose its characteristic features under your magic assault. You see a hint of fear in their eyes as their eye-sockets completely closes in around them, leaving the upper part of their face a smooth wooden surface. At this point, there is nothing to visually distinguish your opponent from an inanimate mannequin... but it doesn't last, as your opponent somehow has found the strength to counter your spell.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Your opponent, panicking even before the spell hits them, quickly finds themselves as a wooden mannequin, again. You don't even see a glint of consciousness in their eyes as the spell remodels the upper part of their face, leaving a nice smooth surface for you to engrave a certain rune on. You approach your newly transformed foe, running your hands along their cool body to see if there is any reaction. Satisfied that they can in no way resist you, you pull out your spellbook and a pocket knife. After looking up the appropriate rune in your spell book, you begin to work on the mannequins face. 
Taking care to get the details right, you carve the enslaving rune into the face of your to-be golem. The rune begins to pulse as you finish your work, causing the doll to spasm with each pulse. The doll almost falls on you, as its legs give in to the beat, causing the doll to collapse in a spasming pile. You curiously watch what you assume to be some kind of internal struggle, ending with the mannequin eventually rising to its knees before you. The rune on its face continues to dim and grow brighter at an increasing rate, until it eventually glows steadily. Expecting to claim your reward, you are shocked to see the mannequin beginning to channel a counterspell, eventually reversing the transformation. Still, even after your target has reversed the spell, you find them looking at you with longing in their eyes.
At least you seem to be doing something right!</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>Your target almost looks eager to let your magic reshape them, and you soon find yourself looking at a faceless mannequin. Not wasting any time, you carve the rune into their face. This time, the spasms are less violent; the doll doesn't even fall as its body is overtaken by the rune. Your victim doesn't even seem to struggle as the rune takes over their mind. You soon find yourself illuminated by the steady glow of their rune. 
Inspecting your new slave, you can't help staring into their rune-engraved face... 
Which you quickly regret, as your mind is flooded with images of you serving your Masters. Deciding that it would be best for you to leave right now, you turn your back on your creation. You swear to never again try out strange magic from old Eerie Estate books. Well, perhaps not never...</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
