<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>You gasp as the spell strikes you in the chest. As you check yourself for changes, you notice that your chest has puffed out a little and is now made of a soft fabric. Though it feels pleasant to touch, you suspect that what may follow won't be so harmless. You easily reverse the changes without any effort.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>As the spell hits you, you feel a familiar sensation in your chest as it expands, slightly more this time, and your skin once again becomes a delightfully soft fabric. You stumble a bit and realize your feet are changing too! The toes on your right foot have curled into a hook-like shape and started to solidify. Meanwhile, the toes on your left foot have solidified into loops. Now worried, you hastily reverse the changes.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>Despite bracing for the spell, when it hits you, you instantly collapse in place. Knowing the previous changes well, you're more interested in seeing what new changes occurred. You realize very quickly why you fell. You grab what used to be your legs, but now all you hold in your hands are bands of fabric with clasping parts at the end. You begin to feel a tingling in your arms and quickly try to change back, afraid of what may happen next. It takes a great effort, but you manage to return to your previous form.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>The spell hits you and you once again find yourself on the ground, having fallen from the changes. The skin on your arms is turning to fabric as your arms themselves flatten out. Wait, is everything getting larger? No, you're shrinking! You're now acutely aware of your intended fate, and the thought scares you. You don't want to be anyone's bra! You want to stay free! You try to push back the fear and concentrate on a reversal spell. You succeed, but barely. You're now reeling, uncertain of how long you can keep this up.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>You're knocked down as the spell hits you yet again. You've shrunken down to the size of a bra. Your legs are flat bands with clasps that hook together. Your arms are now just bra straps that have fused into loops from shoulder to back. Your whole torso has become cups made for supporting breasts. Your head is all that remains. All of your skin is now a soft, smooth fabric. Scared for your very being, it takes every last ounce of energy and concentration to will yourself back to normal. You can't imagine being able to do that again. This might be the end.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>The light is almost blinding as you're struck for the final time. Though it happens just as quickly as before, the changes almost seem to occur in slow motion this time. You actually enjoy the feeling of becoming so soft and supportive. You completely become a nursing bra and can not wait to feel and support your master's breasts. You eagerly await the chance to make them lactate.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>You gasp as the spell strikes you in the chest. As you check yourself for changes, you notice that your chest has puffed out a little and is now made of a soft fabric. Though it feels pleasant to touch, you suspect that what may follow won't be so harmless. You easily reverse the changes without any effort.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>As the spell hits you, you feel a familiar sensation in your chest as it expands, slightly more this time, and your skin once again becomes a delightfully soft fabric. You stumble a bit and realize your feet are changing too! The toes on your right foot have curled into a hook-like shape and started to solidify. Meanwhile, the toes on your left foot have solidified into loops. Now worried, you hastily reverse the changes.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>Despite bracing for the spell, when it hits you, you instantly collapse in place. Knowing the previous changes well, you're more interested in seeing what new changes occurred. You realize very quickly why you fell. You grab what used to be your legs, but now all you hold in your hands are bands of fabric with clasping parts at the end. You also notice that your penis is gone. There is nothing but smooth fabric left in it's place. You begin to feel a tingling in your arms and quickly try to change back, afraid of what may happen next. It takes a great effort, but you manage to return to your previous form.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>The spell hits you and you once again find yourself on the ground, having fallen from the changes. The skin on your arms is turning to fabric as your arms themselves flatten out. Wait, is everything getting larger? No, you're shrinking! You're now acutely aware of your intended fate, and the thought scares you. You don't want to be anyone's bra! You want to stay free! You try to push back the fear and concentrate on a reversal spell. You succeed, but barely. You're now reeling, uncertain of how long you can keep this up.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>You're knocked down as the spell hits you yet again. You've shrunken down to the size of a bra. Your legs are flat bands with clasps that hook together. Your arms are now just bra straps that have fused into loops from shoulder to back. Your whole torso has become cups made for supporting breasts. Your head is all that remains. All of your skin is now a soft, smooth fabric. Scared for your very being, it takes every last ounce of energy and concentration to will yourself back to normal. You can't imagine being able to do that again. This might be the end.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>The light is almost blinding as you're struck for the final time. Though it happens just as quickly as before, the changes almost seem to occur in slow motion this time. You actually enjoy the feeling of becoming so soft and supportive. You completely become a nursing bra and can not wait to feel and support your master's breasts. You eagerly await the chance to make them lactate.</TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>You gasp as the spell strikes you in the chest. As you check yourself for changes, you notice that your breasts have puffed out a little and are now made of a soft fabric. Though they feel pleasant to touch, you suspect that what may follow won't be so harmless. You easily reverse the changes without any effort.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>As the spell hits you, you feel a familiar sensation in your breasts as they expand, slightly more this time, and your skin once again becomes a delightfully soft fabric. You stumble a bit and realize your feet are changing too! The toes on your right foot have curled into a hook-like shape and started to solidify. Meanwhile, the toes on your left foot have solidified into loops. Now worried, you hastily reverse the changes.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>Despite bracing for the spell, when it hits you, you instantly collapse in place. Knowing the previous changes well, you're more interested in seeing what new changes occurred. You realize very quickly why you fell. You grab what used to be your legs, but now all you hold in your hands are bands of fabric with clasping parts at the end. You also notice that there is nothing but smooth, soft fabric where your vagina used to be. You begin to feel a tingling in your arms and quickly try to change back, afraid of what may happen next. It takes a great effort, but you manage to return to your previous form.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>The spell hits you and you once again find yourself on the ground, having fallen from the changes. The skin on your arms is turning to fabric as your arms themselves flatten out. Wait, is everything getting larger? No, you're shrinking! You're now acutely aware of your intended fate, and the thought scares you. You don't want to be anyone's bra! You want to stay free! You try to push back the fear and concentrate on a reversal spell. You succeed, but barely. You're now reeling, uncertain of how long you can keep this up.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>You're knocked down as the spell hits you yet again. You've shrunken down to the size of a bra. Your legs are flat bands with clasps that hook together. Your arms are now just bra straps that have fused into loops from shoulder to back. Your breasts have become cups made for supporting breasts, the rest of your torso had been pulled in for underwire support . Your head is all that remains. All of your skin is now a soft, smooth fabric. Scared for your very being, it takes every last ounce of energy and concentration to will yourself back to normal. You can't imagine being able to do that again. This might be the end.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>The light is almost blinding as you're struck for the final time. Though it happens just as quickly as before, the changes almost seem to occur in slow motion this time. You actually enjoy the feeling of becoming so soft and supportive. You completely become a nursing bra and can not wait to feel and support your master's breasts. You eagerly await the chance to make them lactate.</TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>You aim carefully and your spell strikes your victim directly in the chest. You watch in amusement as they discover what you already know, their chest has puffed out a little and is now made of a soft fabric. They seem more curious than panicked, as they casually reverse the changes without much concern.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>You cast again and your victim's chest expands slightly more this time and their skin once again becomes a delightfully soft fabric. They stumble a bit and realize their feet are changing too! The toes on their right foot have curled into a hook-like shape and started to solidify. Meanwhile, the toes on their left foot have solidified into loops. They hurriedly reverse the changes in a panic.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>As your spell hits your target, their legs become bands of fabric unable to support the weight of their torso, and your victim instantly collapses in place as the previous changes take hold again. You watch as they desperately grab what used to be their legs, but now all they hold in their hands are bands of fabric with clasping parts at the end. Clearly terrified, they quickly try to change back, though it takes longer than before and the effort is an obvious strain on them.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Determined to push the transformation along, you cast your spell again. You strike your victim yet again and in addition to the other changes, the skin on their arms is turning to fabric as their arms themselves flatten out. Your victim is now getting smaller as well! You get excited and can't wait to try them on! You can see the fear in their eyes as they recognize what you aim to turn them into. Your victim closes their eyes, focusing intensely, and manages to undo the changes. Though, they are noticeably fatigued.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Your spell knocks them down again as it hits them. They've shrunken down to the size of a bra. Their legs are flat bands with clasps that hook together. Their arms are now just bra straps that have fused into loops from shoulder to back. Their whole torso has become cups made for supporting breasts. Their head is all that remains. All of their skin is now a soft, smooth fabric. Somehow, they muster the strength to renew their form once more, though, it is doubtful that they could possibly manage such a feat again.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>The light is almost blinding as you land your final blow. You feel the excitement building within you as you watch them change, eager to finally wear them. They have now completely become a nursing bra and you find yourself elated with anticipation to try them on.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>You aim carefully and your spell strikes him directly in the chest. You watch in amusement as he discovers what you already know, his chest has puffed out a little and is now made of a soft fabric. He seems more curious than panicked, as he casually reverses the changes without much concern.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>You cast again and his chest expands slightly more this time, and his skin once again becomes a delightfully soft fabric. He stumbles a bit and realizes his feet are changing too! The toes on his right foot have curled into a hook-like shape and started to solidify. Meanwhile, the toes on his left foot have solidified into loops. He hurriedly reverse the changes in a panic.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>As your spell hits your target, his legs become bands of fabric unable to support the weight of his torso, and he instantly collapses in place as the previous changes take hold again. You watch as he desperately grabs what used to be his legs, but now all he holds in his hands are bands of fabric with clasping parts at the end. Clearly terrified, he quickly tries to change back, though it takes longer than before and the effort is an obvious strain on him.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>Determined to push the transformation along, you cast your spell again. You strike your victim yet again and in addition to the other changes, the skin on his arms is turning to fabric as his arms themselves flatten out. He is now getting smaller as well! You get excited and simply can't wait to try him on! You can see the fear in his eyes as he recognizes what you aim to turn him into. He closes his eyes, focusing intensely, and manages to undo the changes. Though, he is noticeably fatigued.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>Your spell knocks him down again as it hits him. He's shrunken down to the size of a bra. His legs are flat bands with clasps that hook together. His arms are now just bra straps that have fused into loops from shoulder to back. His whole torso has become cups made for supporting breasts. His head is all that remains. All of his skin is now a soft, smooth fabric. Somehow, he musters the strength to renew his form once more, though, it is doubtful that he could possibly manage such a feat again.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>The light is almost blinding as you land your final blow. You feel the excitement building within you as you watch him change, eager to finally wear him. He has now completely become a nursing bra and you find yourself elated with anticipation to try him on.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>You aim carefully and your spell strikes her directly in the chest. You watch in amusement as she discovers what you already know, her breasts have puffed out a little and are now made of a soft fabric. She seems more curious than panicked, as she casually reverses the changes without much concern.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>You cast again and her breasts expand slightly more this time, and her skin once again becomes a delightfully soft fabric. She stumbles a bit and realizes her feet are changing too! The toes on her right foot have curled into a hook-like shape and started to solidify. Meanwhile, the toes on her left foot have solidified into loops. She hurriedly reverse the changes in a panic.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>As your spell hits your target, her legs become bands of fabric unable to support the weight of her torso, and she instantly collapses in place as the previous changes take hold again. You watch as she desperately grabs what used to be her legs, but now all she holds in her hands are bands of fabric with clasping parts at the end. Clearly terrified, she quickly tries to change back, though it takes longer than before and the effort is an obvious strain on her.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>Determined to push the transformation along, you cast your spell again. You strike your victim yet again and in addition to the other changes, the skin on her arms is turning to fabric as her arms themselves flatten out. She is now getting smaller as well! You feel yourself getting excited and simply can't wait to try her on! You can see the fear in her eyes as she recognizes what you aim to turn her into. She closes her eyes, focusing intensely, and manages to undo the changes. Though, she is noticeably fatigued.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>Your spell knocks her down again as it hits. She has shrunken down to the size of a bra. Her legs are flat bands with clasps that hook together. Her arms are now just bra straps that have now fused into loops from shoulder to back. Her breasts have become cups made for supporting breasts, the rest of her torso had been pulled in for underwire support. Her head is all that remains. All of her skin is now a soft, smooth fabric. Somehow, she musters the strength to renew her form once more, though, it is doubtful that she could possibly manage such a feat again.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>The light is almost blinding as you land your final blow. You feel the excitement building within you as you watch her change, eager to finally wear her. She has now completely become a nursing bra and you find yourself elated with anticipation to try her on.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>

</Form>
