<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>As the spell hits you, the light around you seems to get brighter, at the sound of skittering playing at the edge of your hearing. You blink your eyes, lights coming back to normal as you easily dismiss the spell. </TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>The sound of Spiders fills your ears as the lights brighten again. You feel them climb over you, your skin starting to darken as your limbs become more slender, more effeminate. You shake it off, countering the spell quickly before your skin turns to ebony, swearing you can still feel the spiders on your skin.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>Your skin turns solid black now, your body quickly becoming effeminate. The spiders are on you immediately, draping you in their silk as your breasts swell, your hips widen, and your body takes on a sensual grace. Now you can hear whispering, filling you with dark urges of the flesh. The counterspell takes longer this time, those dark desires still flitting through your mind. </TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>A low moan passes through your feminine lips as you are quickly shifted back into The Drow form. Shielding your eyes from the bright lights, The spiders return, their silk lighting up your senses as they start to dress you in their silk. Your flesh shivers with desire, lust filling your urges as you look at the one changing you. "Soon you'll be one of us, my Daughter." You hear in your mind, welcoming the woman's voice as it promises dark passions. Your old voice speaks out, pushing away the feeling, countering the spell and changing you back before you can embrace what you desire.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>Lust flushes your skin as it returns to that rich ebony, your feminine elf body returning. The spiders return to finish their work, clothing you quickly in your spidersilk raiment. As you marvel at your new form, your delicate fingers brushing sensually over your body, you feel her words returning. "That's it my Daughter," She whispers, almost purring in your ear. "You're so nearly there. Soon the surface will be yours." You hear yourself laugh, dark and sensual as the world opens to your senses. Looking over your feminine body, you recognize that the silken slip you're clad in marks you as a follower of Lloth. But again, that now tiny voice of your old life pushes aside your gifts, changing you back, but not for much longer. </TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>"Welcome my Daughter!" The words ring through your pointed ears as the change comes quickly. You embrace the feeling of your silken slip, exhilarated in knowing that it barely covers your feminine but powerful body. You feel the gifts of the Spider Queen take hold as you slip into the shadows, the light forevermore your enemy. You'll teach these surfacers the true meaning of pleasure, using your own wicked wiles to do so. Raising your hands, you feel a whip settle into them, marking you as a Priestess of Lloth, a smirk playing over your lips as you think of the pleasure you'll gain from their suffering. The voice of who you were rises, only to be silenced by the cracking of your whip, forever gone from your mind. You are Lloth's now, and you set off to bring more sister's into the fold.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>Releasing a small spider from your fingertip, you watch it crawl under your targets clothes, a brief flash of red in their eyes as its poison takes hold. Your opponent shakes their head, dismissing the spell, but you know Lloth's poison has taken hold. </TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>Another spider skitters up their leg, this time its passage marked by their skin turning dusky. The red of their eyes stays longer this time as their body shrinks, becoming elfin in nature. They look around, looking for the unseen spider, shaking their head as they counter the spell, but you can almost see the poison building up in their body.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>Several spiders assault now, your targets skin turning solid ebony almost instantly. As they climb, they start spinning silk over their victim, measuring them for Lloth's vestments. Their Elfin body becomes feminine, breasts swelling under their shirt, hips widening as they become Lloth's vessel. You watch as they trace their changing form with delicate fingers, eyes closed as if trying to hear a distant voice. It takes a bit before they can bring the counterspell to bear, shaking from the ordeal.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Their dark elf body shimmers into existence even before the army of spiders can swarm their prey, a low moan escaping their lips as pleasure starts to take over. Thin fingers trace their body as they are clothed in a silken shift, arousal plain on their face. Several of the spiders start to adorn the delicate silk, starting to mark them as one of Lloth's chosen. Spiders pierce their pointed ears, becoming jewelry as they try to stop touching themselves, stammering out the counterspell as if they weren't actively trying. Their eyes snap open, looking over their body in disbelief, as if they already wished to give into the Spider Queen.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Moaning in pleasure, your Victim quickly returns to their dark elf form, shivering as they become infused with dark power. The spiders swarm her faster than your eyes can follow, clothing her in a Spidersilk slip adorned with spider jewelry. The Priestess before you lets out a laugh that both chills your veins with ice, and your loins with heat. You feel torn as the creature before you regards you with almost a predatory hunger, sizing you up like she'd just as easily eat you as pleasure you. You hear a whisper of "Help" as they turn back to normal, but just looking at them lets you know they can't resist much longer.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>With a bloodcurdling scream of utter pleasure, the person before you is reborn, a Drow elf through and through. Clad in the raiments of the clergy of The Spider Queen, she licks her lips, fixing her eyes on you. The way she stands, the way she holds herself you could swear she wants to share a night of purest debauchery. That thought is partially dashed though, as a whip appears in her hand, cracking in the space between the two. A smirk on her lips, she crooks her fingers at you, beckoning you try her brand of pleasure.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>