<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<Description>A sexy princess of an old kingdom. With such big breasts and perfect figure, all the eyes are drawn to her. You always find her smiling and acting nicely. In the morning she acts like normal princesses. She rules the kingdom and help the people, but when the night comes, everything changes.  This princess turns into a sex beast, sneaking out amongst her subjects and making passionate love to any who prince of pauper she takes a fancy to.  She can't control herself and the people around her can't say no to her orders, but some day this might all come back to bite her should she ever return home to explain her actions to a furious father...</Description>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>Your opponent's spell hit you on the belly. You wait to see what will happen, but nothing looks strange to you</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>The spell hits you and you feel something bad is going to happen. Your Skin becomes softer and your whole body looks cuter, but nothing more happens. You reverse the spell and go back to your normal look.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>Your opponent cast the spell again and it hits you right in the head. You suddenly feel the desire to give people orders and fuck them after they do it. You push aside these thoughts. You notice that your body changed, your hair was longer. You hips were wider, while the waist were smaller and your butt were bigger and shaped just like a heart, not to forget the long sexy legs. You had a figure that any girl wishes to have. You gasp at your changing body and fast reverse the spell.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>Your opponent cast this spell again and it hits you again. More thoughts flow to your head. You can't fight the desire to just tell people what to do and mostly order them to go to bed with you. You fight these thoughts and look at your body. You had a perfect figure, a big butt that any guy would love to slap. You had a classy long straight hair. You feel your chest to find that your breasts were bigger, they were around C cup. You gasp and act fast to reverse this, but you know that you can't handle this much more.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>The spell hits you once more and the thoughts flow again to your head and it is hard to fight it now, you can't say no to it anymore. "I ORDER YOU TO FUCK ME, RIGHT NOW" you find these words leaving your mouth without knowing it. You look to see your opponent smiling, but you don't care about it anymore. You look down to see that your breasts had reached what looks like D cup or maybe DD. You smile feeling them as you feel your whole body changing giving you a sexy body that any girl would die to have. You hear your opponent laughing and you remember that you can't give up now. You gather all your strength and reverse this spell, but you know for sure that it will only take one more hit to finish you.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>The spell hits you another time and you know for sure that you won't be able to take it anymore. The thoughts take over your mind and you can't resist it anymore, so you accept the fact that you're a princess, you have a kingdom to rule and people to serve, but in the other hand those people will serve you too. Now you starve for cocks and you'll do anything to have a one. You smile and open your eyes to see that your body has became the body of a very attractive woman. You smile as you feel your new body.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>Your spell hits your target on the belly. You wait to see what will happen, but nothing looks strange to you. Nothing changed about your victim for now.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>Your spell hits your target and you see that your target's skin is becoming softer and their whole body looks cuter now, but nothing more happens. Your target reverse the spell without no effort.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>You cast the spell again and it hits your target on their head. You see your target closing their eyes, your spell must be effecting their mind. You look more at your target and you notice that their body is changing, their hair grows becoming longer, while their hips go upward, when the waist goes inward. You see that their butt grow up becoming bigger and it is shaped just like a heart, you look down at their legs to see long sexy legs. Your target has a perfect figure, even you can't resist it. Your target opens their eyes and they gasp when they see what happened to their body. They act fast and reverse your spell.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>You cast this spell again and it hits your target again and like the last time, you see your target closing their eyes, you don't know what they are thinking, but you're certain that it is something good. You look to see that your target's body is changing again, but like last time, your target is drown in their thoughts and doesn't notice a thing. You see that they had a perfect figure, a big butt that you will die to play with. You look more to see their hair turning into a classy long straight hair. You go with your eyes to your target's chest. they had C cup breasts. Your target opens their eyes to see there changing body and fast reverse the spell going back to their normal look.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>You cast the spell again and you see your target holding their head trying to fight your spell, You smile when you hear your target saying "I ORDER YOU TO FUCK ME, RIGHT NOW", your spell is working, but it looks like your target doesn't care about it anymore. They look happy, you see your target playing with their breasts which reached DD cup. You laugh looking at how much this spell has changed your target. They have an attractive body and you just love it, but your laugh brought your target back to reality. They gasp and fast gather all their strength to reverse this spell. You smile knowing it won't take long to finish your target.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>You cast the spell again at your target and you see that they don't try to fight it anymore. They know they can't resist it, so they just gave up. You smile seeing your target's body changing fast to give them a very attractive body with big breasts, perfect figure and a sexy ass. Your target smile as she feel her body and go to play with her breasts and ass. You stand their watching her and wishing that she might give you something special, after all, you're the reason she is like that now.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
