<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<Description>Before you stands a cute little skunkboi. He has soft shaggy hair and a small cuddly body. A large poofy tail runs out his backside twitching occasionally, as if to attract potential partners as he churs happily, eager to please any cute boy or girl who he comes across. A tiny bulge in his groin reveals his constant state of arousal as well as betraying his otherwise feminine look. The usual skunk stench has instead been replaced by a sweet berry smell. Although he sprays in situations where he feels threatened, he also sprays when commanded to as it has a slight transformation effect on contact with the skin. Too much and you may find yourself just like him. </Description>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>You watch in confusion as your opponent rolls a small orb your way, before you can react it bursts enveloping you in a strange gas. Suddenly a sweet smell fills your lungs as your body begins to feel tingly. Beyond that nothing seems to happen as you wave away the gas and dissipate the effects.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>Once again the orb rolls towards you, knowing it's soon to burst releasing the gas you quickly plug your nose. Laughing at your opponent knowing you've beaten their spell. Before you can celebrate however the gas finds its way into your mouth, you cough and sputter dropping your hand, the scent filling your lungs once more as the familiar feeling returns, a strange pressure building in your rear, your hands growing a fine black fur as you look down in shock, your belly now soft with white fur. Angrily you once again wave the gas away and revert the changes.
</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>Your attacker once again throws down the orb. However they also begin to dig into their pack for something as the smell invades your senses once more, your fur returning as the pressure grows in your rear. You look up to see them holding a mirror in front of you. "Look at what a cute little boitoy you're becoming," they tease as you watch your face bend and form into a cute tiny muzzle, your hair lengthening as you try to fight off the sweet scent. Your concentration is broken as your new poofy skunk tail bursts from your now bubbly rear. Letting out a girlish moan as you fall to your knees. Quickly chanting a counter spell and wave the gas away, embarrassed with your new features noticing they haven't reverted.. </TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>You whine looking at your new features as the orb rolls between your legs, beginning to smell the scent before the orb even bursts you panic. Your attacker comes in close, holding your head in their hands as they slip two of their fingers in your new muzzle shamefully you begin to suck them without thinking. "Oh, someone's good at this aren't they? Are you sure you haven't had practice?" they taunt before standing you back on your feet. Feeling yourself shrink as the smell gets stronger, once again your attacker holds up the mirror, letting you watch yourself turn further into a submissive femboi. Letting out low whimpers your hips widen, the rest of your body becoming feminine as your vision shifts closer to the ground. Looking at your blushing form in the mirror you shake your head, dispelling the gas. This isn't you! You aren't some feminine boitoy. You just need to run, to escape, and figure out a way to reverse your transformation... maybe find a cute boy or two...</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>Feeling your will to fight fading as another orb rolls its way over to you. You eagerly wait for it to burst, to release the sweet smelling scent that you've come to love. Except it never does. So why do you smell it still? Investigating you find the smell is coming from you! You shiver, realizing you're dangerously close to being turned into a femboi, you try and fight. "Where do you think you're going?" your attacker coos holding you still. "Show me what a good little fuckpet you've become." Blushing you obey, reaching down as you let out a tiny moan in surprise, your once impressive member shrunk down to a petite pink cock. Barely 2 inches it twitches, needing release. As you wrap your hands around your pathetic dick, your knees buckle causing you to fall on the ground and spread your legs. As you begin to rub at your dick, you snap out of the submissive roll the spell is making you fit into so well. Desperately trying to fight your transformation and the need to cum, you pant and moan. Fighting the spell is getting harder and harder. You try to pull your hand away, but can't bring yourself to do it as the pleasure is too intense. You struggle weakly as you are close to climax, knowing that if you cum your fate is sealed as their little plaything, made to please your new owners, begging to be filled and made to cum over and over as they command you to... is that really such a bad fate?</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>You let out a loud, feminine moan as the final orb bursts, though you have your doubts that it did anything besides distracted your mind long enough that you couldn't hold back anymore and let out a loud girlish squeal as your tiny boiprick erupts with the last vestiges of your masculinity, spraying it on to the ground in a pitiful little puddle. Your new owner steps forward, their foot stomping down on what remains of your previous self, grinding it into the dirt, sealing you into your new role in life as their possession. Your former opponents pats you on your little skunkboi head, ruffling your hair and smiling and telling you what a good little fucktoy you are now. And they are right, you realize that's what you want to be, to attend to all their needs and pleasure your new owner and be rewarded with all the delicious cock you can suck and fuck for your good work. You can't help but feel excited about your new life as you get on your still wobbly feet giving yourself a reassuring hug and follow them, your fluffy tail happily swaying behind your back showing off your bubbly ass to the world to see.

</TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>You watch in confusion as your opponent rolls a small orb your way, before you can react it bursts enveloping you in a strange gas. Suddenly a sweet smell fills your lungs as your body begins to feel tingly. Beyond that nothing seems to happen as you wave away the gas and dissipate the effects.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>Once again the orb rolls towards you, knowing it's soon to burst releasing the gas you quickly plug your nose. Laughing at your opponent knowing you've beaten their spell. Before you can celebrate however the gas finds its way into your mouth, you cough and sputter dropping your hand, the scent filling your lungs once more as the familiar feeling returns, a strange pressure building in your rear, your hands growing a fine black fur as you look down in shock, your belly now soft with white fur noticing your breasts have shrunk. Angrily you once again wave the gas away and revert the 
changes.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>Your attacker once again throws down the orb. However they also begin to dig into their pack for something as the smell invades your senses once more, your fur returning as the pressure grows in your rear. You look up to see them holding a mirror in front of you. "Look at what a cute little boitoy you're becoming," they tease as you watch your face bend and form into a cute tiny muzzle, your breasts shrinking into nothing as you try to fight off the sweet scent. Wait...did they say boy? Your concentration is broken as your new poofy skunk tail bursts from your rear. Letting out a moan as you fall to your knees. Quickly chanting a counter spell and wave the gas away, embarrassed with your new features noticing they haven't reverted.. 
</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>You whine looking at your new features as the orb rolls between your legs, beginning to smell the scent before the orb even bursts you panic. Your attacker comes in close, holding your head in their hands as they slip two of their fingers in your new muzzle shamefully you begin to suck them without thinking. "Oh, someone's good at this aren't they? You sure had practice!" they taunt before standing you back on your feet. Feeling yourself shrink even more as the smell gets stronger, once again your attacker holds up the mirror, letting you watch yourself turn further into a submissive femboi. Letting out low whimpers feeling your groin heat up, pressure building as your vision shifts closer to the ground. Looking at your blushing form in the mirror you shake your head, dispelling the gas. This isn't you! You aren't some feminine boitoy. You just need to run, to escape, and figure out a way to reverse your transformation... maybe find a cute boy or two...
</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>Feeling your will to fight fading as another orb rolls its way over to you. You eagerly wait for it to burst, to release the sweet smelling scent that you've come to love. Except it never does. So why do you smell it still? Investigating you find the smell is coming from you! You shiver, realizing you're dangerously close to being turned into a femboi, you try and fight. "Where do you think you're going?" your attacker coos holding you still. "Show me what a good little fuckpet  you've become." Blushing you obey, reaching down as you let out a tiny moan in surprise, where your tight little vagina once sat, now shaped and pulled to a petite pink cock. barely 2 inches as it twitches needing release. As you wrap your hands around your pathetic dick, your knees buckle causing you to fall on the ground and spread your legs. As you begin to rub at your dick, you snap out of the submissive roll the spell is making you fit into so well. Desperately trying to fight your transformation and the need to cum, you pant and moan. Fighting the spell is getting harder and harder. You try to pull your hand away, but can't bring yourself to do it as the pleasure is too intense. You struggle weakly as you are close to climax, knowing that if you cum your fate is sealed as their little plaything, made to please your new owners, begging to be filled and made to cum over and over as they command you 
to... is that really such a bad fate?</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>You let out a loud, feminine moan as the final orb bursts, though you have your doubts that it did anything besides distracted your mind long enough that you couldn't hold back anymore and let out a loud girlish squeal as your tiny boiprick erupts with the last vestiges of your womanhood spraying it on to the ground in a pitiful little puddle. You're a tiny boi now. Your new owner steps forward, their foot stomping down on what remains of your previous self, grinding it into the dirt. sealing you into your new role in life as their possession. Your former opponents pats you on your little skunkboi head, ruffling your hair and smiling and telling you what a good little fucktoy you are now. And they are right, you realize that's what you want to be, to attend to all their needs and pleasure your new owner and be rewarded with all the delicious cock you can suck and fuck for your good work. You can't help but feel excited about your new life as you get on your still wobbly feet giving yourself a reassuring hug and follow them, your fluffy tail happily swaying behind your back showing off your bubbly ass to the world to see.
</TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>Finding a suitable subject you begin to cast a spell, rolling a small orb towards them. Before they even have a chance to think it bursts, sending a sweet smelling scent into the air and into their lungs. You can see them blush slightly as they wave the gas away, the spell seeming to do nothing more, as your victim looks annoyed.
</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>Determined to make this spell work you roll another orb towards them, watching annoyed as they plug their nose. Maybe it needs some redesigning as it clearly doesn't work. Before giving in, however, the gas find its way in your victims mouth. You practically jump with joy as they cough, dropping their hand from their nose as it makes it's way in once again. With a happy smile you realize the spell is working wonderfully now, a think layer of hair growing on their body as they feel at their rear. With an angry glare they chant a counter spell and wave the gas away. Confident in the spells power you ready another.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>Throwing another orb at your soon to be skunkboi, you think of something to speed up the process and to get rid of that pesky resistance. Searching through your pack you pull out a small mirror and hold it near their face, so they can watch themselves turn. "Look at what a cute little boitoy you're becoming," You tell them. They blush as their face bends and forms into a cute skunk muzzle. Beginning to fall into the roll you're turning them into, their tail bursts forth, twitching lightly as they emit a surprisingly girly moan and fall on their knees in front of you. You can't help but be proud of how well this spell is going right now. Maybe a little too good, you think, as you watch your victim wave the gas away and chant a counter spell. Seemingly having no effect as their 
new skunk body stays.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Seeing your opponent too distracted with their new paws you send another orb out. Once again it bursts and blankets them with the sweet scent. Determined to help them into their new role even quicker, you approach them and gently holding their muzzle, slipping two of your fingers inside. Giving a quick taunt on what a good cocksucker they are to become, you lift them up, only to watch them shrink. Quickly pulling out the mirror, you let them watch their body become more dainty and feminine, small whines escape their tiny lips. before they seem to shake off the effects, quickly panicking and waving the gas away. They've regained control once again. You know they can't hold on much longer however.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Watching surprised, your opponent seems to jump at the next orb you send out, eagerly waiting for it to burst, to cover them in the scent. However, a hint of disappointment crosses their face as it never does burst. Happily you watch as they realize they no longer need the orbs, their body now shifted fully into a skunk as they now can emit the scent themselves. They shiver, realizing how close they are to turning into a skunkboi. They weakly try to stumble away, but before they can escape you quickly grab their shoulder and pull them back. "Where do you think you're going? Show me what a good little fuckpet you've become!" you say rather sweetly. Delighted as they shyly obey, emitting a tiny squeak realizing the tiny skunk penis. Knowing they cannot hold out any longer, they begin to rub at themselves. Panting and moaning they realize their predicament, if they cum, it's over and you both know it. Deriving pleasure from the spectacle you watch as they weakly fight against themselves and the transformation. Not soon now 
little pet...</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>It's over, you know it as you roll the final orb under them, though you doubt it did any good as they seemed to finalize their transformation themselves. A loud girlish moan emits from them as they climax. The last bits of resistance and their old life dripping into a puddle in the dirt. Determined to show them their new life you step forward and onto it. Stomping and grinding it into the ground. Walking up to the new skunkboi you gently pat his head, telling him what a good fucktoy he is now. Watching a smile form on his cute blushing face, he hugs himself and happily raising to his feet. Following you obediently, his tail swishing from side to side, showing his bubbly ass for the world to see.
</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
