<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>You are hit with a blue mist that washes over you, smelling like a mountainous mist as it dissipates. Not feeling any 
different you look to the caster quizzically before taking a look down at yourself. You are shocked to find your entire 
body a new shade of blue and what looks like blue tinted claws growing from your hand. The affects don't quite hold and you soon find yourself reverted back to normal.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>It feels as if someone splashed a small cup worth of water against your head as the spells power washes over you. 
Instinctively you bring your hands up to wipe at your face only to realize it really wasn't water that hit you despite 
the scent of it in the air. What is more abnormal is that you wiped your face with your birdlike hands. A bit startled 
you quickly look over yourself to discover that your feet are birdlike as well. As quickly as the changes had occurred 
they vanish, leaving you to your previous state as the magic wasn't strong enough to hold.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>Feeling as though hit suddenly with a water balloon you try to shake off the unseen water only to realize it was magic that washed over you. You look over yourself with a shudder as the magic sends a tingle through your form, making you feel nude and exposed when suddenly feathers materialize all over your body. As startling this occurrence is to you the change feels natural. You are brushing your birdlike hands through your plumage when the spell becomes unstable and you revert back to your old self.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>You react as if a waterfall splashes against you as this blue magic surrounds you. It doesn't take long for the spell to have an affect on you as suddenly you are covered in blue feathers and to your surprise an avian tail sprouts from your back end which elects a squawk from your beak... Wait, beak! You quickly bring your birdlike hands to your face and feel along your new found blue beak. Though it would seem most of your other facial features seem intact. You then find yourself craving pine seeds, the thought making you lick along your beak and flutter your tail. But wait, did you ever like seeds in the first place? Before you're allowed enough time to rustle your own feathers they vanish along with your beak, tail and birdlike appendages. Seems as though the spell just wasn't quite strong enough to hold.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>A deluge of blue washes over you, quickly overwhelming you before you even have a chance to react. When things finally seem to be calming down as the spell absorbed into you, your knocked right off balance by thine own massive new wings. Stumbling forward you flap them, their strength surpasses your expectations and with a heavy gust of wind being kicked in front of you the force pushes you back to fall against your rump. A loud squawk sounding forth from your beak as you nearly injure your tail. With an embarrassed look upon your avian face you grab at your head and notice something else doesn't seem right. Your ears seem to have flattened alongside your head and have been covered with blue feathers. As you are feeling at your new ears your vision starts to change, the world becoming more vibrant as you acquire the ability to see Ultraviolet light. All these changes seem to be going to your head as you become more open to the thought of singing with fellow birds stuffing yourself silly on seeds. The changes don't seem to want to go away and instead get worse by the second. You hold on to what little will you have and cast a counter spell, reverting you back.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>You are instantly hit with the sensation of being dunked under water as blue seems to surround you, your body losing control as you bathe in it. Before you know it you find yourself laying against your back on top of your large wings. At first you find this odd but as you sit yourself back up you become more and more accepting of the new you as if your will was changed to accept this fate. You even have trouble recalling what you were before, or where you always like this? No... Maybe?.. It matters to you less and less as time passes. Standing up you hear off in the distance some singing birds. Almost at an instant you sing along with them, testing your new vocal pipes with a happy grin.</TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>You are hit with a blue mist that washes over you, smelling like a mountainous mist as it dissipates. Not feeling any 
different you look to the caster quizzically before taking a look down at yourself. You are shocked to find your entire 
body a new shade of blue, your breasts shrunk and what looks like blue tinted claws growing from your hand. The affects don't quite hold and you soon find yourself reverted back to normal.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>It feels as if someone splashed a small cup worth of water against your head as the spells power washes over you. 
Instinctively you bring your hands up to wipe at your face only to realize it really wasn't water that hit you despite 
the scent of it in the air. What is more abnormal is that you wiped your face with your birdlike hands. A bit startled 
you quickly look over yourself to discover that your feet are birdlike as well and you feel oddly bare at your groin. As quickly as the changes had occurred they vanish, leaving you to your previous state as the magic wasn't strong enough to hold.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>Feeling as though hit suddenly with a water balloon you try to shake off the unseen water only to realize it was magic that washed over you. You look over yourself with a shudder as the magic sends a tingle through your form, making you feel nude and exposed when suddenly feathers materialize all over your body. As startling this occurrence is to you the change feels natural aside from the bulge at your groin. Feeling at your groin you come to find that aside from loosing your breasts you also are fully equipped as a male. You are brushing your birdlike hands through your plumage when the spell becomes unstable and you revert back to your old self.
</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>You react as if a waterfall splashes against you as this blue magic surrounds you. It doesn't take long for the spell to have an affect on you as suddenly you are covered in blue feathers and to your surprise an avian tail sprouts from your back end which elects a squawk from your beak... Wait, beak! You quickly bring your birdlike hands to your face and feel along your new found blue beak. Though it would seem most of your other facial features seem intact. You then find yourself craving pine seeds, the thought making you lick along your beak and flutter your tail. But wait, did you ever like seeds in the first place? Before you're allowed enough time to rustle your own feathers they vanish along with your beak, tail and birdlike appendages, returning you back to your feminine form. Seems as though the spell just wasn't quite strong enough to hold.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>A deluge of blue washes over you, quickly overwhelming you before you even have a chance to react. When things finally seem to be calming down as the spell absorbed into you, your knocked right off balance by thine own massive new wings. Stumbling forward you flap them, their strength surpasses your expectations and with a heavy gust of wind being kicked in front of you the force pushes you back to fall against your rump. A loud squawk sounding forth from your beak as you nearly injure your tail. With an embarrassed look upon your avian face you grab at your head and notice something else doesn't seem right. Your ears seem to have flattened alongside your head and have been covered with blue feathers. As you are feeling at your new ears your vision starts to change, the world becoming more vibrant as you acquire the ability to see Ultraviolet light. All these changes seem to be going to your head as you become more open to the thought of singing with fellow birds and stuffing yourself silly on seeds. The changes don't seem to want to go away and instead get worse by the second. You hold on to what little will you have and cast a counter spell, reverting you back.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>You are instantly hit with the sensation of being dunked under water as blue seems to surround you, your body losing control as you bathe in it. Before you know it you find yourself laying against your back on top of your large wings. At first you find this odd but as you sit yourself back up you become more and more accepting of the new you as if your will was changed to accept this fate. You even have trouble recalling what you were before, or where you always like this? No... Maybe?.. It matters to you less and less as time passes. Standing up you hear off in the distance some singing birds. Almost at an instant you sing along with them, testing your new vocal pipes with a happy grin.</TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>You toss a concentrated blue mist orb at your opponent and watch as it breaks over his head. He looks confused at first and look to you before noticing his changes. He reveals to himself his blue skin and claws before it simply washes away as the spell didn't have enough power to complete the change. That's quite alright as you are sure more of the same will cake on the effects.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>Your spell hits right against your targets head and proceeds to trickle down against him. The spell quickly dispersing and the changes quickly become apparent. Leaving your subject to examine his new birdlike hands and feet before the spell breaks form and he reverts back to normal. Seems like the spell can use quite a bit more reinforcement.
</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>Your target doesn't have time to react as your little blue orb hits and splashes against his body. The magic works quick and in no time he is covered with blue feathers. You nod to yourself, thankful that you are making progress but it is apparent to you that you will need to continue to enforce the spell for it to fully take root.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>Your blue orb flies over your target and slightly expands before rushing down over him. The changes come rapidly, feathers awash his form just before a tail sprouts out behind him along with a beak against his face. He squawks out in surprise at the changes. You can't tell but you think you see him lick his beak at you as if you were a tasty meal. Before you can even make heads or tails of his reaction the changes revert. Curious, only way to fix this is to cast more spells to influence the residual magic flowing through your subject.
</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>With a great blue splash your spell slams into your targets chest and flows through him. The changes are nearly instantaneous. His body changes so fast he is thrown off balance, wings sprouting behind him and with its own force knocks him down against the ground. You watch intensively at the newly changed avian, the spell seeming complete as the bird sits before you complete with feathers, wings, beak, tail... And just as you were going through your mental check list your subject seems to have second guesses and undoes your spell. Looks like he will be needing some more persuasion.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>A burst of blue emits from your target as your spell forces them into an explosion of change. The spell rips through your target and as the bright blue light dies off you can see your subject laying against his back, a total blue chaffinch! You study him as he sits up and when he begins to sing out happily you are reassured that the spell will stick this time.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>You toss a concentrated blue mist orb at your opponent and watch as it breaks over her head. she looks confused at first and look to you before noticing her changes. She reveals to herself her blue skin and claws before it simply washes away as the spell didn't have enough power to complete the change. That's quite alright as you are sure more of the same will cake on the effects.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>Your spell hits right against your targets head and proceeds to trickle down against her. The spell quickly dispersing and the changes quickly become apparent. Leaving your subject to examine her new birdlike hands and feet before the spell breaks form and she reverts back to normal. Seems like the spell can use quite a bit more reinforcement.
</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>Your target doesn't have time to react as your little blue orb hits and splashes against her body. The magic works quick and in no time she is covered with blue feathers. You nod to yourself, thankful that you are making progress but it is apparent to you that you will need to continue to enforce the spell for it to fully take root.
</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>Your blue orb flies over your target and slightly expands before rushing down over her. The changes come rapidly, feathers awash her form just before a tail sprouts out behind her along with a beak against her face. She squawks out in surprise at the changes. You can't tell but you think you see her lick her beak at you as if you were a tasty meal. Before you can even make heads or tails of her reaction the changes revert. Curious, only way to fix this is to cast more spells to influence the residual magic flowing through your subject.
</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>With a great blue splash your spell slams into your targets chest and flows through her. The changes are nearly instantaneous. Her body changes so fast she is thrown off balance, wings sprouting behind her and with its own force knocks her down against the ground. You watch intensively at the newly changed avian, the spell seeming complete as the bird sits before you complete with feathers, wings, beak, tail... And just as you were going through your mental check list your subject seems to have second guesses and undoes your spell. Looks like she will be needing some more persuasion.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>A burst of blue emits from your target as your spell forces them into an explosion of change. The spell rips through your target and as the bright blue light dies off you can see your subject laying against her back, a total blue chaffinch! You study him as he sits up and when he begins to sing out happily you are reassured that the spell will stick this time.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>

</Form>
