<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>You try to dodge, but the boomerang clicks together around your neck, forming an electronic looking choker followed by a soft prick to your skin that you did not notice. The device further clicks and a pair of in-ear monitors slides itself into your ear. You feel disorientated as you hear meaningless and high-pitch buzzes and beeps, much like those from a computer modem or fax machine. Gathering yourself, you will some magic into your hand and tear off the device, freeing yourself of the annoying noise. Though you can’t help but worry that the damage has already been done.
 </TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>Suddenly, you feel rather warm and the sweat pores around your neck seem to go into overdrive. You are shocked when the sweat around your neck coalesces and reforms the necklace. This time there’s no headphones but you hear the beeps and buzzes anyway. Instead of disorientating, the buzzes feel soothing to your confused mind. Wait, are those numbers? For some reason you think you can almost taste them on your tongue as you lick your dry lips. Realizing something is not right, you rip the collar off your neck, glaring at your adversary. It might be your imagination but you think you see your skin changing back to normal from a matte white texture.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>Your eyes glaze over as you start hearing faint beeps and buzzes in your head again. Though this time you are able to understand the noise as voices. 'Quantum Gates in place… Physical conditioning at (69%) …Download complete! Initiating root personality core partition… Converting neural pathways... Language and ethics modules download has begun... Basic motion module download complete. Fine tuning Servos in…5…4…3…2…1…0.00000002163' The feeling of your limbs and fingers suddenly going through a series of very coordinated flexes, turns and rotation snaps you out of the trance and to your horror you find yourself performing inhumanly graceful motions with your segmented limbs and joints. In your panic, you sent out a surge of counter-spell, reversing the changes. As your flesh once again replaces the synthetic components, you can’t help but stumble clumsily, missing the grace of motion the augmented cybernetic parts afforded you.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>Without warning you start hearing the voice again, though it seems to have taken a more female tone. 'Load Augmented Reality UI 100% complete...' Digital overlays immediately starts highlighting everything of interest around you, flooding your mind with an unprecedented wealth of information. Most notably the offending mage standing in front of you. You feel confused as any lingering hostility you feel towards your adversary dissipates as the UI designates the silhouette as Friend. You can’t help but smile and nod at the figure yet it all feels so wrong. 'Initiating Fembot module…' Wait, What?! 'Downloading emotional cue recognition software… Installing Seduction files…' No! No! No! Abort! Abort! The action is stopped short when a loud buzzer noise echoes through your head. 'WARNING! Core personality conflict! Process terminated.' Just as suddenly as it started, the voices and highlights disappears, leaving you more confused and disoriented than ever.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>The voices return again, though you vaguely register yourself mouthing the words before a soothing buzz takes over. 'Resuming download of pre-programmed sub-routines... Advanced reactionary sub-routines complete… Finalizing Basic Bot capabilities... Initializing Advanced Bot functionalities...' You feel an odd sense of fulfillment at the last line of command.
 
'Fembot protocol initiated. Reconfiguring body frame parameters to default Fembot_1. Downloading Etiquette and Pleasure Module… Dom/Sub subroutine installed…' You feel a surge of panic as the new commands flashes through your mind, feeling your body reshaping itself with new parameters into what you know is optimized for pleasure. With it a wealth of knowledge on more sex than you ever cared to know about.
 
'WARNING! Initiation of Core Personality at this stage is premature… Recommend full system reboot in Tabula Rasa to avoid future conflict.
Proceed? (Y/N)'
In a herculean feat of will you manage to override the command and wrest your life back, purging the changes with your magic. The damage has already been done though, as you feel a pang of sadness for not completing your programming. As you glare at your opponent, you can’t help but feel conflicting desire to show them who’s the boss or to get down on all four to please them.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>'Blank state reboot achieved. Mental Conditioning Efficiency increased by factor of 12. Core personality and backup partition in stand-by. Unpacking Exotic_Dance.exe… Synchronizing with cloud archives of existing kinks… Hidden Les_Sapph files detected… blowjob subroutine installed… Unpacking Positions… Synchronizing files… Building Behaviour Matrix Template… Arousal Detection System Online… Initiate lubrication subroutine… Finalizing Fembot Protocols... Re-establishing link to Root Personality Core… Full System Reboot.ini… 
 
Fembot Online.'

You feel yourself back in full control of your faculties. Lines of commands flooding your mind and you feel tiny tinges of pleasure as each little objective are met. Your enhanced optical module takes in the person who did this to you and you immediately catalogue their body language. A predatory smile flashes across your synthetic features as you feel your ADS kick in as your nipples tent and viscous droplets of lube are released from your core.
 
</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>“Compatible target detected.” A robotic voice suddenly announced over your music, surprising you as you assess your latest victim. Hm… Why not? You think as you pull out the old headphones that now resemble a boomerang and charge it with your magic before hurling it at your target, making sure the trajectory stays true. You feel the media player vibrate in your pocket as the device clicks itself around your target’s neck. Pressing the play button that has appeared on the screen, you watch in fascination as a pair of ear plugs jams themselves into their ear. Your target winces and stumbles but tears off the device with little problem though you’re not worried as the display in your hands now reads “Base Nanites implanted. Base Module ready for deployment in 1 minute 11 seconds.” in 1 minute 11 seconds.”</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>You hear a small alert tone and the device vibrates again, grabbing your attention. “Base module ready for deployment. Initiate? (Y/N)” Smiling, you press affirmative and your target looks bewildered as the cybernetic necklace forms around their neck, stopping them in their tracks as they stare blankly into space. You notice their skin tone begins to take a white, synthetic appearance before they manage to shrug it off with their magic and glare at you. You hear an alert tone and the display reads “ERROR. Unexpected interruption detected. Redeployment ready in 30 seconds”</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>Another buzz and you know the nanites are ready again. Pushing the button without looking your opponent’s eyes glazed over and their body grows rigid as the nanites continue their work. Seams and panels begin forming around joints, giving you glimpse of circuitry and servos forming in their body. All of a  sudden your opponent’s body jerks to attention “Running Mobility Diagnostics…” the voice, while unmistakably human, sounds mechanical as your target begins to move and flex every individual joints in pin-point precision which you can’t help but feel envious of. Unfortunately, the sudden motion seems to kick your target back to their senses as they quickly purge the changes with their spell, reverting back into their original form. As expected, a cursory look at your screen reveals the same error message you received earlier.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>This time, the changes come more rapidly and more pronounced as you push down the button. You think you hear mechanical whirling as your target’s eye loses its watery flesh and blood look and become a pair of slightly glowing optic camera housed in its newer ceramic and glass housing. You’re surprised when your target smiles and nods at you before suddenly snarling in anger and confusion as they dispel the transformation with magic again.
 </TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>This time you are ready and press the button exactly as the buzz announcing it is ready goes off. Your target freezes again and starts reporting their status in a digitized voice. As the Fembot subroutine kicks in, you are treated to a pleasant show as your target’s body reconfigures itself into a killer female body template. Unfortunately just before the transformation is completed, your victim manages to overpower and reverse the transformation.
 </TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>Finally! You smile happily as your victim feature shifts rapidly into her final form. Worthy of fembots everywhere. You can almost hear the click in her head as she comes online. Upon seeing you, you can’t help but notice her seductive smile and pose as she hypnotically sashays towards you. Everything she does is so incredibly erotic you can’t help but feel aroused. You’re startled out of your trance when you suddenly hear “Compatible target detected.” And the fembot smiles knowingly at you.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>“Compatible target detected.” A robotic voice suddenly announces over your music, surprising you as you assess your latest victim. Hm… Why not? You think as you pull out the old headphones that now resemble a boomerang and charge it with your magic before hurling it at your target, making sure the trajectory stays true. You feel the media player vibrate in your pocket as the device clicks itself around your target’s neck. Pressing the play button that has appeared on the screen, you watch in fascination as a pair of ear plugs jams themselves into his ears. Your target winces and stumbles but tears off the device with little problem though you’re not worried as the display in your hands now reads “Base Nanites implanted. Base Module ready for deployment in 1 minute 11 seconds.”Nanites implanted. Base Module ready for deployment in 1 minute 11 seconds.”</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>You hear a small alert tone and the device vibrates again, grabbing your attention. “Base module ready for deployment. Initiate? (Y/N)” Smiling, you press affirmative and your target looks bewildered as the cybernetic necklace forms around his neck, stopping him in his tracks as he stares blankly into space. You notice his skin tone begin to take a white, synthetic appearance before he manages to shrug it off with his magic and glare at you. You hear an alert tone and the display reads “Unexpected interruption detected. Redeployment ready in 30 seconds”</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>Another buzz and you know the nanites are ready again. Pushing the button without looking your opponent’s eyes glazed over and his body grew rigid as the nanites continue their work. Seams and panels begin forming around joints, giving you glimpse of circuitry and servos forming in his body. All the sudden your opponent’s body jerks into attention “Running Mobility Diagnostics…” the voice, while unmistakably human sounded mechanical as your target begins to move and flex every individual joints in pin-point precision which you can’t help but feel envious of. Unfortunately, the sudden motion seems to kick your target back in his senses as they quickly purge the changes with his spell, reverting back into his original form. As expected, a cursory look at your screen reveals the same error message you received earlier.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>This time, the changes come more rapidly and more pronounced as you push down the button. You thought you hear mechanical whirling as your target’s eye loses its watery flesh and blood look and become a pair of slightly glowing optic camera housed in it’s newer ceramic and glass housing. You’re surprised when he smiles and nods at you before suddenly snarling in anger and confusion as he dispels the transformation with magic again.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>This time you are ready and press the button exactly as the buzz announcing it is ready goes off. Your target freezes again and starts reporting their status in a digitized voice. As the Fembot subroutine kicks in, you are treated to a pleasant show as your target’s very male body starts reconfiguring itself into a killer female body template. Unfortunately just before the transformation is completed, he manages to overpower and reverse the transformation.
 </TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>Finally! You smile happily as your victim's features shift rapidly into her final form, worthy of fembots everywhere. You can almost hear the click in her head as she comes online. Upon seeing you, you can’t help but notice her seductive smile and pose as she hypnotically sashays towards you. Everything she does is so incredibly erotic you can’t help but feel aroused. You’re startled out of your trance when you suddenly hear “Compatible target detected.” And the fembot smiles knowingly at you.
 </TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>“Compatible target detected.” A robotic voice suddenly announces over your music, surprising you as you assess your latest victim. Hm… Why not? You think as you pull out the old headphones that now resemble a boomerang and charge it with your magic before hurling it at your target, making sure the trajectory stays true. You feel the media player vibrate in your pocket as the device clicks itself around your target’s neck. Pressing the play button that has appeared on the screen, you watch in fascination as a pair of ear plugs jams themselves into her ears. Your target winces and stumbles but tears off the device with little problem though you’re not worried as the display in your hands now reads “Base Nanites implanted. Base Module ready for deployment in 1 minute 11 seconds.”deployment in 1 minute 11 seconds.”</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>You hear a small alert tone and the device vibrates again, grabbing your attention. “Base module ready for deployment. Initiate? (Y/N)” Smiling, you press affirmative and your target looks bewildered as the cybernetic necklace forms around her neck, stopping her in her tracks as she stares blankly into space. You notice her skin tone begin to take a white, synthetic appearance before she manages to shrug it off with her magic and glare at you. You hear an alert tone and the display reads “Unexpected interruption detected. Redeployment ready in 30 seconds”</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>Another buzz and you know the nanites are ready again. Pushing the button without looking your opponent’s eyes glazed over and her body grew rigid as the nanites continue their work. Seams and panels begin forming around joints, giving you glimpse of circuitry and servos forming in her body. All the sudden your opponent’s body jerks into attention “Running Mobility Diagnostics…” the voice, while unmistakably human sounded mechanical as your target begins to move and flex every individual joints in pin-point precision which you can’t help but feel envious of. Unfortunately, the sudden motion seems to kick your target back in her senses as they quickly purge the changes with her spell, reverting back into his original form. As expected, a cursory look at your screen reveals the same error message you received earlier.
 
 </TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>This time, the changes come more rapidly and more pronounced as you push down the button. You thought you hear mechanical whirling as your target’s eye loses its watery flesh and blood look and become a pair of slightly glowing optic camera housed in its newer ceramic and glass housing. You’re surprised when she smiles and nods at you before suddenly snarling in anger and confusion as she dispels the transformation with magic again.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>This time you are ready and press the button exactly as the buzz announcing it is ready goes off. Your target freezes again and starts reporting their status in a digitized voice. As the Fembot subroutine kicks in, you are treated to a pleasant show as your target’s body reconfigures itself into a killer body template. Unfortunately just before the transformation is completed, your victim manages to overpower and reverse the transformation.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>Finally! You smile happily as your victim's features shift rapidly into her final form, worthy of fembots everywhere. You can almost hear the click her head as she comes online. Upon seeing you, you can’t help but notice her seductive smile and pose as she hypnotically sashays towards you. Everything she does is so incredibly erotic you can’t help but feel aroused. You’re started out of your trance when you suddenly hear “Compatible target detected.” And the fembot smiles knowingly at you.
 </TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>

</Form>
