<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>Your attacker's spell hits you... you begin to feel taller, almost more powerful, as a warm energy courses through you. You look at yourself to see your skin slightly darker than before and realize what's going on. You quickly shake off the spell and continue with the battle at hand.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>Again your attacker's spell hits you. Pleasure courses through your whole body as you feel a warm but yet gentle grasp close around you. Suddenly it all leaves you as you remember what is going on. With a flick of your hand you return to normal</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>This time the spell takes you by surprise hitting you square in the chest. Words and symbols start flowing through your head and you begin chanting almost in a trance. But you are not quite that far gone and you change back but with a little more trouble than before.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>With this hit you are almost completely lost in the symbols floating in front of your eyes. So much meaning and potential in these letters.  You feel your features change slightly and your hair turns black. You are just about to let go when you come to. Hurriedly you change back to your normal form.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>Your whole body courses with power, your magic seemingly more concentrated. Your hair is now completely black and your skin a rich caramel color. Your eyes have also turned a magnificent green but you don't notice. This seems... fitting, you think, until you realize this is not you but may be soon.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>The Spell of the attacker hits you. This time there is no turning back. Your skin is a rich caramel, your hair raven black, and eyes emerald green. The voice of Ra is behind you guiding you through whatever he wills you to do. Smiling you set out to convert more followers to his cause.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>Your attacker's spell hits you... you begin to feel taller, almost more powerful, as a warm energy courses through you. You look at yourself to see your skin slightly darker than before and realize what's going on. You quickly shake off the spell and continue with the battle at hand.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>Again your attacker's spell hits you. Pleasure courses through your whole body as you feel a warm but yet gentle grasp close around you. Suddenly it all leaves you as you remember what is going on. With a flick of your hand you return to normal</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>This time the spell takes you by surprise hitting you square in the chest. Words and symbols start flowing through your head and you begin chanting almost in a trance. But you are not quite that far gone and you change back but with a little more trouble than before.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>With this hit you are almost completely lost in the symbols floating in front of your eyes. So much meaning and potential in these letters.  You feel your features change slightly and your hair turns black. Orbs of flesh bounce on your chest and the weight feels... welcome. You are just about to let go when you come to. Hurriedly you change back to your normal form.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>Your whole body courses with power, your magic seemingly more concentrated. Your hair is now completely black and your skin a rich caramel color. Your eyes have also turned a magnificent green but you don't notice.  Even your figure has begun to change into a curvy hourglass form. This seems... fitting, you think, until you realize this is not you but may be soon.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>The Spell of the attacker hits you. This time there is no turning back. Your skin is a rich caramel, your hair raven black, and eyes emerald green. The voice of Ra is behind you guiding you through whatever he wills you to do. Smiling you set out to convert more followers to his cause.</TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>Your attacker's spell hits you... you begin to feel taller, almost more powerful, as a warm energy courses through you. You look at yourself to see your skin slightly darker than before and realize what's going on. You quickly shake off the spell and continue with the battle at hand.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>Again your attacker's spell hits you. Pleasure courses through your whole body as you feel a warm but yet gentle grasp close around you. Suddenly it all leaves you as you remember what is going on. With a flick of your hand you return to normal</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>This time the spell takes you by surprise hitting you square in the chest. Words and symbols start flowing through your head and you begin chanting almost in a trance. But you are not quite that far gone and you change back but with a little more trouble than before.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>With this hit you are almost completely lost in the symbols floating in front of your eyes. So much meaning and potential in these letters.  You feel your features change slightly and your hair turns black. You are just about to let go when you come to. Hurriedly you change back to your normal form.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>Your whole body courses with power, your magic seemingly more concentrated. Your hair is now completely black and your skin a rich caramel color. Your eyes have also turned a magnificent green but you don't notice. This seems... fitting, you think, until you realize this is not you but may be soon.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>The Spell of the attacker hits you. This time there is no turning back. Your skin is a rich caramel, your hair raven black, and eyes emerald green. The voice of Ra is behind you guiding you through whatever he wills you to do. Smiling you set out to convert more followers to his cause.</TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>Your spell hits your enemy, causing them to stumble. Their skin is darkening almost to a light coffee color and their facial features seem to readjust before they snap to and reverse the changes.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>Your enemy isn't struggling just yet but they sense the power they could have if they only let go. Slowly their clothes change into a transparent skirt and shawl. Realizing this change they mumble a quick spell, reversing all the changes.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>This time you opponent is struggling more with the power. They are lost in thought while their body takes on a beautiful hourglass figure with black hair and caramel skin. The transformation is almost complete, however it does not hold and they are able to change back.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>With each and every blow it seems to be getting harder for them to hold on to their current form. If they would only let go Ra would bless them with his presence and guide them to do his magnificent will. But yet again the spell is not strong enough and they change back.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>The transformation is almost complete as your opponent grasps at their breasts, almost able to see through the linen shawl and fully able to see their darker skin. For what seems a while they begin to think this is normal until they see the caramel color filling their fingertips. Then the spell is lost and they struggle to change back.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>Finally the last hit does it. Their body is a rich and beautiful hourglass figure, their hair cascading in frightening raven black hair, and their emerald eyes gleam with a dangerous light. Your opponent realizes their new potential as a servant of Ra and revels in their new found form. </TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
