<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<Description>You are a staff, a long staff that is constantly thinking about other long, thick staff like objects. Your lusty powers radiates all around you as others pick up on your lewd thoughts, making men and women squirm as you expose their secret fantasies. Maybe if you are lucky you can even enslave them to your desires!</Description>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>A blast of energy hits you, but it only annoys you slightly. You look towards your attacker and consider what sort of punishment is proper for such a naughty person. A nice spanking, a whipping, dripping hot wax all over their body while licking it up...However once you consider a good punishment they are already gone!</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>You are blasted again! You turn around, looking for the little slut that shot you. You are going to tie her down and beat her cute little ass. Yeah, beat it until it is red, and then stuff a ball gag in her mouth and fuck her all night long. That will teach her a lesson! Of course, you focus on revenge you don't even see who it was that actually attacked you and they get away.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>You can't get the lewd thought out of your mind. A powerful woman walks by leading a sexy pony girl down the street and you wonder what it would be like to be the pony, or the mistress? You then look around and spot a little school slut bend over, her body being slapped with a paddle. That is pretty hot, very hot. You suck in a deep breath as arousal fills your body. However you can't do anything but just stand there and watch the lewd displays all around. As you stand there your skin starts to grow shiny and more slick, slick like a woman's well fucked pussy...Suddenly you come to your senses.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>You are frozen once again as you watch the lewd displays around you. Women in tight fitting latex outfits, large men in masks and tight pants, all sort of people tied up and squirming as lewd toys are used on them. You could be a lewd toy used on them, you wouldn't mind that. Mmm that sounds kind of sexy in fact...Your body tenses even tighter as your body begins to thin and narrow in an unnatural way and your arms pull in closer to your body. Your legs press together as they begin to fuse. You will love being a little toy...Wait! No, your not the toy in your fantasy, your the master! You take a deep breath as you break free.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>Your body rapidly narrows as your clothing falls off. Your body grows slick and shiny as lewd thoughts send waves of pleasure from you. You turn into a long staff and fall to the ground as your mind goes to another place...You are in a dungeon, the lewd moans of women fill the air. You don't have a body but you can float around the room and you watch as a sexy girl spills hot wax over the heavy tits of a little slut. Yeah take that slut, you been a naughty girl! You turn and a girl is laying on top of a wooden horse, and a women in black tight fitting latex, slaps teases the handle of a whip against her pussy, "You loving the pain yet slut?" She smiles and takes a step back and whips her across her tits.

Suddenly you and taken out of your fantasy as you are touched and you find yourself laying on the ground. You struggle and squirm as you slowly focus on regrowing your arms, then your legs, and after much effort you break the spell.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>You moan hotly as you are hit with the spell once more and your are once more in that sexy dungeon. The lewd cries filling the room, making your body shiver, but were you man or woman? No your a staff, that is right! You are laying in bed and two women in skin tight latex are pressed up against you. Their soft tits rub and stroke against your body as they polish you with cleaning rags. You moan out, "That is right sluts, clean your masters shaft." They giggle as you slip between their breasts as they crush up against each other. Tits on all side of you as they rub your long shaft while they make out. "Mmm yes, being a staff is a nice life..."

You come to your senses and find yourself laying on the ground unmoving. The tip of your body starts to glow with magic and you use it as an eye to sense and scan the area around you before spotting the person that attacked you. "Slave, pick me up and lets go find some sluts...Maybe we can find some twins..." Yeah that would be pretty sexy.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>You smile as you remember the dungeon and the lewd moans and you begin to chant, trying to trap their mind in that same state, the state of lust and ecstasy. It doesn't seem to stick however, and now they look like they want revenge! You quickly hide and gather up more power for your next attack.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>You hit them once again, and their eyes seem to glaze over as their mind sinks into a fantasy of sex and desire, and hidden fetishes. You smile as you wonder what sort of lewd thoughts they might be happening, but then you notice them staring at you and you get the impression they might want to tie you down and beat your little ass. You quickly turn and run!</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>You hit them again and their eyes glaze. You notice them looking towards as passing woman with her pet pony girl, then towards a school slut who is bend over with her skirt up, a teacher paddling her ass for being naughty. Just normal every day things around here, but your target seems to be absorbed by the images, falling deeper into your spell by the moment. Just a little more power and they will be yours!</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Their body quickly starts to narrow, becoming smooth and slick as they start to look like a staff. Yes, now you are making some real progress. A sexy staff for a sexy wizard. You walk over towards it to pick it up but it begins to pulse with magic. You gasp as you are hit with a wave of pleasure and for a moment you are back in that dungeon, hearing the lewd moans of pleasure. You shake your head slightly to come to your senses but your new staff has escaped!</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Zap! They are a staff once again and they fall to the ground with a light thud. Easy shot! You smile as you walk over to pick up your new toy when suddenly a pulse of magic hits you. You find yourself in the dungeon once again, and you spot your target, floating in the area like a ghost of their former self. You watch them as they watch lewd scenes play out. You watch as a sexy girl spills hot wax over the heavy tits of a little slut. You turn and a girl is laying on top of a wooden horse, and a women in black tight fitting latex, slaps teases the handle of a whip against her pussy, "You loving the pain yet slut?" She smiles and takes a step back and whips her across her tits.

Your break out of the daze and reach for your new staff only to find it struggle and wiggling on the ground as arms and legs start to slowly reform. "Damn doesn't this idiot ever give up. I want a new staff already!"</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>You focus all your power and slam it hard into your target! They crumple over and they are a staff once more. You decide to stay back this time, waiting for the pulses of energy coming from the staff to weaken. You catch slight images of woman clad in latex outfit, making out as they polish your new staff. It seems the staff has accepted it's new life after all.

Suddenly the tip of the staff flashes and glows and a voice calls out to you. "Slave, pick me up and lets go find some sluts...Maybe we can find some twins..." You laugh slightly as you walk over and pick up the staff. What an idiot, it can't really think it is the master can it?</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
