<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>You startle as the spell suddenly impacts your body, and blink as you feel your ears change shape and move higher on your head for a brief moment before you counter the spell's effects.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>Again the spell hits you, but you gasp to find that your body seems to have shrunk a little, your shoulders narrowing and your hips widening as you decrease a few inches in height, and you yelp as your manhood shrinks a little between your legs as well. You're about to counter the spell, but then you see a moth, and pause for a moment, raising a hand to bat at it lightly. Suddenly realizing how open you are leaving yourself, you quickly counter the spell, blushing and looking at your opponent in indignation.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>You give a startled yelp as the spell hits you full-force, and to your horror you hear the yelp turn into a distressed meow. Your ears change their shape again, and once again, your hips widen as your shoulders narrow, and you can feel your butt expand a little in your bottom clothes. But then, a new pressure emerges from your hindquarters, and you give another meow as a soft, cute kitty tail springs from above your large, round cheeks. The tail swishes, then wraps around your waist as you blush, biting your now...plumper lips. With no little amount of effort, you manage to reverse the changes before you get distracted again, but the feeling lingers for a moment, making you look at your opponent shyly and shift on your feet before you slowly get back into your battle stance.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>You meow again, the spell almost making you fall to your knees, its effects taking advantage of your weakening state and changing you back, your body going back to a feminine form, your tail and ears again making their presence known. Down below, your package shrinks drastically, and while it thankfully does not disappear altogether, it is now rather...cute rather than masculine. There's a tingling sensation behind your eyes, and should you glance into a nearby reflective surface, you may catch your pupils becoming vertical slits, like a cat's. You hug your tail to your chest as if it is your only friend, meowing at your opponent pleadingly to change you back...you don't wanna be a kitty...do you?  The sudden doubt jars you. Would you possibly want to be like this? You shake it off, however, and through a great amount of concentration, you manage to revert yourself....but you know now that you cannot resist much more of this...if you wish to resist at all...</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>This time, the spell does bring you to your knees. You give a distressed meow, your features changing back to their feline feminine states, your tail swishing behind you in a panic. Your hips widen as your waist and shoulders narrow, the changes so exhausting you that you cannot get back your feet...your tail and ears spring into place, as well as your eyes, and your fingernails lengthen lightly, taking on the appearance of claws, though the ends are dulled and too short to be of any real use in a fight. You find your mind wandering, making it harder and harder to focus on reverting, and you can hear, with your new ears, your opponent striding up to you. With your final ounce of will, you force yourself back to your feet, changing back and giving a defiant look at your opponent, but deep down, you and your opponent both know that unless some miracle happens, this fight is practically over.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>You cannot resist the spell any longer. With a last, panicked meow, you fall back into your rotund ass, the spell wasting no time to change you into the catboy you are to become. You meow helplessly, rolling over onto your stomach and trying to stand, to run, but you cannot get up past your knees, so weak as you are. Your tail swishes above your now large, rotund ass, your cute kitty package making a petite bulge through what is left of your bottom clothes. Footsteps approach, and you look up to see the shoes of your opponent, and gulp. This is the end....you wait for the spell that will end your life, but instead, you feel...a hand, lightly caressing the top of your head before moving down to your cheek. Instinctively, your nuzzle your cheek against the hand, a small purr exiting your throat as you realize....this may not be so bad after all...
**You have been transformed into a Kitten Boi!**</TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>You startle as the spell suddenly impacts your body, and blink as you feel your ears change shape and move higher on your head for a brief moment before you counter the spell's effects.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>Again the spell hits you, but you gasp to find that your body seems to change a little, your breasts shrinking into your chest as you decrease a few inches in height. You yelp as you feel a pressure between your legs, along with a slight pinch as your vagina dissappears, your clit growing and shifting until it becomes a small femboy sized cock. You're about to counter the spell, but then you see a moth, and pause for a moment, raising a hand to bat at it lightly. Suddenly realizing how open you are leaving yourself, you quickly counter the spell, blushing and looking at your opponent in indignation.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>You give a startled yelp as the spell hits you full-force, and to your horror you hear the yelp turn into a distressed meow. Your ears change their shape again, and once again, your breasts and vagina disappear, replaced by a femboy cock, though you feel your butt expand a little in your bottom clothes. But then, a new pressure emerges from your hindquarters, and you give another meow as a soft, cute kitty tail springs from above your large, round cheeks. The tail swishes, then wraps around your waist as you blush, biting your lip. With no little amount of effort, you manage to reverse the changes before you get distracted again, but the feeling lingers for a moment, making you look at your opponent shyly and shift on your feet before you slowly get back into your battle stance.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>You meow again, the spell almost making you fall to your knees, its effects taking advantage of your weakening state and changing you back, your body going back to femboy form, your tail and ears again making their presence known as your breasts' presences exit. You whimper as you feel your cunt fade away into your body, leaving you with a cock, though not an impressive one by any rate; if anything, it could be considered...cute. There's a tingling sensation behind your eyes, and should you glance into a nearby reflective surface, you may catch your pupils becoming vertical slits, like a cat's. You hug your tail to your chest as if it is your only friend, meowing at your opponent pleadingly to change you back...you don't wanna be a kitty...do you?  The sudden doubt jars you. Would you possibly want to be like this? You shake it off, however, and through a great amount of concentration, you manage to revert yourself....but you know now that you cannot resist much more of this...if you wish to resist at all...</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>This time, the spell does bring you to your knees. You give a distressed meow, your features changing back to their feline states, your tail swishing behind you in a panic. Your chest flattens even as your hips widen slightly and your cock returns at the price of your vagina, the changes so exhausting you that you cannot get back your feet...your tail and ears spring into place, as well as your eyes, and your fingernails lengthen lightly, taking on the appearance of claws, though the ends are dulled and too short to be of any real use in a fight. You find your mind wandering, making it harder and harder to focus on reverting, and you can hear, with your new ears, your opponent striding up to you. With your final ounce of will, you force yourself back to your feet, changing back and giving a defiant look at your opponent, but deep down, you and your opponent both know that unless some miracle happens, this fight is practically over.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>You cannot resist the spell any longer. With a last, panicked meow, you fall back into your ass, the spell wasting no time to change you into the catboy you are to become. You meow helplessly, rolling over onto your stomach and trying to stand, to run, but you cannot get up past your knees, so weak as you are. Your tail swishes above your now large, rotund ass, your cute kitty package making a petite bulge through what is left of your bottom clothes. Footsteps approach, and you look up to see the shoes of your opponent, and gulp. This is the end....you wait for the spell that will end your life, but instead, you feel...a hand, lightly caressing the top of your head before moving down to your cheek. Instinctively, your nuzzle your cheek against the hand, a small purr exiting your throat as you realize....this may not be so bad after all...
**You have been transformed into a Kitten Boi!**</TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>Your target blinks as the spell hits him, his ears shifting lightly, seeming to try to climb to the top of his head before he brushes the spell off with a flick of his wrist.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>Your opponent recoils from the impact of the spell, flinching. He seems to shrink in height, his hips widening as his shoulders narrow. He looks at you, and seems ready to counter the spell, when he suddenly sees a moth and bats at it lightly. The distraction only lasts a moment, however, and he sheepishly reverses the changes.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>Your opponent yelps, but then the yelp becomes a meow as the changes take hold, his body shrinking and feminizing as his ears pop up onto the stop of his head, folding back in distress. His hands suddenly fly to his growing butt, but it doesn't seem to be his rapidly expanding cheeks that have his attention...a moment later, a soft black cat tail springs up from behind him, swishing then wrapping around his waist. He looks at you shyly for a moment, then concentrates, reverting his changes, though the shy look in his eyes never seems to waver...</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>Your target recoils under the onslaught, almost losing his balance. Once again, he shrinks and feminizes, his tail and ears readily appearing. You can tell he cannot take much more of this. He looks at you, his eyes changing from the normal human pupils to cat pupils, a distressed meow escaping his petite, plump mouth as he shifts his wide hips, his tail swishing behind him for a moment. He takes a second to compose himself, then reverts back, but it is obvious the fight is leaving him. </TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>Your opponent falls to his knees, the spell quickly overtaking him and changing him into his catboi form once more. His tail swishes above him, and it is rather obvious where this fight is going. You notice that his small, feminine hands develop claws, but even from your position you can tell they are more for looks than as weapons. You advance upon your opponent, preparing to finalize this transformation, but then they push to their feet, eyeing you defiantly before managing to reverse the changes back to his original form. However, you are sure that it will only take one more spell or two to finish this fight...</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>This fight is more or less over. Your opponent falls backwards onto his round, bubble butt, then tries to roll over to stand, but the changes wash over him like a tidal wave and sap his remaining energy, his body too weak to resist for even a second longer. Soon, the now-catboy is left quivering in the wake of the changes, unable to move or even stand. Confident in your victory, you approach him, looking down at the poor kitty before reaching down, petting his soft hair and scratching his ears before caressing his cheek. You are rewarded with a low purr from his throat, and an assurance that your victory is sound and lasting....
**You have transformed (Caster) into a Kitten Boi!**</TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>Your target blinks as the spell hits her, her ears shifting lightly, seeming to try to climb to the top of her head before she brushes the spell off with a flick of her wrist.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>Your opponent recoils from the impact of the spell, flinching. She seems to shrink in height, her hips widening a little as her breasts shrink and disappear. She looks at you, and seems ready to counter the spell, when she suddenly sees a moth and bats at it lightly. The distraction only lasts a moment, however, and she sheepishly reverses the changes.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>Your opponent yelps, but then the yelp becomes a meow as the changes take hold, her body shrinking and femboy-izing as her ears pop up onto the stop of his head, folding back in distress and her chest flattens. Her hands suddenly fly to her growing butt, but it doesn't seem to be her rapidly expanding cheeks that have her attention...a moment later, a soft cat tail springs up from behind her,, swishing then wrapping around her waist. She looks at you shyly for a moment, then concentrates, reverting her changes, though the shy look in her eyes never seems to waver...</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>Your target recoils under the onslaught, almost losing her balance. Once again, she shrinks and femboy-izes, her tail and ears readily appearing. You can tell she cannot take much more of this. She looks at you, her eyes changing from the normal human pupils to cat pupils, a distressed meow escaping her petite, plump mouth as she shifts her wide hips, her tail swishing behind her for a moment before she hugs it close, looking at you shyly. She takes a second to compose herself, then reverts back, but it is obvious the fight is leaving her. </TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>Your opponent falls to her knees, the spell quickly overtaking her and changing her into a catboy once more. His tail swishes above him, and it is rather obvious where this fight is going. You notice that his small, feminine hands develop claws, but even from your position you can tell they are more for looks than as weapons. You advance upon your opponent, preparing to finalize this transformation, but then they push to their feet, eyeing you defiantly before managing to reverse the changes back to her original form. However, you are sure that it will only take one more spell or two to finish this fight...</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>This fight is more or less over. Your opponent falls backwards onto her now round, bubble butt, then tries to roll over to stand, but the changes wash over her like a tidal wave and sap her remaining energy, her body too weak to resist for even a second longer. Soon, the now-catboy is left quivering in the wake of the changes, unable to move or even stand. Confident in your victory, you approach him, looking down at the poor kitty before reaching down, petting his soft hair and scratching his ears before caressing his cheek. You are rewarded with a low purr from his throat, and an assurance that your victory is sound and lasting....
**You have transformed (Caster) into a Kitten Boi!**</TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>

</Form>
