<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>As you feel the spell hit you your nipples immediately harden. You scratch them idly, wondering what this spell is supposed to do before your chest bounces outwards into DD cups. As you put your hands over them to reverse the change you can't help but relish their warm weight with a quick squeeze.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>You feel the rumbling behind your nipples as they once again surge outwards into bouncy double Ds. You look down at them for a moment, then watch as they swell again, doubling in size. Es? Fs? You aren't familiar enough with bra sizes to know if they go this big, but you move your hands to either side of them to reverse the changes regardless, pressing your fingers into the soft, pliant flesh...</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>You stagger forwards, nearly falling over as your breasts expand, doubling and redoubling in size until you have to hold them in your arms just to keep upright. As their warm weight presses into your palms you can't help but heft them happily. They're not that bad. You could actually get used to these. You sigh as you run the magic through your hands into them, loath to see such beautiful breasts ruined.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>You topple forwards onto the ground as your new breasts combined weight is too much for you to hold. You land hard on top of them and brace for pain... but none comes, only a vast wealth of sensation flowing through them. They can't be that bad if they can't feel pain. You wrap your arms around their sides, and squeeze them as hard as you can, still just barely able to reach your nipples with the tips of your fingers. You lay there on the ground for awhile, groping your massive breasts and taking great pleasure in them before you snap out of it, again reducing their size back to something manageable.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>You lurch as the ludicrous breasts pull you forwards, catching you in an airbag of bouncy flesh as they hit the ground way before you do. You lie there in your own cleavage for a moment before trying to pull yourself out, your legs braced against the floor, before realizing that you can't lift them an inch. These things won't budge, you can't even stand! As you continue to pull against them you start to enjoy the sensations. Your arms begin toying and groping your hungry flesh with reckless abandon, your mind consumed by the gratifying pleasure of being squeezed. You come to your senses a little bit later than your forebrain would have liked.  Again you shrink them as your hindbrain calls out at this great injustice, destroying such perfect breasts. You stumble forwards, their great size no longer supporting you. </TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>You embrace your quickly swelling breasts, fingers digging satisfyingly into the flesh as they billow outwards. They grow unfailingly until they reach the ground, dragging your body down on top of them.  They continue their growth, pressing your body upwards, completely supported by these loving masses. They're even bigger than you are, lifting you up and pressing their warmth into you. Your feet touch the ground as if you were standing, but why would you want to? You are utterly entrenched in your own sensitive cleavage, your arms wrapped around their sides lovingly, not even close to being able to reach your nipples buried deep below you between your breasts and the ground. You don't think you'll be moving any time soon, but you can't think of a reason you would want to as you cling to your impossible breasts.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>As you feel the spell hit you your nipples immediately harden. You scratch them idly, wondering what this spell is supposed to do before your flat chest bounces outwards into DD cups. As you put your hands over them to reverse the change you can't help but relish their warm weight with a quick squeeze.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>You feel the rumbling behind your nipples as they once again surge outwards into bouncy double Ds. You feel other parts of your body start to shift towards more feminine features. You look down at them for a moment, then watch as they swell again, doubling in size. Es? Fs? You aren't familiar enough with bra sizes to know if they go this big, but you move your hands to either side of them to reverse the changes regardless, pressing your fingers into the soft, pliant flesh...</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>You stagger forwards, nearly falling over as your breasts expand, doubling and redoubling in size until you have to hold them in your arms just to keep upright. As their warm weight presses into your palms you can't help but heft them happily. They're not that bad. You could actually get used to these. You sway your now womanly hips side to side as you squeeze them. You sigh as you run the magic through your hands into them, loath to see such beautiful breasts ruined.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>You topple forwards onto the ground as your new breasts combined weight is too much for you to hold. You land hard on top of them and brace for pain... but none comes, only a vast wealth of sensation flowing through them. They can't be that bad if they can't feel pain. You wrap your arms around their sides, and squeeze them as hard as you can, still just barely able to reach your nipples with the tips of your fingers. You feel your manhood recede into you as it's replaced with a tight pussy, your body becoming completely female but you barely register it, your attention glued to your chest. You lay there on the ground for awhile, groping your massive breasts and taking great pleasure in them before you snap out of it, again reducing their size back to something manageable and restoring your male form.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>You lurch as the ludicrous breasts pull you forwards, catching you in an airbag of bouncy flesh as they hit the ground way before you do. Completely female, you lie there in your own cleavage for a moment before trying to pull yourself out, your legs braced against the floor, before realizing that you can't lift them an inch. These things won't budge, you can't even stand! As you continue to pull against them you start to enjoy the sensations. Your arms begin toying and groping your hungry flesh with reckless abandon, your mind consumed by the gratifying pleasure of being squeezed. You come to your senses a little bit later than your forebrain would have liked.  Again you shrink them as your hindbrain calls out at this great injustice, destroying such perfect breasts. You stumble forwards, their great size no longer supporting you. </TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>As you feel the spell hit you your nipples immediately harden. You scratch them idly, wondering what this spell is supposed to do before your breasts bounce outwards into DD cups. As you put your hands over them to reverse the change you can't help but relish their warm weight with a quick squeeze.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>You watch your spell connect with your target. They stare down at their chest, confused that nothing seems to be happening except for the clear hardening of their nipples. "Wait for it..." You think to yourself before their chest plumps outwards into a beautiful pair of double Ds. You laugh as you catch them cop a feel a bit before reversing the changes.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>Tits fit for a porn star burst forth from their chest, bouncing around before settling down. They were almost as big as their head now. You can't help but stare a little at their perfection, sitting high and firm on their chest, jiggling a little when they made the tiniest movement. They stare down at the heaving masses in amazement... or arousal? You can't tell which. What you can tell is the pleasure on their face as they push their hands into them to reverse the spell. </TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>They stagger forward, almost falling forwards as their chest bounces out in waves of soft flesh. They press their hands into them as if trying to stop their growth, unsuccessfully. As the growth slows the massive breasts are bigger than their head, and need the support of their arms so not to drag them to the ground. They jostle the boobs in their arms for a bit before seeming to snap out of it. You see a twinge of sadness across their face as they reverse the changes.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Your target topples forward onto the ground. Or onto their breasts rather, quickly expanding out in front of them to catch them like a giant pair of self-contained airbags. You know that it didn't hurt, those babies were magically designed for pure pleasure. You can see it in their face as they grab them, not even caring that they couldn't possibly reach their own nipples, wobbling themselves this way and that, trying to cover as much if their surface as they can with their hands. After a while of groping themselves on the floor they seem to come to their senses and remove the changes, standing themselves back up and wiping the dirt off their (now much smaller) chest.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Again they stumble as they fall into the enormous boobs growing rapidly and pulling them towards the ground. When they finish expanding they're leaning over them at a 90 degree angle and they probably weigh more than they do! They seem to go through several stages of loss as they realize that they can't move! They couldn't lift them if they tried, and how they tried! They wrap their arms around them as far as they could and began to pull, but they quickly become lost in the sensations and they descend into another groping session. The bliss on their face slowly fades and they reverse the changes with sadness in their eyes. </TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>That should do it! With one final burst you sling the spell at them, a direct hit! It lands directly between their breasts, their face becoming a mask of pleasure. The breasts you've worked so hard on billow out of their chest once again for the last time, expanding past the size of basketballs and beach balls and medicine balls and all other manner of sports equipment! As their fleshy bed fills out below them, they rest atop their gargantuan tits, a deep look of contentment across their face as they grope and squeeze every part of them that their arms can reach. You don't think they'll be moving any time soon.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>You watch your spell connect with him. He stares down at his chest, confused that nothing seems to be happening except for the clear hardening of his nipples. "Wait for it..." You think to yourself before his chest plumps outwards into a beautiful pair of double Ds. You laugh as you catch him cop a feel a bit before reversing the changes.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>Tits fit for a porn star burst forth from his chest, bouncing around before settling down. They're almost as big as his head now. You can't help but stare a little at their perfection, sitting high and firm on his chest, jiggling a little when he makes the tiniest movement.  The rest of his body slims down a bit, collecting feminine features here and there, but he doesn't notice. He stares down at the heaving masses in amazement... or arousal? You can't tell which. What you can tell is the pleasure on his face as he pushes his hands into them to reverse the spell. </TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>He staggers forward, almost falling as his chest bounces out in waves of soft flesh. He presses his hands into them as if trying to stop their growth, unsuccessfully. As the growth slows the massive breasts end up bigger than his head, and need the support of his arms so not to drag him to the ground. His hips plump outwards and you see his waist cinch inwards, creating a smooth hourglass silhouette. He jostles the boobs in his arms for a bit before seeming to snap out of it. You see a twinge of sadness across his face as he reverses the changes.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>He topples forward onto the ground. Or onto his breasts rather, quickly expanding out in front of him to catch him like a giant pair of self-contained airbags. You know that it didn't hurt, those babies were magically designed for pure pleasure. You can see it in his face as he grabs them, not even caring that he couldn't possibly reach his own nipples, wobbling himself this way and that, trying to cover as much if their surface as he can with his hands. It's hard to see most of his body from behind the mountains on his chest, but what you can see is now completely girl shaped. After a while of groping himself on the floor. he seem to come to his senses and removes the changes, standing himself back up and wiping the dirt off his (now much smaller) chest.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>Again he stumbles as he falls into the enormous boobs growing rapidly and pulling him towards the ground. When they finish expanding he's leaning over them at a 90 degree angle and they probably weigh more than he does! He's completely female now, but either he didn't notice or he doesn't care. He seems to go through several stages of loss as he realizes that he... she... can't move! She couldn't lift them if she tried, and how she tried! She wraps her arms around them as far as she could and began to pull, but she quickly becomes lost in the sensations and descends into another groping session. The bliss on her face slowly fades and they reverse the changes with sadness in her eyes. </TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>That should do it! With one final burst you sling the spell at them, a direct hit! It lands directly on his chest, their face becoming a mask of pleasure, the female factor of the transformation completing in an instant. The breasts you've worked so hard on billow out of her chest once again for the last time, expanding past the size of basketballs and beach balls and medicine balls and all other manner of sports equipment! As her fleshy bed fills out below her, she rests atop her gargantuan tits, a deep look of contentment across her face as she gropes and squeezes every part of them that her arms can reach. You don't think she'll be moving any time soon.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>You watch your spell connect with her. She stares down at her chest, confused that nothing seems to be happening except for the clear hardening of her nipples. "Wait for it..." You think to yourself before her chest plumps outwards into a beautiful pair of double Ds. You laugh as you catch her cop a feel a bit before reversing the changes.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>Tits fit for a porn star burst forth from her chest, bouncing around before settling down. They're almost as big as her head now. You can't help but stare a little at their perfection, sitting high and firm on her chest, jiggling a little when she makes the tiniest movement. She stares down at the heaving masses in amazement... or arousal? You can't tell which. What you can tell is the pleasure on her face as she pushes her hands into them to reverse the spell. </TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>She staggers forward, almost falling as her chest bounces out in waves of soft flesh. She presses her hands into them as if trying to stop their growth, unsuccessfully. As the growth slows the massive breasts end up bigger than her head, and need the support of her arms so not to drag her to the ground. She jostles the boobs in his arms for a bit before seeming to snap out of it. You see a twinge of sadness across her face as she reverses the changes.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>She topples forward onto the ground, or onto her breasts rather, quickly expanding out in front of her to catch her like a giant pair of self-contained airbags. You know that it didn't hurt, those babies were magically designed for pure pleasure. You can see it in her face as she grabs them, not even caring that she couldn't possibly reach her own nipples, wobbling herself this way and that, trying to cover as much if their surface as she can with her hands. After a while of groping herself on the floor, she seem to come to her senses and removes the changes, standing herself back up and wiping the dirt off her (now much smaller) chest.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>Again she stumbles as she falls into the enormous boobs growing rapidly and pulling her towards the ground. When they finish expanding she's leaning over them at a 90 degree angle and they probably weigh more than she does! She seems to go through several stages of loss as she realizes that she can't move! She couldn't lift them if she tried, and how she tried! She wraps her arms around them as far as she could and began to pull, but she quickly becomes lost in the sensations and descends into another groping session. The bliss on her face slowly fades and they reverse the changes with sadness in her eyes. </TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>That should do it! With one final burst you sling the spell at them, a direct hit! It lands directly between her breasts, her face becoming a mask of pleasure. The breasts you've worked so hard on billow out of her chest once again for the last time, expanding past the size of basketballs and beach balls and medicine balls and all other manner of sports equipment! As her fleshy bed fills out below her, she rests atop her gargantuan tits, a deep look of contentment across her face as she gropes and squeezes every part of them that her arms can reach. You don't think she'll be moving any time soon.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>

</Form>
