<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>Your opponent performs some type of exotic dance similar to a belly dance. Suddenly, they flick a wrist and cast a spell, catching you off guard and enveloping you in smoke. You cough slightly, but otherwise think you're okay. Did your foot just kick something? No matter, you wave the smoke away and cast a reversal spell to make sure there are no lingering effects you didn't notice...</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>Remembering a song from an old TV sitcom that starred Barbara Eden, you start to hum to yourself and miss when a spell from a rival mage hits you. A large cloud of colorful smoke engulfs you. You rub your irritated eyes as the smoke clears. Some of it that is. The rest seems to coalesce around your legs and feet. It almost looks like a pair of big poofy pants. Your foot bumping something, you look down and notice some ornate bottle. It looks like it would make a nice home. The strange thought snaps you out of your fugue state and you finally notice the changes the spell has caused to your body. You reverse the changes, feeling a bit sad as the antique bottle disappears...</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>You're thinking how a hookah could be used as decoration instead of smoking when you suddenly are hit by a spell that explodes into a large cloud of colorful smoke! You wave your hand around and doing so seems to clear the smog a bit, but you realize it's just moving how you wish. It's like you can command it! You start to move the smoke downwards, noticing a bottle nearby that would be the perfect place to store it. As the smoke travels away from your tanned skinned form, you slightly panic as you suddenly notice you can't feel your legs. You can't SEE your legs! It's just the smoke! Like you're some kind of... and then it clicks in your mind, you might be sucked into that bottle! You quickly cast a counter spell, reversing the changes and dissipating the smoke, the bottle disappearing along with them. You sigh in relief but then a thought strikes: aren't Genies extremely powerful magic users...?</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>For some reason, you're wondering who makes a better voice actor, Robin Williams or Dan Castellaneta when you feel a spell strike you. There's a sound like a poof as colorful smoke appears everywhere, but you quickly gather it below you, an easy task for a genie like you. You can feel the power just brimming inside you. You feel magical! You feel powerful! Phenomenal cosmic power is at your fingertips! That's when you feel a sucking sensation and finally notice the ornate bottle at your feet. You can't stop it, you're pulled into the itty bitty living space. Once inside the bottle though, it doesn't feel as cramped. It's actually rather cozy. Maybe living in here won't be so bad. Wait! Live here?! You're not a genie! You quickly reverse the spell, the interior of the bottle disappearing as you find yourself back to your previous form. Your weak form that doesn't even command one tenth of the power you just had...</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>You're singing a Disney song to yourself when you suddenly are hit by a spell! Your eyes glow with your magical power as you rise above the mage, smoke surrounding you. How dare some pesky lesser creature attacks a mighty genie like you! You shall crush them for this insult! You shall obliterate them for their impertinence! As you take a step away from your bottle, imagining what would be a suitable punishment to inflict somewhere in the back of your mind, a voice screams that this isn't right, and before you know what you're doing, you're casting a counter spell, your form changing back to something different, something weak. Now why did you do that?</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>You feel some feeble magic hit you, and you turn to face your attacker ready to smite them! They will soon regret the day they were born! Your power will-what's that noise? You look down to see a bottle making a sound almost like a vacuum cleaner, drawing you inwards! With a pop, you're inside and your bottle is corked! Curses! Right as you were about to unleash an awesome display of your power... You suppose you could muster up the will to step out, though the moment is lost. ...Or maybe you can wait for them to think to try the 'rub bottle, get 3 wishes' bit. Yes, you might be bound to grant them what they ask if they do, but sometimes getting EXACTLY what you want isn't best, now is it? You grin to yourself at the thought...</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>You start humming the song "Jeannie" and dance to the beat with a swing of your hips. You notice you have an audience and decide to take advantage of the opportunity, flicking a spell at someone. The spell connects with the target and explodes into a cloud of smoke. You hear your target cough and clear away the smoke as you hear a clanking sound and a bottle rolls away. They seem none the worse for wear it seems...</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>You notice your target is humming to themselves as you sling a spell at them. A large cloud of colorful smoke obscures them and you notice an ornate bottle near their feet. As some of the smoke that covers their body clears you can see the changes wrought by the spell, at least to their upper body. The smoke clings to their lower body and legs, almost looking like those pants belly dancers wear. Eventually they notice the changes too though, and reverse them, the smoke blowing away along with the bottle disappearing...</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>A distracted opponent means an easy target for a spell! As your spell hits them, it explodes with a "poof" sound, enshrouding the target in smoke. As it begins to clear, you see the damage it has done. In place of your opponent stands a graceful woman. Tan-skinned and exotic looking, she seems to be wearing clothes of a light and gauzy material. Just like a genie. Just as you smile at the thought, you notice that not all the smoke has cleared. Their lower torso is still nothing but smoke. It's not that their legs are hidden, but they don't exist, replaced by the smoke, which is flowing into a nearby bottle that had appeared at some point. It looks as though they're about to be sucked inside when their eyes widen, and they cast a reversal spell, cancelling the changes and returning to their previous form. They do seem to be pondering something though...</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>You're not sure why they're not paying attention, but it makes it easier to hit your target with a spell! A large cloud of colorful smoke block them from your view for a moment, but they seem to have it under control quickly. Soon you see their exotic form, cloaked in veils, as they stand there smiling at you. They seem to be having fun, you think. However the smile turns into a glare as their eyes suddenly eyes glow and they grow in stature. It's like they can play with the very cosmos themselves! The raw magical power they emanate is overwhelming! As you think that you should get out of their way, you hear a strange sound. That's when you notice the bottle at your target's feet sucking them in! In an instant, the smoke, the woman, and the overwhelming presence, is gone, all contained within the bottle. You wonder if you should pick it up when it suddenly is replaced by your target, having reversed the changes...</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>You catch your target singing, not paying attention, and hit them with a spell before they notice you're around. They quickly change into an exotic beauty, who quickly turns to you with murder blazing in their eyes. You're about to stutter an apology when they suddenly gather a vast amount of magical energy to them. They grow in size, the skies darkening with their apparent anger, and you realize it might not have been a good idea to try and create such a powerful magical being, especially one from another mage... As they take a step forward, seemingly intent on destroying you, they suddenly stop and reverse the changes, returning to their former state. The confused look on their face indicates they didn't exactly mean to do it though...</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>As your spell hits your target, you see the anger rise up in them, quite literally! The exotic tan-skinned woman, while sexy, is quite scary towering over you, magical energy crackling around them like wrath called down from the heavens. You're about to kiss your spells goodbye when you hear a sound like a vacuum. You look for its source and see an ornate bottle on the ground beside the angry genie's feet. In almost an instant, the smoke, the magic, the angry girl, are gone, sucked into the bottle that corks itself! You wait a moment as it wiggles once... twice... three times... then it stops. Yes! You've caught a-oh wait, wrong game. Still, it seems they've calmed down. Hrrm... If you rub that bottle, does that mean you get three wishes? Very tempting, but then, imagining that raw power you just saw, that anger, you decide to walk away and not let the genie out of the bottle...</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
