<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<Description>This person—if you can still call her that—has green, plant-like skin, vines for feet, and an ornamental pink flower growing out of her head. You can't help but notice her beautiful body that openly flaunts her B-cup breasts and hourglass curves. As you get closer, you realize there's a very sweet smell emanating from her and permeating the air. Despite her almost-human appearance, she's clearly identifiable as an Alraune, though she seems to be rather ditzy and absent-minded. You suppose there isn't much for a creature like her to worry about as long as she has a warm sun over her and and water here and there, and if she ever feels threatened her mesmerizing scent and thorns will surely help her out.</Description>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>You see an opposing mage lift their arm and point it toward you. You prepare to dodge the incoming magical projectile, but it never comes. Instead, the only thing to assault you is a strong flowery scent. You're slightly puzzled until you notice your skin taking on a greenish hue out of the corner of your eye. You dispel the effect in a hurry before it gets any worse!</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>Your attacker casts their spell again and the same aroma from before returns to fill your nose. Holding your breath doesn't even help; the transformation rapidly forces your skin to take on a dark green color and your hair to turn pink! As your body begins to feel lighter, you manage to counter the spell's effects.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>Before you can blink, another spell hits you hard! Your skin and hair immediately change color again, and your body takes on a younger-looking form; that of a curvy woman with slim limbs and respectable B-cups. You feel energy flowing into you from the sun like you never have before! It's so... it's so... NO! You snap out of the trance with a start and undo the transformation with great concern for your mental stability.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>That familiar scent comes back, turning you back into the green-skinned woman. The changes seem to be more aggressive this time; your pastel pink hair forms an elegant bun on top of your head and, without warning, it blossoms into a beautiful flower that shows off your lovely face. The sun's rays feel so good against your skin. So nourishing, so... wait! This is wrong! You quickly shake your head and revert the changes before they completely take over your mind. There's no time to lose; you need to finish this soon!</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>Your opponent's spell hits you again, causing the fresh aroma to fill the air around you. You don't even try to avoid it this time. It smells so nice, so soothing. You don't care about your skin turning green, nor your hair turning into a lovely pink flower. You're quite proud of that flower, actually. It effortlessly absorbs the sun's rays and energizes you in the most pleasurable way. You feel like humming, singing, taking a sun bath, maybe even soaking up some water. Most of all, you feel the urge to make sure you're pretty for the people watching you like the... wait. The person that turned you this way! You somehow manage to recognize your aggressor and change yourself back to your normal form... though you can't help but think about how good you felt...</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>Taking in the intoxicating scent once more, you feel the same happy sensation from before, but this time you wonder why you ever wanted to turn away from it. Life is so much easier as a pretty flower. You smell nice, you bathe in the sun, you get to enjoy the stares of everyone who passes by. Being an Alraune is so nice and simple, why would you change back... change back to... to what? Hmm. You can't remember, though you suppose it probably wasn't important anyway. You have more important matters to tend to, like enjoying your new life as the embodiment of beauty! </TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>You fire off a spell at your victim, who seems confused by the lack of a projectile. They do, however, seem to take note of the sweet smelling aroma you sent their way. A surprised look crosses their face as they look at their body and realize their skin taking on a greenish hue, though they very quickly counter the attack and adopt a fighting posture. The results were a bit disappointing, but they show promise. </TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>You cast your spell again and are amused to see your opponent cover their nose, as if that would help them at all. You snicker a bit as you watch their skin turn to a plant-like green and their hair starts to become pinkish. Sadly, they cancel the spell's effects before their hair changes too much. At least you know it's taking effect now. Slowly, but surely.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>You unleash the spell again and you're delighted by its quickness; almost immediately your target's skin turns green, though it doesn't stop there this time! You watch as your victim's frame grows smaller and leaner, and their breasts slowly settles on a nice B-cup. Shortly afterward, their hair grows out and shifts into a bright pink! You're pleasantly surprised when they smile briefly before shaking their head and reversing the changes. Bummer...</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>The second the sweet smell reaches your target again, the effects are immediate! Their skin turns a healthy (for a plant) green tone, and their pink hair twirls atop their head, forming a bun that blossoms into a beautiful flower with a soft pop! The best part is getting to see the new alraune's face filled with joy for a short moment; sadly she shakes her head and reverts the changes before long.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Your spell reaches your opponent once more, but this time they don't even try to avoid breathing it in; they actually stand there and take in big whiffs of the sweet scent! The changes are rapid; returning them to their alraune form in a matter of seconds. You see her close her eyes and seem to enjoy taking in the sun with a broad smile. She even giggles at you and shows off her new body for a bit until she seems to realize that you were the one that turned her this way. With an upset glare she counters your spell and returns herself to normal, though you know it won't take much more now!
</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>Your spells hits your opponent for the last time. In merely a second, the person standing before you is a happy alraune. She returns your gaze and smiles brightly while you observe her, expecting her to snap back to her own mind at any second. It never seems to happen though; you guess she has probably already forgotten while she was here in the first place. After a few seconds, she shrugs and turns to wander away. You smile to yourself, pleased that you managed to make the world just a little prettier today!</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
