<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<Description>This young and handsome man seems full of himself, from under the shade of his hat he seems to always have a smirk and he walks with a confidence he shouldn't have in this town. It feels as though he knows something others do not or can not and there is an essence of magic that seems to encompass him. Yet despite the shady look of this well dressed man, he is charming, good looking, when he beckons you see no reason why you shouldn't at least listen to what he has to offer... after all he only wants to make a fair deal. </Description>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>Your attacker pulls out this paying card, black energy falling from it like dry ice as they read whatever is upon it. Before you know it the black fog is all around and you hear a voice call out to you. "Boy, have *I* got a deal for you~!" But you dispel the magic and the fog dissipates leaving you to wonder just who or what was speaking. </TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>The black fog returns once more to surround you. That same familiar eerie voice returns as you tingle from head to toe. "Now come on boy, you haven't even heard." Your body starts to become slimmer but loosing no muscle, your hair becomes a white and slowly longer giving a natural shade over your eyes. "A master of deals of tricks and games, their down fall will be your gain." The voice nearly sings into your ear but no one is there. </TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>You're reunited with the familiar dark fog once again. You breath deeply this time your body once again slim and trim, white hair growing just long enough and you can't help but grin. You feel spry, agile, and lithe as a confidence bubbles within you and you alter your stance without even realizing. "All you gotta do is give in and spread the fun..."</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>Dark fog, your old friend, your heart quickens, body tingles, and you are ready to hear and feel whats next. Lean, trim, confident, you feel great as your body returns to this state. Your skin is smooth and just ever so lightly tanned, your body hair thins and vanishes leaving you smooth just like you words. "It feels good doesn't it? You're gonna be oh so much more then you ever were."</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>Your lungs are filled once more as the fog surrounds you, whatever your attacker thinks they are doing it seems they barely even know, but you do, you understand, they were tricked, fooled, they think they are harming you when in fact they are unleashing the means to their own end.. The chaos of this place, you feel it within your bones, you understand and you know it will be your place to continue to trick and fool these suckers.. it's so much more fun that way. "Just a little bit more.."</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>The dark fog fills you one more, slowly the card stops seeping its magic and slowly the dark cloud enters you. Your body slims once more into the agile and spry, confident and sly form you had before. Just tall enough, just slim enough, and handsome to boot. Your white hair hangs loosely about shoulder length with long bangs that cover your eyes with shade. You feel a need to dress up proper and sharp and you could certainly use a hat and cane with the get up you have in mind, but the town is fickle, you'll have to do with what you can acquire. You hear the voice one last time.. "Now all you gotta do is find those suckers like this one here. Play a game, make em a deal, it's magic stronger then any they can steal."
You smirk and direct your attention back to your caster, a predatory smile but a charming one at that. You speak, "Lets make a deal..." you hear your new voice for the first time, the same charming and tantalizing voice you heard in your head... </TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>Your attacker pulls out this paying card, black energy falling from it like dry ice as they read whatever is upon it. Before you know it the black fog is all around and you hear a voice call out to you. "Girl, have *I* got a deal for you~!" But you dispel the magic and the fog dissipates leaving you to wonder just who or what was speaking. </TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>The black fog returns once more to surround you. That same familiar eerie voice returns as you tingle from head to toe. "Now come on girl, you haven't even heard." Your body starts to tingle in the darkness as you feel your muscles tighten. Your hair starts to turn white and slowly creep back up your body as little features start to become more sharp and strong. "A master of deals of tricks and games, their down fall will be your gain." The voice nearly sings into your ear but no one is there. </TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>You're reunited with the familiar dark fog once again. You breath deeply this time your body once again slim and trim, white hair receding till its just about shoulder length and you can't help but grin. You feel spry, agile, and lithe as a confidence bubbles within you and you alter your stance without even realizing. The world around you starts to get just noticeably smaller as you grow a bit in height and by now your features have a more masculine appeal to them. "All you gotta do is give in and spread the fun..."</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>Dark fog, your old friend, your heart quickens, body tingles, and you are ready to hear and feel whats next. Lean, trim, confident, you feel great as your body returns to this state. Your skin is smooth and just ever so lightly tanned and smooth just like you words. Your new height returns and so does the new strength you feel from this form as you become more and more masculine. Your features become rugged and handsome while your breasts slowly drain away, nipples becoming smaller and less sensitive. Below you can feel something pushing out of you now, slowly and pleasurably as a cock replaces your pussy. "It feels good doesn't it? You're gonna be oh so much more then you ever were."</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>Your lungs are filled once more as the fog surrounds you, whatever your attacker thinks they are doing it seems they barely even know, but you do, you understand, they were tricked, fooled, they think they are harming you when in fact they are unleashing the means to their own end.. The chaos of this place, you feel it within your bones, you understand and you know it will be your place to continue to trick and fool these suckers.. it's so much more fun that way. "Just a little bit more.." Your new body nearly complete feels amazing, you feel as though every step you are about to take will draw others awe and curiosity.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>The dark fog fills you one more, slowly the card stops seeping its magic and slowly the dark cloud enters you. Your body slims once more into the agile and spry, confident and sly form you had before. Just tall enough, just slim enough, and handsome to boot. Your white hair hangs loosely about shoulder length with long bangs that cover your eyes with shade. You feel a need to dress up proper and sharp and you could certainly use a hat and cane with the get up you have in mind, but the town is fickle, you'll have to do with what you can acquire. You hear the voice one last time.. "Now all you gotta do is find those suckers like this one here. Play a game, make em a deal, it's magic stronger then any they can steal."
You smirk and direct your attention back to your caster, a predatory smile but a charming one at that. You speak, "Lets make a deal..." you hear your new voice for the first time, the same charming and tantalizing voice you heard in your head... </TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>A thick dark fog emanates from the card as you speak its words. You can't wait to see the man once more through this person and get yet another 'good' deal. Your foe seems preoccupied as you read. </TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>From within the dark cloud you see your victim listening intently to something as their features slowly change. Their hair becoming white and just slightly longer, their body becoming slimmer yet remaining muscled..</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>you watch in the darkened fog as this person's pose changes and even now you see a confidence within them and a sly grin on their face, you feel a sense of worry for a moment but there is a charm to that smile and you are the one in charge here right?</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>His body is changed, spry and agile his features immaculate and sharp. Even with what he has on now there is an air of confidence and style to him. He stands there in the fog still listening to something as you watch your deal maker come ever so closer to life again. </TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>The confident man within the dark cloud smirks in your direction as he still listens and nods. Almost as before he beckons towards you to come but your spell doesn't have enough energy yet it seems to finalize it and the fog drifts away returning them once more. </TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>The fog clears entering the man who looks just like the one who gave you the card. His predatory smirk catches your eyes as he beckons you over once again. "Let's make a deal..." He offers and this time you are not so sure if you have won the duel. </TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>A thick dark fog emanates from the card as you speak its words. You can't wait to see the man once more through this person and get yet another 'good' deal. Your foe seems preoccupied as you read. </TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>From within the dark cloud you see your victim listening intently to something as their features slowly change. Their hair becoming white and receding up their back, their body becoming taller and more muscled yet keeping a slim trim look..</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>you watch in the darkened fog as this person's pose changes and even now you see a confidence within them and a sly grin on their face, you feel a sense of worry for a moment but there is a charm to that smile and you are the one in charge here right? Their hair is now loose and shoulder length, fully white and shading their eyes a bit aiding in making that grin stand out. Her chest starts to fall back and you can only assume something is beginning to poke out below. </TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>The women is hardly that any more, her features are masculine and sharp, her body toned and muscled, agile and spry. She keeps that confident smile and pose on at all times as she listens to the someone within the fog. They are coming along nicely, not too long until your spell will be complete and you can make a new deal. </TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>The confident man within the dark cloud smirks in your direction as he still listens and nods. Almost as before he beckons towards you to come but your spell doesn't have enough energy yet it seems to finalize it and the fog drifts away returning them once more. </TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>The fog clears entering the man who looks just like the one who gave you the card. His predatory smirk catches your eyes as he beckons you over once again. "Let's make a deal..." He offers and this time you are not so sure if you have won the duel. </TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>

</Form>
