<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>Your opponent hits you in the face with a dust ball. You can't decide whether it's pathetic or disgusting. </TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>You are hit once again by a magic dust ball to your face. Some of the dust enters your nose and makes you sneeze twice quickly. You feel a third sneeze building up and as you do, a feather is launched out of your nose. It slowly floats away and disappears.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>Your enemy's magic dust ball now makes its way up your nose. You can feel it shaking and releasing tons of dust. You try to resist sneezing, but you can feel a strong one building up. Unable to control yourself anymore, you sneeze. As you do, many small feathers are launched out of your nose. You look at them floating to the ground and see your legs. They are totally covered in feathers! You shake them off and the feathers disappear.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>This time, your opponent casts multiple dust ball at you, each one hitting you right on the head and releasing clouds of dust. You can't help but sneeze again and again. You try to dissipate the dust with your hands, but more projectiles keep coming. You have a strange sensation the world is growing over you, until your head is cleared from the dust clouds. You shrunk to half your size! You look down at your legs and realize, in complete awe, that they have been replaced by hundreds of feathers attached to your waist. You are half-human, half-duster. With a quick counterspell, you revert to normal.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>A big cloud of dust is lifted from the ground and sent toward you. Once again, you sneeze on and on as the dust invades your nose. You want to pinch it, but you feel your arms are glued to your body. The more you fight to release them, the stronger they seem to stick to you. Suddenly, a gust of wind makes you loose balance and you start falling on your side. With your arms glued, you are unable to soften the fall and you hit your head on the hard floor. It takes you a few seconds to recover from the pain. You quickly realize you can't move anything but your head. You look down and see your body has been transformed into a shinny black handle. As you feel your face stiffening, you concentrate and chant an incantation to stop your transformation.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>You are surrounded by a cloud of dust once more, but this time, you are lifted from the ground by a magical tornado which makes you spin uncontrollably. Your arms are pushed against your body by the rotation and fused in place. You try to open your mouth to chant another counterspell, but it's filled with dust and chokes you. You feel your body stiffening and going numb. There is nothing you can do anymore from preventing your transformation into a feather duster. Suddenly, the dust tornado vanishes and you drop on the floor. Your head bounces on the floor with no pain, only making a strange noise of plastic material hitting the ground. Your opponent grabs you and starts dusting to humiliate you.  Your new form feels highly sensitive and a strange feeling of excitement and arousal starts building up where your head used to be. To your horror, all this dusting is turning you on! But after all, it was to be expected since you are a feather duster now. </TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>You hit your opponent with a magical dust ball in the face. It's a little bit disgusting, but you also thought it was funny.
</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>You cast another magic dust ball to the face of your target. This time, some of it seemed to enter your target's nose as they start sneezing. You think you saw a feather spurting out of their nose, but you're not quite sure. </TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>This time, you can see your little dust projectile entering the nose of your enemy. You wait for a few moments as you watch your target building up a massive sneeze. As your opponent sneezes, some feathers spring from their nose and feathers also sprout all over their legs. You laugh at your target's feathery pants while they shake them off.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>This time, you cast multiple dust balls at your target, each one hitting right on the head and releasing clouds of dust. Your target sneezes again and again while trying to dissipate the dust with their hands. You can see your victim's legs turning into feathers, each sneeze sprouting even more from their waist. Your target also shrinks and as soon as their head clears from the cloud of dust, you can see the awe on their face as your opponent realizes they have become half-human, half-duster. With a counterspell, your enemy reverts to normal.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>You summon a big magical cloud of dust and throw it at your victim. Once again, your target sneezes on and on as the dust invades their nose. Through the cloud, you can see your target's body darkening and slimming down. You cannot distinguish their arms anymore. A gust of wind throws your target on their side. They now look more like duster than human. You walk closer to your shrinking target, enough to see their face slowly melting into the handle. Their eyes are closed and they look peaceful. Suddenly, they awake and chant an incantation to stop their transformation. You think another hit or two should probably finish the job.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>You summon a massive cloud of dust and throw it at your enemy, imprisoning them in an infernal tornado. The magic quickly transforms your target into a feather duster. First the legs into feathers, than the body into a black shiny handle, all while shrinking to an appropriate size. The tornado vanishes and the duster drops on the floor. You pick up the duster just in time to see your opponent's face melting once and for all into the tip of the handle. You decide to humiliate your victim and start dusting around the place, but you begin to enjoy it and soon, you've dusted the whole room like a good little maid.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
