<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>At the conclusion of the spell ... nothing seems to happen.  Enraged enough to forget that you yourself are quite the competent mage, you rush at the caster - and find yourself almost instantly running chest-first into an invisible wall!  Your hands quickly grope around, testing its limits - you soon realize you are encased in a magic sphere, its diameter around three times your own height.  Slowly, as the magic takes hold, you can see the outlines of your transparent cage take shape - see a faint, pink energy begin to infuse the area inside it, where you are trapped.  You feel just the tiniest hint of arousal as you involuntarily breathe in some of the pink mist as you gather your will to dispel your prison - hopefully, this will not happen again ...</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>The magic sphere forms around you; quicker this time, already visible and full of pink mist before you can even blink.  You open your mouth to begin casting a bolt of force to shatter its walls - and quickly realize your mistake, as the mist seems to rush down your open throat.  You feel your whole body tingling, as you explode into orgasm - powerful enough to briefly make you black out, as you fall to the ground, knocking your head against the sides of the sphere.  Soon enough, you come to.  Everything, like, seems to totally be in order - you've got, like, just the same tight little leggy body, same pert ass, same perky boobies, same cute shoulder-length blonde hair.  Even, like, the same perfect little pussy - you find yourself bringing your manicured hands down to rub it, as a thought breaks through your bubbly pink haze of a mind - "this isn't right, this isn't me!  I need to break out!"  And you do - the walls around you vanish, and soon your body returns to its former self, memories of your time in the sphere already beginning to fade ...</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>The sphere again encases you.  This time, you remember to keep your mouth shut; holding your breath, you fruitlessly pound again and again against its crystalline walls, but it is of no use - you do not even put a scratch on them.  Soon enough, you are forced to take a deep gasping breath, and the mist invades your lungs again.  This time you, like, stay awake as the yummy mist remakes you.  You totally cum from your tight little pussy without like even touching it, as you get a look at your sexy body - long blonde hair, tiny waist, flaring hips, heart-shaped ass - big ol' DD-cup titties standing, like, totally firm - gawd, you just look so hawt!  And you feel like, just sooooo horny ... you totally lay down at the bottom of the sphere, pressing your tight stomach, your big boobies up against it.  One hand, like, starts rubbing up and down your cunny, another starts totally tweaking your nipples.  The crystal walls feel like, so warm, and look so kewl - you're sure, like, any cute guys watching you would totally get a hard-on from this.  The tenth orgasm is particularly strong; in its aftermath, your boring former self is able to break through the haze; the boring old mage soon reasserts itself.  You quickly break out of the sphere, and, like, totally restore your dull ol' body ...</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>Like, the glass ball thing is totally coming for you again!  You giggle ... it's, like, cumming right for ya!  Soon enough, you're, like, just gulping down that beautiful pink mist, and you totally feel yourself getting, like, your real body back!  Yay!  You take like just a moment to look over yourself - tiny, tiny waist - big wide hips like exploding out from it - a big 'ol jiggly booty behind ya.  You, like, gasp as you get a look at your boobies - they're, like, totally huger than ya remember, like, maybe a G, or that letter after G!  You bring your hands up to cup the giant nipples, and feel a few drops of white fluid escape from them ... m-milk?  You dab a bit on your finger, bring it to your mouth, and like totally lick - gawd, you taste yummy!  The thought is enough to collapse on the floor of your sphere, and begin masturbating furiously.  You like cum, and cum, and cum - for what could totally be minutes or like weeks - milk and feminine juices beginning to pool beneath you - until you hear the boring voice of some old fuddy-duddy, demanding that you, like, change back.  Somehow it, like, takes control - and you find yourself clothed again, totally standing outside the sphere, your perfect little body gone, icky thoughts of vengeance invading your head ...</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>Ohmigawd, hurray! - you're totes getting your sweet sexy body back!  The sphere surrounds you; the mist is consumed; your sweet body, with even more improbable curves, is soon lying, writhing against the floor of the sphere, like totally lost to the world, your universe reduced to your own pleasure.  You like lie there, fisting yourself with one hand, the other like, tweaking, squeezing your huge nipples, milk spewing forth in thick, yummy streams.  So, like, absorbed are you, that you don't even notice as the sphere begins to shrink - 10 feet across, then 8, then 6, then 4 ... the world outside, like, seems to be growing!  The thought that it is you yourself who is shrinking does not even cross your mind, as you cum again and again and again ... sometime, long after your mind would've lost count, you momentarily black out ... and - like yuk! - find yourself changed back to your former old boring body.  But with, like, a bit more practice, you're like sure you can totally cum as much as you like without losing concheesen ... consushn ... cunshesne ... without, like, blackin' out and stuff!</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>The spell cums for you again, and, like, this time, you resolve to, totally not black out again!  You need ta, like, cum and cum and cum some more, always, everlasting - your will to do anything else seems to fade away, as you regain that perfect body, and fall to the warm floor of your now eternal prison, beginning a masturbation session that, like, will totally never end.  Through the orgasm fueled haze, you like see the world around you growing bigger and bigger and like, even bigger - when your owner picks up your ball, they like look ginormous, maybe like forty feet tall?  Or, like, are you only a few inches high now?  It totes doesn't matter - fucking, milking yourself feels like, so gewd ... and you just, like, know your owner is gonna take such good care of you.  You're, like, waaaaay too hawt for them not to, ya know?  The milk and female cum continue to flow, filling the bottom of the sphere ... but you couldn't care less, as you continue to, like, totally fist your tiny little heart out ... forever.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>You pick out a likely candidate - a particularly strong-willed opponent, who could stand to be taken down a peg.  Imagining the benefits of removing them from the battlefield, adding their will to your own - you begin to cast the spell.  Nothing has happened to the naked eye, except that you have attracted the attention of one angry looking magus; forgoing their spells, your opponent instead makes as if to charge you directly - and bounces off an invisible wall!  You stand there, cackling evilly, as you watch them grope the confines of their invisible prison, looking like a demented street performer.  The cackling only intensifies as the walls of the sphere waver into visibility, and you can see a fine pink mist fill your opponent's chamber ... but, it is not to be for now, as they manage to break free.  </TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>You are able to form a stronger version of the sphere this time - it springs into existence fully formed around your victim, instantly filling with that lovely pink mist.  Mist which they breathe in, as they foolishly open their mouth to begin the counterspell!  You suspect your opponent does not notice anything but their mind-blowing orgasm - strong enough for them to black out, falling against the spherical walls of their prison - but you see more.  You see their body slowly changing, turning into that of a leggy blonde girl as they sleep, a perfect tight little naked form.  Slowly, heavily-mascaraed eyes blink open, and she takes in her new body, reacting not in shock, but in ... lust?  As her manicured hands reach down to explore her pussy, you think to yourself that this is going even better than expected - but quickly, she seems to snap out of it.  The sphere pops out of existence, and a pissed-off, unchanged mage soon stands before you.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>The impregnable sphere again forms around your victim.  This time, they are able to remember to keep their mouth shut ... but you know they will have to breathe in, eventually.  They even waste their effort on pounding against their prison's walls, but they do not manage to so much as make a dent in the crystalline sphere.  Soon enough, they are forced to take a gasping breath - and the pink mist rushes in.  Their transformation into the leggy blonde bimbo is faster this time, more complete - they do not lose consciousness this time as their body orgasmically contorts into their overly-proportioned female form.  She soon falls, DD-sized chest first, to the floor of the sphere, and begins vigorously jilling off, oblivious to the world; you hear some high pitched moans, and some sounds that could be "ohmigawd" and "like, totally, YESSSSSSS" as she cums again and again.  You lose count, but the tenth release or so seems particularly strong - apparently strong enough for her to break free and cancel out your spell.  "I'm, gonna like, totes get ya for that!" you hear your opponent cry at you, voice a mismatch for their restored body ... somehow, you are not worried in the slightest.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>This time, your victim almost seems to welcome their - her - imprisonment, as she practically gulps down the pink mist suffusing the sphere.  You get a good look at her this time as she writhes in pleasure.  A big wobbling ass, topping off long, smooth, curved legs ... long, flowing blonde hair coming down past her impossibly tiny waist to reach her wide, jutting hips ... and most notably, an absolutely enormous rack - you'd guess maybe an H-cup?  You see her bring her fingers to her huge erect nipples, and coo in surprise as they are covered in a thick white liquid - she brings her manicured fingertips to her mouth for a lick, and decides she must taste delicious.  And then, the self-fucking starts - she collapses to the floor of the sphere, and plunges her entire fist in and out of her cute little pussy over and over and over.  You think that for sure that it must all be over, that her mind is totally gone now, the spell nearly complete; you even look away for a time, scanning your surroundings for other potential threats.  When you look back - your old opponent is standing before you, glaring - though in a posture just oozing feminine sex appeal.  They call you a "mean ol' doodyhead" - but you can tell their heart really isn't in it.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>No doubt about it - your opponent is pleased as punch to again be imprisoned in your crystalline orb.  Her body looks even more cartoonishly proportioned this time; you wonder how her organs even fit within that tiny waist, or how she stands erect with that huge ass, or those enormous, milk leaking breasts.  Perhaps she doesn't, as she soon falls to the ground, furiously masturbating and milking herself, lost to the world.  She doesn't even seem to notice as the sphere begins to shrink in on her - 12 feet in diameter, then 10, 8, 6, 4, further ... you watch fascinated as she shrinks within, rapidly approaching a size just perfect for carrying around the city, showing her off to her former 'friends' ...  you begin to reach for the crystalline sphere, but you notice that last orgasm had her black out again.  That wasn't supposed to happen, she's supposed to have the energy to keep self-fucking 24/7.  And sure enough, you soon see her eyes flicker open again, and glare at you - and your opponent soon stands before you ... unharmed?  Well, by the way they stand, rubbing at their own chest and genitals, lewdly moaning in public ... you wouldn't say 'unharmed'.  They might even welcome a final, permanent cast of your spell at this point ...</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>There is no obvious difference in the spell you cast this time - but you can tell.  This is it - repeated exposure to your spells has finally broken your victim's mind.  There will be no return for her.  The impossibly proportioned, milky bimbo returns moaning, gleefully flopping down against the floor of the sphere, her enormous breasts pressed against its walls, already beginning to leak.  The first of her endless orgasms begins as the walls of the sphere begin to contract ... further and further, until the whole thing is less than a foot around, your victim only inches high.  You watch her for a time, as the floor of the sphere begins to fill with milk, with her own feminine juices - seeing that her fate is truly sealed, you move over to pick up the crystal ball.  She barely breaks stride, only looking up at you, smiling, pressing her nipples against the wall within your gaze, lewdly touching herself - before going back to the vigorous self-fucking.  A warm tingle passes up your arm as you grab her; you feel like her very will, her essence is being siphoned up into you as you hold her.  Excellent.  Unfortunately, she is a bit unwieldy to carry, and you will have to take care to not drop her, lest she roll away ... but she will make a most wonderful pet indeed ...</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
