<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st> A massive bolt of frost hits you chilling you to the bone.  Frost splashes over you as you feel it molding your body, shaving some your height and mass off of your body. You are confused as the air around you gets colder suddenly. You focus on warming back up using your own body heat to do so, and reversing the changes.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>A larger bolt of frost collides with your torso. You shiver against the cold using the motion trying to keep warm. Your pigmentation seems to change, turning to a darker, more vibrant color darkening to an celestial blue. You concentrate on summoning a wisp of fire to reverse the changes of the frost.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>Your foe propels a continuous blast of frost, streaming around you and encompassing your small wisp, willing it out of existence. Their frost taking your will, draining it from your body as it enfolds you. Your hair changes,  first darkening from your original color to a baby blue, and lengthening to just above your shoulders. Once more your frame decreases yet again, shaving the sides, making you shorter and more lithe almost petite in stature. You washed away the enemy spell by conjuring a blaze of flames using the time to reverse the changes.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>Watching the attacker carefully, you brace for an attack. Instead of one attack they fling a barrage of frost bolts in your direction. They slow you down, nearly halting your movement and changing you once again. Your face changes starting with your eyes, one shifting to an icy white the other changes to a pale blue.  The barrage changes your bust size to a moderate "B" cup as the frost is absorbed into your chest. You smile at your adversary as the ice begins to speak to you, the barrage being thrown at you vanishing before it even hits. "We shall encase them all in ice, giving you nice sculptures never to be free again." You  panic from the voices of winter inside of your head, and all the ice splashes into water on the ground, while you reverse the changes with a hurried pace.
</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>A ring of frost appears out of thin air surrounding you, moving slowly inwards towards you. It reaches a certain point around you and implodes, the shards of ice flying towards you, making all the prior changes to you in a matter of seconds. After this your body color darkens even further changing to a periwinkle blue. The hair appears once more, green streaks appearing among the baby blue as even that changes to a darker variation of the color. Frost accumulates on your body, shaping your curves making them accentuated. Your hips widen, changing them into child bearing hips. The frost vanishes around you as you hear the voice once more urging you to encase them in ice. Power flows freely into you as the air crackles as the cool air whirls around you in the heat of summer. Angry at what they have forced upon you, you contemplate it as the power feels right to you. You force these thoughts painstakingly slow out of your head, using the power of the frost to do so, as you reverse the changes.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>Icicles rain down around you, as your enemy raises his hands towards the skies. They have trapped you effectively in an icicle cage.  The cage changes you, reconstructing all of your prior implements that have been made against you, and new ones as the power itself molds your body and mind into one under the frost and ice.  Your hair lengthens to halfway down their backside, as the air itself around you drops to adjust to your new form. The voices return once more, "we shall leave this one alone but there are plenty more in this city to make into sculptures for your home." Walking off, you search for another person to torment.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>You  unleash a massive bolt of frost on your prey, chilling them  to the bone. You watch as the frost starts molding their form, shaving off a few inches of their height and their mass. The look in your prey's eyes is one of confusion as the streets around them cool down by a few degrees. Heat from their body melts the frost as they reverse the changes you have made.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd> After they reverse the changes of your first spell you charge a smaller amount of extra energy into this next bolt, shooting it at them aiming for their torso. You watch as they shiver in the sheer cold of the ice, struggling to keep warm. Their pigmentation seems to shift, turning to a darker, more vibrant color darkening to an celestial blue. The opponent summons a wisp into their hand, using it to warm themselves while reversing the changes huddled over the small orb.
</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>You propel a continuous blast of frost, streaming around them and encompassing the small wisp, willing it out of existence. Your frost taking away your victims will along with it resuming the changes upon them once more. Their hair changes,first darkening from their original color to a baby blue, and lengthening to just above their shoulders. Their frame decreases once more, shaving the sides, making them shorter and more lithe almost petite in their stature. Your spell is washed away in a blaze of flames from your foe as they take this time while you refocus to reverse the changes.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Watching their power take over your cone of frost, you think of a more powerful blast and drop back allowing it flit to the back of your mind for now. Using most of your mind, you fling a barrage of frost bolts at your target, focusing on slowing them down and changing them into your personal ice queen to keep you company. Watching their face, one of their eyes shifts to an icy white the other eye changes to a pale blue.  Your barrage changes their bust size to a moderate "B" cup as the frost is absorbed into the target’s chest. You watch as they smile at you, the barrage you are throwing at them vanishing before it even hits them. They panic and all the ice splashes into water on the ground as they reverse the changes with a hurried pace</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Your spell readies itself in your mind and you throw the frost ring around them, willing it inwards as an implosion. The spell slows down around your target. The ring implodes sending shards of ice into their body, creating the previous changes once more, but the body color darkens even further changing to a periwinkle blue. Their hair appears once more, green streaks appearing among the baby blue as even that changes to a darker variation of the color. The frost accumulates along the future queen’s body, shaping their curves, making them accentuated. Their hips expand and widen, providing them with child bearing hips. The frost vanishes around your adversary, the air crackling with the sound of the cool air whirling in the heat of summer. Watching the almost-queen's face, you see anger alight upon it and then dissolve as they reverse the changes, dispelling them using the magic you have been using on them but painstakingly slow as if distracted by something mentally.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>The spell you had pushed to the recesses of your mind flows forth, ready to be invoked. Raising your hands to the skies, you rain down icicles upon your victim, trapping them effectively in an icicle cage.  The cage changes them, reconstructing all of your prior implements upon them, and new ones as the power itself molds their body and mind into one under the frost and ice.  Their hair lengthens to halfway down their backside, as the air itself around them drops to a freezing chill. Goosebumps break out along your uncovered skin. You wonder if unleashing her onto this city was such a good idea in the first place. As your new creation walks off the air warms back up and you shrug. Not your problem anymore.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
