<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>As you get hit you feel strangely compelled to strip naked. You can barely mutter the counter-spell in time to avoid striping your underwear.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>


<TFMessage_Completed_1st>Again your enemy gathers their magic for an attack. But you keep asking yourself if your opponent is really your enemy. As the bolt of magic races to you, you don't even try to evade or resist anymore. You just stand there and welcome the feelings back. You sink back down with your leather garments forming. You are ready. You know it. You want it. You raise your head to plead your loyalty to your new owner when suddenly a strong light flashes. As you come to your senses you find yourself in a dark room. The darkness is pierced by a single window, showing you the place where you fought from a strange angle and mirrored letters that take you a moment to read as “Bondage Kitten Magazine Edition 1”. You helplessly collapse in front of the window, feeling the shame, fear and horniness return. In addition to that you feel lonely, and you hope your owner finds you. A moment later you spot your owner coming towards your window. But something is off. Your owner gets bigger and bigger, towering over you and your window like a giant. As your owner picks up your window and room you prepare yourself to be violently shaken around but nothing happens. Even as your window points to the floor you can stand normal. With a sudden insight you realize you are in a picture or as you glance at the widows written mirrored words in a magazine cover! As your owner flips you over, about to open you magazine, that flashing light blinds you again. As you come to yourself you are in a bondage dungeon with every tool, furniture and article of clothing a sub or dom dreamed of having. But the best part is you see your owner. You rush over and pledge your loyalty. What follows are hours of intensive role-playing, sex and wicked stuff you never imagined. The only thing that distracts you a little is the faint sound of someone writing with a pen. As you and your owner break down exhausted the light flashes you again and you are back in your dark room. As you look out your window you realize no time has gone by outside. Your owner takes quite some time to read inside your magazine and you wonder if that pen writing sound from before are now the words your owner reads. As your owner closes your magazine you pose very sexy. After all as a cover-girl you have a reputation to maintain. </TFMessage_Completed_1st>


<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>The moment your foe's spell connects with you a shock sweeps through your mind. “Are you really dressed?  You shouldn't be! Your owner will surely punish you for this!” You quickly undress yourself. Sinking to your knees you hope your owner is merciful. After several seconds passes without anything happens you come to your senses and dispel the enchantment on you. As you collect your clothes you can't help to notice the smirk on your opponent face.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>Again you are hit by your enemy. Again you strip naked and sink to your knees, even faster this time. As you wait for your punishment you feel the strangest sensation. Looking down on your body you see body paintings appear out of nowhere. With a slight nervousness you realize those are detail drawings of wrist, arm, thigh and ankle cuffs. In addition to that drawings of leather straps paint you in an exquisite harness. Small tingles around your neck hint that you even wear a drawn on collar. With embarrassment you realize that this makes you very wet. You take the short way to collect yourself by casting an all purpose counter-spell, freeing you from the mind control and the drawings.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>You strip naked before you even realize you have been hit yet again. You shiver with excitement as you feel your drawings return. But something is different this time. The paint gets thicker and thicker until with a sudden plop all your drawings turn to real object. You feel and smell the leather that decorates now your body. Your harness and cuffs gently caress you. Your collar forces your head a little bit upwards. All these give you a sense of security and make you quite horny. Lost in thought you nearly miss that your arms are forced behind your back. Small chains appear and connect your wrist and arm cuffs. But as soon as they appear they keep getting shorter until your arms are fixed in a reverse prayer. Shame, fear and the wetness swell higher and higher until you can't take it anymore and cast the counter-spell. For just a moment you regret doing it.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>Fearing what will happen to you, you steel yourself for the next attack. But all is in vain. You are hit and shortly after you are nearly naked on the floor. Horny and bound in leather. Your arms in a reverse prayer position. You feel a need so strong you never felt before. You want to be used. Punished. Embarrassed. You look pleadingly to your enemy. Stray strands of red hair sway into your view, hinting that your body changed a little too. Your opponent comes closer and asks you if you are ready to give up. You want to give up. Give in. But a small part resists. And in a moment of weakness you listen to that part and whisper the counter-spell. As you stand up, freed from your chains and cuffs you swipe a tear from the corner of your eyes.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>


<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>The moment your foe's spell connects with you a shock sweeps through your mind. “Are you really dressed?  You shouldn't be! Your owner will surely punish you for this!” You quickly undress yourself. Sinking to your knees you hope your owner is merciful. You feel quite uneasy as you notice that the area around your nipples is slightly swollen. You would mind it more if you weren’t so wet down there. Your thoughts freeze for a moment to look down. Your penis is awfully small and you are sticky with something that is not pre-cum. “OK that is enough” you think as you use your counter-spell. As you collect your clothes you can't help to notice the smirk on your opponent's face.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>Again you are hit by your enemy. Again you strip naked and sink to your knees, even faster this time. As you wait for your punishment you feel the strangest sensation. Looking down on your body you see body paintings appear out of nowhere. With a slight nervousness you realize those are detail drawings of wrist, arm, thigh and ankle cuffs. In addition to that, drawings of leather straps paint you in an exquisite harness, framing your now B-cup breasts. Small tingles around your neck hint that you even wear a drawn on collar. With embarrassment you realize that this makes you very wet. Looking down you don't see your penis anymore but a beautiful vagina. In addition your whole body seems to be curvier, much like a woman. You tear your eyes away from this strange but erotic view to collect your thoughts. Casting the counter-spell you free yourself from the mind control and the drawing and return your body to the normal form.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>You strip naked before you even realize you have been hit yet again. You shiver with excitement as you feel your body change back to that of a woman and a tingle marks the return of your drawings. But something is different this time. The paint gets thicker and thicker until with a sudden plop all your drawing turn to real object. You feel and smell the leather that decorates now your body. Your harness and cuffs gently caress you. Your collar forces your head a little bit upwards. All these give you a sense of security and make you quite horny. Lost in thought you nearly miss that your arms are forced behind your back. Small chains appear and connect your wrist and arm cuffs. But as soon as they appear they keep getting shorter until your arms are fixed in a reverse prayer. Shame, fear and the wetness swell higher and higher until you can't take it anymore and cast the counter-spell. For just a moment you regret doing it.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>Fearing what will happen to you you steel yourself for the next attack. But all is in vain. You are hit and shortly after you are a nearly naked woman on the floor. Horny and bound in leather. Your arms in a reverse prayer position. You feel a need so strong you never felt before. You want to be used. Punished. Embarrassed. You look pleadingly to your enemy. Stray strands of red hair sway into your view, hinting about yet another change to your body. Your opponent comes closer and asks you if you are ready to give up. You want to give up. Give in. But a small part resists. And in a moment of weakness you listen to that part and whisper the counter-spell. As you stand up, freed from your chains and cuffs you swipe a tear from the corner of your eyes.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>


<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>You catch your opponent off-guard.  Your target shows such a shocked face that it can't even be explained by your sudden lucky shoot. Before you can react your opponent practically tears their clothes off. As your target sinks to their knees and lowers their head, you are unsure what to do, giving your victim time to collect themselves and cast the counter-spell.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>


<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>Again you gather the magic to wave your spell. Looking at your target you are sure that you have time. Your opponent doesn't even start to put up defenses. Only a moment later a twenty-something redhead sits bound to your feet, waiting to be order to do anything that pleases you. As you are about to give your first order, a sudden flash of light blinds you for a moment.
When you can see again your lovely new slave is gone, replaced by a high gloss fetish magazine. At loss you pick it up, only to see your eager sub posing as a cover-girl under the big written words “Bondage Kitten Magazine Edition 1”. At first you think it's a trick of the mind but your lovely redhead is alive. striking various poses on the cover to please you. Amazed you decide to see what's inside, only to be rushed by a wave of magic for a moment. Well nothing bad happened so you ignore it and open up your magazine. Several high gloss pictures not only show your bondage-girl but you in dominant attire as-well. What follows are a string of photo-shoots how you dominate your poor girl in different situations. Accompanied by each photo-shoot is a text written with the point of view from your sub. Smiling, you close the magazine and see a quite satisfied cover-girl winking at you. Well it wasn't what you had in mind but this trophy is worth a lot on its own.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>


<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>You use a weakness in your target's defense and hit him. You knowingly smile as you see your victim peel his clothes away, giving you an amazing view. Sadly he realizes what he has does just in time to prevent himself from discarding his underwear by muttering the counter-spell.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>


<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>He strips naked and sinks to his knees as you manage to hit him again with your spell, even faster this time. As he waits patiently, waiting for something, body-paintings appear on his body.  On his wrists, arms, thighs and ankles the drawings of leather-cuffs can clearly be seen. In addition to that drawings of leather straps paint him in an exquisite harness, highlighting his slightly swollen nipples and some breast-tissue that wasn’t there before. Even a collar can be seen on his neck. Looking further down you see a shrinking hardened penis covered in something wet that you think is not pre-cum. A short time later he breaks out of his trance and dispels everything.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>You manage to hit him again, by avoiding all of his defenses. He quickly resumes the position where your last spell stopped to work and his body resumes to become a woman, this time with B-cup breast and a curvy body. As his penis shrinks away and trades place with a lovely vagina you know that he is now a she. The body-paint returns but this time it's different. The paint gets thicker and thicker until with a sudden plop all her drawings turn to real object. She gently explores her new garments until suddenly her arms are forced behind her back. Small chains had appear and connect her wrist and arm cuffs. But as soon as they appear they keep getting shorter until her arms are fixed in a reverse prayer. You clearly see the shame, fear and her horniness written all over her face. This last for quite some time until she suddenly snaps out of it and speaks the counter-spell. Back as a man and fully dressed you see the small hint of regret on his face.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>You shatter your victim's defenses, as you can clearly see his struggling, to defend himself at all. His body transforms to a beautiful woman once again to make him a she. Now she doesn't even resist anymore as the leather restrains once again appear and force her to a reverse prayer bondage on her knees. She clearly looks you in the eye and you can see all there is now to her, just a puddle of misery waiting for you to rescue her. As you enjoy the view you notice some changes to her body. Her hair turns red and her eyes green. She loses that little extra fat you barely noticed before. You think it's time to end it and move close to her, asking her if she gives up. You think you see her answer clear as day written over her face until she suddenly, with a toss of her head, is whispering the counter-spell. As she returns to being a he, you can tell how close it was by the tears that started to form in the corner of his eyes.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>


<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>You use a weakness in your targets defense and hit her. You knowingly smile as you see your victim peel her clothes away, giving you an amazing view. Sadly she realizes what she has does just in time to prevent herself from discarding her underwear by muttering the counter-spell.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>


<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>She strips naked and sinks to her knees as you manage to hit her again with your spell, even faster this time. As she waits patiently, waiting for something, body-paintings appear on her body.  On her wrists, arms, thighs and ankles the drawings of leather-cuffs can clearly be seen. In addition to that drawings of leather straps paint her in an exquisite harness. Even a collar can be seen on her neck. She reaches down between her legs and you see the telltale sign of wetness on her finger. This breaks her out of her trance and she dispels everything.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>You manage to hit her again, by avoiding all of her defenses. She quickly resumes the position where your last spell stopped working. The body-paint returns but this time it's different. The paint gets thicker and thicker until with a sudden plop all her drawings turn into real objects. She gently explores her new garments until suddenly her arms are forced behind her back. Small chains had appear and connect her wrist and arm cuffs. But as soon as they appear they keep getting shorter until her arms are fixed in a reverse prayer. You clearly see the shame, fear and her horniness written all over her face. This lasts for quite some time until she suddenly snaps out of it and speaks the counter-spell. Even fully dressed you see a small hint of regret on her face.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>You shatter your victim's defenses, as you can clearly see her struggling, to defend herself at all. She doesn't even resist anymore as the leather restrains once again appear and forcing her into a reverse prayer bondage on her knees. She clearly looks you in the eye and you can see all there is now to her, just a puddle of misery waiting for you to rescue her. As you enjoy the view you notice some changes to her body. Her hair turns red and her eyes green. She loses that little extra fat you barely noticed before. You think it's time to end it and move close to her, asking her if she gives up. You think you see her answer clear as day written over her face until she suddenly, with a toss of her head, is whispering the counter-spell. You can tell how close it was by the tears that started to form in the corner of her eyes.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>


</Form>