<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>Fire springs forth from your attacker's hands, as you bring your hands to cover your face, futilely trying to ward off the flame. It continues to issue forth in waves, eventually encasing you in a mass of living flames. Oddly, it does not burn, nor does it seem to change you - though for some reason your dick is standing steel-hard and erect through the whole process.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>Again, you are encased in apparently harmless flame. Again, your dick becomes shockingly hard - though, horrifyingly, it seems to have lost over half it's former size. Your hands are drawn to your pectorals, which seem swollen, your nipples greatly enlarged - rubbing them sends a shock to your diminished pecker. 'So, a gender-change spell', you think - 'easy enough to counter.' And you do, returning fully to your masculine self.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>You are again encased in the feminizing flame, finding it harder to put up an effective resistance. This time your gender is completely lost - your manhood replaced with a tight, wet slit - C-cup breasts sprouting forth from your chest - your whole body shrinking, changing into more feminine proportions - you even have to brush a strand of fire-engine red hair from your eyes. You are briefly overcome - and shamefully give into the desire to explore your new equipment right out here in the open. A voice echoes inside your own head 'YES - GIVE IN TO YOUR DESIRE, BECOME MY LIEUTENANT OF LUST' - but instead of driving you to climax, it snaps you out of it. You are able to reverse the spell - though surprisingly, you feel a sense of loss as you return to your old body, and a sense of... plain wrongness... as your dick settles back in between your legs.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>This time you almost welcome the flame, more than a little eager for it to return you to what you are shocked to find yourself thinking of as your natural form. It's even faster this time - your cock vanishes almost instantaneously, quickly yielding to the hungry little hole that best suits your hyper-sexualized feminine body. Your large breasts bounce violently as you assault your needy sex, first with one finger, then two, then three, then your entire fist. You scream as you quickly reach your first female orgasm - the sensations entirely alien. You even feel what feels like an ejaculation from your spine, and two spots on your forehead. 'YESS... SOON YOU WILL BELONG TO ME, BODY AND SOUL' you hear the voice say, as you inspect your body, only to find two tiny horns on your head, and a 6-inch tail with a barbed spade at the end on your rear. Shocked, you are snapped out of your orgasmic trance, and are able to bring yourself to - very reluctantly - reverse the spell. You immediately regret doing so, and can only hope your opponent will soon return you to your state of lustful bliss.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>You practically leap into your opponent's flame, the desire to shed this pathetic male body overwhelming any sense of restraint, or thought of permanent consequences. It takes a mere 10 seconds to lose all vestiges of the man you were - though even that wait seems unbearable. Despite the changes it brought last time, you quickly bring yourself to orgasm again and again and again. You cry out in delicious agony as your skin seems to burn, turning a blood red; you scream with bliss as your horns grow long and curled; you feel incredible joy and wonder as your tail lengthens, becoming long and flexible enough to assault your own pussy. Change after change - some increasing your sexuality (the G-cup tits, the enormously wide hips) and others your increasingly hellish nature (the pointed ears, the foot-long, forked tongue) - you quickly lose track of them all, as you lose yourself in the never-ending waves of passion. 'YES! YES! BUT ONE STEP REMAINS - USE YOUR NEW FORM TO ENSNARE ANOTHER, AND YOU WILL FULLY BE WORTHY OF MY GIFT.' Thoughts of assaulting those around you fill your mind - your lips wrapped around some Beefy Dude's throbbing cock as two more take you from behind - and, for just a fleeting moment, your old mind re-asserts itself. 'You aren't a chick' it says, between thoughts of further debaucheries, 'let alone a servant of Hell. Get ahold of yourself man!'... and somehow, you do, and the magic fades. Though you quickly find yourself getting down on your knees (painfully pinching the scrotum you forgot you even had) and begging your attacker to cast the spell once more...</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>The flames assault you for what you resolve will be the final time. Before the flames even fully subside, you leap upon your attacker, your mouth instantly attached to their groin. As you lick and suck, you feel their pleasure building inside yourself. You cum in waves, each quickly restoring parts of your demonic glory - which only intensifies as other passerbys watch your performance, the more strongly affected masturbating on the spot. A fight breaks out among the beefy dudes about who will get to claim you, before you suggest that a) you have two holes back there and b) they can take turns.  Despite this going on for what seems like hours, your attacker simply won't cum - as their ardor builds and builds, you feel a similar feeling of pent-up tightness between your shoulder blades. Finally, they scream in ecstasy - as two bat-like wings unfold from your own shoulders, finally making you complete. There is no going back now - you have fully become a Sexy Succubus. The voice confirms it 'YES. GO FORTH. TRANSFORM OTHERS TO JOIN MY ARMIES, AND YOUR REWARD WILL BE GREAT. FAIL ME AND... WELL, LET US JUST SAY THAT YOU SHOULD NOT FAIL.' This is going to be so much fun...</TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>Fire springs forth from your attacker's hands, as you bring your hands to cover your face, futilely trying to ward off the flame. It continues to issue forth in waves, eventually encasing you in a mass of living flames. Oddly, it does not burn, nor does it seem to change you - though for some reason the flames set your nipples erect, and cause your pussy to be practically soaked from arousal.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>Again, you are encased in apparently harmless flame. Again, you become exceedingly aroused - one hand drawn to your moistening snatch, another to your - suddenly much larger - breasts. You briefly rub your erogenous zones until you remember this is only an effect of the spell. 'Some sort of bimboizing spell - countered easily enough.' And you do, returning quickly to your natural state.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>You are again encased in the bimboizing flame, finding it harder to put up an effective resistance. Again, you feel an overwhelming sense of lust, as your hands are drawn to your drooling snatch. You feel your proportions shifting, becoming much more exaggerated - thinner waist, wider hips, MUCH larger breasts. You find it nearly impossible to avoid tearing off your undergarments and fingering yourself. Strands of fire-engine red hair flick past your eyes as you violently thrust into yourself, heedless of any onlookers. A voice echoes inside your own head 'YES - GIVE IN TO YOUR DESIRE, BECOME MY LIEUTENANT OF LUST' - but instead of driving you to climax, it snaps you out of it. You are able to reverse the spell - though oddly, having your libido relatively in check fills you with a great sense of regret.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>This time you almost welcome the flame, more than a little eager for it to return you to what you are shocked to find yourself thinking of as your natural form. It's even faster this time - your body hypersexualizes in the blink of an eye, your mind immediately clouded by overwhelming lust as your fingers seek your hungry little hole. Your large breasts bounce violently as you assault your needy sex, first with one finger, then two, then three, then your entire fist. You scream as you reach orgasm more quickly than ever before - though this time the climax brings a feeling of something shooting out from your spine, and from two spots on your forehead. 'YESS... SOON YOU WILL BELONG TO ME, BODY AND SOUL' you hear the voice say, as you inspect your body, only to find two tiny horns on your head, and a 6-inch tail with a barbed spade at the end on your rear. Shocked, you are snapped out of your orgasmic trance, and are able to bring yourself to - very reluctantly - reverse the spell. You immediately regret doing so, and can only hope your opponent will soon return you to your state of lustful bliss.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>You practically leap into your opponent's flame, the desire to shed this pathetic body overwhelming any sense of restraint, or thought of permanent consequences. It takes a mere 10 seconds to lose all vestiges of the woman you were - though even that wait seems unbearable. Despite the changes it brought last time, you quickly bring yourself to orgasm again and again and again. You cry out in delicious agony as your skin seems to burn, turning a blood red; you scream with bliss as your horns grow long and curled; you feel incredible joy and wonder as your tail lengthens, becoming long and flexible enough to assault your own pussy. Change after change - some increasing your sexuality (the G-cup tits, the enormously wide hips) and others your increasingly hellish nature (the pointed ears, the foot-long, forked tongue) - you quickly lose track of them all, as you lose yourself in the never-ending waves of passion. 'YES! YES! BUT ONE STEP REMAINS - USE YOUR NEW FORM TO ENSNARE ANOTHER, AND YOU WILL FULLY BE WORTHY OF MY GIFT.' Thoughts of assaulting those around you fill your mind - your tongue penetrating some Blonde, Busty Bimbo's cunt as two Beefy Dudes take you from behind - and, for just a fleeting moment, your old mind re-asserts itself. 'You aren't some sex-crazed slut' it says, between thoughts of further debaucheries, 'let alone a servant of Hell. Get ahold of yourself girl!'... and somehow, you do, and the magic fades. Though you quickly find yourself getting down on your knees, and begging your attacker to cast the spell once more...</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>The flames assault you for what you resolve will be the final time. Before the flames even fully subside, you leap upon your attacker, your mouth instantly attached to their groin. As you lick and suck, you feel their pleasure building inside yourself. You cum in waves, each quickly restoring parts of your demonic glory - which only intensifies as other passerbys watch your performance, the more strongly affected masturbating on the spot. A fight breaks out among the beefy dudes about who will get to claim you, before you suggest that a) you have two holes back there and b) they can take turns.  Despite this going on for what seems like hours, your attacker simply won't cum - as their ardor builds and builds, you feel a similar feeling of pent-up tightness between your shoulder blades. Finally, they scream in ecstasy - as two bat-like wings unfold from your own shoulders, finally making you complete. There is no going back now - you have fully become a Sexy Succubus. The voice confirms it 'YES. GO FORTH. TRANSFORM OTHERS TO JOIN MY ARMIES, AND YOUR REWARD WILL BE GREAT. FAIL ME AND... WELL, LET US JUST SAY THAT YOU SHOULD NOT FAIL.' This is going to be so much fun...</TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>Fire springs forth from your hands, as your victim raises his hands to cover his face, futilely trying to ward off the flame. The fire spews forth in waves, encasing him in a mass of living flames. Oddly, it does not burn, nor does it seem to change him - though you can tell that his dick is standing erect, steel-hard and erect through the whole process.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>You shoot another ball of flame at your victim. Again, his dick stands erect - though it seems much smaller than before. His hands are drawn to both his groin, and his suddenly swollen pectorals. 'So, a gender-change spell', he says, incorrectly - 'easy enough to counter.' And so he does. But little does he realize...</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>This time, the flames fully feminize your victim - though he... well, she... is lacking a few curves compared to some of the magically afflicted around you, her C-cup breasts and long, flowing fire-engine red hair leave little doubt. And all doubt is removed as she removes her garments, and begins fingering herself right on the spot. 'WELL DONE - SOON ENOUGH SHE WILL GIVE IN AND JOIN US', you hear the voice say. But 'soon' is not now - she... well, he... has cancelled the spell, and returned to his former self.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>Your victim almost seems to welcome the flames this time. It takes no time at all for all traces of her former maleness to vanish, only the red of his flaming mane distinguishing her from the Blonde, Busty Bimbos all around her. Again, all thoughts are consumed, as she focuses intently on bringing herself to orgasm. 'SHE IS LOSING HERSELF - HER SOUL WILL SOON BE OURS' - and you quickly see what the voice means as she climaxes for the first time - and two small horns spring from her forehead, while a short, barbed tail snakes its way out of her behind. Shocked by this occurrence, she immediately snaps out of her trance, and is able to cancel the spell - though you see what may be a look of regret in his eyes after he has done so.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>Your victim practically leaps into the flame shooting forth from your palms, the desire to return to the state of primal lust overwhelming any sense of restraint, or thought of permanent consequences. Within seconds his bimbo body returns, and she quickly sets off bringing herself to repeated orgasm, despite the changes it brought on the previous time. Her body twists repeatedly - the blood-red skin, the long curled horns, the cloven hooves just a few of many marking her fate as a demon of lust (not to mention the G-cup breasts and impossibly wide hips putting the mere mortals around her to shame.) She seems most pleased by the lengthening of her own tail, which she quickly puts to use assaulting her own snatch. You think her transformation must be complete, but the voice returns: 'SHE IS VERY CLOSE. ANOTHER CAST OR TWO AND SHE WILL BE LOST FOREVER - DO NOT FAIL ME IN THIS, MAGUS'. And you find the voice is correct - somehow, your victim regains his composure, and returns to his old male form. You are genuinely surprised to see him get down on his knees, and BEG you to cast the spell at him again... soon...</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>You assault your victim with the flames for what will be the final time. She leaps upon you, assaulting your groin with her mouth. The demonic changes accrue rapidly - though her skillful ministrations prevent you from recognizing the majority of them. Though your own lusts re-double as she acquires a foot long, forked tongue. You are vaguely cognizant of her shouting for others to join her impromptu orgy, as she reminds those around her that she has two holes back there...  Your release never seems to come, as the tension builds, and builds, and builds. 'DO NOT CONCERN YOURSELF OVERMUCH, MAGUS. SURELY, YOU ARE POWERFUL ENOUGH TO RESIST LOSING YOUR SOUL TO YOUR OWN CREATION... ARE YOU NOT?' Finally, after what seems like an eternity of delicious torture, you find that you apparently are - you cry out in orgasm, just as a large pair of bat-like wings erupts from her back. 'YES, SHE BELONGS TO M... I MEAN, TO US, NOW, MAGUS. YOU ARE TO BE COMMENDED. I GIVE YOU YOUR LIFE. FOR NOW.' And finally, the newborn succubus detaches herself from your groin, blinks a few times, takes a good look around - and moves off, no doubt intending to add further to the legions of Hell.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>Fire springs forth from your hands, as your victim raises her hands to cover her face, futilely trying to ward off the flame. The fire spews forth in waves, encasing her in a mass of living flames. Oddly, it does not burn, nor does it seem to change her - though you can see that her nipples are standing erect, and catch a hint of moisture from lower down...</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>You shoot another ball of flame at your victim. Again, her breasts swell, larger than before. Signs of arousal are apparent as her hands are drawn both to the inflated mammaries, and to her suddenly leaking snatch . 'Some sort of bimboizing spell', she says, incorrectly - 'countered easily enough.' And so she does. But little does she realize...</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>This time the flames more quickly affect your victim - she is quickly lying there, panting, her exaggerated curves putting many of the magically afflicted around her to shame. You note that her mind is obviously being changed as well - you look with a bit of shock as she removes her garments, and begins fingering herself right on the spot. 'WELL DONE - SOON ENOUGH SHE WILL GIVE IN AND JOIN US', you hear the voice say. But 'soon' is not now - she manages to cancel out the spell, returning to her former composure and proportions.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>Your victim almost seems to welcome the flames this time. It takes no time at all for her hypersexualized proportions to return. Again, all thoughts are consumed, as she focuses intently on bringing herself to orgasm. 'SHE IS LOSING HERSELF - HER SOUL WILL SOON BE OURS' - and you quickly see what the voice means as she climaxes for the first time while under your influence - and two small horns spring from her forehead, while a short, barbed tail snakes its way out of her behind. Shocked by this occurrence, she immediately snaps out of her trance, and is able to cancel the spell - though you see what may be a look of regret in her eyes after she has done so.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>Your victim practically leaps into the flame shooting forth from your palms, the desire to return to the state of primal lust overwhelming any sense of restraint, or thought of permanent consequences. Within seconds her bimbo body returns, and she quickly sets off bringing herself to repeated orgasm, despite the changes it brought on the previous time. Her body twists repeatedly - the blood-red skin, the long curled horns, the cloven hooves just a few of many marking her fate as a demon of lust (not to mention the G-cup breasts and impossibly wide hips putting the mere mortals around her to shame.) She seems most pleased by the lengthening of her own tail, which she quickly puts to use assaulting her own snatch. You think her transformation must be complete, but the voice returns: 'SHE IS VERY CLOSE. ANOTHER CAST OR TWO AND SHE WILL BE LOST FOREVER - DO NOT FAIL ME IN THIS, MAGUS'. And you find the voice is correct - somehow, your victim regains her composure, and returns to her old form. You are genuinely surprised to see her get down on her knees, and BEG you to cast the spell at her again... soon...</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>You assault your victim with the flames for what will be the final time. She leaps upon you, assaulting your groin with her mouth. The demonic changes accrue rapidly - though her skillful ministrations prevent you from recognizing the majority of them. Though your own lusts re-double as she acquires a foot long, forked tongue. You are vaguely cognizant of her shouting for others to join her impromptu orgy, as she reminds those around her that she has two holes back there...  Your release never seems to come, as the tension builds, and builds, and builds. 'DO NOT CONCERN YOURSELF OVERMUCH, MAGUS. SURELY, YOU ARE POWERFUL ENOUGH TO RESIST LOSING YOUR SOUL TO YOUR OWN CREATION... ARE YOU NOT?' Finally, after what seems like an eternity of delicious torture, you find that you apparently are - you cry out in orgasm, just as a large pair of bat-like wings erupts from her back. 'YES, SHE BELONGS TO M... I MEAN, TO US, NOW, MAGUS. YOU ARE TO BE COMMENDED. I GIVE YOU YOUR LIFE. FOR NOW.' And finally, the newborn succubus detaches herself from your groin, blinks a few times, takes a good look around - and moves off, no doubt intending to add further to the legions of Hell.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>

</Form>
