<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>You gasp as a powerful surge of magic binds you in place. You blush brightly as your clothing evaporates into mist, leaving you completely naked and helplessly paralyzed in place. Your mouth suddenly begins to ache as it is slowly forced open, despite your best efforts to resist. You spot a strange object beginning to materialize before your eyes and you soon come to realize that is is the bit and harness that would go on a horse's head, only sized to fit you! You struggle and manage to gather your magic to break free from this curse, looking around to try to find the source of the spell. After spotting no one around, you nervously gather your re-materialized clothing and redress, keeping a wary eye open to any further attacks.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>You feel a tingle run up your spine before you are once again stricken stiff as a board by the unknown spell. Your clothing immediately vanishes and you feel your cock unwillingly getting hard as a wave of arousal seeps into your flesh, attempting to lower your will. You groan gently, wishing you could stroke yourself off to relieve this growing urge that is throbbing between your legs. You fail to notice as your muscles begin to slightly soften while your hair is slowly growing longer. Your mouth is once again forced open and a effeminate moan escapes your lips. This foreign sound you make causes you to blush and begin to struggle as the harness is slowly wrapped around your head. You catch the faint taste of the polished metal on your tongue before your will overpowers the unnatural arousal of the spell and you break free. You drop to your knees and pant as your body slowly regains its masculinity and your clothes re-appear. You stand and begin to run, trying to escape this freakish spell.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>As you continue your escape you feel yourself run right back into the spell that has been assaulting you. You manage only a meek whimper before the magic pours into your body. The influence it has over you growing stronger with every cast against you. You moan as the cold air hits your body when your clothing vanishes yet again. You look down at your rock hard member in time to see yourself beginning to orgasm. You whimper pathetically as you literally watch your cock beginning to dwindle in size as you cum, and soon there is a stomach churning slurp that comes from between your legs as a puffy female mound forms. You can't help but moan and rub your thighs together as your new pussy quivers excitedly and causes your mind to cloud even further as the spell continues to change you. You feel a pressure in your chest as two large bulges push out and form into perfect C cup breasts with perked aching nipples. Meanwhile your body has lost all its masculine muscle tone for that of an athletic female body. You whinny in pleasure and blink, realizing that while you had been so distracted with your sudden gender change you failed to notice the mental effects of the spell. You begin to struggle as the bit and bridle appear in front of your face, but this time you open your mouth willingly, almost inviting it inside. You dully neigh as the bit fits snugly into your mouth and the straps wrap around your head, but you suddenly feel a surge or resistance grow within your mind and you struggle free from the binds of the spell. You roughly drop to the ground and lay there still naked, and still female, as you begin a panic induced sprint away from the spell.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>You glance over your shoulder as you try to cover your naked body as well as you can manage. You stumble to the ground as you find your foot trapped to a now glowing sigil on the ground. That is how they are casting their spells you realize, but this comes to late as the magical trap once more pulls your body over it. You find yourself hovering in mid air over the sigil with your body on full display. You do not feel yourself changing this time which fills you with a false hope, but your thoughts are short lived as all around you items begin to form. Leather straps, thigh length hoof boots, arm bindings, and last but not least your beloved bit and bridle form in the air around you. You struggle weakly against the spell until a wave of docility forming a blanket over your mind. You smile and let out a giggle as you happily open your mouth, taking the bit inside while the bridle was securely strapped into place. Looking down you watch as your dainty little feet are gently guided into the warm embrace of the boots. You wiggle your feet in discomfort as you know you will be forced to walk around on your tip toes to give the illusion that you are truly walking on hooves. You neigh happily and hear a strange buzzing. Looking up you see an electric razor right before it moves forward, shaving your hair into a mohawk to give the appearance of a horses' mane. Whimpering at the destruction of your wonderful hair you begin to struggle once again. Struggling against your bindings, both physical and mental until you drop to the ground and are free once again. You wobble as you stand, realizing that you are still wearing your new hoof boots as well as your bit and bridle. Taking them off doesn't even cross your mind because a good pony like you always wears them right? You begin to clumsily trot forward with a cute sounding clip clop and continue running away from... something as you slowly begin to forget why.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>You stop, looking around and wanting something to drink. You cannot find and sugar cubes, or grass, but you do spot an apple setting out on a nearby table. You whinny happily and trot over to the apple, picking it up with your hands and lifting it to your mouth. You blink and neigh in frustration when you remember your bit is still in your mouth and blocking you from eating your apple! You whinny and neigh in frustration before a friendly hand reaches from over your shoulder and gently un-clips your bit, letting it slip out of your mouth. You turn to thank the friendly stranger, maybe nuzzle them even, but are surprised to see no one there when you turn. You shrug it off and dig your teeth into the delicious apple, munching away happily and blissfully unaware of the ominous glowing underneath you. You suddenly stiffen and float into the air, the remaining pony gear appearing around you. You smile, excited to finish becoming a pretty pony girl! You neigh softly as the smooth leather straps caress over your skin. You let out a pleasure neigh as one of those wonderful straps covers your pouting pussy lips. You shiver softly as your arms are pulled behind your back and the arm bringing is pulled over them, wrapping more leather straps around your shoulders and belly to keep your arms unusable. After all a pony like you doesn't need arms. You neigh in discomfort as you are bent over. You look between your legs and see your tail slowly floating towards your backside, attached to an oddly shaped cone. Your dulled animal mind cannot process what is going on so you ignore it. But that is short lived as a sudden discomfort in your anus cause you to panic and neigh frantically. As your butt plug tail is pushed in you managed to break free from the spell and gallop away in panic, no longer human but a wild animal one or two casts away from being reduced to a mindless pony girl pet.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>You frantically look around, slowly calming down now that the initial soreness of your rump had worn off. You trot around, fully bound and geared up like a good little pony girl. You stop and look in front of a panel of glass, gasping as you see what you have become. You do not recognize the creature in the reflection, it isn't a pony girl. Your old self is in the reflection, trying to tell you who you are, begging you to escape this lie that you have become. You begin to question your pony self just before a hand is placed on the back of your head. In an instant your reflection cries out in pain as their entire body morphs into that of a fully feral horse before your eyes. Your smile contently, your mind abolished to a puddle of horsey bliss. You turn and let your owner clip on your reigns and puts your bit back into your mouth. Your follow them unquestioningly, willing to do anything they wish because you are a simple animal inside a human body.</TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>You gasp as a powerful surge of magic binds you in place. You blush brightly as your clothing evaporates into mist, leaving you completely naked and helplessly paralyzed in place. Your mouth suddenly begins to ache as it is slowly forced open, despite your best efforts to resist. You spot a strange object beginning to materialize before your eyes and you soon come to realize that is is the bit and harness that would go on a horse's head, only sized to fit you! You struggle and manage to gather your magic to break free from this curse, looking around to try to find the source of the spell. After spotting no one around, you nervously gather your re-materialized clothing and redress, keeping a wary eye open to any further attacks.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>You feel a tingle run up your spine before you are once again stricken stiff as a board by the unknown spell, your clothing immediately vanishing. You can feel your pussy unwillingly getting wet as a wave of arousal seeps into your flesh, attempting to lower your will. You groan gently, wishing you could finger yourself to relieve this growing urge aching between your legs. You fail to notice as your muscles beginning to tone and grow slightly more powerful, as if you have gone through a lot of track or running exercises. Your mouth is once again forced open, a weak neigh escaping your lips in place of a moan. This foreign sound you make causes you to blush and begin to struggle as the harness is slowly wrapped around your head. You catch the faint taste of the polished metal on your tongue before your will overpowers the unnatural arousal of the spell and you break free. You drop to your knees and pant as your body slowly regains its masculinity and your clothes re-appear. You stand and begin to run, trying to escape this freakish spell and whatever it is trying to do to you.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>As you continue your escape you feel yourself run right back into the spell that has been assaulting you. You manage a meek whimper as the magic pours into your body, growing stronger in it's influence with every cast against you. You moan as the cold air hits your body when your clothing vanishes yet again. You feel your body becoming toned and athletic once more, your breast burning in pleasure as they change to perky C cups. You shiver as your pussy drips as the erotic fire the spell burns in your mind dulls your sense of self and allows you to feel every change it makes to your body. Your butt tightens and takes on a perfect hear shape while all your body hair from your neck down falls out, leaving you perfectly smoothed. You whinny in pleasure and blink, realizing that while you had been so distracted with your sudden physical changes that you failed to notice the mental effects of the spell. You begin to struggle as the bit and bridle appear in front of your face, but this time your mouth open willingly, almost inviting it inside. You dully neigh as the bit fits snugly into your mouth and the straps wrap around your head. But you suddenly feel a surge or resistance grow within your mind and you struggle free from the binds of the spell. You roughly drop to the ground, still naked as you begin a panic induced sprint away from the spell. </TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>You glance over your shoulder as you try to cover your naked body as well as you can manage. You stumble to the ground as you find your foot trapped to a now glowing sigil on the ground. That is how they are casting their spells you realize, but this comes to late as the magical trap once more pulls your body over it. You find yourself hovering in mid air over the sigil with your body on full display. You do not feel yourself changing this time which fills you with a false hope, but your thoughts are short lived as all around you items begin to form. Leather straps, thigh length hoof boots, arm bindings, and last but not least your beloved bit and bridle form in the air around you. You struggle weakly against the spell until a wave of docility forming a blanket over your mind. You smile and let out a giggle as you happily open your mouth, taking the bit inside while the bridle was securely strapped into place. Looking down you watch as your dainty little feet are gently guided into the warm embrace of the boots. You wiggle your feet in discomfort as you know you will be forced to walk around on your tip toes to give the illusion that you are truly walking on hooves. You neigh happily and hear a strange buzzing. Looking up you see an electric razor right before it moves forward, shaving your hair into a mohawk to give the appearance of a horses' mane. Whimpering at the destruction of your wonderful hair you begin to struggle once again. Struggling against your bindings, both physical and mental until you drop to the ground and are free once again. You wobble as you stand, realizing that you are still wearing your new hoof boots as well as your bit and bridle. Taking them off doesn't even cross your mind because a good pony like you always wears them right? You begin to clumsily trot forward with a cute sounding clip clop and continue running away from... something as you slowly begin to forget why.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>You stop, looking around and wanting something to drink. You cannot find and sugar cubes, or grass, but you do spot an apple setting out on a nearby table. You whinny happily and trot over to the apple, picking it up with your hands and lifting it to your mouth. You blink and neigh in frustration when you remember your bit is still in your mouth and blocking you from eating your apple! You whinny and neigh in frustration before a friendly hand reaches from over your shoulder and gently un-clips your bit, letting it slip out of your mouth. You turn to thank the friendly stranger, mabey nuzzle them even, but are surprised to see no one there when you turn. You shrug it off and dig your teeth into the delicious apple, munching away happily and blissfully unaware of the ominous glowing underneath you. You suddenly stiffen and float into the air, the remaining pony gear appearing around you. You smile, excited to finish becoming a pretty pony girl! You neigh softly as the smooth leather straps caress over your skin. You let out a pleasure neigh as one of those wonderful straps covers your pouting pussy lips. You shiver softly as your arms are pulled behind your back and the arm bringing is pulled over them, wrapping more leather straps around your shoulders and belly to keep your arms unusable. After all a pony like you doesn't need arms. You neigh in discomfort as you are bent over. You look between your legs and see your tail slowly floating towards your backside, attached to an oddly shaped cone. Your dulled animal mind cannot process what is going on so you ignore it. But that is short lived as a sudden discomfort in your anus cause you to panic and neigh frantically. As your butt plug tail is pushed in you managed to break free from the spell and gallop away in panic, no longer human but a wild animal one or two casts away from being reduced to a mindless pony girl pet.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>You frantically look around, slowly calming down now that the initial soreness of your rump had worn off. You trot around, fully bound and geared up like a good little pony girl. You stop and look in front of a panel of glass, gasping as you see what you have become. You do not recognize the creature in the reflection, it isn't a pony girl. Your old self is in the reflection, trying to tell you who you are, begging you to escape this lie that you have become. You begin to question your pony self just before a hand is placed on the back of your head. In an instant your reflection cries out in pain as their entire body morphs into that of a fully feral horse before your eyes. Your smile contently, your mind abolished to a puddle of horsey bliss. You turn and let your owner clip on your reigns and puts your bit back into your mouth. Your follow them unquestioningly, willing to do anything they wish because you are a simple animal inside a human body.</TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>You watch as your opponent gasps as a powerful surge of magic binds them in place. They blush brightly as their clothing evaporates into mist, leaving them completely naked and helplessly paralyzed in place. They groan as their mouth is slowly forced open, despite their best efforts to resist. Their eyes widen as they spot a strange object beginning to materialize before their eyes and they must soon come to realize that is is the bit and harness that would go on a horse's head, only sized to fit a human instead! They struggle and manage to gather their magic to break free from your curse, looking around to try to find the source of the spell. After spotting no one around, they nervously gather your re-materialized clothing and redress, keeping a wary eye open to any further attacks.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>You loose sight of your victim, expanding your mind to sense if they have triggered any more of your traps. As you continue to profile them you peek around a corner to notice them once again floating a few feet from the ground as another one of your spells corrupts their humanity further. You smile at their obvious arousal as more pony play gear begins to appear. But before you get to have any more fun they break free and begin to flee yet again. You sigh and continue to trail them from behind, plotting the next step in your dastardly plan.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>As your victim rounds into an alleyway you quickly cast another spell on the ground ahead of them right as they look over their shoulder. They once again become ensnared by your spell and are stripped naked, this time their clothing was not coming back. You can feel your own sex burning in arousal as you watch them change into a toned and athletic girl, and sign of their old human form gone and replaced with the perfect body for a pony girl. Alas they manage to break free again, leaving them stuck in their pony girl body, but not with their pony girl mind. With a huff you begin to follow them in the shadows yet again.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>You follow the frightened girl, who is trying to hid her naked body from view as she runs from cover to cover. You smile and just managed to get a sigil underneath her. She is lifted into the air, her face gaining a slightly peaceful expression as she begins to accept her fate. You watch as her thigh length leather boots are slowly inched onto her legs, forcing to walk on her tip toes on the boot's special hoof shaped sole. You also spot that they are moaning into their now beloved bit in their mouth while their head is shaved into a perfect pony girl mane. They drop to the ground and you begin to walk up behind them to attach their reigns, but they spook and take off clumsily making little clip clops on their new hooves.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>You smile as you watch your increasingly animal minded victim as they search for water or food. You snap your fingers, causing an apple to appear on a nearby bench. The little pony neighs into her bit and trots over to the apple, picking it up and trying to nibble on it, but her bit was in the way and she was to ignorant now to remember how to take it off. You reach aronud from behind her and unclip the bit from her mouth. She neighs and begins to mindlessly munch her apple, only turning after a few moments to see no one there. Soon they are forced into the air again as the rest of their bondage gear appears. You watch eagerly as their arms are bound behind them and the leather straps are put into place, still leaving her naked for all to see. She admire her dribbling sex as her horse tailed butt plug is slowly pushed into her rump. But sadly the sudden shock of her anal invader was to much for the poor pony. She breaks free and gallops off, now nothing more than an animal a few casts away from being a permanent part of your stables. You have to finish her quickly before she can cleanse.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>You manage to catch up to your lost pony, noticing she is standing in front of a pane of glass. You gasp, knowing she is trying to get her human mind to regain control. You cannot have that. You stroll up behind her and take a firm grip on the back of her head with your hand. Your magic burns into her mind, literally destroying any remaining piece of her humanity. She snorts and neighs, causing you to smile as you hook the reins onto her tack. You lead your new pet off while she faithfully prances behind you, now nothing more than a animal brain in a human body.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
