<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<Description>This player is now a living suit of armor! Her from seems to indicate that she was meant to be worn by a well shaped woman, however even though it should offer full protection, which the spikes on the shoulder pads, feet, knee pads and gauntlets, you notice that there is a lack of armor where the hips, thighs and the upper arms should be. Also there is a big gap on the chest which would normally reveal a nice cleavage and behind.  However the helmet is nicely detailed portraying a beautiful woman's face, with a space in the back to let long hair flow. It would, however, be a good idea to stay away from her as she remains fully animate and seems to be looking for someone to 'embrace'. Wouldn't want that someone to be you, eh?</Description>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>You get hit by a silver colored bolt! As you get hit you get ready for any major changes but instead your skin becomes shiny and you start feeling empty. You quickly and efficiently reverse the changes.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>You get hit by a silver colored bolt! The feeling of emptiness comes back straight away as your skin turns to metal. You wonder what type of robotization spell this is as your belly becomes chain mail links and you chest becomes plated and two bumps push outwards. Your legs and arms also become more feminine as you stop wondering and reverse the changes.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>You get hit by a silver colored bolt! The transformation is faster as your back to being a fullmetal being. You shoulders get bigger as the become pads. It is at that time that you realize that  your being turned into a piece of armor!  Your face becomes very feminine but stuck in place and your hair melts into your head. The feeling of emptiness gets greater and greater as you slowly hollow out. Before you hollow out more you reverse the changes.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>You get hit by a silver colored bolt! The changes are quick to come back as now your hands seem to thicken into gloves and your face becomes a beautiful but motionless visage with a gap opening up to allow your future wearer to let her hair out. Spikes also grow out of your shoulder pads, gloves and knee pad as you look on to your opponent to try and protest, who is smiling as you turn. Your feet also become bigger and the toes of each feet meld into pointed ends. The hollowification becomes faster now as your main body is now empty. You reverse the changes with a bit of remorse as you turn back.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>You get hit by a silver colored bolt! The changes propagate themselves even faster now as all that is left is hollowification and a few minor details. A huge gap opens up on your chest which would in theory reveal a nice cleavage of your wearer. You start thinking of beautiful times you will get with your master as you fight as one against creatures of myths and legends. You snap Back into reality as one of your hands fall off as your upper arm disappears. You quickly and efficiently reverse the changes before your other arm and your legs fall off. However a weird feeling stays with you as your back in human form, a feeling of emptiness as now you wish someone to be in you. Hopefully you'll get your wish.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>You get hit by a silver colored bolt! The changes flow over you instantly as you fall into pieces, a full set of magical armor. You wait in eager anticipation as your master looks over you, smiling. Shock and horror comes as your master smiles and walks away, leaving you alone on the floor. After an hour your wails of agony and anger seem to come to life as you feel possessed. A ghostly form comes out of your armor. This is what you would have looked like if you weren't inanimate. The naked but ghostly form then starts equipping you onto her as you come to life. After a couple of moments you regain full control of movement as you now stand as a very feminine piece of armor. Now you are on a quest to find a wearer suitable enough to wear you! </TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>You hit your opponent with a silver colored bolt! As your opponent gets hit they is ready for any major changes but instead their skin becomes shiny. They quickly and efficiently reverses the change.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>You hit your opponent with a silver colored bolt! The feeling of emptiness overwhelms your target as their skin turns to metal. "What robot you trying to turn me into?" They wonder as their belly becomes chain mail links and their chest becomes plated and two bumps push outwards. The legs and arms also become more feminine as they stop wondering and reverse the changes.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>You hit your opponent with a silver colored bolt! The transformation is faster as they're back to being a fullmetal being. the shoulders get bigger as they become pads. It is at that time that they realize that you are turning them into armor!  Their face becomes very feminine but stuck in place before they can complain and their hair melts into your head. You can feel an aura of emptiness getting greater and greater around them as they start hollowing out. Before they hollow out more they reverse the changes.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>You hit your opponent with a silver colored bolt! The changes are quick to come back as now you notice their hands seem to thicken into gloves and your their becomes a beautiful but motionless visage with a gap opening up to allow their future wearer to let their hair out. Spikes also grow out of the shoulder pads, gloves and knee pad. You smile as they turn to you and try to protest. Their feet also become bigger and the toes of each feet meld into pointed ends. The hollowification becomes faster now as your the body is now empty. They reverse the changes with a bit of remorse on their face as they turn back.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>You hit your opponent with a silver colored bolt! The changes propagate themselves even faster now as all that is left is hollowification and a few minor details. A huge gap opens up on their chest which would in theory reveal a nice cleavage of the wearer. Your opponent is still as you imagine them thinking of the beautiful times they will get with their master as both fight as one against creatures of myths and legends. YThey snap Back into reality as one of their hands fall off as the upper arm disappears. They quickly and efficiently reverse the changes before their other arm and your legs fall off. However a weird feeling stays with them as they are back in human form, a feeling of emptiness on their face as they now wish someone to wear in you. Hopefully they'll get your wish.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>You hit your opponent with a silver colored bolt! The changes Flow over them instantly as they fall into pieces, a full set of magical armor. You smile as you can imagine them eagerly waiting for you to equip them. You turn around letting shock and horror go through the piece of armor, if it has those feelings, as you walk away, leaving the armor alone on the floor. You don't realize that the magic of your opponent is still within the armor. After an hour their wails of agony and anger seem to come to life as they feel possessed. A ghostly form comes out of the armor. This is what they would have looked like if they weren't inanimate. The naked but ghostly form then starts equipping the armor onto her as you come to life. After a couple of moments the person in the armor regains full control of movement as a very feminine piece of armor stands. It ow on a quest to find a wearer suitable enough to wear them! </TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
