<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>You and your opponent have a heated exchange of spells. Magic shields are cast and shattered as fast as new offensive spells are flung through the room. Suddenly, your opponent manages to get a magic ball through your defenses and hits your legs. You are swept off your feet as your legs explode into fine pinkish-red dust. What a dirty trick. You cast your counter-spell and prepare yourself for the next round.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>This time your opponent seems to target your head. A grave mistake, as you are swept once again off your feet. This time, however, the dust your legs have become starts to vibrate until it rises up in the air between you and your attacker. You notice a distinctive form as the dust rises higher. It somewhat reminds you of a short dress. So that's what your attacker wants. As you are not ready yet to become a piece of clothing, you cast the counter-spell.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>You are temporarily overwhelmed by a massive attack from your opponent, hitting your legs and your right arm and converting them to dust. Again the dust assumes the shape of the dress, but this time it also changes into fabric. Oddly your senses are split, as you can not only feel your own body, but that of the dress as well. What little remains of the dust seems to compress itself into decorative gems. Just before those gems can settle down, you cast the counter-spell.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>You try your best to defend yourself, but the previous transformations have weakened you. You are not really surprised as you find yourself on the floor again and both your arms and everything below your chest turns into that pinkish red dust. Once again, the dress forms itself and starts to decorate itself with gems. But the amount of dust is not enough and parts of you remain barren. Wait. Did you just think of yourself as the dress? You quickly dispel and return to your normal form.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>Your mind shatters for a moment as your whole body turns to dust. Slowly, you gather yourself and then you try the same with your body. It takes you a moment, but then you are the perfect little dress as always. Smartly cut and sexy as hell, you are the best dress this side of Paris. Your decorative gems all over you help to draw everyone's stares towards you. But strangely, no one is wearing you right now. You try hard to remember why, and then you do: you were never a dress to begin with. With what little remains of your willpower and tremendous effort, you bend your magic to return yourself to your former body.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>Your enemy hits you again before you can fully collect yourself from your last ordeal. A moment later, you are the sparkly cocktail dress that you were designed to be. Flashbacks tell you the story how a talented youngster of a designer who created you in her spare time. You remember many things: how she scouted for the perfect fabric, settling on a pinkish-red one; the many hours of careful cutting and sewing; the agony of fixing all the tiny gems onto you to make you oh so sparkly; the moment you were first worn in public on a runway show for new talented designers; how your owner had to beg the young designer so that she would sell you to her; the first time your owner wore you. As you return to the present, you know who you are: the most sparkly cocktail dress on a mission to highlight your owner everywhere. You don't know why you aren't being worn right now, but you know that you will be worn again soon. Who could resist wearing something as gorgeous as you?</TFMessage_Completed_1st>



<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>You and your opponent have a heated exchange of spells. Magic shields are cast and shattered as fast as new offensive spells are flung trough the room. You notice a weakness and thread a bolt of magic through your enemy’s defense. Your victim falls down as their legs explode into fine pinkish-red dust. However, your foe recovers quickly, dispelling your changes and preparing for the next round.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>This time, you are targeting your opponent's head, to again use their weakness against them. Your spell swipes your foe off their feet and changes their legs to dust again. You use your magic to control the pinkish-red dust to slowly rise. You are trying to form the shape of a dress with the dust, but your enemy dispels your magic and regenerates their previous body.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>As you see the beads of sweat running down your opponent's body, you know that you are close. You launch one massive attack to break your enemy’s remaining defenses by brute force. As you break through, you hit the legs and right arm, turning them to dust. You try again to form the dress, this time with more success. You even manage to change the dust into a velvety material. As you see some dust left over you gather it up and compress it into dozens of small gems. As you try to fix these gems onto the dress, it falls apart, returning to your enemy as their counter-spell takes effect.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>One look at your enemy tells you that you are close to winning. Your enemy looks exhausted, so you cast a quick spell before your target recovers. As most of your victim's body turns to dust, you can see that only the head and chest remain of your foe. This time, you make great progress at forming and decorating the dress, until you run out of dust. As you prepare to create more, the dress bursts into dust again and flows back to your foe. You thought your target did not have it in them to fight anymore. A mistake on your part.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Annoyed by your last mistake, you gather your magic for a new brute force attack. As you release it all at once, it shatters your victim's defenses and makes your target burst into dust completely. As you put your hands on your hips and think “That's it.”, you witness the dust begin to move. You worry that your target had already cast their counter-spell, but as the dust settles by itself into the shape of a dress, you can only smirk. Slowly, it turns velvet and decorative gemstones appear all over it. This is it. The one dress you envisioned. Your heart nearly breaks as your foe casts a counter-spell again. Your victim still has some will left; it's time to change that.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>One bolt: That's all it takes to transform your target to dust again. As your victim shapes itself into the dress you love, you prepare another spell. Time to get rid of that pesky will. But then a sudden idea hits you. Why get rid of it? Why not bend your victim's will to your needs? You cast a memory spell on your victim, changing the very memories that define your foe. As you are done you wait a moment, hoping nothing happens. After a few minutes have passed, you pick up your prize. As your fingers touch the dress, a flood of feelings rush into you. Your dress loves you, needs you and above all wants to be worn by you. You look at your new sparkly cocktail-dress and hope that your memory spell lasts for a long time.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>