<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>A bit new to the conflict, you are at first concerned to be the target of a spell.  But when it hits you, you feel - healthier.  Stronger.  It may even be your imagination, but it looks like you're taller too.  Flexing your arms, you see a noticeable bicep.  And down below - the spell must be unnaturally arousing you.  You are rock hard down there - and maybe even bigger than before?  You contemplate not cancelling the spell at all - but decide doing so would be for the best.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>You are hit again by the same spell - the Male Enhancer, as you are thinking of it.  This time, there is no thought of imagining it - you ARE stronger.  Half a foot taller, at least - and your arms and legs are much bigger around.  Even your dick is a good two inches longer - and you feel your testes churning, just waiting to go out there, find a transformed woman and  ...   Wait.  What are you thinking?  ARE you thinking?  This isn't you.  You quickly cancel the spell, ashamed at your own thoughts of unbridled sexual conquest.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>The man spell again.  You're starting to really like this.  A good foot taller, big muscles on your arms - forget magic, you can pound any scrawny wizard that comes after you.  Pound?  Pound - your balls have grown, your cock is giant - you are ready to pound the chicks walking by.  Those are some crazy looking chicks - there's one that looks like a rabbit, another like a dog - a lot that look human, but smokin' hot - over there is one that looks normal, but her skin is red and she has horns.  "Succubus" - the multisyllabic word enters your consciousness as you look her up and down - and you realize that you really AREN'T thinking at all.  Horrified, you quickly cancel the spell - and as your muscles fade, your lust cools down.  Mostly.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>Again, the magic person makes you strong.  So big, so strong - you think of hitting them, kicking them, showing them who is the boss.  But you cannot be mad when you are so strong.  Much taller.  Much more good looking.  Your dick is big.  Very big. Halfway to your knee if it was soft.  But it is hard.  Very hard.  Sticking out of your shorts.  Ready to find a chick.  Or two.  Or three.  Or ... another chick at the same time.  One of those big-titted, milk leaky ones would be awesome ... Your new persona lost in a lust-fueled reverie, your true mind takes the opportunity to emerge, and cancels out the effects of the spell.  You watch your muscles shrink, your ridiculous foot-long penis returning to more human proportions - and can't help but sigh a little in regret.  Would it really be that bad to give in?</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>You no longer tiny wizard - you giant beast.  Strongest one there is.  You take on all other tiny wizards.  You smash them good.  Take all woman.  Your fuck-stick - it biggest one there is.  Hardest one there is.  You ready fuck all woman.  Normal woman, big woman, small woman, red woman, bunny woman - it no matter.  You fuck all woman good and hard.  It good to be big and strong, easy to get woman.  Fuck woman, all woman ...  Your thoughts continue in this vein, stuck on a seemingly infinite loop of randy Hulk-speak.  You slowly realize that there IS a you to comment on these thoughts - and with enormous difficulty, you are able to escape from your brutish prison, unsure if you will be able to do so again.  One thing though - he's right.  You tiny wizard now - no get woman.  NOT being him just doesn't feel right anymore ...</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>It over.  Tiny wizard gone.  You big man now, no think of old time.  Time to go out, find woman, fuck woman, find new woman.  It be good life.  You hear voice, inside your head.  It you?  No, it old you.  You not him now.  You not want listen.  It keep talking, make you listen.  "You ... yes, you, big man.  You want woman?"  You nod.  "Good, good.  I get you woman.  All kinds of women.  Just let me cast some spells..."  You look angry - you no wizard, you strong man now, wizard be tiny and weak, not like you -  "I ... I mean, let me do all the talking.  Yes, that's right, the talking. You get all sorts woman, find them change just for you.  You like, yes?"  And you do like.  Yes.  Strange voice do much talking, find many woman for you cock, woman who look not same after voice do talking.  It no matter to you, you fuck all woman, you happy.  Some time voice seem sad, but you think it happy too.</TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>
You are assaulted by an unfamiliar spell. You can't quite place it. It is not causing you to feel extra-feminine, extra-sexy or extra-slutty like most of the animate transformations - and it certainly cannot be an inanimate transformation, as it is not making you feel extra-weak. In fact - you feel strong. Pretty amazingly strong, actually. You flex a bicep, and see some noticeable muscle tone. You look down at the ground, and notice it's several inches further away than before. Is the spell turning you into some sort of Amazon warrior? The thought arouses you more than you would have thought possible - your nipples standing erect (are your breasts smaller?) and ... a bit of a bump showing through your panties? Startled at the implications, you quickly cancel out the magic.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>
The strange spell returns. This time, you feel even stronger, more powerful - perhaps like a champion of the martial arts. You look down, and find you are nearly a full foot taller - and you feel like you've gained at least 50 pounds, all of it pure muscle. What you DON'T see looking down is more worrisome. Your breasts are - well, your gleaming pectorals confused you at first, but any femininity about them is completely gone. And looking further ... yes, there is a rather definite bulge down below. Pulling down your lower garments, you see ... Well, at 2 inches erect, with a tiny, nearly empty sack (hanging over a dimpled seam where your vagina seems to be closing up on itself) - if you saw these genitals on a potential sex partner, you'd laugh him out of the room. On you, however ... you shudder, and QUICKLY cancel the spell, regaining your feminine form.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>Again, you are hit by the strange manly spell. It's starting to feel GOOD. You are stronger than last time. Taller than last time. Bigger around. Your arms and legs are huge and strong. No curves on you like a weak woman. No giant boobs, no trim tummy, no wide hips, no bouncy ass, no wet cunt. Your dick grows hard at such thoughts. 8 inches, easy. Big balls, full of seed, ready to pump into closest slut. It will be easy to find a slut, since you're so big, and strong, and manly ... Suddenly, your old mind re-asserts itself, startled at the thoughts - and for that matter, the lack of thoughts - and is able to cancel out the spell. Your penis shrinks back into your skin, your muscles atrophy, your curves return. You sigh, conflicted. It is good to have your mind back, but you felt so powerful, so right under the spells effects ...</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>Wizard attacks again. He dumb - spell make you strong, strong enough to crush puny wizard. You no small like wizard - you good seven feet tall. You no weak like wizard - your muscles big, huge, good to crush foes. Then find woman. Voice in head, say you ARE woman. What it know - you no woman. Woman have big boobies, you no have boobies. Woman have big soft ass, you ass nice, hard, strong. Woman have pussy, you no have pussy. You have big, strong f*** stick. More than foot long, leaking, ready to go. It also big and strong, ready to find woman. All woman. Voice keep talking, say this not right. Say it "change you back" ... you not want change. You find self crying as change to woman - it not surprise, woman is weak, while you stro ... and just like that, your old mind returns. Though you catch yourself with a hand down your pants, regretting the loss of that male equipment ...</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>Why magic person fight you? You big, strong, strongest there is. Magic person small, weak, get crushed. By you, by other - you no care. You not always want fight - but always, always want f***. Magic person best not want woman. Woman for you, all woman. You grab woman, two woman, one in both big, strong arm. You take both woman home. You use fuck-stick. Big, big f*** stick - bigger than woman arm. Pound one woman. Pound other woman. Go out, find more woman. All woman. You big, strong. Strongest there is. Can get all woman, will get all woman. Woman no mind, woman like f*** you, you big, strong, strongest there is. Voice, tiny voice, cry out in head: "No, stop, this isn't right!" - you no listen, no want listen, not remember voice, not understand how the magic is altering your genetic makeup ... and suddenly, your mind returns. You feel incredibly weak in your female body now - the desire to give in, become the giant brute, is almost overwhelming. (And he's right too - the women observing your transformation looked VERY willing - at least as much as magically altered bimbos can be. Your other self is QUITE the stud ...)</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>It over. Old, weak woman gone, not you, how could be you? You big man now, no think of old time. Time to go out, find woman, f*** woman, find new woman. It be good life. You hear voice, inside your head. It you? No, it old you. You not her now. You not want listen. It keep talking, make you listen. "You ... yes, you, big man. You want woman?" You nod. "Good, good. I get you woman. All kinds of women. Just let me cast some spells..." You look angry - you no wizard, you strong man now, wizard be tiny and weak, not like you - "I ... I mean, let me do all the talking. Yes, that's right, the talking. You get all sorts woman, find them change just for you. You like, yes?" And you do like. Yes. Strange voice do much talking, find many woman for you cock, woman who look not same after voice do talking. It no matter to you, you f*** all woman, you happy. Some time voice seem sad, but you think it happy too.</TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>Despite this spell likely being much more interesting when applied to a female, you pick out a likely-looking at and begin the first step of his journey into becoming a Big Burly Brute - obsessed only with his own muscles and genitals, finding opponents to pound with the first and women to ... well, you guess, also pound with the second.  He does look a little bigger, a little dumber, a little hornier with the spell - but not hugely so; and he is able to reverse the spell quickly.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>This time, it is obvious to your victim that the masculine changes are not simply in his imagination - he is half a foot taller, his arms and legs notably bigger around, his chest much more muscular.  He flexes a bicep in appreciation.  Then he notices the contents of his boxer shorts - the bulge in which is ALSO noticeably bigger.  His hands go down there, intrigued ... but quickly he gets ahold of himself (er, mentally) and cancels out your enchantment.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>Your victim seems to be starting to really enjoy his state.  It takes mere moments for him to acknowledge his much greater height, his massively expanded muscles ... before all thoughts obviously come to rest on his considerably enlarged package.  He fondles it idly, as he stares slack-jawed at the many altered women around him, failing to show any sense of shame or intelligence as he fondles himself, drooling.  Then, suddenly, the light returns to his eyes, and he realizes where his giant hands are - which he raises, mortified at what he is doing, in the motions of the counterspell.  Soon he is shrinking back down to his former self - and you think you hear him sighing, almost regretfully.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>Nearly all traces of the crafty wizard you are fighting vanish, as he regains his Herculean form - this time, even bigger, taller, stronger, dumber, and more lust-crazed.  Looking at the women around him, a stupid grin forms on his face as he becomes paralyzed by indecision - should he go make a move on the bunnygirl?  Maybe try his luck with the succubus?  The doggirl, even now rubbing up against his leg, obviously in heat and smelling his engorged manhood?  Perhaps that trio of bimbos down the street?  Or even that untransformed female magus, eying him with a mixture of lust and horror?  Unable to decide, he stands there, drooling, playing with himself.  After a few minutes of this, his old consciousness seems to break through, and soon enough, your opponent stands before you unaltered.  But he looks ... sad?  Some part of him must really like being the alpha male ...</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>Your opponent is almost unrecognizable.  More beast than man ... wait, the way things have been going in this city, you should choose your words more carefully ... more man than any half-dozen unaltered men - he stands there, muscles bulging, enormous penis (over a foot at least, much, much larger than any natural one you've ever seen) throbbing, as his tiny brain considers how to use it.  As if to answer, you hear him speak - in deep, gruff monosyllables, that you would never have believed could come from a fellow magus - "Me strong.  Me find woman.  All woman.  Fuck woman.  All woman.  They like strong man.  Me strong man.  Me find woman ..."  His infinite loop of a monologue continues, seemingly oblivious to the actual, very interested woman (er, women) all around him.  As the randy Hulk-speak continues ... somehow, your old opponent breaks free, and you see him standing, unaltered before you.  Sighing dejectedly, as the women fawning over him move away ... right now, you bet if you launched the spell again, he'd jump in front of the blast, dick first.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>It is over.  The Big Burly Brute you have created is fully in control of your opponent.  You have unleashed a 7-foot tall, 300 pounds of pure muscle, sex-obsessed hypermasculine hulk on the city.  You can't say that the women around him object, other than a very few of the unaltered ones;  you notice even some of the unaltered males seem to greatly approve of his new form.  Suddenly, you see lights form around one of the more normal-looking women hanging off of your creation - you watch as her breasts momentarily grow several cup sizes, her hair turning bright blonde ... and realize that the spell was cast by your opponent!  Somehow, his old mind must still be in there, and still capable (though with obvious difficulty) of casting transfomative spells!  You weren't worried about fending off his physical strikes - but if his old mind is still in there somewhere, capable of revenge ... perhaps this is one giant of a man that you should avoid in the near future.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>While this spell could be cast for "male enhancement" as it were, where's the fun in that? You target a lovely-looking female, setting her on the first step of her journey into becoming a Big Burly Brute - obsessed only with 'his' own muscles and genitals, finding opponents to pound with the first and women to ... well, you guess, also pound with the second. Her new form is that of a strong, manly woman - her breasts have greatly atrophied, her muscles becoming visible, her height increasing by a number of inches. She looks around, pleased, flexing her new muscles like some kind of amazonian princess - one showing an un-noticed small bump in her pants. Fairly quickly though, she breaks out of the trance and reverts to her old self.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>This time, the true intent of your incantation cannot be hidden from your victim - even with the dimming intelligence in 'his' eyes. For one thing, he is taller than any woman you've ever seen - and while a few female body builders may be more ripped than his current state, they at least retain some visible curves. While still thin, the straight torso - and total lack of breasts - mark your victim as nearly fully male. And when 'he' - shockingly - pulls down his pants - exposing a 2-inch penis, and a ballsack forming over a vagina that seems to be caving in on itself - you decide that you can never think of your victim as 'she' again. Even after he reverts the changes.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>Your victim seems to be starting to really enjoy his state. It takes mere moments for him to acknowledge his total loss of womanhood, his much greater height, his massively expanded muscles ... before all thoughts obviously come to rest on his package, much, much larger than before. He fondles it idly, as he stares slack-jawed at the many altered women around him, failing to show any sense of shame or intelligence as he fondles himself, drooling. Then, suddenly, the light returns to his eyes, and he realizes where his giant hands are - which he raises, mortified at what he is doing, in the motions of the counterspell. Soon he is shrinking back down to his former self - and you think you hear him (well, 'her', though even with the restored body it is becoming difficult to think of your new brute that way) sighing, almost regretfully.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>All traces of your victim's feminine body vanish, as he regains his Herculean form - this time, even bigger, taller, stronger, dumber, and more lust-crazed. Looking at the women around him, a stupid grin forms on his face as he becomes paralyzed by indecision - should he go make a move on the bunnygirl? Maybe try his luck with the succubus? The doggirl, even now rubbing up against his leg, obviously in heat and smelling his engorged manhood? Perhaps that trio of bimbos down the street? Or even that untransformed female magus, eying him with a mixture of lust and horror? Unable to decide, he stands there, drooling, playing with himself. After a few minutes of this, his old consciousness seems to break through, and soon enough, your opponent stands before you restored. And ... crying? It looks like "she" is having major second thoughts about "her" place on the great gender divide ...</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>Your opponent is almost unrecognizable. More beast than man ... wait, the way things have been going in this city, you should choose your words more carefully ... more man than any half-dozen unaltered men - he stands there, muscles bulging, enormous penis (over a foot at least, much, much larger than any natural one you've ever seen) throbbing, as his tiny brain considers how to use it. As if to answer, you hear him speak - in deep, gruff monosyllables, that you would never have believed could come from a fellow magus, let alone a former female - "Me strong. Me find woman. All woman. f*** woman. All woman. They like strong man. Me strong man. Me find woman ..." His infinite loop of a monologue continues, seemingly oblivious to the actual, very interested woman (er, women) all around him. As the randy Hulk-speak continues ... somehow, your old opponent breaks free, and you see 'her' standing, unaltered before you - carrying 'herself' in such a posture that using a feminine pronoun seems almost absurd, despite fulling regaining a woman's body. You can imagine 'her' jumping in front of your next spell, groin-first, aching to return to what she must believe is her true form ...</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>It is over. The Big Burly Brute you have created is fully in control of your opponent. You have unleashed a 7-foot tall, 300 pounds of pure muscle, sex-obsessed hypermasculine hulk on the city. You can't say that the women around him object, other than a very few of the unaltered ones; you notice even some of the unaltered males seem to greatly approve of his new form. Suddenly, you see lights form around one of the more normal-looking women hanging off of your creation - you watch as her breasts momentarily grow several cup sizes, her hair turning bright blonde ... and realize that the spell was cast by your opponent! Somehow, her old mind must still be in there, and still capable (though with obvious difficulty) of casting transfomative spells! You weren't worried about fending off his physical strikes - but if the old mind is still in there somewhere, capable of revenge ... perhaps this is one giant of a man that you should avoid in the near future.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>

</Form>
