<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>Out of the corner of your eye, you see her - another of those giggling bimbos that seem to be plaguing the city lately.  Luckily, they all seem to have been ignoring you so far - even though you find them incredibly sexy, you've heard the stories.  About how they're all carrying some sort of virus - the "Bimbonic Plague", as some wag dubbed it - how exposure to it wears down ones immune system, slowly changing them, forcing them to become just another airheaded bimbo wandering the streets - in search of others to infect.  But you can't take your eyes off her - even as she comes strutting over to you.  "Like, hi stud!  You like what ya see?" she says, giggling, looking down at your crotch, which even now is hardening.  You barely hear her as she keeps flirting with you, telling you about all the fun you two could have together - but it takes a kiss on your cheek, saliva running down towards where you cut yourself shaving this morning, to wake you from your trance.  You run off, screaming, hoping against hope that you are not infected - and like, so far, you totes don't seem to be.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>You see her again - well, you think she's the same giggling bimbo, but it can be, like, so hard to tell.  You think about running away, but decide it might be best not to attract her attention, so you act natural, continuing what you were doing.    It doesn't work - she runs over to you, jiggling, as fast as her high heels can allow her.  You think to start sprinting off, but it's too late - her arms wrap around you, holding you like totally tight.  "Like, where are ya goin', Mister Stud?" she says, in her high-pitched, oh-so-sexy voice.  "Dontcha, like, want to have a little fun?"  You can't help yourself as she brings her ruby-red lips to yours, kissing you deeply, thrusting her tongue in.  You passionately return the kiss for a time ... and then, the dawning realization hits - she's filling your mouth with her saliva.  Her INFECTED saliva.  Screaming, you break the kiss, push her off, and run for it - "Like, what's got into him?" you hear her say, as you round the corner.  Odd - do you, like, normally sway so much when you run?  You, like, grab a lock of your long hair to chew on, as you stop to think about it, your other hand resting on your outthrust hips ...</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>Your previous encounters with the bimbos have left you looking, like, a bit effeminate - enough that, like, while no one can mistake your gender, people are starting to make, like, some assumptions about your sexuality just from glancing at ya.  And it's not like they're totally wrong either - even if you, like, didn't before, you're totally, like, starting to understand what those bimbos see in a nice hard cock.  But dangit - you're still, like, totally a guy - you should be the cocksuckee, not the cocksucker.  Or - you let out a giggle - at least, like, some of the time ...   You can tell that the bimbo - the same one? - that approached while you were, like, totally spaced out is picking up on your thoughts.  "Um, like, hi sexy.  If I, like, said I wanted to suck your dick, what would you do?"  It's, like, totes a terrible pickup line, but desperate to prove your masculinity, you quickly drop your pants, and present your hardening member to her.  It's not like long at all before she's just like going to town, totes lickin at yer balls between deep slurps at the shaft.  Afterwards, you like barely even remember thrusting down her throat, or even cumming ... but ya, like, must have.  Instead - you remember pulling yer dick out, and, like, seeing it smaller?  Nah - just, like, not hard anymore, right?  Still, you couldn't like help but cry, as you sashayed away from her - concerned about, like, the tears totes ruining your mascara ...</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>The repeated bimbo encounters have been, like, totally getting to you.  You've even, like, started dressing like one of them; you've already like, got the cutest little outfit picked out, and your makeup like, totally matches your purse and heels.  At least part of you is rebelling at the change, wanting to prove your masculinity, that you really do, like, totally have a (shrunken) cock beneath your skirt.  So it's not too surprising when one of the giggling bimbos comes by, and asks you "Like, what's wrong cutie?" you respond: "Um, I'm ... like, totes not feeling like a man anymore, miss - can you, like, help me?"  A light goes on in her vacant eyes - she like, bends way over, showing her cute little butt - without panties, no less - to you, and starts babbling something about having lost something big, long, and like totally hard - last seen like, just thrusting in and out of her.  You're, like, totes smart enough ta get the hint, and soon the two of you are just totally goin at it.  But even as you feel her, like, gush out in orgasm, you can feel your dick, uh, like getting all soft and stuff - even smaller, and, like, falling out of her.  She looks like she totes blacked out or somethin, so you slowly sashay away from her, like, feelin your curves expand as ya do.  It seems, like, somethin must be wrong, but it's just like, so hard ta think about what it is, ya know?</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>You've, like, totally run into those bimbos so much by now that ya know you're, like, starting ta think like them.  You're even, like, really startin ta wish that ya looked like them too - they're like, so hawt and sexy and stuff, while you ...  Well, like, you guess, like, you are kinda cute, but you look mostly like a flat-chested, skinny girl with like, none of their awesome curves.  And, like, look - one of them's totes strutting your way right now!  You, like run over to her.  "Like, you!" you say, in your high-pitched voice - "You're the one, that's, like, been changing me!"  You don't, like, see her respond quick enough, so you totally pull down your miniskirt ta show her.  "Look, like - I don't even have a pussy yet ... you gots ta help!"  She responds, in a voice similar to your own "Well, like, if ya need pussy so much, mine's totally available?"  Smiling as she lies down, spreading her legs, you like get down on your hands and knees, and totally start ta lick.  As you do, you can, like, totes feel your body changing - it, like, makes you want to lick even faster, lapping up her awesome juices.  Your hips and ass plump up; your legs, like, get totally longer while the rest of ya shrinks.  Your hair is, like, totally getting in your way as it lengthens.  And, like, best of all!  Your boobies are totally getting huge, just like hers!  You cum as you think about it - and realize it's your own newly formed pussy!  Finally, you like get up, and get a good look at yourself - you look almost totally like the hawt girl in front of you.  So kewl!  Eventually, you like, have to wave goodbye - but you're already thinkin of going out to find some cute guys ... or maybe, like, find that hawt bimbo again ...</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>You bounce over to the bimbo that's been, like, totally making you so hawt. "Like, hi cutie!" she greets you, and you respond "Like, hi yerself?  You're the one that, like, changed me, huh?"  "Yeppers."  "Um, well, I like, love my new body and stuff ... but, um, like, I don't really know how ta use it good, ya know?" She think - "I don't know, ya look, like, totally sexy to me - ya picked out like that cute outfit and everything, and I've even seen ya, like move.  Do you like, need help with how to, like, have fun with the boys?"  You blush deeply, thinking about, like, all the cocks an stuff you've totally done lately ...  "No ... no, like, I'm like, totally awesome at that!"  "Oh, so what - do you, like need a makeover?  A kewl shopping trip?"  You shake your head, like feeling your long hair move behind ya.  "No, like ... I kind of feel like I should be making more of us, ya know?"  She nod, sagely.  "Yeah, I know what ya mean.  Well, the secret is ta, like, get all horny and stuff, and then, like, get them like, exposed to ya.  Here, like this!"  She like leans in, and gives you a sloppy, WET kiss - totally, like, locking you inta your fate.  "Oh, like, I think I totally see!" you says, feeling like, the way to share this lovely body with others.  "Now, like, let's go shopping" She nod happily.  "Yeah, like, there's sure to be, like, totally a lot of cute guys at the mall."  "But, like, probably not as many when we leave" you say - and you both burst out in a fit of giggles.</TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>Out of the corner of your eye, you see her - another of those giggling bimbos that seem to be plaguing the city lately.  Luckily, they all seem to have been ignoring you so far - even though they look incredibly sexy, you've heard the stories.  About how they're all carrying some sort of virus - the "Bimbonic Plague", as some wag dubbed it - how exposure to it wears down ones immune system, slowly changing them, forcing them to become just another airheaded bimbo wandering the streets - in search of others to infect.  And there's one in front of you now.  She's dressed like a whore, and has just ridiculous curves, it's clear there's not a thought in her empty little head.  You shudder, imagining what it must be like to be like her - to lose your intelligence, your personality, to have it replaced with only the desire to look good and to fuck.  Oh no ... she's coming up to you!  And she looks ... angry?  "Hey, like, cutie.  Why do all of you skanks have ta be, like, so mean to me all of the time?"  the bimbo says, pouting, as she coughs slightly in front of you.  Wait, who is she calling a skank?  Wait - WHY AREN'T YOU RUNNING?  You quickly sprint off, worrying you might have been exposed.  Are ... are you wiggling your hips a bit more as you move?</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>You've been feeling ... odd, recently. But it wasn't the bimbo, you're sure of it - you can't be infected. It's just, hot all the time - that's why you've been wearing such skimpy outfits lately. And, it must just be ... hormones, or something ... your breasts look a bit swollen, and you feel horny all the time ... but it must be hormones. And you're not flirting with all those cute guys ... there's, just ... a lot more of them around, ya know?  Aw, like, crap!  While you were standing there, daydreaming, one of those infected bimbos (the same one?) has snuck up on you.  She seems quite angry for some reason ... she's (very weakly) slapping you, over and over, screaming stuff like "bitch!", "slut!" and "like, leave some dick for me, ya ugly skank!"  You consider fighting back, but soon realize that her long, hot pink, manicured nails have scratched your skin ... Screaming, you run away, leaving the ditz happy in her martial prowess... and as you do, you can see your hair, like, totally getting in your face like it never did before, and your boobies are starting ta tingle ...</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>Half of you, like, wanted to just stay home, totes hiding in shame from the plague that's changing ya, ya know?  But, you like, can't stay hidden forever, and a growing part of you totes wants to show off your new super hawt bod.  And ... oh piss in a cup! There she is again - the same bimbo, you're sure of it.  "Hey, Slut!" she begins, working herself up for, like, totally another catfight. "Like, wait?!" you say to her, in a voice whose airheadedness doesn't quite match your thoughts ... like, yet. "We totes don't need ta, like, fight cutie! There are, like, enough hunks for both of us, ya know?". She giggles back at you: "Ah, OK sexy. Why don't we, like, kiss an make up?" She leans, like, way over, and plants a big sloppy kiss on your lips. You kiss back for awhile, totes frenchin her ... but then your mind like, comes back to ya.  Tears stream from your eyes as you scream in a high-pitched voice, that sounds much like hers: "Noes, I'm like, turnin into one of you!" You run off, planning to hide, but you're startin ta feel, like, just sooooo horny - you, like, doubt you'll be able ta keep yourself alone for real long, ya know?</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>You were totally right, ya just couldn't stay away ... the plague, it's like, moving through you so fast, that you just, like, can't help yourself.  You're already, like, out on the streets, dressed in the skimpiest, sluttiest outfit you could like find.  Ya like, just had to go out for a night on tha town, ya know?  So, like, yer down on yer knees, totes blowin some guy right out in the open an stuff, takin his shaft in your mouth, pullin out to lick his big yummy balls, just like, totally lost in tha moment - when she like, comes up and slaps ya again.  "Hey, slut! Like, leave some cock for tha rest of us, ya know?" You act to like totes ignore her, yer, like, smart enough ta know who the important guy here is- "Oh, hey stud - like, my friend's here - you, like, ready for that threesome?" you lie to the beefcake. The bimbo's eyes light up - the two of you, like, both start lickin' him together.  Seeing the stud doesn't like, mind, you start totes makin' out with the bimbo, hopin he'll like, get super hard just watchin, ya know?  Both sets of your jiggling boobies rub against each other, as ya make out for a super long time ... before a, like, annoying part of ya tells you this is totes wrong.  You motion for the bimbo to, like, take over on cock-slurpin duty for ya ... and while she's totes occupied, you like, make a break for it. Whew.  At least you're, like, safe for now, ya know?</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>Somethin' about yer new smokin bod ... everyone's, like, been runnin away from ya lately.  Its totes not fair!  You're like, super hawt, and so horny all the time ... but everyone's, like scared of you an stuff?  What, like, gives? An then, ya see her - someone who you, like, know won't run, and who looks like, almost as sexy as you!  You like totes run up to her, titties jigglin, and give the bimbo a big ol' hug. "Like, hi!" you say, "You aren't gonna, like, run away from me too, are ya? Like, totes everyone has been lately, and I'm super horny, ya know? So, you like, wanna fuck?" She, like, seems ta think about it for a little bit... so, you like, undo your skimpy top, and let yer miniskirt fall to show you're, like totes not wearing any panties ... an she totes can't help herself. Before ya know it, you're both going at it - tongues lickin ruby-red lips, lickin heaving giant breasts, lickin tight bellies, and finally goin inta tight wet pussies. She's, like, totally awesome at this - almost as good as you! After a whole buncha orgasms - math's, like, too hard for ya to keep track of how many - you finally stop. She giggles: "Don't ya, like, wish you could do that foreva and eva? It would be, like, so kewl!" An, like, you totes wanna ... you think you, might, like come see her again real soon, ya know?  </TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>You, like see the bimbo again, an ya, like, feel that it's finally time.  The super annoyin voice in yer head sayin she's like, dangerous fer some reason has, like, finally shut up - so you run up to her, strutting, thrusting your wide hips from side to side. Your boobies feel like they're totes gonna fall out of yer cute, tiny top, as you reach her, and, like, plant a big ol' kiss right on her lips! "Like, hi cutie!" she says, and you respond "Like, hi yerself? You've been, like, changing me, huh?" "Yeppers." "Um, well, I like, love my new body and stuff ... but, um, like, I don't really know how ta use it good, ya know?" She thinks - "I don't know, ya like, have used it plenty good on me, and you're totes sexy! Do you like, need help with how to, like, have fun with the boys?" Psh, as IF: "No ... no, like, I'm like, totally awesome at that!" "Oh, so what - do you, like need a makeover? A kewl shopping trip?" You shake yer head, the long tresses moving behind you. "No, like ... I kind of feel like I should be making more of us, ya know?" She nod, sagely. "Yeah, I know what ya mean. Well, the secret is ta, like, get all horny and stuff, and then, like, get them like, exposed to ya. Here, like this!" She leans in, and gives ya a big, sloppy, WET kiss - completely sealing yer fate, not that ya like, even notice. "Oh, like, I think I totally see!" you says, yer eyes alight with the new transformative knowledge. "Now, like, let's go shopping" She nods happily. "Yeah, like, there's sure to be, like, totally a lot of cute guys at the mall." "But, like, probably not as many when we leave" you say - and you both burst out in a fit of giggles.</TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>You spot, like, just totally the cutest guy ever, and start strutting over to him.  Weird!  Like, when he sees you strutting over in your yummy slutty outfit, you'd think he'd be staring at your big jiggling boobies, or like maybe at your swaying bubble butt - he should, like, totes be getting nice 'n hard just lookin at ya!  Pouting just a bit, you finish your strut.  "Like, hi stud!  What's the matter - don't ya like what ya see?"  An outside observer would call him 'frozen in a state of panic' - but you barely even notice.  You lean over to breathily whisper in his ear "C'mon handsome, you don't like need to be afraid of me?  We can, like, totes have lotsa fun together?" - an then you, like, lean down, to give him a big sloppy kiss on the cheek.  Much to your vacant-eyed surprise, he runs off, screaming all the way.  "Stud?  Like, come back Stud?!" you call after, but it's no use.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>"Mmmmm..." - you lick your ruby-red lips - this city totes needs more beefcake walkin around; it like seems everyone you see is like a total whore, tryin  ta take your guys away!  But, like, just as you're thinkin about findin a nice dick to have totally all to yourself, you see him - a total stud-muffin, just standin around, with like, nothin at all to stop you!  You quickly run over there, jiggling, totes as fast as your high heels can take you, before some other slut like takes him.  Not, like, takin any chances, you wrap your arms around him totally quick - holdin him, like, super-tight.  "Mmmm ... you look, like, super-sexy, Mr. Stud" you giggle - and while he looks, like, all scared and stuff for some reason, you smile as you see him like, totally starin down your cute skimpy top at your giant boobies.  "And I can tell that, ya, totally like what ya see!"  With that, you like bring your lips to his, and start like, totally makin out.  At first he's lookin all totally horny, and like wrestlin with your tongue - but when your salvia ... sallyva ... your spit like goes down his throat, he suddenly pushes you back, and like runs off screaming!  You pout, watching the studmuffin run away, eyes focused on his totally cute ass ... which seems ta be, like, totally movin from side ta side more than you'd, like, expect, ya know?</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>You're, like, just totally walkin along thinkin about, like, how super it would be to be suckin a cock right about now - when you see him.  Have you, like, seen him before?  You've been with, like, so many cute guys, it's hard to tell.  This one, like, seems to recognize you - he's like, just standing there - his hands on his hips, in a, like, totally girly pose; but his eyes are following you, and he's, like, smiling.  An you totally see a growin bulge in his pants!  Still, you're, like a little worried he might not be inta girls, so you like, wiggle on over to him, and ask totally as sexily as you can:  "Hey there cutie.  If I, like, asked if I could suck yer dick, like, what would you say?"  And then - he like totally drops his pants, like right there in front of everyone.  Afterwards, you like barely remember gettin down on your knees, takin that big hard shaft into yer mouth, stoppin the like, frantic suckin sometimes to lick at his yummy balls.  What ya like, mostly remember tho, is seeing him, like, cryin afterward for some reason.  And, like, bein' totally confused and stuff by his dick lookin, like, a whole lot smaller when ya finished blowi' him than when ya started.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>You're just happily giggling to yourself as ya, like, think about what your gonna wear tomorrow - when ya like, see him.  Again?  Yeah, it's like, totally the same stud - but it was like, hard ta tell, since he's like, wearin a buncha makeup, and like, a miniskirt and heels?  Huh.  You saunter over to ... him?  "Uh, hi there cutie?" you say, questioningly.  "He" looks at you, a bit of crazed lust in 'his' eyes.  "Uh - like, Miss?" he stammers, in a high pitched voice that, like, kind of reminds you of ... someone?  You like, totally can't put your finger on it.  "Miss, like ... I'm totally not feelin like a man anymore ... can ya, like, help me?" he asks.  Hmm.  You like, think about it for like, half a second, then bend like, totally way over in front of him, showing your pantyless crotch.  "Oopsie, I like, dropped somethin?" you giggle - "Have ya, like, seen it Mister?  It was like, big and long and hard, and the last I saw it it was like, thrustin in and out 'a me ..."  He, like, figures out what ya mean real fast - and soon he's just totally like poundin away at ya, with his like, disappointingly small dick.  Still, it's like, totally more than enough ta get ya off ... just before ya like, feel him pullin out early?  No, like ... his dick seems ta have, like, shrunk out of ya ... and then he, like, just wanders off, struttinaway on his heels, without like sayin a word to ya.  Well, you, like, got what ya wanted, ya know?</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>You're, like, daydreamin about some cute guys, when, like, a young woman comes like runnin up to ya.  Or you, like, think she's a chick - there's, like, a hint of manliness in her face.  "Like, you?!" she(?) says to you, with a look on her face that, like, she probably thinks is angry, but winds up just totes cute.  "You're, like, the one doin this to me?" she(?) queries.  "Like, look!"  She pulls down her(?) mini-skirt, revealing a totally smooth groin.  "Like, my dick is like totally gone now!  Please, like, help me?"  "Ya know" - you say back to her - "if ya, like, want a pussy so bad, mine's totes like, available!"  Grinning, you lie down on the ground, legs spread, giving her easy access - and you're like, totes not surprised to see her lying down between them, starting to lick.  As she does, you see her whole body, like, start ta shift.  Her curves that were, like, barely enough before ta make ya totes sure that she was a girl start growin:  hips, and butt start like gettin big, and ya see she's got a pair of boobies almost as hawt as yours.  Her legs like, start gettin longer while the rest of her is shrinkin ... her hair is like, totes gonna get in the way of yer lickin if it keeps up its growth.  From what ya can see of her face, it's, like, gettin covered in makeup, and lookin totes familiar, somehow ... but before ya can place it, she, like, hits yer G-spot, and ya cry out and cum.  An after, like, cumming down (*giggle*) ya get a good look between her legs, and see that she's all girl now.  And she, like, doesn't seem to mind ...</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>This time, when you, like, meet your victim, you like, realize what's going on.  That she's, like, "your victim" for, like, one thing - and, like, totes looks just like you, for another.  You like, strut over to her, greeting yer new sister.  "Like, hi cutie!" you say, and she responds "Like, hi yerself?  You're the one that, like, changed me, huh?"  "Yeppers."  "Um, well, I like, love my new body and stuff ... but, um, like, I don't really know how ta use it good, ya know?" You think - "I don't know, ya look, like, totally sexy to me - ya picked out like that cute outfit and everything, and I've even seen ya, like move around in tha super hawt way.  Do you like, need help with how to, like, have fun with the boys?"  She blushes:  "No ... no, like, I'm like, totally awesome at that!"  "Oh, so what - do you, like need a makeover?  A kewl shopping trip?"  She shakes her head, the long tresses moving behind her.  "No, like ... I kind of feel like I should be making more of us, ya know?"  You nod, sagely.  "Yeah, I know what ya mean.  Well, the secret is ta, like, get all horny and stuff, and then, like, get them like, exposed to ya.  Here, like this!"  You lean in, and give the new girl a big, sloppy, WET kiss - completely sealing her fate.  "Oh, like, I think I totally see!" She says, her eyes alight with the new transformative knowledge.  "Now, like, let's go shopping"  You nod happily.  "Yeah, like, there's sure to be, like, totally a lot of cute guys at the mall."  "But, like, probably not as many when we leave" she says - and you both burst out in a fit of giggles.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>You still totes can't believe all the sluts and total whores in this city.  Some of these bitches are, like, no better than animals!  All of them, strutting around, keeping all the yummy cock to themselves.  Even, like, running away from you, when you're in the mood for some super hawt girl-on-girl action.  It's like, they think you're continge - contiguo - uh ... that, like, they'll get sick if you come near them!  Most of them, like, run away tha second they see you coming. (*giggle* ... cumming.)  Some of the winged sluts even fly from you.  Well, like, no more!  You see one of them, totes close to you, but she like hasn't seen ya yet.  You decide to, like, strut over to her, cough unexpectedly, but then ask:  "Hey, like, cutie.  Why do all of you skanks have ta be, like, so mean to me all of the time?"  She looks totes scared for some reason, and like sprints off - though she's, like, wriggling a bit as she does it?  So weird.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>You like, see another skank hanging around the city, her big boobies just totes hanging out of her skimpy clothes.  She's like, totally trying to take one of your guys away from you too!  This just, like, can't stand, ya know?  You run over to her - jiggling in your own, considerably skimpier outfit as you do.  "Like, hands off whore, I saw him first!" you yell.  She looks - you aren't, like, totally sure.  Confused?  Scared? Jealous?  It, like, doesn't matter - you're soon calling her like all kinds of nasty names, and like, slapping her for all you're worth.  (Which ain't much.)  She starts to fight back ... until, like, you scratch her with your bright-pink nails.  Her eyes get, like, super huge, and she totes starts running away.  Was her hair, like, that long before?  You like, didn't think her boobies were so big you could like, see them from behind before ... but you are like, such a ditz sometimes ... maybe you, like, forgot?</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>Another day, another total slut standing there, trying to take all the cock for herself.  This one looks, like, kinda familiar - like maybe you, like, confronteded her before?  But, she's got like, super big boobies, and real long hair, and totes more makeup than you think you saw her with?  "Hey, Slut!" you begin, working yourself up for, like, totally another catfight.  "Like, wait?!" she says to you, in a familiar-sounding voice you can't quite place, "We totes don't need ta, like, fight cutie!  There are, like, enough hunks for both of us, ya know?"  Hmm.  She, like, has an awesome point - she must be, like, super smart or somethin.  You giggle: "Ah, ok sexy.  Why don't we, like, kiss an make up?"  You like, lean way over, and plant a big sloppy kiss on her lips.  She kisses back for awhile, totally frenchin ya ...  but then her eyes get all super huge, and she breaks off.  Tears stream from her eyes: "No, I'm like, turnin' into one of you!"  Wow, like, what a weirdo.  </TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>This time when you see her, she's, like, busy - she's kneelin down, right there in the open, suckin off some sexy guy!  She like, really is a total whore, just like you said, in one of, like, less ditzy moments.  Mmm ... but, like, she looks even sexier before, and her fashion sense has totes improved - why, her skimpy pink outfit and heavy makeup kind of reminds you of ... hmm.  Not, like, wanting to think about it, you totes say: "Hey, slut! Like, leave some cock for tha rest of us, ya know?"  She totes ignores you, and talks to the guy instead - "Oh, hey stud - like, my friend's here - you, like, ready for that threesome?"  Your eyes light up - maybe she's, like, not a TOTAL bitch, if she's gonna share!  You begin by like, tryin to get him just so hard by totally makin out with the slut - you like take off each other's tops, start like pawing at each other's giant titties, like stick your tongues waaay down each other's throats ... it's, like, super hawt!  But then, like, when you turn around to start suckin off the guy ... your mind must've totes wandered off again, cuz the next time ya look around, she's like nowhere to be seen.  Crazy slut.  At least you've, like, got this beefcake all to yourself now.  Huh - is his dick, like, smaller than ya remember?</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>She's totes alone this time, you can't help but giggle a bit happily.  Looks like the guys don't really like TOTAL sluts like her, ya know?  But she's like ... running, big boobies jigglin in her sexy outfit, comin up to give you a big hug!  "Like, hi!" she says, "You aren't gonna, like, run away from me too, are ya?  Like, totes everyone has been lately, and I'm super horny, ya know?  So, you like, wanna fuck?"  Hmm.  It's a hard choice - she is, like, a mega-slut, and you're totes too good for her; but she's just so sexy, and has such good taste in makeup and clothes ... and as she undoes her skimpy top, lets her miniskirt fall to show she's totes not wearing any panties ... you like, just can't help yourself.  Before ya know it, you're both going at it - tongues lickin ruby-red lips, heaving giant breasts, tight bellies, finally exploring tight wet pussies.  She's, like, totally awesome at this - almost as good as you!  After a whole buncha orgasms - math's, like, too hard for ya to keep track of how many - you finally stop.   You say: "Don't ya, like, wish you could do that foreva and eva?  It would be, like, so kewl!"  She does seem ta, like, really think about it ... but doesn't like answer you.  Maybe next time?</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>Again, she runs up to you, strutting, thrusting her wide hips from side to side.  Her boobies look like they're totes gonna fall out of her cute, tiny top, as she reaches you, and, like, plants a big ol' kiss right on your lips!  "Like, hi cutie!" you say, and she responds "Like, hi yerself?  You've been, like, changing me, huh?"  "Yeppers."  "Um, well, I like, love my new body and stuff ... but, um, like, I don't really know how ta use it good, ya know?" You think - "I don't know, ya like, have used it plenty good on me, and you're totes sexy!  Do you like, need help with how to, like, have fun with the boys?"  She blushes:  "No ... no, like, I'm like, totally awesome at that!"  "Oh, so what - do you, like need a makeover?  A kewl shopping trip?"  She shakes her head, the long tresses moving behind her.  "No, like ... I kind of feel like I should be making more of us, ya know?"  You nod, sagely.  "Yeah, I know what ya mean.  Well, the secret is ta, like, get all horny and stuff, and then, like, get them like, exposed to ya.  Here, like this!"  You lean in, and give the new girl a big, sloppy, WET kiss - completely sealing her fate.  "Oh, like, I think I totally see!" She says, her eyes alight with the new transformative knowledge.  "Now, like, let's go shopping" You nod happily.  "Yeah, like, there's sure to be, like, totally a lot of cute guys at the mall."  "But, like, probably not as many when we leave" she says - and you both burst out in a fit of giggles.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>

</Form>
