<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>Funny. That spell didn't seem to do...well, anything, really. Did it? Somehow, it did make you pause, like you were waiting for something...but what?
You brush back a lock of hair back behind your ear, not noticing as it fades slowly back from blonde to its natural color.
</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>This time the spell did something for sure...even if all it was wrinkle your skirt! It's not until you lean down to adjust the tiny little thing that it occurs to you that this wasn't what you were wearing before. And it isn't until you notice that, that you realize how perfectly made up your nails are suddenly, or how dainty your pretty hands.
With a huff, you will it back to normal with ease...but it still feels wrong, somehow.
Like you've overstepped your boundaries. </TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>The feeling of the fishnets suddenly spiderwebbing up your legs is alien to you...but looking down at them, they really do accentuate your uniform, don't they? You wonder for a moment if your Masters and Mistresses will approve, as you run a hand down them, balancing in your shiny black heels.
Then you blink.
Uniform?
Masters!? 
This was starting to get out of hand. 
And yet, you nearly catch yourself opening your mouth to ask for permission before you concentrate, slowly reversing the changes--your perfect black skirt, uniform heels, stockings and blouse reverting to the usual cacophony of your outfit. Should you have waited for someone to tell you if that was the right thing to do?</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>This blast hits your right in the chest, pulling your apron suddenly tiiight over your perfectly inflated bosom, a valley of cleavage forming that strikes you as unprofessional, but you can't help but show off a little bit. Your breasts feel especially accentuated against your slim, small frame; even in your heels, you barely feel tall enough to look most people in the eyes...but, that's alright, no one expects you to, do they?
...
N-no, they should. Because you're not some...you're not a maid! You shut your eyes, but quickly force the changes away.
Well, okay. Not quickly, but you do it.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>Your hair is bouncing in pretty blonde ringlets
(You need to reverse this)
Your uniform is immaculate, down to the last inch, swaying with you as you walk.
(You need to reverse this)
All you need now is orders...right? You stand at attention, fishing into your bust and pulling out your lipstick to freshen up. 
(You NEED to reverse this)
Luckily(?) you only make it halfway before you realize, with a little pout, that you really, really need to fix yourself before you can't muster the will to...even though it is pretty hard now.
Looking around for implied permission, you hesitate, and then give a little curtsey...before you pull yourself together and force yourself back to normal.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>There is a brief, sharp moment, where your mind seems to burn, as the spell pulls tight around you...and then....then everything seems normal again.
Right?
Your skirt twirls around your creamy thighs, leaving just a few inches of flesh before you stockings start.  Your chest heaves in just the way that you know all the eyes on you like to see. 
The perfect little maid, ready to please.
And...well, you are that, aren't you? You know you were fighting it before...but...isn't it just..easier to do what people want? The harm no longer seems apparent.
In fact, without thinking, you cross your arms behind your back, chest sticking out as you stand at attention. Someone has to give you an order soon, right?

"What can this maid do for you?"</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>You have to look closely to see what your spell even did, honestly. There is a momentary confusion in your target's eyes though, like the suddenly became a touch dizzy, perhaps. For a moment, you think you can see a flicker of blonde hair, but it's gone before you're sure.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>The target's look of confusion is prolonged as they don't seem to notice their changes so much as...slip into them. The skirt they are suddenly wearing shifts on their shapely legs, but before they can take full note, they seem to be distracted by their sudden manicure, wiggling their now-perfect fingers...before they take a breath and reverse the changes.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>Your spell hits the victim like a liquid chessboard, spilling intricate patterns of black and white artfully over their clothing. The shift, certainly, must be impossible to miss, and yet, your  'volunteer' almost seems to, striking a slight pose for the onlookers as they run a hand down their soft, pale thigh as it's enmeshed in almost too-eyecatching fishnets. They don't even notice, as their center of balance shifts to accommodate their new, extra-tall heels, or the pretty pink lipstick spreading thin on their lips...
No, it takes at least a half a minute before the changes seem to fully register. And the other half of the minute to negate their changes.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>From the viewer's perspective, the effects seem to be dramatic, as your target dwindles in size--not shrinking per se, but becoming certainly diminutive. Petite, even. Their heels help them to measure up, but it's clearly a losing battle, with the side effect of making them look almost like a pretty porcelain doll up on their lovely platform heels.
Of course, not all dolls have the measure of cleavage that this one does, pressing out tight against the thin layers of their top and apron. The cleavage seems to be distracting your target, and from their erect nipples, well, you can see why it might take them so long to negate it.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>The uniform seems to sweep all around your target at once. It's nearly perfect, in fact, from the pretty, short skirt, to the towering black platform heels, to the perfect, doll-like makeup and vacant-eyed look, you could swear they're done...and in fact, you see that they feel nearly the same. Finally. something seems to click in their head, and they push the form slowly back, changing to normal. Or, previous, at least.
But not before they give a small bobbing curtsey.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>Your target seems at a loss for words as their clothing darkens back to black, apron pulling tight as their skirt shoots up to above their knees. For a long moment, their is silence, as they toy with the hem of their skirt, nearly biting their lip, you can tell, but thinking better of it, as they straighten, taking a deep, uncertain breath, as you watch the last of their motivation start to seep slowly from their eyes. 
Maybe they still have that spark in there somewhere, but for now, they're standing at attention--you've won.

"What can this maid do for you?"</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
