<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>Your hair grows down a few inches, its color flushing to an unnaturally bright yellow from the roots.  You are able to reverse the changes without much difficulty, however.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>Your hair suddenly tumbles just down to your shoulder, long, luscious, and very blonde with a slight cherry fragrance.  You flick it back and reverse the changes.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>Your face feels numb as your hair flushes blonde, growing down past your shoulders, carefully groomed with a ribbon tied in the back.  You smack your lips, tasting bitter lipstick, and your eyelashes seem to darken as mascara forms around them.  You are able to reverse the changes with a bit of difficulty.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>In addition to your hair transforming long and blonde and makeup appearing on your face, your body itself begins to reshape forming sexy, ultra-feminine curves.  DD-cup breasts inflate out of your torso, threatening to pop out of your shirt as your pants creak under your inflating ass.  You are able to focus enough to reverse the changes, but it's growing quite difficult.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>In addition to your hair transforming long and blonde and makeup appearing on your face, your body itself begins to reshape forming sexy, ultra-feminine curves.  DD-cup breasts inflate out of your torso, threatening to pop out of your shirt as your pants creak under your inflating ass.  What's worse are the sudden pangs of lust that begins to make you damp between your legs in your new lady parts, your eyes drifting over your attacker's chest and ass, hormones surging... at the last moment you are able to reverse the changes, but one or two attacks may leave you stuck as a blonde bimbo.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>You can't take it anymore.  Your body shifts into hyper-feminine proportions, DD-cup breasts jiggling with every motion, long blonde hair tickling your neck and shoulders as you eye every human-looking shape, your vagina's fluids starting to seep down your legs.  You are a sexy, busty blonde woman, by all accounts a bimbo.  At least you are still human, though a drop in IQ and all your lustful urges might prove somewhat of a distraction.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>Your target's hair grows down a few inches, its color flushing to an unnaturally bright yellow from the roots.  They are able to reverse the changes without too much difficulty, however.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>Your target's hair suddenly tumbles just down to their shoulder, long, luscious, and very blonde with a slight cherry fragrance.  They flick it back and reverse the changes.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>Your target's face looks confused as their hair flushes blonde, growing down past their shoulders, carefully groomed with a ribbon tied in the back.  They smack their lips, detecting bitter lipstick. Their eyelashes darken as mascara forms around them.  They are able to reverse the changes with a bit of difficulty.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>In addition to your target's hair transforming long and blonde and makeup appearing on their face, your target's body itself begins to reshape forming sexy, ultra-feminine curves.  DD-cup breasts inflate out of their torso, threatening to pop out of their shirt as their pants creak under an inflating ass.  They are able to focus enough to reverse the changes, but evidently it's growing quite difficult.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>In addition to your target's hair transforming long and blonde and makeup appearing on their face, your target's body begins to reshape forming sexy, ultra-feminine curves.  DD-cup breasts inflate out of their torso, threatening to pop out of their shirt as their pants creak under an inflating ass.  Your target is  able to focus enough to reverse the changes, but it appears to be becoming quite difficult.  You notice your target's attention wavering as they eye your chest and crotch, licking their bright red lips hungrily.  They finally snap out of it and reverse the changes, but one or two attacks may leave them stuck...</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>Your target can't resist anymore.  Their body shifts into hyper-feminine proportions, DD-cup breasts jiggling with every motion, long blonde hair tickling their neck and shoulders.  They eye every human-looking shape, a damp spot starting to form around their crotch.  Your target has become a sexy, busty blonde woman, by all accounts a bimbo.  Although your target is still most definitely human, a drop in IQ and their lustful urges might prove somewhat of a distraction.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
