<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>You shiver as a powerful surge of magic enters your body. You can feel your muscles tightening and becoming more pronounced. You smirk proudly at your attacker, wanting to laugh that their spell did nothing but make you stronger. You fail to pay attention to your itching ears, even as the tips gain small points and your nostrils flare slightly. You just feel to strong to care, but reluctantly change yourself back to normal in case this was some kind of trick.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>You groan as your muscles swell again, but this time they focus more around your rump. Your clothing begins to tear as your ass expands, rippling with powerful muscles. A small nub appears, pushing out from your tailbone. Soon that small nub explodes into a long shower of whispy black hairs, swishing over your much larger backside. You turn and glare angrily at your attacker, your ears changing and migrating to the top of your head as they morph and change into perked horse ears, covered in short chocolate brown fur. You snort through your elongated nostrils and turn yourself back, feeling weak and confined in your full human self again, your clothing magically repairing themselves.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>You gasp, a hint of a whinny in your voice this time as your changes return in full force and with a more overwhelming wave. Your ears twitch, changing back into their horse forms. Your face painfull stretches outwards into a broad muzzle, your nostrils flaring and sniffing for a mare in heat. Your toes would slowly fuse together into shiny black hooves, your tail swishing over your vass amass of ass, even as your pucker plumps up and becomes more pronounced. The most concerning thing this time is that your gender has most definately become male. While you were distraced you have sprouted a very large horse cock, twitching between your legs and standing an impressive 22 inches long. You nicker softly, taking ahold of your new tool in your thickening hand and stroking it, neighing out in pleasure before your human mind returns, telling you these beastial feelings are wrong. Yuo sigh and manage to reverse the changes, standing there panting and horny from this assault on your humanity.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>You grunt as your changes strike you one more. Your mind immediately focuses on your large cock as it returns, but when you go to grasp it, your find your fingers fusing together into hooves. As your body continues to bulk up you neigh in annoyance, unable to get the pleasure you deserve. Although physically you do not change much more than last time this spell was cast on you, this time your mind is realing as new thought, instincts and desires pour in and overwhelm your human mind. IN the drowning sea of stallion lusts and pleasures your humanity takes the reigns and changes you back with a loud whinny of a spell. You know this is getting harder and harder to control the raging stallion inside you. And the worst part is that you actually want to finish changing.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>With a loud whinny your changes explode out from your human body. Your head transforming, tossing your flowing black mane and snorting through your large flared nostrils. Your ears pivoting to the smallest of sounds. Your neck thickens as you finally drop to all fours with a clop, the shreds of your clothing littering the ground under your powerful form. Your proud, mottled cock twitches under your belly, eager to hilt itself in a eager mare as dribbles of pre land on the ground under you. Your tail swishes and your flanks heave, your entire powerful body covered in a a dark chocolate coat of fur, that gave an alluring sheen in the sunlight. you rear back on your hind legs and let out a whinny, just as your eye begin to darken into a mindless animal brown.....but at the last possible second your human mind pulls you back and with a very slow and almost painful process you change back to normal, laying naked on the ground and panting heavily. You know if that spell hits you once more your a goner....but would it really be all that bad?</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>With a loud whinny your changes explode out from your human body. Your head transforming, tossing your flowing black mane and snorting through your large flared nostrils. Your ears pivoting to the smallest of sounds. Your neck thickens as you finally drop to all fours with a clop, the shreds of your clothing littering the ground under your powerful form. Your proud, mottled cock twitches under your belly, eager to hilt itself in a eager mare as dribbles of pre land on the ground under you. Your tail swishes and your flanks heave, your entire powerful body covered in a a dark chocolate coat of fur, that gave an alluring sheen in the sunlight. you rear back on your hind legs and let out a whinny, just as your eye begin to darken into a mindless animal brown. Your eyes glaze over and you know you need to make a harem, to get mares to obey and carry your foals. You begin to trot off, not caring that someone might have a bit, bridle, and saddle with your name on it.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>Your target shivers as a powerful surge of your magic enters their body. You see their muscles tighten and become more pronounced. They smirk at you like an idiot thinking all you did was give them strength. If only they knew your true intentions... Their ears gain small points and their nostrils flare slightly. They look like they just feel to strong to care, but reluctantly change back to normal.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>Your target groans as their muscles swell again, but this time they focus more around their rump. Their poor clothing begins to tear as their ass expands, rippling with powerful muscles. A small nub appears, pushing out from their tailbone. Soon that small nub explodes into a long shower of whispy black hairs, swishing over their much larger backside. They turn and glare angrily at you, their ears changing and migrating to the top of their head as they morph and change into perked horse ears, covered in short chocolate brown fur. They snort through their elongated nostrils and turn them-self  back, looking weak and confined in their full human self again, their clothing magically repairing themselves.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>They gasp, a hint of a whinny in their voice this time as their changes return in full force and with a more overwhelming wave. Their ears twitch, changing back into their horse forms. Their face stretches outwards into a broad muzzle, their nostrils flare and sniff. Their toes slowly fuse together into shiny black hooves, their tail swishing over their vast ass, even as their pucker plumps up and becomes more pronounced. The most noticeable change is that they are now sporting a huge horsecock nearly 2 feet long. You didn't notice at first since you were watching the other changes. They nicker softly, taking a hold of their new tool in their thickening hand and stroking it, neighing out in pleasure before their human mind returns. They sigh and manage to reverse the changes, standing there panting and horny from this assault on their humanity.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Your opponent grunt as the changes strike them one more. Their huge equine rod quickly returns. When they go to grasp it, they find their fingers had fused into hooves. As their body continues to bulk up they neigh in annoyance, unable to get the pleasure they crave. Although physically they do not change much more than last time this spell was cast on them, this time you suspect much more mental changes are taking place. In the drowning sea of stallion lusts and pleasures their humanity takes the reigns and changes them back with a loud whinny of a spell.  It looks like it is getting  harder and harder for them to control the raging stallion inside.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>With a loud whinny your target's changes explode out from their  human body. Their head transforming, tossing their flowing black mane and snorting through their large flared nostrils. Their ears pivoting to the smallest of sounds. Their neck thickens as they finally drop to all fours with a clop, the shreds of their clothing littering the ground under their powerful form. Their proud, mottled cock twitches under their belly, eager to hilt itself in a eager mare as dribbles of pre land on the ground under them. Their tail swishes and their flanks heave, their entire powerful body covered in a a dark chocolate coat of fur, that gave an alluring sheen in the sunlight. They rear back on their hind legs and let out a whinny, just as their eye begin to darken into a mindless animal brown.....but at the last possible second their human mind pulls them  back and with a very slow process they change back to normal, laying naked on the ground and panting heavily. You know if that spell hits them once more they're  a goner</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>With a loud whinny your target's changes explode out from their  human body. Their head transforming, tossing their flowing black mane and snorting through their large flared nostrils. Their ears pivoting to the smallest of sounds. Their neck thickens as they finally drop to all fours with a clop, the shreds of their clothing littering the ground under their powerful form. Their proud, mottled cock twitches under their belly, eager to hilt itself in a eager mare as dribbles of pre land on the ground under them. Their tail swishes and their flanks heave, their entire powerful body covered in a a dark chocolate coat of fur, that gave an alluring sheen in the sunlight. They rear back on their hind legs and let out a whinny, just as their eye begin to darken into a mindless animal brown. Their eyes glaze over and you can see you have won. They begin to trot off a complete horse.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
