<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>The spell sinks in and seeps through your body with a warm glow of pleasure.  Your skin tingles, softening and smoothing, taking on a slightly flushed 'peaches-n-cream' tone.  A shudder of pleasure runs through your body as your beautiful new skin is kissed by the air.  You are almost reluctant to reverse the changes, but they are just too distracting to enjoy them properly right now.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>This time, the spell ripples through your body and strikes cords of pleasure in you like harp strings.  Once again, your skin tingles as it softens and grows more sensitive, but the changes don't stop there.  You feel dizzy and lightheaded for a moment, before you look around and realize that you are no longer the same size as before.  In fact, your entire body has been changed, shrinking in some places and growing in others, overall leaving you with a rather stunning figure and very unimposing stature.  You can feel the warmth of arousal stirring in you as you realize that you are almost the perfect size for a lap-dance, before you shake away the devious thoughts and begin unraveling the spell.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>The magic slips through your defenses with frustrating ease, reshaping your body and heightening the pleasure it gives you.  Forced into that soft, shapely form once more, you can feel the changes focusing on your face this time.  Your head spins as your features shift fluidly beneath your perfect skin.  Soft, moist lips and large, captivating eyes stand out among your angelic looks with just enough vulgarity to provide a deliciously deviant contrast.  Silken strands of hair trail down into your field of view, obscuring your vision till you lift one slim-fingered hand to brush them aside.  You can feel your hair tickling the tops of your buns behind you, and a thrill runs through you at the thought of what all that soft, smooth, sensitive skin would feel like under eager, talented hands.  For just a moment, you lose yourself in the fantasy.  You feel those large, warm hands peel off your clothing, bit by bit, caressing every inch of your naked body as if worshiping it.  You can feel their breath hot against your slit...and you snap out of it with a start, so shaken by the vividness that for a moment, you almost forget to dispel the transformation!</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>Fiendishly elusive power wraps around your aura, bleeding through in a lurid smear of red and gold hues.  Before the glow of magic has even begun to fade, you find yourself back in the shapely, distractingly sensitive, and decidedly feminine form from before.  You hear a sweet, seductive voice cry out in ecstasy, and are shocked to realize it is your own!  Like the cry of a siren, you feel it stir your lusts with a shiver.  What must it sound like to everyone else?!  Biting your plump lower lip in concentration, you are just about to undo the spell when you wonder, briefly, what you must look like right now.  That thought sends your mind spinning away again, lost in fantasy.  You are straddling someone's lap, facing them with your arms above your head, your top wrapped tightly around your wrists.  As the music pulses and throbs, muffled by the thickly carpeted walls, you grind your hips against their lap.  You can't help it...aren't even sure if you want to.  Your breasts feel sooo good as they grow, swelling bigger and bigger with every bill your customer slips into your thong...  Wait a minute, GROWING?!  You come to with a jiggling start, the plentiful orbs on your chest still swelling before your very eyes.  You cup them in your hands, another cry of pleasure dripping from your lips when you discover how very nice that feels.  Fighting as hard as you can, you manage to stop their growth.  Reversing it, however, is a slower and more tedious process...to say nothing of the other changes!</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>Suddenly, you are standing naked in a warm room.  Soft music begins to play, and with a mind of their own, your hips begin to sway to the beat.  Your hands flow along the curves of your body, soon joined by the hands of a man behind you.  Another pair of hands joins the first...and then another, all caressing your body as you slowly undo buttons, snaps, and zippers.  Item by item, you strip as you dance, giving three sets of hands (not counting your own) more and more of yourself to explore.  And with each piece you take off, you feel yourself growing hotter and hotter.  The more naked you are, the more turned on you become, pressing back with your hips and feeling a very appreciative bulge pressed between the cushions of your smack-inviting backside...then you awake, feeling the surge of warmth and wetness between your legs.  The labia of your womanhood plump just a bit more, your love-pearl throbbing at the haunting memories of a rendezvous that never took place.  It makes it almost as hard to concentrate as you painstakingly lift the spell as the thought of just how easily you fell prey to it once again.  You almost didn't even notice, that time...</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>You gasp in sudden arousal as you find yourself upon a stage.  The heat of the lights makes your pale, creamy skin almost glow from within.  The music thumps as dozens of hands wave money at you, begging for your attention or another glimpse of your beautiful, naked body.  Your pussy throbs as you reach down to take a tip from a particularly brawny young man, tucking it into the strap of your thong even as your breasts tingle with pleasure.  Your thick, puffy nipples crinkle and harden, pushing out as if leading the charge as your titties swell another cup size larger.  You feel them grow bigger and heavier, the weight of them tugging gently at your shoulders and constantly swaying or jiggling with the slightest provocation.  You wait until the growth stops, your globes spilling over the cups of your DD-cup bra, before you peel it off and toss it to the young man howling in appreciation.  When you come to, you realize it was nothing more than another vision brought on by the spell as it re-orders your mind...but you don't care.  You just regret that it wasn't real, and lick your lips at the thought of what might happen if your next foe waves money instead of just their fingers!!</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>The spell sinks in and seeps through your victim's body with every sign of being quite pleasurable.  Their skin grows softer and smoother, taking on a slightly flushed 'peaches-n-cream' tone.  A shudder runs through them as their beautiful skin is kissed by the air.  They seem almost reluctant to reverse the changes, at first...</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>This time, the spell ripples through your victim's body and strikes cords of pleasure in them like plucking harp strings.  Once again, their skin grows softer and smoother, but the changes don't stop there.  Your victim dwindles, their entire body shrinking in some places and growing in others, leaving them with an overall stunning figure and very unimposing stature.  They are just about the perfect size for a lap-dance...which they seem to realize as they glance in your direction and hastily reverse the changes with a gasp and a shiver.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>Your magic slips through your foe's defenses easily, forcing them back into that soft, shapely form once again.  They groan softly as the changes focus on their head and face this time.  Soft, moist lips and large, captivating eyes stand out among thier angelic looks with just enough vulgarity to provide a deliciously deviant contrast.  Their hair grows longer and softer, spilling down their back and over their shoulders in a silken tumble, obscuring their vision until they lift one slim-fingered hand to brush it aside.  They shiver in excitement when their hair tickles the top of their ass, staring off into space for a moment with a dreamy look in their eyes.  After a few moments they snap out of it with a soft, erotic moan in their seductive new voice, so shaken they nearly forget to reverse the changes!</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Fiendishly elusive power wraps around the aura of your victim, bleeding through in a lurid smear of red and gold hues.  Before the glow of magic has even begun to fade, your foe finds themselves back in the shapely, distractingly sensitive, and decidedly feminine form from before.  You hear a sweet, seductive voice cry out in ecstasy, and smile at the shock on your victim's face when they realize it came from them!  Like the cry of a siren, you feel it stir your lusts with a shiver.  They bite their plump bottom lip, seemingly about to unravel all your hard work, when they pause suddenly.  Soft, sensual coos emanate from the lips of your prey as they seem lost in a daydream for a few moments, so with a shrug, you push just a little more power into the spell.  Your target comes to with a jiggling start, the small mounds on their chest still swelling before their very eyes!  They cup them in their small, delicate hands, another cry of pleasure dripping from their lips when they discover just how pleasurable you've made those titties of theirs.  Fighting the spell as hard as they can, the growth of their breasts comes to a jiggling halt just this side of huge.  Reversing the effects, however, seems a slower and more tedious process.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Your enemy doesn't even seem to notice your spell strike home this time, closing their eyes and swaying to music only they can hear as their body is shaped and molded to your desires once more.  You can feel the power building up inside them, making it a little bit easier to change them with every cast.  Your victim's hands draw your eyes as they absently rub their groin...then moan and cup themselves between the legs.  With the sweetest little gasp you've ever heard, your victim stops enjoying the sensations of pleasure and arousal your spell has gifted them with long enough to realize that she's been struck again!  Hmm...maybe you overdid it on the 'add G-spot' component of the spell...ah, well.  Her plump, eager pussy must still be throbbing for attention, if the difficulty concentrating she seems to be having is any indication.  One or two more casts, and she'll be too busy trying to keep her hands off herself that she won't have a prayer of breaking the curse.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>The final spell slams into your target, reshaping their body with a sizzling *snap!* and sending them crashing to their knees with a erotic moan of pleasure.  But the soft, curvy, and decidedly female form forced on your foe by the spell is only a side-effect of the process.  The most devious part of the spell, by far, is that the whole time it has been burning new pathways in their mind.  When the music plays, they have no choice, no desire, but to show off their sexy body in the most seductive ways they can.  She is an exhibitionist, now, growing more aroused the more naked she is, and the more eyes are on her.  She blinks her smoldering eyes once, twice...and bites her lip with a demure smile.  Her nipples harden when your eyes alight on her cleavage, and you feel the curse bind itself tightly around her.  If you had some cash to offer as a tip, who knows what you might be able to talk her into...</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
