<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>As the spell connects with your chest you don't feel much besides a tingling in your nipples as they become hard. You wash away their magic with yours before anything else happens.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>Another blast of their spell hits you and this time you know exactly what it did. A jiggly pair of C cups rests on your chest, but for some reason they feel... more important than the rest of you. You dispel their odd spell with a flick of your wrist.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>The breasts your opponent is trying to burden you with are bigger this time, probably a DD cup if you had to guess. You find it difficult to focus on anything other than them as they bounce and sway... You shake your head and snap yourself out of it, undoing the spell before you notice that your hands and feet had begun to fade away.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>As the spell crashes into you, a feeling of utter belonging washes over you. The E cups hanging beautifully from your chest are the best part of you, and you couldn't bear to have them go. Until you notice that your arms had disappeared from the elbow up. Your missing limbs shake your attention away from your breasts and you focus your magic to dispel them again.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>The now-familiar breasts bounce forth from your chest again, filling you with feelings of warmth and contentment. You almost don't care as your arms fade away into the breeze, your legs beginning to do the same. As long as your beautiful breasts are safe you don't need anything else. They're all that's important. You come out of your boob-loving stupor just before your neck had finished evaporating, pushing you to action. You wash away the magic, if your estimations of your willpower are correct, for what you fear might be the last time.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>The whole world blossoms forth from your chest into two perfect bouncing globes. At least they're your world. You can't imagine finding meaning anywhere else in this universe besides the warm comfort of your bosoms. In the back of your consciousness you feel the rest of your body fade away, but you aren't concerned, you didn't need those parts anyway. You feel yourself fall, then bounce on the ground a few times, waiting to be picked up, to be held, to be groped. All of your attention focuses on your hardening nipples as you imagine a new owner molding you onto their chest, willing to experience the same comfort you feel.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>As your spell connects, the only thing you manage to give them is a confused expression and some hard nipples. They wash away your spell with a gesture, still not sure what kind of spell you're trying to cast on them.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>Your spell blasts into their chest again. And what a chest! A new pair of cute C cups now bounce about freely in the open air. A quick smile appears on their face before they give you a scowl and reverse the change. You smile back, knowing they'll be happier about it once you're finished with them.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>Their new breasts look even more spectacular now, blooming out into soft D cups on their chest. They caress their assets with a look of bliss on their face, groping them with great fervor. When they snap out of it, they wave their hands to remove the spell, not noticing that their fingers were just starting to fade away.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Another wave of comfort crosses their face as they caress their precious endowments, probably at least E cups now. They don't stop pressing their hands into their soft new flesh until they realize that their arms have completely vanished up to the elbow, at which point they quickly cast a counter spell. You know that soon they won't want to stop.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Their beautiful breasts bounce forth once again, their face a mask of pleasure and contentment. They grope away at their bountiful bosom, not seeming to care when their arms face away into their torso. They just start to sway on the spot, jiggling their breasts back and forth in the air. Their state of euphoria is only interrupted when their legs are completely gone, and their neck had just started to vanish. Their limbs return and their breasts recede with their burst of spell power, but you know by the look on their face that they couldn't stand to leave that happiness too many more times.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>You got them! Your target is immediately lost in waves of ecstasy, but the pleasure showing on their face soon becomes irrelevant as their head, as well as the rest of their body is blown away in the wind, vanishing completely except for the two perfectly large breasts culminating into two perfectly soft globes falling to the ground. They bounce to the floor, then roll around a bit, finding their new center, hard nipples poking up into the air, almost as if they're asking to be picked up. You know that they can still feel everything, and they'll make a beautiful pair for someone less gifted in the chest department, or maybe an extra pair for someone more ambitious. Either way their new lives are going to be full of pleasure.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
