<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>You aren't quite sure what to make of this spell.  Sure, the feminization is standard, though while you look like quite the attractive redhead, you aren't overtly sexualized like so many other victim.  No, what surprises you is the height loss - generally the hallmark of being turned into a wearable object.  But you do not feel stiff at all ... no, you feel ... energetic, alive, ready to fly ... er, run around everywhere, sharing your energy with the world!  Still ... it is unnatural, and you are slightly relieved as the effects fade.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>Again, you become the tiny redhead - clocking in around two feet, this time.  Your clothes have vanished entirely, but you are so full of energy that you do not notice.  Instead, you run hyper-actively around the area, constantly jumping into the air, as if you were expecting to take flight ... and given the large bumps developing under your skin, just below your shoulders, you may well have wings after another casting.  Your barely have time to take in the soft, cyan glow emanating from your skin, before the effects of the spell wear off.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>You are her again, the tiny redhead - though this time, you have wings!  They are not yet strong enough to fully support your foot-tall frame ... but that doesn't stop you from trying, as you happily run to and fro, examining every object in sight.  You fall on your face quite a few times after leaping in the air, but you do manage to get in some significant hang-time.  Soon, you'll be happily flitting all across the landscape, seeing the wonders of the city - "Hey! Listen! A bimbo!" - you imagine yourself saying.  You wonder who you could be talking to in the vision, as the spell effects slowly fade, the cyan glow around you vanishing as you regain your former height and form.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>Again you become her, the tiny woman ... the ... the fairy, you finally realize.  You are 6 inches high with a wingspan greater than your own body; your perfect, nude form hidden from those not examining you closely by a bright cyan glow surrounding you - you realize that, from a distance, you likely resemble nothing more than a sphere of light attached to your wings.  You are starting to get the hang of flying ... you can't quite stay permanently airborne yet, but you're able to go for long stretches at a time.  You think you could manage a mile or more in one go - but oddly, you don't feel like moving far from the one casting on you.  You feel they need ... guidance.  Instruction.  To be told all about the world around them.  You want to stay with them forever and ever and ever and ... suddenly, the spell breaks, and you realize that you were having those thoughts about your attacker.  Frightening.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>Again, you return to your fairy state, sensing the changes are nearly complete.  Smaller now - 3 inches high - your glow brighter, visible from a good quarter mile off.  Your wings are more powerful, and you are practiced enough to hover with them indefinitely.  You flit ecstatically about your owner, pointing out the people and geography all around the two of you.  "Hey!  A stick! A cowgirl!  A demoness!  HEY! LISTEN!  A slightly different stick!"  It feels so good to be helpful, so good to fly around in circles, being so useful to your master.  Suddenly, the magic fades - you fall to the ground, resuming your former shape.  And yet, you still feel bound to your attacker ... perhaps if you ask nicely, you will be able to return to fairy-kind?</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>Though you feel no different, no less hyperactive and excitable than before, you sense that this time the spell is complete - you are bound forevermore to your new master as a fairy familiar.  You fly all around your master's head, telling them how grateful you are, pledging to assist them in any way possible.  You are going to be ever so useful as a scout, pointing out the dangers of the city to your master - though you are shocked to find you are much more valued as a source of spell energy.  And you are even more shocked when they reach for a bottle to store you in after the 5000th enemy magus you warn them of, muttering about "finally getting some peace and quiet"...</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>You start the process of binding your victim to you as a familiar ... a fairy.  The initial changes do not greatly separate them from the crowd - she (for your victim has become an attractive, but not overtly sexualized female) stands out only for her long red hair, and her unusually short stature - perhaps 4 feet tall.  She seems ... full of energy, shifting back and forth from foot to foot, happily chatting with passersby.  Soon enough, the spell fades ... but you vow to continue the transformation.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>You continue the process of binding your soon-to-be fairy to you as a familiar.  She again loses half her height, standing around 2 feet tall - and you can see her entire lithe body, as - although she does not realize it - her clothes have vanished.  She is even more hyperactive - running around the immediate surroundings, often jumping into the air, as if she were trying to take flight.  Her skin ... it's even glowing, a bright cyan.  She appears to be well on her way ... but soon, the magic fades, and your opponent stands before you again.  </TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>The changes continue in your victim.  By now, her final state must be becoming apparent to her - she is only a foot tall, the cyan glow has intensified, making it difficult to see her naked flesh from a distance.  Most notably, she has grown large wings, the span of which dwarfs the main part of her body.  She is still having difficulty using them - while running around pointing at various objects, she occasionally leaps into the air - and despite some significant hangtime, keeps falling flat on her face.  She is undeterred however, as the next intensely interesting sight beckons, and leaps off to see it again ... this goes on for several minutes, before the spell energy fades, and your opponent is restored.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Her changes continue.  Again, the halving of her height - only 6 inches tall now.  The cyan glow has again strengthened, so that, without inspecting her closely, she looks like nothing so much as a sphere of light attached to her wings.  Wings that she seems to be getting the hang of - she has to land on occasion, but she is happily flying about the area.  And ... you notice that she never moves far from you, the familiar binding starting to take effect in earnest.  "Hey, Magus! Listen!  A bimbo!" she cries to you, pointing at one of your opponents ... moments before she lands on the ground, flickers, and resumes the shape of your victim.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Her physical changes are complete - the glow is bright enough to be seen from a quarter-mile away; but closely examining the winged sphere shows a 3-inch tall, hyperactive nude redhead.  Her bond with you is strengthening, as her flight - she no longer needs to land - is simply taking her in circles around you.  You hear her address you, pointing out the scenery around you: "Hey!  A stick! A cowgirl!  A demoness!  HEY! LISTEN!  A slightly different stick!".  You think to yourself ... is having her augment your own spells really going to be worth this kind of monologue?  You have only one or two more castings to reconsider ... and given the way your restored opponent is looking at you, it may already be too late to escape their permanent attentions...</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>It is done - the fairy is now bonded to you, for good or for ill.  She seems extremely grateful - she continually circles your head, calling you 'master', giving you all sorts of (what she must consider to be) "helpful advice".  Having her flit about you IS greatly enhancing your spellcasting ... but after the 5000th time she points out a potential opponent to you, you start seriously considering locating a bottle to store her in, so you can finally get some peace and quiet...</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
