<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>The spell hits, and you immediately regress to an 18-year-old version of your current self, your thoughts reshaping into that of a petulant teenager, with appropriate inner monologue:  "My parents are like, such total fascists! And this high school - it's soooo lame.  I can't wait to finally get free, to live on my own in the big city!  Man, I hope Saint Circe's got my application ... it looks like such a rockin' party school, and the guys and girls on campus are so totally hot!"  But then your body - and soon your mind - return to their former state; you blush a bit at your temporary immaturity, and wonder a bit at the memories that aren't quite your own ...
</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>Again your age regresses to perhaps 20; though this time, your body shifts completely, becoming a young schoolgirl.  Nibbling on a lock of your long red hair, you take a look in the mirror ... "Yes, I think I'll open one more button on my blouse before I go 'talk' with Professor Wayne about my grades".  Quickly, you unbutton it, press your large breasts together just so, and go off to find him.  "Oh, Doctor Wayne, is there ANYTHING I can do for a better grade?" you practice saying coyly, already imagining kneeling down before him, really earning your A.  Wait ... you're not a schoolgirl ... are you?
</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>You find yourself in a twenty-five year old body, naked except for a G-string and some body glitter.  The job market's been tough around here; there are only so many openings for a woman with a Master's in Sexual Education; you're still looking for something better, but stripping down at the Treasure Chest is helping make ends meet for now.  As you practice gyrating back and forth, getting ready for tonight's set, it suddenly hits you - it wouldn't be all that hard to get certified as a teacher, go back to the old alma mater and teach a new generation of young girls the things you have learned.  Even as you strut out onto the stage, you resolve to start taking classes the next day; but for now, you think as you approach the audience of lust-filled men and women, the show must go on ... you approach the pole, and begin to dance...
</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>You find yourself a few years later, dressed in a smart black pantsuit, addressing your first class of young students.  "Welcome class, my name is Miss..." - and then you're interrupted by a burst of giggling from the classroom, from a young girl who could have been you ten years ago.  You address her: "Yes, Miss Wallace, do you find something funny about taking Sex Ed 101?"  "We all, like, already know how to screw ma'am.  This class is going to be a total waste of time."  "Oh is it?" you reply, "You may know the basic theory, but what about advanced technique?  And there is always room for more practice.  In fact" - sizing the young girl up, winking at her, you add in an especially sultry tone - "I want you to see me after class."  As Miss Wallace squirms, you think you handled that pretty well - you can't let them walk all over you, though you ARE here to teach...</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>Another few years have passed, and you see yourself teaching an advanced level course; you address the room.  "Good evening class - many of you may already know me" - a familiar redhead waves at you from the front row, but you crack the whip you are carrying to demand silence. "But for the duration of this course, Bondage through the Ages, you may address me as Doctor Kitty von Spanken-Tusche."  Laughter echoes nearby. "Oh, do you find something amusing Miss Wallace?  Tell me" - you say, pointing to an object nearby - "do you know what this is?"  "Why, it's a bar-spreader Mis ... Doctor Kitty von Tushie."  Another whipcrack.  "DOCTOR KITTY VON SPANKEN-TUSCHE, Miss Wallace - I think I'm going to have to demand you see me after class, for your punishment."  The young girl sighs happily, as you continue the lecture.  "Now, the Marquis de Sade lived in France in the late nineteenth century ..."</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>The spell completes, and you are done reminiscing about the past.  "Shit!" you exclaim, "I'm late for my lecture!"  You run off towards Saint Circe's as fast as your high heels can carry you; "at least Miss Wallace can handle things for a few minutes" you think, praying that your TA didn't skip class to spend time with one of your freshman students again.  Though, considering the near orgies your 'office hours' have been degenerating into lately, you aren't sure you're in any real position to reprimand her.  "Punish, though" you think, licking your lips - "that I can do."  Really, she's lucky though, you think - if only every young woman could have had a teacher like yourself...</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>Deciding that Saint Circe's really could use a new sex ed teacher, you pick a target and release the first of many spells on them, aiming to have them gain the appropriate experience through living the proper life.  At the first touch of your spell, your victim regresses to ... well, you hope age 18, given how you continue to stare at them.  As you hear them muttering about their fascist parents, and how they hope their application at Saint Circe's was accepted, you see your plan is working...</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>You continue your victim's journey through their new life, the spell causing them to take on the form of a schoolgirl near the age of 20.  You see her nibbling a lock of her long red hair, acting like she's posing in a mirror.  She's muttering to herself:  "Yes, I think I'll open one more button on my blouse before I go 'talk' with Professor Wayne about my grades".  You see her unbutton it, pressing her breasts together just so, before she strikes a particularly coy pose:  "Oh, Doctor Wayne, is there ANYTHING I can do for a better grade?" you hear her practice.  Excellent.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>A few years older again, your victim appears to have graduated, and fallen on hard times; she looks like nothing so much as a stripper, standing there in only a G-string and body glitter, apparently getting ready for her set as she gyrates back and forth.  You here her muttering again, about all the lustful men in the audience she's not allowed to touch; about how the job market sucks, and she's only doing this to make ends meet.  A quick subliminal suggestion from you changes the course of her life; she realizes it wouldn't be that hard to get a teaching certificate, to go back to her alma mater, and teach a new generation of young women a thing or two.  Apparently AFTER tonight's show though - you settle in to watch her bumping, grinding, even twirling around an invisible stripper pole...</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>You continue progressing the woman through her new life; today appears to be her first day on the job.  She stands there, a few years older, in a smart black pantsuit, seemingly imagining herself speaking to a classroom full of new students.  "Welcome class, my name is Miss..." she says, then seems to think she's been interrupted.  "Yes, Miss Wallace, do you find something funny about taking Sex Ed 101?" she says, apparently to an uppity student.  "Oh, a waste of time since you 'already know how to screw' is it? You may know the basic theory, but what about advanced technique?  And there is always room for more practice.  In fact" - at this she winks, and continues in an especially sultry tone - "I want you to see me after class."  Oh my.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Another cast at the woman, and she seems far more confident, as if she has been teaching for several years.  She begins with what seems to be another day one lecture:  "Good evening class - many of you may already know me" - for some reason she cracks the whip she carries, annoyed, "but for the duration of this course, Bondage through the Ages, you may address me as Doctor Kitty von Spanken-Tusche."  She glares in front of her, eyes focusing on someone who is not really there.  "Oh, do you find something amusing Miss Wallace?  Tell me" - she says, pointing at empty air - "do you know what this is?"  "The name is DOCTOR KITTY VON SPANKEN-TUSCHE, Miss Wallace - even though you recognized the spreader bar, I think I'm still going to have to demand you see me after class, for your punishment."  Her eyes gleam wickedly as she continues with a prepared lecture: "Now, the Marquis de Sade lived in France in the late nineteenth century ..."</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>Her body does not change as you complete the spell, but you sense that the magic is complete, locking her into her new life, her new memories.  Suddenly, she looks at her watch:  "Shit!  I've been daydreaming too long, I'm late for my lecture!" she exclaims, and starts to run off in the direction of Saint Circe's, as fast as her high heels can carry her.  You hear her muttering as you go about hoping her TA can handle things, that "Miss Wallace better not have taken off with one of my freshmen again" and laugh, wondering if she's really going to find the same disobedient students she's been imagining once she arrives at her workplace.  Perhaps she will; magic has caused stranger things to happen.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
