<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<Description>A thin, beautiful elvish woman, with long raven dark hair; something about her face just screams 'priestess' (or another, similar word).  However, she is rather clearly a bard - her be-sequined outfit suggests she may be performing at any moment, and from what little you have heard so far, her voice is truly captivating.  She doesn't appear to be much of a fighter; though you've known bards -even spoony ones- to be quite effective on many battlefields.  You can tell that she has quite the repertoire of songs - and once she's done taking care of business, she may just decide to use them on you ...</Description>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>A rival mage attacks you, though their incantations seem less like a spell, and more like ... a song.  Not an old ballad, but not any of this modern pop trash either ... it almost sounds like old time rock 'n roll ... And then if affects you.  Your hands are shaking, your knees are weak; you can barely stand on your own two feet. Your  tongue gets tied when you try to speak: "What - what have you done to me?"  before your vision of the real world fades; you see yourself standing in a crowded concert hall, before the lights, performing for thousands of screaming fans.  Looking down at your tight, female Elvish body, you grin; momentarily happy for your new life, the riches, the fame, the raw sex ... just as you're wondering who to thank for such luck, the vision wavers, and you stand before your opponent again back in the real world.  All shook up.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>Your tormenter again attacks you - and suddenly, even as your body takes on the shape of the Elvish songstress from your vision, you find yourself irrationally terrified of being inanimated, amazed to find yourself pleading with your attacker.  In song.  "Oh you can make me a dog / you can make me a cat / you can make me a bimbo / I'm totes fine with that / you can make me a drow / or turn me to goo / but uh uh wizard don't make me those shoes / yeah don't you ... make me those blue suede shoes / anything that can move but don't make me those blue suede shoes."  Your attacker looks ... stunned ... to say the least.  But it appears to have worked, they leave without turning you into shoes ... or restoring your old body.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>You decide to take a walk through the city, transforming all of those around you.  You find one horny young man trying - and failing - to catch a bunny girl; "Stop - you ain't no friend of mine!" she screams at him.  Pointing at the brute, you announce "You ... you ain't nothin but a hound dog" - and sure enough, your words come to pass; a new Bitch in Heat is born.  But absolute power corrupts absolutely - and you feel quite in the mood for some corruption right now.  Spotting an angel strolling around, you grab her tightly.  Addressing her:  "Oh, you may look like an angel; walk like an angel; talk like an angel - but I know you're really a devil in disguise ... oh yes you are."  And sure enough, the angel's formerly azure eyes glow a bright red, as she begins to play with herself openly on the street ...  this power, it's really helping you take care of business in a flash.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>Suddenly, you find yourself caught in a trap, and you can't walk out.  The mage who initially changed you confronts you, power glowing in their eyes, holding your lithe Elvish form motionless with their magic, ready to strip away your new found transformative might.  "Please!"  you plead - "Don't be cruel!  Did I make you rage, from someone I might have changed?  Please - let's forget the past; the future looks bright ahead!"  Your words do not melt your attacker's wooden heart.  "No", they respond, "we can't go on together when I can't believe a word you say."  And sure enough, you feel most of your magic power being stripped away from you; you know that without access to real magic that - despite your retained musical talent - you're going to be feeling lonesome tonight.  So lonely you could die.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>With nothing else to do, you've decided to make a living performing around the town, having found a receptive audience in the local castle.  After completing your number about wanting to be her good luck charm, you continue with a new song for the lady of the house.  "Just wanna be / your teddy bear / put a chain around my neck / and lead me anywhere / let me be / with you every night / snuggling close to you / letting you cleanse just right / oh let me be / your teddy bear ..."  Taking a quick bow, you look at her face ... her surprising pale, fanged face, as the vampiress answers.  "Yes, vell, Childe, I can grant your vish ..." and you feel your body reshaping into a cute, cuddly inanimate form ... it takes you quite some time to leave the building.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>Feeling weakened, worn out, even looking significantly flabby, your attacker confronts you directly again; is this the end?  The final curtain?  They ask you what you think of your new body, and how you've been using it around the city.  "Regrets?" they ask.  "I've had a few" you answer, "but then again, too few to mention."  "You did what you had to do?"  "Yes, and saw it through without exemption."  You're feeling stronger now, thinner, more alive , back to your old Elvish self.  "There were times, when I had doubt - I chewed it up, and spit it out ..."  Your rival looks disturbed at imagery, or perhaps simply your renewed vitality. "I've faced it all, I stood tall, and did it ..."  Cutting you off: "Your way?"  You nod.  "TCB, baby.  Uh-huh."  And then you are off - though you may pay that nice mage another visit in the near future ...</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>Remembering the concert, you resolve to create a fine Elvish Bard, and begin casting the words of your spell at a likely looking victim; the words sound almost like they could be a song - not an old ballad, or modern pop trash, but good old rock 'n roll.  Your spell is rather definitely affecting your target;  their hands are shaking, their knees are weak.  They can't even seem to stand on their own two feet.  Their tongue gets tied when they try to speak to you: "What - what have you done to me?" when their eyes go blank; your victim has left the building.  Extending your presence, you can even view their hallucination in your mind's eye: you see them standing on a brightly lit stage, thousands of screaming fans - mostly young women - in attendance, chanting the name of the young, Elivsh woman performing before them - your rival.  And then, the vision snaps, and your victim stands again before you.  All shook up.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>You again attack your victim, finding your spell has already given them the form of that Elvish songstress in real live.  You are about to call it a day, consider it a job well done, when she begins to ... sing?  You listen, rapt, and rather amused, as they plead for their life:  "Oh you can make me a dog / you can make me a cat / you can make me a bimbo / I'm totes fine with that / you can make me a drow / or turn me to goo / but uh uh wizard don't make me those shoes / yeah don't you ... make me those blue suede shoes / anything that can move but don't make me those blue suede shoes."   You ... weren't planning on it; happy to see your spell a success, you move on from the scene, leaving her to roam the city.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>You spot your victim in the streets, going on a transformative rampage.  You find one  horny young man trying - and failing - to catch a bunny girl; "Stop -  you ain't no friend of mine!" the bunny screams at the brute.  But then, pointing at the brute, your Elvish victim pronounces sentence:  "You ... you ain't nothin but a hound dog" - and  sure enough, your words come to pass; a new Bitch in Heat is born.  But  absolute power is corrupting her absolutely - and she seems to feel quite in the mood for  some corruption right now.  Spotting an angel strolling around, she grabs the divine being tightly.  Addressing her:  "Oh, you may look like an angel; walk  like an angel; talk like an angel - but I know you're really a devil in  disguise ... oh yes you are."  And sure enough, the angel's formerly azure eyes glow a bright red, as the corrupted celestial begins to play with herself in the street ... you're really going to have to do something to reign in the bard's power.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Knowing you need to stop your creation's carnage, you set a clever snare for them.  Soon enough, they are caught in your trap; they can't walk out.  Your eyes glow with power as you prepare to strip away the magic you inadvertently blessed their Elvish form with.  "Please!"  she pleads - "Don't be cruel!  Did I make you rage, from someone I might have  changed?  Please - let's forget the past; the future looks bright  ahead!"  Her words do not melt your wooden heart.  "No",  you respond, "we can't go on together when I can't believe a word you say."  And sure enough, you can almost feel the magic power being stripped away from her; you know that without access to real magic that - despite her retained musical talent - she's going to be feeling lonesome tonight.  So lonely she could die.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Checking up on your former rival, you find that she has taken to performing around the city; you sneak into the local castle to observe a performance.  After unwisely singing about wanting to be the lady's good luck charm, she launches into her main number:   "Just wanna be /  your teddy bear / put a chain around my neck / and lead me anywhere /  let me be / with you every night / snuggling close to you / letting you  cleanse just right / oh let me be / your teddy bear ..."  Taking a quick bow,  she finally gets a closer look at the lady's face ... her surprising pale, fanged face ... as the vampiress answers.  "Yes, vell, Childe, I can grant your vish ..." and her body suddenly reshapes into a cute, cuddly animate form.  Slipping out before you are seen - did the Vampire Queen just wink at you? - you stake out the castle exit for some time - eventually seeing your charge leave the building.  </TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>Feeling  weakened, worn out, even looking significantly flabby, you spot your victim.  Will this be the end?  The final curtain?  You ask her what she thinks of her new body, and how she's been using it lately.  "Regrets?" you  ask her.  "I've had a few" she answers,  "but then again, too few to mention."  "You did what you had to do?"   "Yes, and saw it through without exemption."  She's looking stronger  now, thinner, more alive , back to her old Elvish self.  "There were  times, when I had doubt - I chewed it up, and spit it out ..."  Your feel a bit disturbed at the imagery, as well as her renewed vitality "I've faced it all, I stood tall, and did it ..."  Cutting her off: "Your  way?"  She nods.  "TCB, baby.  Uh-huh."  And then she is off.  But she lives; you may see her again, someday very soon ...</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
