<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>Before you can react, your attacker bathes you with magical fire.  Something is wrong though.  While it looks like a deadly conflagration, it washes over you leaving you unharmed and confused.  Shouldn't that have hurt?  Perhaps they're just not very good at fire spells?</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>Your attacker gestures, and you are hit full on by another wave of magical fire.  Once again though, it washes over you without any obvious effect.  It actually feels almost refreshing.  Your skin feels a little stiff, and you idly scratch at it, as you easily brush aside any lingering magic.  Whatever they're doing, it doesn't seem to be working.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>Another blast of magical fire.  This time, you felt something, but it wasn't at all what you expected.  The fire still doesn't hurt.  And in fact, you feel BETTER after it has washed over you.  Excited.  Full of magic.  Also, you notice that you're a little bit shorter than you were before, and your skin is definitely getting stiffer.  As you scratch at it, you notice that your fingernails are a bit longer than normal as well.  Clearly they're up to something.  Not wanting to find out what it is, you quickly reverse the changes and force your form back to normal.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>Something is wrong.  As your attacker bathes you once again in magical fire, you find your view lowering as you shrink.  Everything feels all wrong.  Your legs don't work quite right any more, and you find yourself hunching forward.  If this keeps up, you suspect you'll be on all fours soon.  A quick glance at your hands supports this.  They already look more like claws than anything else.  Your skin has started to take on a greenish tinge, and is breaking out into patches of scales.  In spite of all this, you feel more magic coursing through you than you've ever felt in your life.  Part of you doesn't want it to stop, and wants to cling to the feeling, but you grit your lengthening teeth and force your body back into its old shape.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>Your attacker makes an arcane gesture, and once again you're covered with that strange magical fire that doesn't seem to hurt you.  Suddenly everything about your body goes wrong all at once.  A shift in your hips forces you onto all fours, but the changes in your hands and arms make this a comfortable position.  There is a wriggling feeling near the back of your seat, and a tail, as thick as your torso, bursts out at the base of your spine.  Your neck lengthens, your skin hardens into green scales, and you can see your nose trying to reshape itself into a snout.  A small wisp of smoke escapes from one deformed nostril.  And through it all, the magic!  You realize now why the fire isn't hurting you.  It's powering you!  Somehow you're absorbing it, and feeding it into the roaring magical furnace that you can feel inside your gut.  You've never felt this much magic before, and it is intoxicating.  You almost want to just give in, but a small part of your mind is able to resist, just enough to break the spell.  As you stagger back to your feet, you eye your opponent warily.  They almost had you that time.  If they do that much more, you're not sure you'll be able to turn yourself back.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>Your attacker gestures, and suddenly you're covered with fire.  And you realize, with a sinking feeling, this time, you've been caught.  Instantly, your body reshapes, and you are forced back onto all fours.  Your neck extends, your tail grows out, and after a wriggling sensation from your spine, two wings burst out of your back.  Looking over yourself (which is easy now, with your serpentine neck) you confirm with a sinking feeling that it's over.  You're completely a dragon now.  Covered in emerald scales, and with smoke wafting out of your nostrils, you look like something straight out of a fantasy movie.  Except, you realize with a start, that you're also only about two feet long.  Apparently your attacker is more interested in you as a pet then as a mount.  You try, one last time, to reverse the changes, but this time, the magic won't come.  You can still feel the magic coursing inside of you, whirling in your gut, and powering the flames you feel within you, but you can't seem to get at it, or make it come out as anything other than fire.  Apparently you can no longer CAST magic, and will have to content yourself with merely BEING magical from now on.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>Before they can react, bathe your target in magical flames.  They look puzzled - Clearly they were expecting to be burned by the fire, rather than simply absorbing it.  You grin to yourself.  If they keep that up, they'll be in for quite a surprise.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>You gesture, and another wave of magical fire hits your target before they can dodge.  Once again though, you can see the confusion register on their face as they emerge unburned.  They scratch idly at their hand as their skin thickens in preparation of becoming scales, but don't seem to realize what's happening yet.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>You engulf your target with another blast of magical fire.  This time though, they realize something is up.  You can tell they can feel the changes, as the fire is absorbed by their very essence.  You see them examining their fingernails, as they begin to lengthen into claws, and it's hard to ignore the fact that they've lost a few inches in height.  They clearly haven't figured out your end goal, but they're wise enough to dispel your changes and return themselves to normal.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>You bathe your target in magical fire, and this time it's obvious that they are beginning to panic.  Their limbs have started to shift, and they're getting close to being forced into a quadrupedal stance.  Their hands reshape into claws, and the entirety of their skin has started to change into a brilliant shade of green.  Yes, you think to yourself, they will make an exceptionally fine looking dragon.  They force themselves back into their old shape through magic and willpower, but can feel their resistance weakening.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>You make an arcane gesture, and once again, your target is covered with magical fire.  All at once, the changes snap back into being.  Their limbs reshape, and they're a quadruped now.  A tail erupts from their backside, their neck lengthens to match, while their skin segments and hardens into beautiful green scales.  A wisp of smoke escapes while their nose tries to reshape itself into a proper snout, and you find yourself thinking what a fine dragon they're going to make.  The wings haven't formed yet, but you're sure that's going to happen soon.  You actually start to think you might have them, when they abruptly force themselves back and stagger to their feet.  From their wary expression though, it's clear that this contest is nearly over.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>Another gesture, and your target is covered in fire.  And then suddenly they're not there any more.  In their place is a beautiful dragon, with the most exquisite scales, no more than two feet in length.  You hold your breath, waiting to see if they can manage to counter your spell this time, but from the resigned way they inspect their new form, you know you have them.  You can see the enormous amounts of magic - both their own inherent power as a wizard, and the not-inconsiderable quantities of magic you pumped into them - beginning to stabilize.  Yes, having them bound in this form will be quite useful.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
