<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>Their spell washes over you and you feel more confident, more powerful, like you are ready to face any danger heads on. You blink, debating whether to even dismiss this spell, but realize you can't truly trust it and with a wave of your hand shatter the magic affecting you.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>Once again you feel more powerful, and ready to rush headfirst against danger, but strangely you find yourself smaller. Your hair hangs at your shoulder, and your hips are womanly and wide. A voice whispers in your mind, calling you to the All Father's duty. You manage to reverse the changes and dismiss the spell.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>You feel your hips expanding, and waist narrowing. Fat melts away, and your muscles slim down, leaving you svelte and toned. Breasts blossom on your chest, as your hair touches the small of your back. Despite this you feel stronger, and more powerful, ready to face whatever comes against you. Your eyes scan the battlefield, looking for those who have proven themselves valiant, for a moment before you snap out of it returning to your former self.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>Again your body shifts, quicker this time, your cock shrinking down to leave you with a doll-like smoothness at your crotch. Your hair, now raven black, hangs down to your ass, as your breasts firm and fill out. You find yourself swaying somewhat while you walk, sensual and powerful, beautiful and deadly. You look around for the bravest of warriors to grant them their reward, but shake yourself from it, this isn't you, it's not.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>You feel your breasts swell into form d-cup beauties, your stomach becoming firmed and flat. Your mass shifts, muscle becoming leaner, hips becoming more sensual, and waist thinner, your hair beginning to tie itself into a long braid behind your back. Your cock retracts into your body, forming a nice, fresh pussy, and you find yourself sighing at the pleasure of the merest touch or breeze across it. You stand in this battle city, looking about for the most valiant of warriors, to face in battle or to grant their reward... or maybe both. You shake your head, remembering this must be baleful magic, and manage to slip free, but you find yourself saddened as you feel that power and self-certainty leaving you once more.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>The transformation happens quicker this time, the magic already built up. You find yourself still tall, over six feet, but svelte with tight, beautiful muscles, and firm d-cup breasts. Your black hair, short in front, falls to your tight ass in a braid, and your cock is completely gone now, and you feel it won't be coming back this time. Something about that makes you smile, this new hole ought to be more fun. And this power you feel, strength beyond what your appearance would indicate. Yes, you could grow to like this you think, as you begin to scan the battlefield looking to do your duty and reward the most valiant and greatest warriors. Oh how you will reward them, you smile, with a glance at the mage who just transformed you, maybe they're a good place to start?</TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>Their spell washes over you and you feel more confident, more powerful, like you are ready to face any danger heads on. You blink, debating whether to even dismiss this spell, but realize you can't truly trust it and with a wave of your hand shatter the magic affecting you.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>Once again you feel more powerful, and ready to rush headfirst against danger, and you find your muscles growing more toned across your body. A voice whispers in your mind, calling you to the All Father's duty. That whisper is just enough to make you reverse the changes and dismiss the spell, you aren't sure you like where this is going.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>You feel your muscles growing once again, your hair darkening to black as it touches the small of your back. An urge to battle swells up within you, a desire to seek out the most valiant, the bravest warriors in the land. You feel your tight, d-cup breasts, bounce on your chest as you look around this city of battles, ready to rush headfirst into combat or to reward the valiant who have fought before. You begin to utter the counter curse, but hesitate; this power does feel nice. No. It's not you, you remind yourself, finishing the reversal spell.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>Your legs are longer now, toned and firm, your torso extended as well. You feel strong, strong enough to stroll through the field at axe time and fare against the strongest and not only put forth a good showing but be victorious. You feel your raven black hair brushing against your ass, your powerful but lithe muscles across your arms, and you stride forward your d-cup breasts bouncing against your chest. The exhilaration of life fills you as you look for the valiant, to perform your duty, but a small voice reminds you this is not yourself. The voice grows louder until, reluctantly, you utter the counter spell.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>The transformation is faster this time. You feel an almost sexual flush as the feeling of power, of might, returns. Your black hair weaves itself into a long braid, brushing against your ass, as you grow tall and strong once more. Your icy blue eyes gaze across this city of battles, looking to do your duty to the All Father and test the mettle of and reward the most valiant warriors within. A pesky voice reminds you that this is not you, but you silence it reveling in your new power. It repeats itself louder and louder, even as you find yourself eying the mage doing this to you. You try and silence the voice, but it refuses and inevitably you find yourself reluctantly breaking their spell, but perhaps next time you can remain as you were, powerful and beautiful.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>The change is almost instant this time, you body, your mind, your soul all three rejoicing in welcome at it. You are stronger, fitter, just more powerful than before, and you like it. You've never felt this confident, or self-assured before, and honestly it's a wonderful feeling. You step forward, ready and able to take on the world. Your movements are powerful and confident, beautiful long legs stretching beneath you, and proud d-cup breasts hanging above your smooth, plank-like stomach. The tip of your long, black, braided hair hangs at your ass brushing against it as you walk. Your eye flick across the battlefield, a desire to do your duty and grant the valiant their eternal reward surging through you. Well there is the mage who just fought you...</TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>You watch as a look of confidence and power comes over your target's face, his cheekbones rising slightly and his face growing more feminine. Before the change can proceed much further he manages to reverse your spell.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>The look of confidence and power grows on his face again, and you can watch as it grows pale and feminine. His hair turns raven black and brushes the tops of his shoulders. For a moment he seems as if he has a higher calling, his eyes distant, but then he snaps back and counter your magic.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>Your victim's waist cinches in as his hips grow wider and more feminine. Pert b-cup breasts blossom from his chest as his hair darkens to raven black and grows out to brush the middle of their back. Confidence, perhaps overconfidence, shows on their face as you watch, but their will proves too strong as they manage to reverse the effects.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>Your victim's breasts grow to firm, c-cups, as his hips become full and womanly, his waist narrow and shapely. He stands over six-feet tall, and whatever bulge he once had is gone as his groin becomes doll-like in its smoothness. Even so he has more confidence than ever before as he takes a few experimental steps on his long, toned, feminine legs, before countering the spell.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>The victim's breasts grow to quite full, and luscious, d-cups, as his hips and waist return to their full womanly beauty. You can see him shudder with apparent ecstasy as his cock vanishes and a new pussy opens up under her plank-like stomach and luscious breasts. She has long, lean, beautiful, runner's legs, and has the appearance of a tall, statuesque beauty with her raven black hair, tied back in a long braid which dips just bellow their slender waist. </TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>The changes are almost instant this time, as if your target's own will is helping your magic along. He, or now she, stands over 6' tall, beautiful and hard, with high cheekbones, piercing blue eyes, her raven hair in stark contrast to her pale, pale skin. Her d-cup breasts are firm, and ripe, as she begins to walk across the battlefield, sensual and sexual despite being a warrior's walk. She makes no attempt to reverse the magic, but seems practically ecstatic over the change.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>You watch as a look of confidence and power comes over your target's face, their cheekbones rising slightly and their face growing more classically beautiful. Before the change can proceed much further they manage to reverse your spell.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>The look of confidence and power grows on her face again, and you can watch as it grows pale, her eyes turning an icy blue. Her hair turns raven black and brushes the tops of his shoulders. For a moment she seems as if she has a higher calling, her eyes distant, but then she snaps back and counter your magic.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>Your victim's body becomes more muscled and tone, her legs and torso stretching somewhat as she grows to over six-feet in height. She looks about, her breasts firm and perky, her legs like finely carved marble, smooth, muscled and flawless. Her black hair stops just at her waist, and her majestic face is as harsh as it is beautiful. A look of overconfident pride washes across her face before finally she dismisses your magic.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>The transformation is faster this time, and your target takes a few experimental strides with her longer legs, her ass length hail slapping her butt, looking about with a face filled with the fervor of the axe time. The ecstatic madness on her face lasts longer this time, as she almost seems to prowl her full d-cup breasts jiggling slightly, but she manages to return to herself to dismiss the spell.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>Again she takes on the form of a beautiful, raven-haired valkyrie. Her face has high, regal cheekbones, her icy blue eyes above a petite nose and lips which stand out red against her pale flesh. The thrill of battle is upon her, the eye that scans for the worthy. Her firm, but slim, muscles look like they were sculpted by the finest Classical sculptors, and she moves like a goddess of war, beautiful and deadly. She reverses the spell, but not without hesitation and a look of sadness. Perhaps the next spell will be enough.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>The changes are instant this time, as if aided instead of opposed, by your victim's will. She walks, hips swaying, stomach smooth, breasts jiggling slightly, more than six feet tall, beautiful, and as deadly as a cobra's bite. Her face shows unequaled confidence, as she looks about with a predatory gaze; seeking battles or worthy suitors, you can't be sure which.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>

</Form>
