<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>With a shout, you're opponent distracts you enough to hit you with a spell. A tingle travels through your body and you can't help but feel people are staring. Is the spell lingering on your rear? Or is that where the stares you feel just centered at? You shake the feeling off along with a counter spell that you hope reverses anything that changed...</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>A flashy pose has you staring at your rival, but not the spell that just hits you. The wave of magic passes through you, seeming to concentrate on your backside. Which is fine with you, it's one of your better attributes after all. Just thinking that has you giving it a little wiggle, hoping to direct some stares and make you the center of attention. Maybe you should wear some brighter colors, or maybe a small skirt? Wait, why are you thinking that? You quickly reverse the spell trying to shake the arousal away with it...</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>For some reason you're wondering how light pom poms are when a rival hits you with a spell. As the magic passes through you, a thrill passes down your spine. At least you think it goes down your spine. It feels a little shorter than normal. You'd ponder it more except you can't help but feel the stares of everyone at your backside. Before you can help it, you're imagining yourself as the center of attention. A large crowd, bright lights, and cheering. Lots of cheering. A vivid daydream of being on the sidelines of some St. Circe Community College event and you as one of the cheerleader. No, wait, not one of the cheerleaders. But you're there. The confusion snaps you out of the fantasy and realize you should cast a counter spell. It dispels the feeling of stares you had, but you're still confused about that dream you were having...</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>Pondering what you could rhyme with St. Circe Pigs, you miss as you're hit by a spell. You feel your body shifting, but you can't focus on that as a fantasy overtakes you. Cheerleaders on the sidelines kicking and flipping to stir up the crowd. You can feel as the crowd watches, trying to get a tantalizing glimpse of you as you cover the rear of one of the cheerleaders. The short skirt they wear only occasionally blocking their looks. You revel in their naked lust as you stop your owner from being naked themselves. You suddenly realize what you're daydreaming about and snap out of it to find yourself laying on the ground as a pair of spankies. You panic, worried your stuck when you take a moment to cast a reversal spell and return to your former shape. You let out a sigh of relief, though glad you made at least a sexy looking pair of undergarments....</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>As you try to recall just what spankies are to begin with, you forget to dodge out of the way of another spell. You feel yourself hugging the curves of a cheerleader as they give a more...personal show for someone. You hug their crotch and stretch over their rear as they give it a wiggle towards their lucky audience. You can feel them staring as the short skirt flips occasionally, revealing the words "Spank Me" across their backside, and know that soon someone will give that a try. The shock of that thought breaks the daydream you were in. You find yourself stuck in the form of the spankies you imagined just now, but somehow you're able to reverse the spell and your back to a more humanoid shape. However you can't help be disappointed you didn't get further in that fantasy...</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>Tired of just imagining what it would be like as part of the cheerleader's uniform, you don't bother trying to dodge out of the way of the spell. You feel your body condense, forming into a pair of cheerleading spankies. You feel the words "Spank Me" form on your backside and can barely contain your excitement that the invitation may soon be taken up. Taken up like you hope someone will take you up and slide you on...</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>You give a shout, distracting your opponent and hit them with the spell. It doesn't seem to change them much, but they glance around furtively, as if they think everyone is staring at them. They suddenly shake their head though, as if to dispel a fog, and the spell itself with a counter spell.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>Using a cheerleading pose, you catch your rival off guard and able to strike them with your magic. You're not sure if the spell is changing them, but they seem to move their hands to their rear. With a smile, they give their backside a little wiggle, as if asking you to stare at it. You can't help but think they're perfect cheerleader material, or at least they may soon be, but then they seem to reverse the spell. Looks like you need to try harder...</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>Noticing your enemy is distracted, you slip another spell past their defenses. You watch as they seem to shrink, but they don't notice as they seem lost in some daydream. Their eyes closed, their body seems to take on the texture of fabric as it turns a pinkish hue. Your opponent seems to be going through some type of cheer routine in their fantasy, acting it out a bit in front of you when they suddenly snap out of it and cast a counter spell, reversing the changes. They seem a bit confused though, as if their thoughts still linger on what they were imagining earlier...</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>For some reason, you're thinking about doing a jig when you notice your rival isn't paying attention to you. So you hit them with a spell! They don't seem to notice as well as their bodies contorts and shrinks. Obviously they're lost in some sort of fantasy, a rather enjoyable one by their smile and sounds they're making. Least as long as they have a face. It isn't long before they turn into a pair of cheerleader spankies. Colored pink, you notice there seems to be words written on the back, but before you can check what it says, your opponent somehow reverses the spell and returns to their previous form. Oddly they seem disappointed...</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Seeing your opponent on the ropes, you hit them square in the chest with a spell. They shrink and contort into a sexy looking pair of pink spankies, they look on their face as it morphs into fabric seeming to indicate they enjoy the process. Or at least whatever they're imagining as it happens. You step closer to them and see the words "Spank Me" written on the rear. You're about to pick them up when they suddenly change back into your opponent. It takes them awhile, and even when done, they seem dazed and out of it, as if their mind is elsewhere...</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>As you throw the spell at your target, they seem to almost lean into it as their body reforms into a sexy pair of cheerleader spankies. You pick them up and look at the words "Spank Me" emblazoned across the back. You can only imagine how many people would take the advice of these provocative cheerleading clothing. In fact, you're pretty sure you felt the spankies quiver in excitement at the idea of that happening. Well you'd hate to disappoint...</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
