<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>As your opponents spell slips past your defenses the small fireball bursts against you. The flames covering you in fine silver hair that starts to spring up across your body. As you feel your bones reshaping slightly the hair thickens into true fur. Before the spell can do much more though you quickly mutter a counter spell. You look at your opponent, judging what you think the spell was trying to do.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>Again your opponent slips their spell around your magics and this time it bursts square against your chest. Silver fur immediately rising from the point of impact and spreading across you in a wave. Your breasts perk up to a firm D-cup as your body shifts into a more canine form and sprouting a fine fox tail. Your eyes widen as you realize that this isn't just a physical change as parts of the spell are aimed at your mind, but you are able to control your panic and counter the spell before its able to take hold of you.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>Knowing your opponent means business you throw everything you have into blocking their spell. Unfortunately everything you have isn't enough apparently, as the little fireball strikes you again. Your ears raise up as the rest of your body returns to the shape of the silver furred vixen. Fear flows through you at how clearly outmatched you are, but you think the physical changes are done. As you begin concentrating on blocking the mental portion of the spell pleasure causes you to let out a gasp of surprise as 3 more pairs of breasts form under your top pair, dwindling from Ds to As. The distraction is all that was needed for the pressure to return to your mind and you aren't able to block it out. Letting out a quick yell of defiance you manage to blurt out the counter spell in Japanese. You stand there looking at your opponent, while trembling in fear... you don't know how to speak Japanese.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>Still reeling from the last attack you are a bit late in gathering your defenses and the ball of fire strikes you again. Your body shifting entirely into that of a female vixen within seconds of the spell hitting you, and as you begin preparing to defend yourself against the mental assault a sharp pain above your butt breaks your concentration. You look back in time to notice a second tail splitting off from the first, and the pain causes you to shift back and forth hoping it will go away. You begin to worry about the shrine in the park. What were you thinking!?  You haven't taken care of it in ages and need to return to your duties. As you turn to leave your old mind resurfaces and quickly casts the counter spell.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>Giving up entirely on defending yourself you throw yourself away from the spell, rolling across the ground. As you come up out of the roll your 8 swinging breasts confirm you weren't successful. Memories of the years you spent taking care of the shrine in the park flow into you as your third tail finally comes in. You can't believe you went and abandoned your duty like that! As you turn to hurry back to the shrine a new desire flows through you. Smiling mischievously you turn towards your opponent, hips jutting out as you begin to saunter over to them. May as well have a bit of fun before returning to work, but at that moment your old mind rebels against the idea and quickly blurts out the counter spell. You collapse to the ground panting unsure of how much more you can take.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>Well it was fun sneaking away from your duties for a while, but you decide it is time to return to the shrine as you walk into the last fireball of your opponent. Your lovely 8 pairs of breasts returning, 3 tails with white tips, and deliciously soft silver fur coating your body except for some white underbelly and dark on your limbs. You make a lovely kitsune and you know it. Locking eyes with your opponent you begin walking towards them again. The movements of your body making them feel all sorts of different emotions. As you get to them you don't stop however, letting out a giggle at their surprise as you summon your Shrine Maidens outfit to cover you. It is always so fun to tease the people in this city, but maybe you'll come back for them later.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>As your opponents spell slips past your defenses the small fireball bursts against you. The flames covering you in fine silver hair that starts to spring up across your body. You shrink a little bit as the bones in your legs reshape slightly and the hair thickens into true fur. Before the spell can do much more though you quickly mutter a counter spell. You look at your opponent, judging what you think the spell was trying to do.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>Again your opponent slips their spell around your magics and this time it bursts square against your chest. Silver fur immediately rising from the point of impact and spreading across you in a wave as you lose several inches of height. A heat in your chest makes you blush as your nipples widen and your pecs inflate to a firm D-cup as your body shifts into a more canine form and sprouting a fine fox tail. Your eyes widen as you realize that this isn't just a physical change as parts of the spell are aimed at your mind, but you are able to control your panic and counter the spell before its able to take hold of you.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>You spot a potential victim and summon a little ball of fire into your hand. As your opponent tries to block it you gracefully maneuver it through their defense and strike them. Fine silver hairs start spreading across their body. As it covers their legs the bones reshape slightly into a more digitigrade stance as the hair thickens into true fur. Before it can go any further your opponent speaks their counter spell and stares at you questioningly.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>You sling another fireball at your target dancing it around the magics they try to bring up to defend themselves. Your aim is true and it splashes right across their chest. Their chest swells to D-cups as silver fur sprouts up immediately and rolls across them in a wave returning the canine proportions to their body as you see a fox tail sprout above their firm butt. Judging by the look on their face they've noticed that your spell isn't purely physical, but they reverse the changes before too much longer.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>This time your opponent coalesces an impressive defense, but it doesn't matter as your spell streaks in and strikes them again. Their ears raising up and growing painted as they return fully to the body of the silver vixen from before. They close their eyes and begin working on countering the spell when suddenly their eyes snap open and they start panting as an additional 3 pairs of breasts grow in. Ranging from the top pair of Ds to As at the bottom she makes an impressive sight to behold. You smirk knowing your opponent is losing ground against your spell as they speak the counter spell in Japanese, and from the fear in their eyes when they look at you they know it too.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Before they can recover you launch another fireball at them, your spell catching them off guard and easily striking them. Their body fully returning to that lovely silver vixen form you had them in just moments before. A little yelp of pain escapes them as you see a second tail split from the first finally giving a hint as to their final form. As they examine their new tail you see their blue eyes cloud over with worry before they start hurrying off towards the park. Before too long though they slow down and return themselves to their previous form.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Your opponent seems to have given up on defending themselves and tries to run away. As you lob the fireball at them they dive across the ground trying to avoid it, but it is no use, your aim was good. They roll once before coming back to their feet, all 8 breasts swaying from the sudden movement. They don't even seem to try to defend themselves this time as they start walking towards the park as their 3rd tail grows in. They stop though, a smile spreading across their muzzle as they turn and look at you fixing you with a piercing stare from their glowing blue eyes. They slowly roll their hips as they seductively begin to saunter over to you. You smile thinking the spell has worked but just before they get to you they speak that pesky little counter spell in Japanese and return to normal. You are certain they can't take much more of this after that display though, and you want to play with your new toy.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>You throw one last fireball expecting your opponent to run again. They surprise you by doing nothing and you almost miss, but at the last second they walk willingly into your spell. The fire flashes over their entire body leaving a perfect 3 tailed Kitsune where they used to be. The mischievous smile already playing across their lips as they walk towards you. The way their body moves so beautifully and seductively causing you to imagine doing things to them without a second thought. As they reach you though they just give you a little wink and giggle as they walk right past you, much to your dismay. The new Kitsune ignores you as she conjures up a Shrine Maiden uniform around themselves and walk to the park. Just great you think, you've created a tease.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>You spot a potential victim and summon a little ball of fire into your hand. As your opponent tries to block it you gracefully maneuver it through their defense and strike them. Fine silver hairs start spreading across their body. As it covers their legs the bones reshape slightly into a more digitigrade stance causing them to lose a few inches of height as the hair thickens into true fur. Before it can go any further your opponent speaks their counter spell and stares at you questioningly.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>You sling another fireball at your target dancing it around the magics he tries to bring up to defend himself. Your aim is true and it splashes right across his chest. His pecs immediately swells to a perky D-cup as he loses several inches of height. Silver fur sprouts up across his new chest and rolls across their body in a wave returning the canine proportions to them as you see a fox tail sprout above their firm butt. Judging by the look on their face they've noticed that your spell isn't purely physical, but they reverse the changes before too much longer.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>

</Form>
