<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<Description>You're a pink dog collar.  While no longer able to really move, you enjoy the feeling of hanging around the neck of your master and the sensation of moving, as your master goes to a new destination. Sometimes you need to keep excitement down though, as you could choke your owner a bit...</Description>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>Your attacker's spell connects, though did it really? You don't feel a lot of change in your body, but for some reason you do feel soflty compelled to wrap yourself around something. Quickly shaking of the thought, you use a counter spell just to be sure.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>Your attacker's spell connects, you feel your skin become rougher and begin wondering how it would feel to be worn by something... You snap out of your thoughts and immediatly use a counter spell, making your skin change back to normal.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>Your attacker's spell connects. You watch as your skin begins coloring pinker than it already is and begin feeling like you're positioning yourself in the wrong way. Your attacker also catches your eyes more than previously, what would it be like to get worn... You shake your head and form a counter spell, undoing all the changes.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>Your attacker's spell connects. You feel yourself shrink a few feet. You also feel all your skin having changed into something compressed and smooth, the pink color coming out even more than before. Your arms begin merging into the sides of your body, as your legs begin forming one appandage. Your opponents neck begins dominating your thoughts, but you eventually get those sorted out and form a new counter spell, changing you back to normal.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>Your attacker's spell connects. You feel yourself shrink to the size of an arm. Your skin fully changed and your body almost one single band, you feel your head split open and get a metallic feeling. Several pits begin to form a bit above the end of your one leg. You feel other metal pins grow outward your spine and two metal rings grow out of your sides, a bit below your changing head and neck. You begin wondering if you should bend over in between the thoughts of being worn by something. After some heavy mental disputes, you finally succeed in forming a counter spell, changing you back to normal.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>Your attacker's spell connects. You shrink to the length of half an arm, as your skin turns into a bright pink leather and you say goodbye to your arms and legs. Your entire body changes into a pink belt, or rather collar, as a few holes penetrated your form. Three metal 'rings' formed, with the first having a metal pin which you force through a hole in your body, as you bend over and form a circle. The changes settling in, you can't wait to find out what will be wearing you first.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>Your attacker's spell connects, though did it really? You don't feel a lot of change in your body, but for some reason you do feel soflty compelled to wrap yourself around something. Quickly shaking of the thought, you use a counter spell just to be sure.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>Your attacker's spell connects, you feel your skin become rougher and begin wondering how it would feel to be worn by something......
You snap out of your thoughts and immediatly use a counter spell, making your skin change back to normal.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>Your attacker's spell connects. You watch as your skin begins coloring pinker than it already is and begin feeling like you're positioning yourself in the wrong way. Your attacker also catches your eyes more than previously, what would it be like to get worn... You shake your head and form a counter spell, undoing all the changes.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>Your attacker's spell connects. You feel yourself shrink a few feet. You also feel all your skin having changed into something compressed and smooth, the pink color coming out even more than before. Your arms begin merging into the sides of your body, as your legs begin forming one appandage. Your opponents neck begins dominating your thoughts, but you eventually get those sorted out and form a new counter spell, changing you back to normal.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>Your attacker's spell connects. You feel yourself shrink to the size of an arm. Your skin fully changed and your body almost one single band, you feel your head split open and get a metallic feeling. Several pits begin to form a bit above the end of your one leg, as you see your manhood shrink away into your body. You feel other metal pins grow outward your spine and two metal rings grow out of your sides, a bit below your changing head and neck. You begin wondering if you should bend over, in-between the thoughts of being worn by something. After some heavy mental disputes, you finally succeed in forming a counter spell, changing you back to normal.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>Your attacker's spell connects. You shrink to the length of half an arm, as your skin turns into a bright pink leather and you say goodbye to your arms and legs. Your entire body changes into a pink belt, or rather collar, as a few holes penetrated your form, erasing the smoothness left behind by your gone manhood. Three metal 'rings' formed, with the first having a metal pin which you force through a hole in your body, as you bend over and form a circle. The changes settling in, you can't wait to find out what will be wearing you first.</TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>Your attacker's spell connects, though did it really? You don't feel a lot of change in your body, but for some reason you do feel soflty compelled to wrap yourself around something. Quickly shaking of the thought, you use a counter spell just to be sure.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>Your attacker's spell connects, you feel your soft skin become rougher and begin wondering how it would feel to be worn by something......
You snap out of your thoughts and immediatly use a counter spell, making your skin change back to normal.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>Your attacker's spell connects. You watch as your soft skin begins coloring pinker than it already is and begin feeling like you're positioning yourself in the wrong way. Your attacker also catches your eyes more than previously, what would it be like to get worn... You shake your head and form a counter spell, undoing all the changes.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>Your attacker's spell connects. You feel yourself shrink a few feet. You also feel all your skin having changed into something compressed and smooth, the pink color coming out even more than before. Your arms begin merging into the sides of your body, as your legs begin forming one appandage. Your opponents neck begins dominating your thoughts, but you eventually get those sorted out and form a new counter spell, changing you back to normal.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>Your attacker's spell connects. You feel yourself shrink to the size of an arm. Your skin fully changed and your body almost one single band, you feel your head split open and get a metallic feeling. Several pits begin to form a bit above and below your womanhood. You feel other metal pins grow outward your spine and two metal rings grow out of your sides, a bit below your changing head and neck. You begin wondering if you should bend over, in-between the thoughts of being worn by something. After some heavy mental disputes, you finally succeed in forming a counter spell, changing you back to normal.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>Your attacker's spell connects. You shrink to the length of half an arm, as your skin turns into a bright pink leather and you say goodbye to your arms and legs. Your entire body changes into a pink belt, or rather collar, as a few holes penetrated your form above and below the hole from your womanhood. Three metal 'rings' formed, with the first having a metal pin which you force through a hole in your body, as you bend over and form a circle. The changes settling in, you can't wait to find out what will be wearing you first.</TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>Your spell hits the target. They seem confused about its effects even staring out to the sky with a blank look for a few seconds, before changing back to their original thoughts.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>Your spell connects. You see their skin change texture and seemingly showing off less wrinkles. Again, they seem lost in thoughts for a few seconds, before using a counter spell.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>Your spell hits home. You watch as the pink color of the skin becomes more apparent, your target seems more interested in you than before and seemingly begins straightening its pose a bit. They eventually get back to normal though...</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Your spell hits. You watch as they shrink a bit and get a leathery look about their skin, with a more apparent pink color. You watch as their arms shrink away and their legs join together in a single appandage. They seem even more focused on you than before, but eventually manages to change back again. You feel it won't be long anymore before you've got a new collar.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Your spell hits again. You watch as your target shrinks even more, as their skin fully becomes leather and their body forms a single long band. Their head changes into metal and begins forming a hollow square. You see several pits appear on the other smooth leather and a few metal studs grow out of the back of the band. Two more metal rings grow out of the sides, a bit underneath were the head had been and the entire thing begins squirming around, trying to figure out it's next position. After a while, you look dissapointed as your target once again manages to change back.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>Your spell hits for the last time you feel, as your target shrinks to its smallest size yet and their skin turns into a bright pink leather, as their arms and legs fuse and shrink with their body. A penk band is left behind, before a few holes penetrated the bottom part and two metal rings formed underneath the square metal ring at the other end. For some reason, it bends itself in the rings and forces a metal pin through one of the holes, leaving itself in the form of a cirlce, already inviting something to be put in-between.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>Your spell hits the target. He seems confused about its effects even staring out to the sky with a blank look for a few seconds, before changing back to his original thoughts.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>Your spell connects. You see his skin change texture and seemingly showing off less wrinkles. Again, he seem lost in thoughts for a few seconds, before using a counter spell.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>Your spell hits home. You watch as the pink color of the skin becomes more apparent, your target seems more interested in you than before and seemingly begins straightening his pose a bit. He eventually gets back to normal though...</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>Your spell hits. You watch as he shrinks a bit and gets a leathery look about his skin, with a more apparent pink color. You watch as his arms shrink away and his legs join together in a single appandage. He seems even more focused on you than before, but eventually he manages to change back again. You feel it won't be long anymore before you've got a new collar.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>Your spell hits again. You watch as your target shrinks even more, as his skin fully becomes leather and his body forms a single long band. The band smoothens out a bit more, as his manhood shrinks away. His head changes into metal and begins forming a hollow square. You see several pits appear on the other smooth leather and a few metal studs grow out of the back of the band. Two more metal rings grow out of the sides, a bit underneath were the head had been and the entire thing begins squirming around, trying to figure out it's next position. After a while, you look dissapointed as your target once again manages to change back.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>Your spell hits for the last time you feel, as your target shrinks to his smallest size yet and his skin turns into a bright pink leather, as his arms and legs fuse and shrink with his body. His manhood also quickly disappears into the leather. A smooth pink band is left behind, before a few holes penetrated the bottom part and two metal rings formed underneath the square metal ring at the other end. For some reason, it bends itself in the rings and forces a metal pin through one of the holes, leaving itself in the form of a cirlce, already inviting something to be put in-between.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>Your spell hits the target. She seems confused about its effects even staring out to the sky with a blank look for a few seconds, before changing back to her original thoughts.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>Your spell connects. You see her skin change texture and seemingly showing off less wrinkles. Again, She seem lost in thoughts for a few seconds, before using a counter spell.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>Your spell hits home. You watch as the pink color of the skin becomes more apparent, your target seems more interested in you than before and seemingly begins straightening her pose a bit. She eventually gets back to normal though...</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>Your spell hits. You watch as she shrinks a bit and gets a leathery look about her skin, with a more apparent pink color. You watch as her arms shrink away and her legs join together in a single appandage. She seems even more focused on you than before, but eventually manages to change back again. You feel it won't be long anymore before you've got a new collar.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>Your spell hits again. You watch as your target shrinks even more, as her skin fully becomes leather and her body forms a single long band. The band smoothens out a bit more, as her breasts shrinks away. Her head changes into metal and begins forming a hollow square. You see several pits appear on the other smooth leather, below her womanhood and a few metal studs grow out of the back of the band. Two more metal rings grow out of the sides, a bit underneath were the head had been and the entire thing begins squirming around, trying to figure out it's next position. After a while, you look dissapointed as your target once again manages to change back.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>Your spell hits for the last time you feel, as your target shrinks to her smallest size yet and her skin turns into a bright pink leather, as her arms and legs fuse and shrink with her body. Her breasts too quickly disappear into the leather. A smooth pink band is left behind, before a few holes, above and below her womanhood penetrated the bottom part and two metal rings formed underneath the square metal ring at the other end. For some reason, it bends itself in the rings and forces a metal pin through one of the holes, leaving itself in the form of a cirlce, already inviting something to be put in-between.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>

</Form>
