<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>You pant as a sudden increase of your body weight causes your legs to tremble and fail . You scratch your nose, feeling something odd, noticing that your nose feels flatter.  Moaning, you reverse the changes.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>You squeal, terrified, begging your attacker to stop. Your face seems to be changing, becoming longer as your ears turn floppy. With a snort you undo the curse, showing more effort this time.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>You drop to your knees as your internal organs shift.  As your body mass increases, your breasts grow larger, four more soft, sensitive breasts appearing down your belly.  Gripping your lengthening face with your hands, you push against the change, forcing the change to revert.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>You drop to your knees as your internal organs shift.  As your body mass increases, your breasts grow larger, four more soft, sensitive breasts appearing down your belly.  Gripping your lengthening face with your hands, you push against the change.  You lose your balance and fall into a mud puddle that you didn't notice before.  You look eagerly at your attacker, just asking for more, ready to begin life as a pig girl. You stand back up, undoing the change.
</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>You squeal in excitement and horror as your instincts begin to take over. Your breasts are becoming teats, swelling and plumping out to full size.  Your ears, now pink and pointed, flop down the sides of your head.  Small tusks slowly push their way from your mouth.  You start to feel a wonderful sensation as your curly tail pokes its way out of your backside.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>You squeal in fear and excitement, your subconsciousness preventing you from returning back.  Your extra breasts have once more become teats, swelling as your entire body gains mass, primarily around your stomach.  Your pink, pointy ears regain their shape and flop down to your sides and again feel a wonderful, tickling sensation right above your ass., a cute pink curly tail.
You feel your fingers become stiff, partially hooves, but not entirely, leaving you with parts of your human hands.  This is it--you can't fight the magic anymore and you are, at least for the time being, stuck in the body of a half pig, half human girl with an overpowering urge to snort and roll in the nearest muddle of mud.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>Your victim's body begins to bulge, filling out into a barrel shape.  They scratch their nose, feeling something odd, noticing that their nose is flatter.  Moaning, your victim reverses the changes.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>This time your victim squeals, begging for you to stop.  Their face begins changing, becoming longer with their ears becoming pointed and flopping to their sides.  With a snort they manage to undo your curse, showing more effort.
</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>Your victim falls to their knees as their internal organs shift the slightest bit.  As their weight increases, their breasts begin to grow slightly larger and two more pairs of sensitive breasts start to pop out a bit further down their belly.  Your victim grabs their lengthening face in horror with their hands, forcing your changes to revert.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Your victim loses their balance and falls in a large puddle of mud, causing them to land on their fat body.  They suddenly look at you with a face that is just begging for more, ready to begin life working on a farm.  Your victim stands back up, using some of their last remaining will power to undo the change.
</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Your victim squeals in pure euphoria, breasts turning into three rows of teats.  Their ears, now pointed, flop down the sides of to the sides of their head.  Small tusks slowly push their way from your victim's mouth.  Suddenly, a curly tail pushes its way out of your victim's backside, right above their ass.  They struggle to undo the changes as they become more permanent.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>Your victim squeals in pure excitement as their transformation becomes permanent.  Their extra breasts reform, and become teats again, swelling as their entire body gains mass, mainly around the waist and stomach.  Their pointy ears regain their shape and flop down to their sides sides.  Finally, a curly pink tail pushes its way out of their backside for a final time.  Your victim looks up at you, squealing and shouting happily.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
