<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<Description>She's a real beauty; you can't denythat, but do not get fouled by her beautiful blond hair or her piercing blue eyes. She's not your everyday Bimbo!  Don't worry, she still loves sex very much, a good banging now and them always keeps her happy, but what she loves most is exposing her wonderful body to everyone. Full time exhibitionist, she just want to lay around in the sun showing her goddess body to everyone who wants to see it. Just the thought of people gasping at her beauty if enough to boost her arousal at his limits and make her squirm. Once she's all set relaxing exposing herself and dreaming about naughty situations, it's takes all her strength to walk around to a new location. However, absorbing the sun energy for so long gave her extra offensive and defensive abilities. </Description>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>You're struck with a blindingly-bright ray of energy, one that leaves your skin tingly and warm and your vision swimming. As you blink the tears out of your eyes, feeling like you've just stared into the sun, you turn your head up to the sky and reminisce about the feel of sunlight on your skin. For a moment, the idea of sunbathing right here and now seems like an amazing idea, but you come to your senses quickly and cast a counterspell to rid yourself of the impulse. </TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>A blindingly-bright beam comes over you suddenly, leaving you nice and warm and toasty inside and out. The urge to just forget everything and kick back and relax is tremendously tempting now. Dreamily you stretch your lithe, tanned limbs and brush a bit of blonde hair out of your face, looking about for a place to spread out and lay down -- thankfully, you don't find a good place before you realize that you're definitely under the effect of a spell. Countermagic returns you to your previous form. </TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>The bright beam flashes over your body again, transfixing you in your place for a moment as the warmth spreads through your body again. The urge to find a place to lay out and bake is almost overpowering now, but there's something different about it now... something eager, something that wants you to be laying in the most prominent place that you can find. You want to be seen sunbathing. You want to show off that body of yours. You want to entice someone to you and get a little bit of sugar on the side. Smacking your lips, you can taste the strawberry lip balm as you imagine a pair of hands on your body -- a thought that jars you back to yourself. You recite the counterspell, but the warm fuzzies at the notion of being on display are the last to go. </TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>You're bathed in sunlight again, and the now-familiar laziness and warmth floods through your system almost immediately. Before you can start hunting a place to lay out and wiggle your hips at passers-by, you catch sight of your reflection in a window. Oh my gawd, when did you get so hot? Bleached-blonde hair, an awesome tan, and a killer bod -- they're all going to stare at you when they pass by, and the thought just drives you giddy with a more directed warmth between your legs. Wouldn't it be totally awesome if you could lay down, relax, get a cutie to come your way, and then they would totally do you? The idea leaves you giggling aloud as you cup your totally sweet rack in your hands, imagining someone else's on you, and the sheer volume of your moan is the only thing that snaps you back to awareness. It is a tremendous act of will to fight the urge to just take a sunbathing break and make the counterspell happen. The sense of warmth all over will haunt you for some time, though. </TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>Like, what just happened? You remember being in the city, and you remember the bright light over your body, and then everything got warm and gooshy inside. It takes you a moment to realize you've been laying out in the sun for you don't know how long, soaking up the rays, and eyeing the hotties as they come by. Oh my gawd, and you were calling them your way too. You're in the beach bimbo body someone's been trying to put you in, showing yourself off to everyone and anyone, and you LIKED it. Another cute one comes by, and you're so horny that you actively have to fight the urge to invite them to enjoy the view. You know you should remember the counterspell to change back, but it's super-hard to remember why it's so important to do it when you feel so nice and horny letting everybody watch you... but with a sigh, eventually, with laborious effort, you make the sign of reversal and retake your original body. </TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>The bright light comes over you one more time and you just like give up. If they're going to shine those bright lights on you, you may as well get an awesome tan out of it, y'know? And so you instinctively find the comfiest spot to relax on, making sure that it's also nice and visible for everyone to see just how sexy you are. You've got plenty of lazy summer days ahead of you now, filled with babes and boys -- and as you start to soak in the sun and the appreciative gazes of others, you find that exactly as you'd like it.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>You struck your target with a blindingly-bright ray of energy, one that leaves their skin tingly and warm and sends their vision swimming. As your victim blink the tears out of their eyes, rubbing them away, your target turn their blue eyes up to the sky and you see a feeling a calmness over their face. Your target come to their senses quickly and cast a counterspell to get rid of the impulse.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>A blindingly-bright beam comes over your target, leaving a nice, warm and toasty inside and out. The urge to just forget everything and kick back and relax is tremendously tempting in its face. You see your victim stretch their lithe, tanned limbs and brush a bit of blonde hair out of their face, looking about for a place to spread out and lay down -- sadly, your target doesn't find a good place before realizing that it's definitely under the effect of a spell. Countermagic returns your victim to their previous form. </TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>The bright beam flashes over your targets body again, transfixing your victim for a moment as the warmth spreads through their body again. The urge to find a place to lay out and bake is almost overpowering now, but there's something different about it now... something eager, something that wants your victim to be laying in the most prominent place that it can find. Your victim want to be seen sunbathing. You can see that she wants to show off that new female body. She wants to entice someone to her and get a little bit of sugar on the side. You can see her shivers as she's probably thinking about a pair of hands on her body -- a thought that jars your target back. She recite the counterspell, but you can feel that the warm fuzzies at the notion of being on display are the last to go in your target mind.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Your target is bathed in sunlight again, and the now-familiar laziness and warmth floods through their system almost immediately. Your target quickly takes back its female form as it start to wiggle their hips at passers-by, you see her catch a reflection of herself in a window. "Oh my gawd, when did you get so hot? Bleached-blonde hair, an awesome tan, and a killer bod -- they're all going to stare at you when they pass by", she says to herself with a dreamy look in her face and a hand between the legs. She start giggling aloud as she now cup her big breast in her hands. The sheer volume of her moans is the only thing that snaps her back to awareness. You can see that it is a tremendous act of will for your target to fight the urge to just take a sunbathing break and make the counterspell happen.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Your target is hit by the light again, your victim almost instantly takes back a female form. With a dreamy look on her face she finds the most exposed spot nearby as she lay on her back enjoying every sensations It takes her a moment to realize she's been laying out in the sun very long, soaking up the rays, and eyeing the hotties as they come by. She even winked at you, and blow you a inviting kiss. You can see by her little moans of pleasure that she's very enjoying the attention she's getting. You see her struggling to remember the counterspell to change back, but it's like super-hard for her to remember why it's so important to do it when she feels so nice and horny letting everybody watch her... but with a sigh and with laborious effort, she finally make the sign of reversal and your target takes back their original body.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>The bright light comes over your target one more time and your victim just seem to give up. Embracing its growing female  body, she begin to giggle aloud and she instinctively find the comfiest spot to relax on, making sure that it's also nice and visible for everyone to see just how sexy she is. She look at you with an hungry look in her eyes as she motion at you to get closer and embrace her finale form.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
