<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<Description>Until used you reside in the form of a fleshy ball with a pussy vaguely aware of your surroundings, unable to move, but certainly able to feel. When worn your new body is alive, you are dimly aware of your fate and surroundings but most importantly of your owners needs. You can feel your folds, everything that enters you fills you entirely, and you know you are nestled between a warm pair of legs. You'd like to think you control them but their urges control you, you entire being is hot when they are, wet when excited, but mostly you find yourself eager to be filled... by anything. You twitch a muscle or two now and then to send a shiver of pleasure through yourself and your owner, reminding them not to ignore you. It's not a terrible fate, you will be well cared for and fed often. </Description>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>As you are engulfed by the spell you feel a pleasant warmth invade your body and mind. You easily reverse the effects without effort. </TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>The warmth spreads within you once again as you feel more sensitive all over, a tentative rub across your body sends a quick shiver down your spine but you were just testing, you reverse the spell once more. </TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>As you are hit this time it feels as though a powerful orgasm rolls through your body and the sensitivity is so much better then it was before. You think you are getting shorter as well and it snaps you out of your groping enough to reverse the effect. </TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>This time you aren't just on edge, you feel like you came and came again. Your body is warm, its begging to be touched, you want something in you. As you quickly start heading to the ground, your body feeling less and less mobile, your view of the world starts to fade as your body shifts inwards. Your arms stuck at your sides you start to feel an opening in your chest and a sudden pang of fear breaks you out of it. You have some trouble reversing the spell, unsure you want to give up the pleasure you felt for mobility and rational thought, but you manage. </TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>You feel yourself lost in pleasure as the spell hits you causing orgasm on contact this time. Your body quickly reverts to the sensitive form it was, your other senses dulled and fading as all that matters is touch. You vaguely understand that you're barely a person at all anymore, your a ball of flesh needing to be touched and you realize you were wrong before, you didn't just want something in you, your entirely was something people put things in. If there was any goal beyond pleasure your form was giving you now it was to fill your womb with a child... and with this you understand what you are to become and without haste you painstakingly use whats left of your humanity to reverse the spell. </TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>As quickly as it began it's over... or is this a new beginning? You are racked with debilitating pleasure as you are returned almost immediately to the flesh form you were not so long ago. You drool with hunger, you are warm with insatiable lust, and you need to be used. As your new owner takes hold and places you between there legs you feel complete and whole again forgetting why it mattered you were ever anything but a pussy to be played with and fucked. Your new desires take hold and you understand this new existence has plenty of pleasurable benefits, too bad you have no choice in the matter any more. </TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>You watch your victim squirm under the heat of your spell. You know it isn't much to start with but it will get so much better from here. </TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>This time you watch as they rub themselves over lost for a few moments in the pleasure of their sensitive skin. It's only the start..</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>The fun begins, you watch as they begin to shrink as they play with themselves. Their body just barely starts to change in color and shape before they reverse the spell. </TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Your victim is contorted in pleasure on the ground, their features remaining in the front of this ball of flesh they are starting to become as their arms form the outer folds of their soon to be form. You can see they are having a tough time comprehending what is happening especially with the lust of their new form taking over their mind.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Your victim cries out in pleasure as their form shrinks down once more. The flesh blob on the ground rolls back and forth slightly with what little ability it has left. You can see your victims face wrought in pleasure among the folds of their new form, their last saving grace before the form would take over. It's only a matter of moments before you will have your very own, very special, pussy. </TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>Finally they are defeated. In your victims place is a ball of flesh with a pussy, wet and ready, on one side facing you. You pick up your newly transformed pussy and with a small bit of additional magic you replace whatever boring parts were between your legs before for a newly formed playful pussy, which unlike your old equipment has the barely coherent, pleasure wrought mind of your victim ready and eager to be played with. As if to confirm you feel them twitch between you legs sending a wave of pleasure up your spine. </TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
