<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<Description>A very pretty anthro bitch who is a shadow of her former human self. Her eyes look longingly at everyone she glances at, her tail raised to show she is willing for any mate to take her. Her fur is sleek and soft, covering her from head to paws. She has 3 rows of perky breasts with achingly hard nipples that are just begging to be sucked on. Clearly she is nothing more than a walking sex machine with only enough of her humanity left to continue changing others</Description>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>You  pant as a rush of heat fills your loins, your eyesight blurring as everything appears grey to you for a moment. You shake your head and scratch your itching neck, noticing fur sprouting on the back of your neck and your nails beginning to fold into blunt claws. With a grumble you reverse the changes without any real effort.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>You openly shudder this time and let out a heated moan, the fronts of your pants gaining a damp spot from a small orgasm.  Your ears change and become floppy, covered in brown fur, your hands losing some dexterity as they change to look more like paws. With a whimper you  revert to normal once again, but the glaze of sweat on your forehead tells your opponent it was harder this time.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>You  drop to your knees and whine in a dog-like manner. As your body becomes much more feminine, your breasts grow larger, more pairs of sensitive breast flesh appearing down your belly. Your ears change once more, but this time your nose becomes black and wet as well, starting to push forwards into a muzzle. Gripping your lengthening face with your paws you push against the change, forcing yourself to transform back, leaving you panting hotly on the ground from the effort of resisting.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>You  wobble and fall to your belly, your feet changing into dog-like paws as the fur returns, covering your entire body now. You whimper and let out a pitiful bark as a fluffy tail pushes out from above your butt, flagging to show that you are horny and eager. You look up at you, their face now fully resembling a dog's, although their eyes remain human and maintain a spark of resistance. They push yourself off the ground with your rapidly changing paws, and cast the counter spell once more, reverting to normal but looking at your attacker with a hint of fear in your eyes.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>You  bark openly, yoru extra breasts swelling and plumping out to full size as your entire body becomes covered with that wonderful soft fur. Your ears flop cutely at the sides of your head, your longer tongue lolling out of your muzzle as you pant in lustful need. You drop to their knees before your attacker and look up at them obediently, lifting your paw-like hands into the begging position as you begin to act like the proper bitch you are turning into. You rub your furry thighs together as your plump pussy lips twitch hotly, whimpering in pleasure and desire out of your slutty muzzle. Before your human mind is overwhelmed however you pull yourself out of it and painstakingly change back to normal. They smile at you knowing one or two more times and you will be a sexy new bitch in town.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>You  bark openly, your extra breasts swelling and plumping out to full size as your entire body becomes covered with that wonderful soft fur. Your ears flop cutely at the sides of your head, your longer tongue lolling out of your muzzle as you pant in lustful need. You drop to their knees before your attacker and look up at them obediently, lifting your paw-like hands into the begging position as you begin to act like the proper bitch you are turning into. You rub your furry thighs together as your plump pussy lips twitch hotly, whimpering in pleasure and desire out of your slutty muzzle. Your human mind is overwhelmed with new desires and instincts, corrupting your original desires and twisting them into more perverse ones. The newly transformed anthro bitch you have become barks happily, eager to take on the world again and have sex with everyone you meet, at least until you either get pregnant or ends up an inanimate object.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>Your opponent pants and a rush of heat fills their loins, their eyesight blurring as everything appears grey to them for a moment. They shake their head and scratch their itching neck, noticing sprouting fur on their neck and their nails beginning to fold into blunt claws. With a grumble they reverse the changes without any real effort.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>Your opponent openly shudders this time and lets out a heated moan, the fronts of their pants gaining a damp spot from a small orgasm.  Their ears change and become floppy, covered in brown fur, their hands losing some dexterity as they change to look more like paws. With a whimper your opponent reverts to normal, but the glaze of sweat on their forehead tells you it was harder this time.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>Your opponent drops to their knees and whines in a dog-like manner. As their body becomes much more feminine, their breasts grow larger, more pairs appearing down their belly. Their ears change once more, but this time their nose becomes black and wet as well, starting to push forwards into a muzzle. Gripping their lengthening face with their paws they push against the change, forcing their self to transform back, leaving them panting hotly on the ground from the effort of resisting.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Your opponent wobbles and falls to their belly, their feet changing into dog-like paws as the fur returns, covering their entire body now. The whimper and let out a pitiful bark as a fluffy tail pushes out from above their butt, flagging to show that they are horny and eager. They look up at you, their face now fully resembling a dog's, although their eyes remain human and maintain a spark of resistance. They push themselves off the ground with their rapidly changing paws, and cast the counter spell once more, reverting to normal but looking at you with a hint of fear.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Your opponent barks openly, their extra breasts swelling and plumping out to full size as their entire body becomes covered with that wonderful soft looking fur. Their ears flop cutely at the sides of their head, their longer tongue lolling out of their muzzle as they pant in lustful need. They drop to their knees before you and look up at you obediently, lifting their paw-like hands into the begging position as they begin to act like the proper bitch they are turning into. They rub their furry thighs together as their plump pussy lips twitch hotly, whimpering in pleasure and desire. Before their human mind is overwhelmed however they pull themselves out of it and painstakingly change themselves back to normal. You smile knowing one or two more times and their will be a sexy new bitch in town.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>Your opponent barks openly, their extra breasts swelling and plumping out to full size as their entire body becomes covered with that wonderful soft looking fur. Their ears flop cutely at the sides of their head, their longer tongue lolling out of their muzzle as they pant in lustful need. They drop to their knees before you and look up at you obediently, lifting their paw-like hands into the begging position as they begin to act like the proper bitch they are turning into. They rub their furry thighs together as their plump pussy lips twitch hotly, whimpering in pleasure and desire. Their human mind is overwhelmed with new desires and instincts, corrupting their original desires and twisting them into more perverse ones. The newly transformed anthro bitch barks happily, eager to take on the world again and have sex with everyone she meets, at least until she either  gets pregnant or ends up an inanimate object.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
