<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>You feel dark energy swirling about and through you. Your cock hardens in your pants, but with an irritated gesture you manage to dismiss the magical force afflicting you.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>The energy comes back, stronger this time and somehow sweeter. Visions of power flash behind your eyes, great and fathomless. Returning to your senses you can feel your cock straining against your pants, seed leaking from its tip. Embarrassed at your arousal you manage to dismiss the magic affecting you.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>As they say the spell again you can feel the power that you were only shown previously. Fantastic and cosmic in scope, near limitless, the power is all but at your fingertips. You almost find yourself lost in the ego erasing magnitude of it, but you manage with difficulty to find your way back. Blinking you realize your body has changed, you flesh hard and rock-like, a black deeper than a cloudy night's. Your cock has swollen to twice its former size, sperm flowing freely from it, and breasts seem to be swelling from your chest. As you utter the counterspell you realize your voice is harsher and more gravely, reminiscent to the sound of stones crushing together.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>They say the spell again and a part of you welcomes it. You revel for a time in the power of it, exulting in such strength as to rend the cosmos asunder. You stand, taller now by almost three feet, with fledgeling wings sprouting from your back. Your erect cock stands over two feet in length, drooling sperm like a hungry dog, and looming over it two massive breasts hang from your chest dripping milk. As suddenly as it came you can feel the power leaking from you before you can even put it to proper use. Try and hasten it or stop it the result is the same and within moments you have returned to your previous form.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>You hear the words again and can't help but find yourself welcoming the power rush it brings with you. Once more you feel that might, that power, and once more you stand in the world like a titan of Hell, ready to stride forth. Then something changes. You feel yourself growing smaller, your entire body shrinking into your cock which seems to glow with power. You try and resist, but horrified you realize this power you now hold was never meant for this universe, and cannot exist unsealed. Gnashing your teeth like a beast you manage to release the power before you are sealed with it, but as you return to your previous form you find yourself shaking with loss.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>You feel the rush of power once again, but fear comes with it now. You struggle against the force trying to seal you, but you realize that despite the power you have gained you have lost the humanity needed to resist and to exist in this world unsealed. Howling with impotent rage, you feel your body shrink into your cock. Even that shrinks further, a handle sprouting from its woefully shrunken fourteen inch shaft. You can feel power flowing through you, lighting a series of runes across your throbbing shaft, even as it hardens permanently. Even now spooge drips from your tip, and as you feel your fantastic cosmic power, sealed within this pathetic form, a part of you laughs. You will feed on the one who thinks they are your master, and you hunger for the life force of foes as well.</TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>You feel dark energy swirling about and through you. Your nipples hardens as you feel your pussy dampen, but with an irritated gesture you manage to dismiss the magical force afflicting you.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>The energy comes back, stronger this time and somehow sweeter. Visions of power flash behind your eyes, great and fathomless. Returning to your senses you can feel something straining against your pants. Looking down you see a fresh cock, rising from where your clit should be. Feeling invaded you manage to dismiss the magic affecting you.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>As they say the spell again you can feel the power that you were only shown previously. Fantastic and cosmic in scope, near limitless, the power is all but at your fingertips. You almost find yourself lost in the ego erasing magnitude of it, but you manage with difficulty to find your way back. Blinking you realize your body has changed, you flesh hard and rock-like, a black deeper than a cloudy night's. Your cock has swollen out over a foot in length, sperm flowing freely from it, and your leaking breasts now loom from your chest larger than coconuts. As you utter the counterspell you realize your voice is harsher and more gravely, reminiscent to the sound of stones crushing together.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>They say the spell again and a part of you welcomes it. You revel for a time in the power of it, exulting in such strength as to rend the cosmos asunder. You stand, taller now by almost three feet, with fledgeling wings sprouting from your back. Your erect cock stands over two feet in length, drooling sperm like a hungry dog, and looming over it two massive breasts hang from your chest dripping milk. As suddenly as it came you can feel the power leaking from you before you can even put it to proper use. Try and hasten it or stop it the result is the same and within moments you have returned to your previous form.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>You hear the words again and can't help but find yourself welcoming the power rush it brings with you. Once more you feel that might, that power, and once more you stand in the world like a titan of Hell, ready to stride forth. Then something changes. You feel yourself growing smaller, your entire body shrinking into your cock which seems to glow with power. You try and resist, but horrified you realize this power you now hold was never meant for this universe, and cannot exist unsealed. Gnashing your teeth like a beast you manage to release the power before you are sealed with it, but as you return to your previous form you find yourself shaking with loss.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>You feel the rush of power once again, but fear comes with it now. You struggle against the force trying to seal you, but you realize that despite the power you have gained you have lost the humanity needed to resist and to exist in this world unsealed. Howling with impotent rage, you feel your body shrink into your cock. Even that shrinks further, a handle sprouting from its woefully shrunken fourteen inch shaft. You can feel power flowing through you, lighting a series of runes across your throbbing shaft, even as it hardens permanently. Even now spooge drips from your tip, and as you feel your fantastic cosmic power, sealed within this pathetic form, a part of you laughs. You will feed on the one who thinks they are your master, and you hunger for the life force of foes as well.</TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>You watch as your target's cock hardens, his head back in a thrill as images of power barrage his mind. A grin touches your lips, knowing that such power can never be here, not free and unsealed.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>You watch as your target's cock swells, leaking pre-cum, and hints of breasts form on their chest. Unfortunately, they are not lost long in the promise of antedeluvian power and soon return to their senses.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>Their form becomes demonic as power from the primal chaos flows into them. Their skin turns the deepest black you've ever seen, even as it becomes a strange substance not known to this world. Their cock swells, doubling in size, as it releases its unholy jism, and teats blossom from their chest, dripping with milky substance. Their mind returns too soon, though, and with a deep voice they utter the counterspell.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>Once more their form becomes demonic. Horns spiralling from their head, and small wings sprouting from their back. Their cock and breasts are larger than ever, and you can see them almost losing themselves in the extra-temporal power that is flooding their unprepared mind. They look at you, the power flowing through them, and for a moment you feel fear that you may have created a monster you cannot face but then you see the power slipping away from them. They will not be able to hold it in that form.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>You watch as their form becomes demonic once more, a melding of male and female in a size not meant for humans. The transformation seems quicker now, and it proceeds further. You can't help but grin as you see their power turn against them, shrinking them, forcing them into a bound form, a weapon to be wielded by "lesser" creatures. Unfortunately, at the last second, the bindings prove too weak and they manage to hold themselves back from that precipice.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>The transformation is even quicker this time, and you watch as that goliath of demonic might dwindles into nothing more than a cock a little over a foot long; their whole body being sucked into its shaft. You can feel power thrumming from the dildo as a sword-like hilt extends itself from it, and you hear their last impotent howl as they become locked within permanently.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>You watch as your target's pussy moistens, her head back in a thrill as images of power barrage his mind. A grin touches your lips, knowing that such power can never be here, not free and unsealed.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>You watch as something swells beneath your targets pants, and liquid not quite milk begins to flow from her breasts. Unfortunately, they are not lost long in the promise of antedeluvian power and soon return to their senses.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>Their form becomes demonic as power from the primal chaos flows into them. Their skin turns the deepest black you've ever seen, even as it becomes a strange substance not known to this world. Their clit swells into a cock, easily a foot long, and releases unholy jism. Their breasts swell, becoming the size of coconuts as they begin to leak an unholy white substance. Their mind returns too soon, though, and with a deep voice they utter the counterspell.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>Once more their form becomes demonic. Horns spiralling from their head, and small wings sprouting from their back. Their cock and breasts are larger than ever, and you can see them almost losing themselves in the extra-temporal power that is flooding their unprepared mind. They look at you, the power flowing through them, and for a moment you feel fear that you may have created a monster you cannot face but then you see the power slipping away from them. They will not be able to hold it in that form.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>You watch as their form becomes demonic once more, a melding of male and female in a size not meant for humans. The transformation seems quicker now, and it proceeds further. You can't help but grin as you see their power turn against them, shrinking them, forcing them into a bound form, a weapon to be wielded by "lesser" creatures. Unfortunately, at the last second, the bindings prove too weak and they manage to hold themselves back from that precipice.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>The transformation is even quicker this time, and you watch as that goliath of demonic might dwindles into nothing more than a cock a little over a foot long; their whole body being sucked into its shaft. You can feel power thrumming from the dildo as a sword-like hilt extends itself from it, and you hear their last impotent howl as they become locked within permanently.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>

</Form>
