<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st> Your toe nails begin to elongate sharpening as they do. Your pinky toe on each of your feet vanishes in to the base of each foot. The bottom of your feet softens into padding covering both the base of your feet and each of your toes. The padding silencing your unconscious step forward towards your attacker. You reverse these minute changes effortlessly. (With the increase of transformation towards 16%) Your nails retract into your feet as your feet change to a yellowish color as the fur spreads over them completely. Reaching down and touching your foot you fall backwards after feeling the softness. Quickly you stand and reverse the changes quickly. </TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>The spell hits you directly in the legs causing fur to ripple upwards. . The yellow wave of fur reaching just above the shin. You teeter with uncertainty as your muscles tighten without thought willing you to pounce at your foe from the surrounding trees. Confused by the thoughts creeping in your head slowly as if you are not alone with your opponent. Discarding this thought you concentrate on removing the changes reversing it taking more time than before (With the increase towards 32%) The fur expands higher encompassing both of your legs black and orange spots begin to appear tracing along the fur on your legs forming circles of various sizes and lengths. Something or someone speaks into your mind "We are getting closer to becoming free of this body that shackles us both, " you hear a feminine voice say. You glance at your adversary and wonder what sort of sorcery they are using on you. Reversing the changes takes more effort than all of your prior attempts as if the magic itself is resisting you.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>This next hit continues spreading the up to your waist. Your tailbone elongates stretching out of your clothes growing until it reaches out a foot and a half. Your gender becomes a moist wet pair of lips aching for attention, your mind loses concentration as you glance hungrily towards your rival thinking more of what they have below their clothes than feasting upon them.  Baffled by these thoughts you attempt to reverse the changes and are successful at halting their progression. (With he increase of transformation energy to 56%) Your short tail continues to grow from a mere foot and a half to a whopping 4 foot long . Flow flowing upwards still it progresses up your chest as your breast grow larger into a moderate C cup. You touch them tenuously and reel backwards as their softness and sensitivity send sensations throughout your entire body. The voice in your head returns "Yes feel what freedom can give and surrender to its pleasurable embrace," the voice says. Hesitantly you begin to reverse the changes once again it only deters the spread but no sign of returning you back to normal.   </TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>A second pair of breasts appear directly underneath you first set ripening to a modest B cup. Fur expands down your shoulders the muscles expanding and reforming . Your hands begin to reform just as your feet had, this time your thumb disappears into the palm of your hand. Fingernails lengthen into claws as you feel the fur elongates down. You reverse he changes with immense concentration. (As the transformation energy rises to 71%) You feel your palm rearrange into a supple padded paw.  You feel hair begin to trickle down the back of your neck stopping at shoulder length. Another pair of breasts emerge right below your second pair growing to be a large A cup. as you fondle your new breasts you feel your self beginning to feel grateful to your enemy for this change. "That's it I feel your will breaking as I emerge from this shell your body once shackled us in,"she says eagerly. By focusing with what thoughts you can you reverse the changes.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>The final pair of breasts grow suddenly from your midsection into an AA cup, settling themselves just under you 3 pair of breast. Your eyes change color to a golden slitted yellow, as they both spread a little bit further apart from each other. Your nose begins to change shape expanding and rearranging itself outwards with your mouth along for the ride forming a snout. You scent excitement and lust rising in the air surrounding you. You know your foe smells of excitement but you wonder who is the lust coming from. With extreme concentration you reverse the changes. (With the transformation energy landing at 94%) Your ears begin to shift upwards towards the top of your head. They expand and twitch at the new sounds that emerge from your surroundings. Your hair lengthens to rest at the middle of your back.  "We are so close now you cannot escape this  and you know it," the feminine voice in your head said mockingly, " I will finally be free to roam and stalk." You attempt to reverse the changes by focusing on the voice and it fall silent. </TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>Your foe’s blow hits you square in the chest shaking you to your core. You feel the spell click throughout your entire body as if it were a lock just opened for the first time. You shake your head fighting uselessly as she surges into your mind once more. She roars through your mind,"We are free together we shall make all of this world tremble in fear at the shadows that we hide in, nowhere shall be safe as long as we prowl. " But first we must take care of our friend here I am so very lonely after being caged for so long I need a sister to travel with." Your body moves with grace towards your soon to be sister. </TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd> The spell hits them square in the legs and begins to work toe nails begin to elongate sharpening as they do. Their pinky toes vanish into the base of their feet right before your eyes.  They take a step towards you if you hadn't been watching you would have never known from the silence. The enemy reverse these minute changes effortlessly. (With the increase of transformation towards 16%) The opponent's nails retract into their feet as their feet change to a yellowish color as the fur spreads over them completely. They reach down and touching one of their feet and fall backwards after doing so. Quickly they stand up again and reverse the changes you cast on them swiftly. </TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>Your next spell bolt strikes them directly in the legs causing fur to ripple upwards from their feet. The yellow wave of fur reaching just above the shin. They teeter back and forth as you watch their muscles tighten. They look at you confused as they shake their head as if shaking away the attack. They take more time than before to reverse the changes you have pushed upon them. (With the increase towards 32%) The fur expands higher encompassing both of your foe's legs black and orange spots begin to appear tracing along the fur on your victim legs forming circles of various sizes and lengths.  They glance at you confusedly. Their attempts to reverse the implemented changes takes more effort than all of their prior attempts you see this as their face tightens with strain. </TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>This barrage of power continues the spread of fur advancing up to their waistline. They gaze around to their backside as you see a tail begin to emerge from their posterior Growing until what you believe to be about a foot and a half. Their gender becomes a moist wet pair of lips dripping wetness to the ground below them. Your foe seems distracted and then glares at you with almost a husky expression in their eyes. Fear appears in your enemies' eyes as they  attempt to reverse the changes and are successful at halting their progression for now. (With he increase of transformation energy to 56%) This hit expands their short tail continues to grow from a mere foot and a half to a whopping 4 foot long  by your guess. Your adversaries fur begins  flowing upwards still it progresses up their chest as you watch their breast grow larger into what you believe to be a  moderate C cup. You watch as they touch them cautiously and stumble backwards as they blush from the touches they have done.  Hesitantly they begin to reverse the changes once again but watching you see  no sign of returning them changing back into their old form.   </TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>With another flourish of your wrists a second pair of breasts appear directly underneath their first set ripening to a nice B cup. Gradually the fur expands down their shoulders the muscles expanding and reforming in their arms as if under your exact orders. Their hands begin to reform just as their feet had, this time the opponent's thumb disappears into the palm of their hand. Fingernails lengthen into claws as the fur elongates down to reach the tips of their hands. Gazing upon them they close their eyes as if they are focusing only on reversing your attacks upon them. (As the transformation energy rises to 71%) You watch as their palms rearrange themselves into a supple padding on the bottom of their new paws.  Hungrily you watch as their hair slowly grows down the back of their neck stopping at approximately shoulder length. Another pair of breasts emerge right below their second pair growing to be a large A cup.  You watch as your victim begins fondle their new breasts gazing at you with could almost be acceptance. They reverse the changes almost tantalizingly slow.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>A fourth and final pair of breasts grow suddenly from upon their midsection into an AA cup, settling themselves just under their 3 pair of breast. Your watch as their eyes change color to a golden slitted yellow and both spread apart from each other. Their nose begins to change shape expanding and rearranging itself outwards to form a snout. Their nostrils flare as they pull in the air around them. Your excitement becomes all too real that your victim will be yours soon . They reverse the changes with at an agonizingly slow pace. (With the transformation energy landing at 94%) Their ears shift upwards towards the top of your foe's head. They expand and twitch moving in all directions. You focus next on their hair lengthening it to rest at the middle of their back. They seem to be focused on something while they are reversing the changes as if something specific about your spell they want to be rid of more than anything else.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>You watch as your new Leopardess' entire body shakes as if emerging to be the dominant you have desired from her. She saunters over towards you and declares,"You have my thanks for unleashing me but first we need to change you to a more fitting form." You wonder whether to be excited or scared at her proclamation and weigh the decision to run or enjoy a new life as you can see she enjoys it.  </TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
