<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<Description>A small delicate bird girl, with beautiful red feathers, with small breasts, and a pair of wings settled atop of her arms. Very short, and doesn't get as tired from moving around, due to the ability to fly. Small orange bird feet, but big enough to still fit correctly with human legs. About 4 feet in height.</Description>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>You hear a small lingering buzzing noise in your ears...suddenly your hearing changes, your ears are gone, and you feel slightly shorter. You realize its an attempt at a spell and brush it off.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>You look down at your arms feeling something is off...not only has your hearing and height changed, but looking down near your arms you notice red feathers, and reverse the effects fairly easily.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>You now have a small pair of wings. Cute red feathers line above your arms now allowing flight. Your butt feels much smaller than before, and a bit of light red hair pours into your eyes, right above your...beak? No...something is off. You cast a counter-spell and regain your senses once more.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>Again the changes consume your body, and before you can do anything you look down and notice a small worm. You squawk in delight and quickly rip it off of the ground with your beak and swallow it whole...until you realize what you're doing and revert the changes...disgusted at what you just swallowed.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>You feel very small and agile, noticing you've lost a lot of weight, and height. You experimentally flap your wings a few times, and flutter around the area. A creature in the area chuckles at you, and your heart races...afraid of it, you nearly fly away. Somehow, you regain your senses...you concentrate as much as you can to revert the changes, difficult, but you manage to pull it off, still a bit of animal instinct forces fear into you from the one who cast the spell on you. </TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>Your breasts are now small, as well as your height, which seems to be around 4 foot tall. You have small red feathered wings, and bird feet, and a light red shoulder length hair. You are partially human, and partially bird. You lack a pair of ears, and have small holes to hear from. You have a small orange beak on your face, and are now missing your teeth. You let out a small tweet and fly off in the distance. You are now a Dainty Birdgirl.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>you cast the spell, and watch as your target's ears sink into their head and height slowly shift down. Effortlessly they brush off your spell before anything major could occur.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>Again, you attempt the spell...this time you successfully cause a few feathers to grow upon your victim, however its short lived as they counter once again.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>A small pair of wings begins to form upon your target, and what appears to be a beak... they soon notice this and realize something is off, and cancel the spell.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Curiously you watch your victim as they strike at the ground with their beak. You notice a worm for a split second in between their beak before its quickly gulped down. The spell is cancelled after the realization of what they just swallowed. You smirk knowing it won't be much longer until the transformation is complete.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>The transformation is nearing completion. You watch as the transformation turns your victim into a small birdgirl. She runs around fluttering her new wings. You chuckle at this view, but obviously that startled her enough to make her realize that something was off. She slowly backs away from you and begins to concentrate on changing back...obviously it was very difficult, and you can still see the fear in her eyes.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>Your target begins to shift once again. Shrinking in size, to around 4 feet tall. The wings grow back once more, and light red hair reaches their shoulders. The beak appears again, and small breasts rest upon her chest. She's still part human in body, but not anymore in mind. She let's out a small bird-like tweet, seeing you again she flies off into the distance. </TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
