<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<Description>You are a two-inch tall tube of ruby-red lipstick in an amazingly shiny case. The casing of the lipstick starts at the middle of your thigh and travels downwards, whereas above your mid-thigh you are a sexy, large-breasted woman. The more you are used, the less human you feel as you slowly realize that your new purpose in life is to be owned and to make your owner happy by making them – and their lips – look very, very sexy!</Description>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>An enemy mage hurls a spell at you! It strikes you in the lower leg, and soon after you feel your body become a little more feminine. Your legs begin to tingle and take on the texture of plastic, but you utter a counter-spell and push aside the changes.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>As your assailant hits you with another spell the skin on your arms and chest turn a reddish colour, and it feels like your chest swells a bit, too. With a sigh, you revert the changes and focus on defending yourself from further attacks.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>Your opponent lands another spell on you, causing your legs to fuse together! Your chest swells up again, breasts growing into what you consider to be a nice size. Oddly, you feel calm. You feel like you want to be owned... To make a woman look good... No! You shake the thoughts from your head and quickly cast a counter-spell to undo the transformation.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>As you're hit by a spell yet again, the feeling of calmness returns. As you think about how much you want to be used and kept in a purse, your legs fuse together and take on the texture of plastic once more. You barely even notice the skin on your upper body shifting to a shade of deep red, or how you're shrinking down to about a foot tall. Looking down at yourself, you're alarmed to see you've taken on the shape of a VERY large-breasted woman! Your sense of calmness is shattered by the shock of this realization, and you immediately counteract the spell, returning yourself to normal.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>You take another hit and you realize you have to win now or it's all over for you! You shrink to a few inches tall, and almost perfectly resemble a tube of lipstick apart from the last few human aspects of you. Despite your form, you feel so sexy. You feel like you NEED to be kept and used. You even consider letting the magic take you over completely, though you eventually manage to summon up the will to fight back and recover your original body!</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>"I need to be used by my owner. I need to be kept and make my owner proud. I need to make her look sexy." You are now a two-inch tall tube of dark ruby-red lipstick, which itself looks like a very sexy lady with an impressive set of breasts. You apply the perfect colour to your new owner's lips and you love it! You wonder why you ever tried to stop it as the last of your mind fades away. "Must be used... Sexy lips... Must be used more..."</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>As your assailant hits you with another spell the skin on your arms and chest turn a reddish colour, and it feels like your chest swells a bit, too. As well, your penis begins to shrink and your testicles are sucked up into your body, tickling you a little bit. With a sigh, you revert the changes and focus on defending yourself from further attacks.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>You launch a powerful attack at your opponent, but they move back and you just hit their leg! You do, however, see an effect as it changes colour, taking on a reddish hue. You smile at the thought of having new lipstick as you take note of the changes the spell inflicts. Unfortunately, your amusement is short-lived as your victim recovers with ease.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>You hit them with another spell and immediately see it take effect. Most notably, the intensity of the red colour increases. They look down on their transforming body with a concerned look on their face. You smile as you notice their chest getting larger underneath their shirt and their legs appearing to shine, almost as if they were made of glass or plastic. They recover but seem to struggle a little with doing so.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>Your attack hits your opponent and they stagger back a little bit. Both their legs fuse together whilst their upper body turns completely ruby-red. Their breasts continue to expand, settling down at a J Cup. You decide to increase your spell power to try to speed it up a bit. You can see your victim start to relax as their mind is being affected, though they seem to snap back and recover.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Hitting them again, you can see your work is almost finished! Their legs fuse and form a cylinder that makes up the tube of the lipstick and their upper body turns completely red completely. You can't wait to try your new lipstick. You watch them shrink down and hope this is it, but they seem to regain control and recover their normal body. By the conflicted look on their face, you suspect that they are still struggling internally – you just know they will love their new life in a purse!</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>You charge your magic for what you hope will be a final powerful attack! Your target seems distracted and you know it won't be long! You launch the attack and hit them in the centre of their chest. Instantly, their eyes go blank and their body rapidly begins changing. Their legs combine to form a perfectly cylindrical tube that shines amazingly. Their arms fuse to their body and their neck shrinks to that of the perfect woman. Their upper half turns a deep red colour as they shrink down to a few inches tall. You find yourself feeling a little jealous of the size of her breasts which, fortunately, stop growing around an I-cup. Looking at the lipstick on the ground you see that although it's a normal casing, the lipstick itself is in the shape of a very sexy, busty woman. Just as you think you have won they seem to regain control, and with a struggle, recover their former body. Just one or two more hits. You can sense it!</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>You launch an all-out attack at your opponent, confident that this is it!  Seemingly having given up, they don't even attempt to evade the oncoming barrage as it smashes into them at full force! They rapidly reform into the tube of beautiful ruby-red lipstick from before and fall to the ground. You pick the tube up and admire your own image in its reflective surface. Satisfied that they won't be changing back, you twist the lid up and generously apply it to your lips. "Wow," you think to yourself, "I should have done this years ago!" Before replacing the cap, you take a brief moment to examine the figure of what they looked like when you previously turned them into a woman. The detail is meticulous, as if it were carved in by a master. You smile at the things magic can do and drop your sexy new lipstick into your bag, ready for whenever it's needed. Patting your bag, you address your new lipstick one more time, "There we go. I'm sure I'll be using you every day, honey!"</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
