<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>The spell hits you and you feel as if hundreds of small insects are crawling all over your body.  You shiver involuntarily and remove the spell.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>The spell hits you again, flowing across your body in concentrated pulses.  The energy seems to be focusing on your chest and legs, and you reach into your pants to check.  You feel very soft hairs growing there.  "A furry spell, then" you think as you disarm the spell.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>You almost dodge the spell as it just grazes your chest, before it seems to swing back and hit you in the rear.  Your chest immediately swells, and you reach up as two noticable breasts begin to grow.  You are secretly delighting in how they feel when your ass suddenly expands.  You fall back as you feel the magic adding more weight to your hips, and an insistent pressure beginning to grow.  Disappointed with having to lose your new breasts, you disperse the magic. </TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>The spell throws you to the ground, the sudden weight on your rear keeping you there.  You see breasts push out of your chest, but the magic is keeping you from reaching for them.  Your face feels like it's tightening, and you fight hard to stop the magic.  As you get it under control you stand back up.  Easily.  Your senses are better, you move quicker, and you are starting to identify weaknesses in your opponent's attacks.  You idly reach down and feel your feminine thighs as you prepare to counter attack.  You stroke back, a little surprised at the fine hairs down ther and find... another leg.  Startled, you look back at the identical pair of tightly muscled, but clearly female legs behind you.  With a shock you finish removing the rest of the spell.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>You almost welcome the change back to your hunter's senses.  You smile as your body quickly morphs into an athletic female, and one hand unconsciously reaches up to feel your small and perky breasts, the other sliding back to your enlarged rear.  You are ready this time when a second set of legs slowly emerge, then another, then more.  You are lifted up as your legs grow, almost ecstatic at your enhanced movement.  You look back and cry out in horror as your beautiful feet squash down into barbed points, and your shapely legs begin to tighten and become more insect-like.  Years of ingrained fear help squash the magic and return you to your male self.  Barely.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>You are finally ready.  You want to hunt.  You need to feed.  The magic comes close and you grab it and hungrily devour its energies, the transformative power flowing through you.  You are a woman before you realise it; beautiful, athletic, and deadly.  Already your legs are growing longer, sharper, as your ass pushes out.  Two more pairs of legs, clearly not human, push out behind your changing limbs, and finally the last two legs emerge.  From the waist down you are a spider - born to hunt.  From your new tingly sex upwards you are a beautiful seductress - and you know which half is the deadlier.  You smile, looking around at all the plentiful sources of energy scurrying around you and then focus on your opponent.  Perhaps you'll start with that one...</TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>The spell hits you and you feel as if hundreds of small insects are crawling all over your body.  You shiver involuntarily and remove the spell.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>The spell hits you again, flowing across your body in concentrated pulses.  The energy seems to be focusing on your face and legs, and you reach into your pants to check.  You feel very soft hairs growing on your legs.  "Is this an anti-shaving spell?  Ewww" you think as you disarm the spell.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>You almost dodge the spell as it just grazes your chest, before it seems to swing back and hit you in the rear.  Your chest and waist tighten, and you can feel the lithe muscle there becoming stronger.  You are secretly delighting in your new svelte waist when your ass suddenly expands.  You fall back as you feel the magic adding more weight to your hips, and an insistent pressure beginning to grow.  "A big booty spell?  No thanks".  You disperse the magic.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>The spell throws you to the ground, the sudden weight on your rear keeping you there.  You see the skin of your chest and arms turn a slight blue colour, but the magic is keeping you from touching it.  Your mouth feels like it's tightening, and you fight hard to stop the magic.  As you get it under control you stand back up.  Easily.  Your senses are better, you move quicker, and you are starting to identify weaknesses in your opponent's attacks.  You idly reach down and feel your toned thighs as you prepare to counter attack.  You stroke back, a little surprised at the fine hairs down there and find... another leg.  Startled, you look back at the identical pair of tightly muscled, but clearly female, legs behind you.  With a shock you finish removing the rest of the spell.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>You almost welcome the change back to your hunter's senses.  You smile as your body quickly morphs into an athletic human female, and one hand unconsciously reaches up to feel your small and perky breasts, the other sliding back to your enlarged rear.  You are ready this time when a second set of legs slowly emerge, then another, then more.  You are lifted up as your legs grow, almost ecstatic at your enhanced movement.  You look back and cry out in horror as your beautiful feet squash down into barbed points, and your shapely legs begin to tighten and become more insect-like.  Years of ingrained fear help squash the magic and return you to your regular self.  Barely.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>You are finally ready.  You want to hunt, you want to feed.  The magic comes close and you grab it and feed off its energies, the transformative power flowing through you.  You are a striking human woman before you realise it; beautiful, athletic, and deadly.  Already your legs are growing longer, sharper, as your ass pushes out.  Two more pairs of legs, clearly not human, push out behind your changing limbs, but you don't mind.  They'll help you catch more prey.  Finally the last two legs emerge.  From the waist down you are a spider - born to hunt.  From above your tingling sex you are a beautiful seductress - and you know which half is the deadlier.  You smile, looking around you at all the plentiful sources of energy scurrying away from you and then focus on your opponent.  Perhaps you'll start with that one...</TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>You launch the spell at your opponent.  The magic splits upon contact, and thousands of tiny energy particles run across their body.  They shiver, but quickly disperse the magic.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>The spell hits you opponent again.  Again the energy splits, crawling across their body, getting under their clothes, into their hair.  There must have been an effect, because they are looking strangely at their legs.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>Your opponent almost dodges the spell, but it bends at the last second, finding its prey like a hunter.  Your opponent looks surprised, his eyes widening as he reaches up to his chest to feel the breasts appearing there.  You smile at his improved appearance before he screams and falls on the ground, clawing at his rear.  Just before he gets the magic under control, you see two extra limbs trying to force their way out. </TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>The other 'caster is flung to the ground by the force of your spell.  It seems to bind him, surround him, trap him like a little fly in a web.  The magic is absorbed by his changing body, and you are pleased to see breasts appear on his thrashing chest, as his waist shrinks down.  His hips suddenly swell and you watch as two more legs appear from behind.  In the blink of an eye he is back on his feet - all four of them.  Even his new breasts can't distract him from the extra limbs, and with a cry he slowly reverses the spell.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>Your opponent actually jumps in the air and catches the spell before it can hit him.  He starts playing with it, making strange patterns as it is absorbed.  His hands fly straight to his chest, anticipating his breasts' return.  He smiles and seems to be lifted into the air as two, then four, then six new legs appear out of his... her?.. swelling rear.  Her face changes, gaining a predatory look as her features become sharp, yet very feminine.  She looks behind her as her legs crack and start forming points.  Something primitive in her mind snaps and she screams, forcing herself to return back to being a man.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>There is no resistance this time.  Your opponent's mind exists only for the hunt.  The spell hits him, and almost instantly transforms him into a beautiful seductress, complete with perky breasts, an athletic waist, and toned legs.  Her ass seems too big for her body, though, and it is still growing.  It eventually balloons out as a second set of legs grow out of it, then two more, until she is standing tall on eight legs.  You're not sure where she produced it from, but she is suddenly holding a ball of silk, making intricate patterns with it as her legs turn chitinous, her feet turning to barbed points as silky hair grows along their length.  The creature - half beautiful woman, half giant spider - looks over at you and smiles.  Perhaps it's time to run? </TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>You launch the spell at your opponent.  The magic splits upon contact, and thousands of tiny energy particles run across their body.  They shiver, but quickly disperse the magic.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>The spell hits you opponent again.  Again the energy splits, crawling across their body, getting under their clothes, into their hair.  There must have been an effect, because they are looking strangely at their legs.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>Your opponent almost dodges the spell, but it bends at the last second, finding its prey like a hunter.  She looks surprised, her eyes widening as she graps her waist, which becomes slim and toned as you watch.  You smile at her improved appearance before she screams and falls to the ground, clawing at her rear.  Just before she gets the magic under control, you see two extra limbs trying to force their way out. </TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>The other 'caster is flung to the ground by the force of your spell.  It seems to bind her, surround her, trap her like a little fly in a web.  The magic is absorbed by her changing body, and you watch as her body changes to an athletic human's.  Her hips suddenly swell and you watch as two more legs appear from behind.  In the blink of an eye she is back on her feet - all four of them.  The different movement causes her to look back, and with a cry she returns herself to normal.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>Your opponent actually jumps in the air and catches the spell before it can hit her.  She starts playing with it, making strange patterns as it is absorbed.  She smiles as she is lifted higher into the air as two, then four, then six new legs appear out of  her swelling rear.  Her face changes, gaining a predatory look as her features become sharp, yet very feminine.  She looks behind her as her legs crack and start forming points.  Something primitive in her mind snaps and she screams, forcing herself to return back to normal.  You start to question whether this line of spellcasting is a good idea...</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>There is no resistance this time.  Your opponent's mind is now just on the hunt.  The spell hits her, and almost instantly transforms her into a beautiful seductress, complete with perky breasts, an athletic waist, and toned legs.  Her ass seems too big for her body, though, and it is still growing.  It eventually balloons out as a second set of legs grow out of it, then two more, until eventually she is standing tall on eight legs.  You're not sure where she produced it from, but she is suddenly holding a ball of silk, making intricate patterns with it as her legs turn chitinous, her feet turning to barbed points as silky hair grows along their length.  The creature - half beautiful woman, half giant spider - looks over at you and smiles.  Perhaps it's time to run? </TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>

</Form>
