<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<Description>You are a pair of plain pink panties made out of a smooth, silky fabric.  Your design is plain, designed for comfort instead of sexiness.  When you are being worn you feel your owner's crotch up against you, sweet sweat and the occasional sexual fluid--not always belonging to your wearer!--delicious against your taste buds.</Description>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>For a moment the hairs on your arms retract, your flesh itself starting to flush a silky pink.  You rub your fingers over it... very smooth and somewhat worrying.  You manage to reverse the effects without any trouble.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>You feel your legs weaken and nearly fall to the ground.  You see your legs growing thin and limp like strips of cloth, the silky pink texture returning.  Luckily you're able to reverse it before losing your balance.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>You fall to the ground, clutching your legs as they shrink into two elastic straps.  Your fingers begin to melt together into elastic bands as well, but you're able to muster the energy to reverse the changes.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>Both your arms and legs begin to shrivel, turning into elastic straps dangling from your torso.  Your entire chest has turned pink and silky and you feel your body starting to collapse in on itself.  It takes some effort, but you do manage to reverse the changes.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>This time your entire body is almost fully overwhelmed by the transformation magic.  Your limbs retreat into your torso while the torso itself begins to collapse from the shoulders down to the hipline.  You are a bundle of silky red cloth, nearly fully transformed, when you are finally able to overcome and slowly reverse the effects.  Next time, though...</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>You collapse, your willpower and energy drained, as your entire body withdraws to your hips.  Your vision goes dark as your face melts into what was once your crotch, leaving you lying flat on the ground, a pair of plain, silky panties at the mercy of whoever picks you up.  You inwardly sigh.  This is your new life.  You'd better prepare to get used to the smell of crotch.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>Your target's arms begin to turn silky and red, clothlike in its appearance and texture.  They are able to reverse the changes easily.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>Your target stumbles as their legs begin to wane thin and limp like strips of cloth, the skin turning pink and silky.  They do not fall and is able to reverse the changes.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>Your target falls to the ground as their legs shrink into elastic straps circling around his thighs.  Their fingers begin to melt into elastic straps but he is able to reverse the changes before any further changes occur.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Both your target's arms and legs withdraw into their torso.  Their entire chest has turned pink and silky, just starting to collapse from the shoulders down to the hipline.  However, your target is able to reverse the changes with great difficulty.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Your target collapses, their arms and legs shrinking into elastic straps as their torso collapses down to the hipline, leaving behind a bundle of silky red cloth vaguely in the shape of panties.  Astonishingly, your target is still able to muster enough energy to reverse the effects, but you suspect they may not be able to pull it off again.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>Your target collapses, their willpower and energy drained, as their entire body shrinks down to pair of plain, pink panties.  You wait for a second but nothing happens.  It seems your target is stuck this way for good, just waiting to be integrated into someone's underwear drawer...</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
