<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<Description>This sneaky rat boasts a mischievous grin and a twinkle in his eye. He twitches at even the scent of coin and will stop 
at nothing to fuel his insatiable hunger for it. His deft paws allowing him to succeed where others would alert 
suspicion. His fur dark as the night making the shadows a natural friend of his. Despite his thievish behavior he is 
quite handsome for a rat. He has a face that could charm even his greatest enemies. His body is well toned and supple.</Description>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>As the spell washes over you the affects aren't quite noticeable. Though as you try to look about you then notice your 
eyes can now look in different then one another at once. Before you know it they shift back to normal as the spell 
disperses.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>The spell rushes through your form leaving you feeling a bit more agile. You nearly slump over and lose your balance as 
you feel a rat tail shoot out from your back end. These affects don't last long and quickly diminishes.
</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>Spell power rushes through your form, your entire form is then covered with midnight black fur and your face elongates 
with your new rat snout, leaving you with a handsome twitching nose. Just as the fur is getting comfy the spell loses 
structure and reverts.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>The magic ball crashes against your face instantly turning your face into that of a handsome rat. Round ears forming 
against your head as the changes continue through your body. Furred up and tail wagging behind you. The spell doesn't 
seem to be slowing down so you quickly counter it before you are consumed by this form.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>Magic energy courses through you and your entire form gives into the sensation. Your body now taking the form of an 
anthropomorphic rat standing upon two large feet. You think the changes are done and over with when you suddenly get the craving for valuables. And not just any valuables, but ones that others posses. Your mind struggles against itself but you successfully make the connection that your mind set is being adjusted and quickly cast a counter spell before your intentions won't allow it.
</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>Your body surrenders itself as the last spell crashes into you. In a blink of an eye you are left with the body of a 
handsome rat. Your eyes shift around as if searching for something as your mind melds at the mercy of the spell. You 
soon find yourself wanting. No, needing valuables! Its out there, all you need to do is get your grubby paws on it. 
Your handsome rat face forms a grin and you are then lost in thought about becoming the greatest thief before searching for the nearest shadow to plot your master plan.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>You land your spell against your target leaving them confused as their eyes glaze over into that of a rat's. The spell 
soon diminishes and the change washes away.
</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>As your spell connects with your target it makes them stumble about at the immediate changes. They nearly trip over 
their own rat tail before the spell can dissipate.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>You feel good about your progress thus far as when your target is struck by your spell their entire form poofs out with 
black fur and a ratlike face. in time you think you will have yourself an efficient thief on your hands!</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>You slam that magical force against their face, changing their head into that of a rat. It doesn't stop just there and 
it works along their form, flushing them out into more and more of a rat before your eyes. They grow worried of it and 
counter it before it's too late.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>You blast your target with a wave or magical energy, their form quickly taking one of a rat's. You smile as you look 
over the handsome rat, feeling sure that ought to do it when he seems to be having second guesses. His mind doesn't 
seem to alter correctly and he forces himself back out of his rat body.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>Confident in your abilities you wrack your target's body with a powerful blast of magical energy. They can do nothing 
but yield to your power as it courses through them, turning them completely into that of a rather handsome rat. You 
stand before him as he seems to be lost in his mind, paws fiddling about as his eyes dart about. He then scurries off 
into the darkness. If you've done your spell correctly you should see some valuables in the near future... If not, 
better hold onto your belongings before they walk away from you!</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
