<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>You watch as the attackers finger glows a beam of light striking your body as you start to feel just a bit tingly. Your body starts to heat up ever so slightly as you feel a bit, sluggish, and as you look downwards you could swear that your body seemed to harden just a bit and glow with a shine that isn't natural. But a moment later you shake your head and the feeling clears as your body resurges with magical energy and you reverse the spell!</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>Another beam of light hits you as the attacker utters some incoherent babble, or it sounds like it anyways at you. The beam strikes your chest and bounces back at the attacker as more of your energy is drained, their body glowing with the stolen energy. This time when you look down at yourself, you definitely see your skin hardening, a shine in your arms and legs as the clothes you are wearing seem to disappear for a moment leaving you naked. A moment or so later though you work up the energy to reverse the spell and as you look down sweating you see that your skin is back to normal and clothes reappeared upon your person.
</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>A strange thing happens this time as you are hit by the spell again. Your eyes looking straight ahead would find that ... the attacker isn't quite so evenly matched in height with you anymore, your eyes somewhere down at their chest/stomach area. Clothes definitely gone as the tingling sensation spreads through your body again, arms shrunken down considerably until they just rest outside of your torso. Your legs start pushing together, fusing briefly before your eyes widen and you surge with energy again dispelling this foreign attack though this time you are really starting to feel drained.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>This again? God this spell was giving you a massive headache, the attackers fingers glowing as purple soul energy drains from your body to the attacker, you find yourself really looking up at the other now as in addition to your arms pulling in almost completely, your legs would be fusing together, causing you to fall to the ground as your body stiffens and hardens from the waist down forming a gem like consistency, legs coming to a point. Wide eyed once more you furiously fight back the spell and slowly regain your limbs and clothes but its getting harder and harder to resist with the attacker draining your energy.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>Agh, again you are hit by the spell, a steady beam of purple light draining from your belly as you continue shrinking down even further, falling to the ground on your side, legs fused together into the bottom half of a crystal as your arms fully pull inside that torso. Upper half wise, your shoulders would be pointed edges as your neck thickens and head comes to a point, that headache really coming to a climax here, more migraine like as you look up from the ground at your attacker, almost finished by the spell but through some miracle you manage to dispel it, unsure if you could really fend it off one last time.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>With a grin, you watch your attacker cast the spell one final time. Your body rapidly shrinking and forming back down into the crystal form it'd been slowly being shaped into. Your arms and legs completely gone, head pulled inwards against your torso and pointed to the very tip of the crystal as your body tingles with energy, all of your inner soul causing your purple crystal self to glow and you feel your body starting to levitate up and around your attacker who with a simple bit of concentration could tap into your reserves whenever they wished. And at this point, with your mind so drained of energy and soul you could think of nothing better then to help them by giving them whatever you can!</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>Your target is hit dead center of their chest . They let out a gasp as their body starts to drain of its soul energy and you feel a bit stronger as their skin takes on the slightest hue of purple on their arms and legs. But other then that they just seem a bit winded... For now.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>Your spell hits the target again, sucking more of their soul energy from them to feed your own as that purple hue definitely takes over more of their body, which you can see as the clothing temporarily disappears. Their chest arms and legs taking on a rather low shine as you see them start to shrink somewhat, down from eye level to maybe about your chest.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>You hit the target again and this time they'd really start to shrink downwards, their eyes down near your chest as the purplish hue is all over their face, arms legs and chest. Their legs are starting to fuse together giving them an awkward standing position as well as their arms slowly shrinking inwards against their sides. A bit of sweat trickling down their still normal head over their hardening torso/ lower body.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Upon hitting the spell this time, you'd find the target shrunken down to about your knee caps, their arms completely pulled into their sides and just a few feet beneath the underside of their pointed lower body. Their eyes are wide, and slowly widening as for a second as their upper half starts to point upwards into the upper half of a crystal, neck shrunken in almost completely as a head sits atop the point at the top.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>This casting of the spell sends them to their sides as the feet disappear from beneath the crystal giving them no way to balance they topple over onto the ground. Looking up at you with their head still just barely atop the point of the crystal as their arms are completely gone and body shaped into a small purple crystal with quite a bit of shine and glow to it.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>Finally, the spell manages to stick this time as you watch the beam hit the target. Slowly your energy starts to flow through them as their own energy levitates them around your body, orbiting your torso and glowing purple with their soul energy. Upon concentrating, you find that you can tap into their energy any time you like to supplement your own!</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
