<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<Description>This isn’t where you had expected to be later in life; a pair of light white socks, knee high in length, perfect for complimenting uniforms and exercising, your light patterned fabric breathing easily, never allowing your owner to become hot or sweaty. The feeling of being worn more than makes up for it, caressing every inch of their long legs and tickling their toes, orgasmic pleasure filling you with every step. It could be worse...</Description>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>Your opponent produces a flame within their hand, the level of heat radiating off its small surface enough for you to feel it from a distance. You wait with tightened nerves, ready to dive out of the way of such a lethal projectile. Instead, the flame continues to grow, dropping from his hand and forming a bonfire, fueled by nothing more than the magic in the area, draining both you and your opponent. They seem worn by their actions, the magic draining their energy whilst you hastily reverse the spell, quickly siphoning it off into you. This welcome boost in energy allows you to destroy the flame with a flick of your hand, canceling the spell.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>They create the flame once again, though you can’t fathom why; all it seems to do is assist you, filling you with so much energy you’re practically vibrating upon the spot. Your nerves are alight, especially in your legs, your senses confused over how soft your skin has become, a pair of strange red bands marking your thighs. You ignore these sensations and begin to work on a counter spell to banish the fire once again, hopping from one foot to the other in an attempt to concentrate, the excess energy filling your mind with a desire to exercise. It isn’t enough to break your focus and banish the fire once again, however.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>Your heart is beating a mile a minute, shivering and shaking with such force that you begin to jog on the spot, stretching and exercising in an effort to remove this outlandish amount of energy filling your form from that beautiful fire. You can’t concentrate for long enough to begin to cancel your opponents spell, mind driven by the one thought of exercise. As you touch your toes, (When were you this flexible?) the strange feeling of softness is enough to distract you from your madness and look upon your feet. They have become an off white, toes merging into one shape as a form of fabric has begun to replace your skin, all the way up to your thighs where they are bordered by two bands of red. They seem only partially formed, the magic yet to concentrate long enough to truly affect you. Using this chain of thought is enough to drive a wedge in the spell affecting you, breaking the chain all the way to the fire.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>It’s too much. At this rate, you’re going to have a heart attack, you simply cannot burn it up quickly enough. You feel hollow, empty, drained and filled at the same time, brimming with energy, and yet you can’t shake the feelings of lethargy. The sock pattern has become more distinct, allowing you to see that it isn’t a plain white, but a form of patterned lace design. The thought that these are your legs you are speaking about doesn’t arrive, merely the curiosity at your new sock feet. They seem thicker now, the magic bonds more tightly woven into your skin. The rest of you seems to pale in comparison, as if you were lesser somehow, more indistinct. Each stretch, each push up seems to highlight them further as your arms grow weaker. For a moment you collapse to the floor briefly, incapable of supporting your weight, but giving you long enough to create the wedge once again, breaking the chain, though you cannot keep this level of pace up forever.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>A thought strikes you mid sit up as you stretch your silky legs forward, enjoying the feeling of touching and rubbing them together. In hindsight, that fire was stronger than you anticipated, filling you with a burning desire to exercise off this unnatural energy, but the flow ceased long ago. Whatever energy you’re burning off now, it is your own. You can feel yourself becoming indistinct, spirit and magic merging with the long socks you are quickly becoming. They already feel hollow, maintaining their shape but with nothing beneath them. The feeling of rubbing your new feet is inexplicable, like a body wide sensation of pleasure, the sensation of squeezing their hollow form alluring and somehow comforting, though not as much as being worn. Being.. worn? The shock from this sudden thought awakes you from your daze, realising with a start that you have fully transformed, lying on the ground at their feet. Before your opponent can pick you up, you struggle for life and movement, forcing the magic from your body.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>The fire bursts into life before your eyes, its shifting form mesmerising what is left of your already addled mind. Images seem to swirl on its surface, patterns forming and changing, only staying for the briefest of moments to imprint itself within your mind. “Star jumps” It seems to whisper, a pair of socks jumping high in the pattern. Your limbs feel sluggish and weak, but this isn’t about what you want anymore, it’s about what the fire wants, and it wants you to exercise. Beginning is difficult, but once you start, the struggle seems to fade. Each jump you feel lighter, your toes merging into one on the second jump, feet losing distinction on the third. “Work off that energy of yours.” The crooning voice gloats, “You don’t need anything more than your new form.” It sound smug, an absurd thought considering it is a fire, but it knows it has won nonetheless. You’re lighter than ever before, each jump far higher than you could have done before this wonderful spell began to affect you, beautifully whitening your skin into a light patterned cotton. This spell must be really affecting you, as you swear the ground is getting closer with each jump.You try to swing your arms to counteract this unusual sensation, but they have little affect, now little more than hollow tubes slowly absorbing themselves into your sides. You’re too busy focusing upon this recent development to land properly and you stumble, your hollow legs no longer able to support you as the rest of your torso collapses into the socks, your last sight before your head opens up like a ripe melon into two openings for their feet is your opponent, standing tall on their long legs, just waiting to be decorated by you..</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>You concentrate your will, no, your desire to transform your opponent into a spell, a flame bursting into life before you, a physical manifestation of your thoughts and magic. Your opponent seems confused, still ready to dodge or reflect a spell back. Using this time wisely, you quickly fuel it with your growing lust at the images of a nice pair of socks in your head, establishing the link between this extension of your mind and your opponent opponent. The spell and its effect begin to take root, but it is only active for a short time before your opponent banishes it with a flick of their wrist, fueled by the very fire they destroyed.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>You quickly reestablish the fire, its recent castings allowing you to recreate it with significantly less effort, the link attaching itself to your victim. You begin to whisper into their mind -  “Fuel the spell. Give in. Don’t fight back” - hypnotic suggestions being heard on one level or another in their mind. They’re jittering and jiving, the mistaken sense of excess energy clearly driving them mad. You can just about see the faint red lines marking their legs now before they banish the fire yet again.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>The suggestions are clearly working, as your opponent is practically dancing on the spot before you have even created the fire. It must be maddening, especially when that “excess energy” is in actuality your body, turning it into their new form by their own hand. Your opponent has begun to exercise, mind driven almost to the brink of madness by what you have done to them, leaving your opponent completely unaware as they begin to shrink, skin lightening into a bright white cotton as their toes merge together, resembling the end of a sock, something you can’t wait to put your feet into. You have no idea what your opponent is seeing as they are transforming, or if they can even see it at all, red bands marking their thighs before an ice pick of pain pierces your skull, the fire fading quickly as you realise they cut the link rather than the source.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>This time you decide to add more whispers to your current suggestions, just so that you cover all of your bases - “Socks. Long legs. School girls in short skirts, Mary Janes underneath you..” - Their mind snaps, you can feel it from here, madness driving them into a fit of energy as they burn more of their form, revealing their new shape underneath. Your opponent is losing mass quickly, legs fully resembling socks from the knees down, the rest of their body slowly sinking into these points, forming the rest. Your opponent stretches outwards for a moment and you can clearly see through them, their fabric so light now that they stumble, hollow sock feet incapable of supporting their (rather light) weight. You catch a brief glimpse of your victim's desperate face as it begins to sink into the fabric before they desperately shout, catching the right spell in time and reversing their sockification, much to your annoyance.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>The spell has to succeed this time, you’re sure of it. Your opponent has been driven so mad by your suggestions you haven’t even created the fire, merely cast the spell for the transformation. Their flexibility is impressive you can't help but notice as they bend almost fully backwards, now completely hollow, merely a thin patterned fabric in the shape of a person, though not for much longer from the rate that they are collapsing into their legs, fabric wrapping around an invisible limb, forming the socks. Your opponent is able to maintain their balance for a while longer than before, though this is likely because they are completely hollow now, face nothing more than an impression, as if they were pressing their faces against the fabric from the inside. Much to your relief, it quickly fades away, the spot where the face had been replaced by two red bands at the top of the socks. They slowly topple to the floor, wiggling erratically like some form of absurd snake, or a sock puppet, now that you think about it. This “sock puppet” still has enough salt in its craw to change back too it seems, much to your annoyance. They erratically wave around as the magic is slowly dispelled, arms pressing out of the sides and lifting themselves up, the magic leaking away.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>It was fun whilst it lasted, but you aren’t interested in watching your opponent recover their form again. A small amount of hypnotising may be in order. Whilst idly casting the transformation spell for your new socks, already dismissing them as an opponent; they’re simply too distracted to fight you anymore, you cast a brief glance in their direction to confirm your reservations; your socks are too busy performing sit ups to even register you anymore. The fire burns within, only taking a slight amount of concentration for it to burst into life before your opponents eyes, their face hanging slack at its light. You aren’t quite sure what they are seeing in the fire, or even what they are hearing; the fire is no longer a part of you, but its own separate entity. Your opponent dances in the light of the fire, graceful shadows becoming twisted and strange as they begin to change, arms disappearing into their sides, the shadow gracefully jumping and skipping through the air as the torso becomes tubular, matching the rest of its now soft and bright white form. Your opponent.. no, your new socks jump one final time, moaning with delight and relief as their head disappears, opening up into two holes for you to slide your long legs into, its surface now marked by two bright red bands. The last sight you see of their original form is their eyes, staring at you as they fall to the floor, nothing more than a pair of cotton socks.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
