<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>The ground darkens beneath you, shadows collecting and forming in a wide circle. You quickly jump out of its perimeter, feeling only a slight tickling sensation as a shadow reaches out and brushes your foot, darkening before the magic dispels itself.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>The ground darkens beneath you, shadows collecting and forming a wide circle. You attempt to jump out of its range, but the spell roots you in place, you feet frozen to the spot. Quickly, the shadows coalesce on your feet, binding them in an unusual black haze. Despite the severity of the situation, you involuntarily giggle as it tickles, your feet losing sensation as your toes form into one solid mass. The tickling only increases and you close your eyes, hands covering your mouth. As soon as it begun, it is over. You open one eye again, a darting glance at the ground. What... you... it created a pair of shoes? You reach down and brush the sides, shivering with pleasure at the touch. No, these aren't just shoes. Your feet have flattened, now resembling a pair of women's flats. You banish the spell quickly with a swish of your hand.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>You instinctively jump as your opponent casts the spell once again, but it is fruitless. The shadows beneath you dart upwards, wrapping around your feet even as they transform into women's shoes again. The landing feels odd, your now leather feet/shoes capable of feeling through the hard sole, all of it very much a part of you. This time the spell doesn't simply fade away however, the black colouring spreading across your ankles and what is left of your visible foot in a thin band. Your unaffected skin begins to turn a pale white, becoming a light fabric. A feeling of looseness washes over you as it feels as if you are shrinking, your heels rising as it gains a one inch wedge heel, a strap forming across the front and a cute bow flourishing on the front as more of your mass is used to create the shoes! You shake your feet quickly, sensations returning as it fades.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>Your feet are practically a homing beacon, the magical shadows shooting from your opponents hands flying directly towards you at breakneck speed. You hold up an arm, gazing in wonder and horror at your new skin, a white patterned fabric, lace collecting along your edges in a pattern. Pressing a hand against one arm, you almost jump when it depresses inwards, revealing your now hollow nature. Your mild revelry is broken when you realise you were moaning at your touch, blushing at having forgotten you are being attacked. Your shoes/feet are not affected by this lightness, no, they have become much heavier as more of you are in them. They no longer resemble a pair of little girl's school shoes, now sporting a three inch heel and pointed front. You hadn't even noticed the shift in balance, too busy with your new cotton skin. The effort to dispel is apparent, straining yourself to purge the magic from your body.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>The magic doesn't hold you in place, at least not directly. Your now heavy feet weigh you down, your body now completely hollow and rapidly shrinking, filling the insides of the shoes with your cotton white embrace. The silk still remains erratic across your surface, but this hardly matters now. You're confused, your sense of sight now coming from all angles, capable of seeing from any part of the shoes. Mild vertigo sensations affect what is left of your stomach as the heel grows higher, using your body as fuel for the magic. Four inches now, you resemble a pair of strappy Mary Janes, sleek and feminine, now paired with the rest of your body which has become a pair of socks, you realise with a start. You wiggle in place, resembling a strange white worm as you slowly remove the magic, piece by piece.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>This time you make a half hearted attempt to run rather than jump, but your rising heels causes you to stumble, feet already resembling a pair of five inch high heels. Pleasure emanates from what passes for your shoes... you mean fe.. no... shoes.. You try to raise your arms to slap yourself, but they seem to have disappeared, absorbed into your tube shape. You sigh in relief that it is over, mouth widening considerably as it becomes the hole for your owners feet. The lace collects properly this time, forming a ring around the top of you, a lace crown for what can only be the most feminine of shoes you have ever seen. You smile inside, knowing you're at the top, even now....</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>The spell is slow. You cannot simply throw the energy at your target, dark tendrils escaping from your hands and spiraling towards them, collecting on the ground. They look surprised for a moment then simply jump away, the spell half heartedly reaching for them before it dispels itself. Were their feet darker for a moment?</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>Directional efforts are pointless if the spell will resolve that for you. You raise your hands this time, releasing the magic into the air, shooting forward in a rapid stream, twenty or so of those unusual black snakes. Your target doesn't seem to expect it to suddenly grip them before they can jump again, the outer rim closing inwards as they coat your opponent's feet. The circle quickly disappears into them, your target now appearing to wear a pair of women's flat shoes. Oh, but they aren't. No, they are very much a part of them..</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>They jump into the air at the first opportunity, but the spell knows the game. It doesn't head towards the floor first, instead targeting the feet directly. By the time your target lands, they are already "wearing" the flat shoes again. They stumble on the fall, a confused look upon their face as they scratch their arms then staring at their pale white skin. You can already see through them slightly, the thin fabric that now composes their upper body a light silk, the excess mass pouring into the spell as the black magic eagerly drinks it up. Their shoes writhe as a cute wedge heel forms and a bow on the front, now resembling the perfect pair of Mary Janes. But you aren't going to stop so soon, not until they are every fetishist's dream...</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>They jitter and jive, desperate to avoid any further confrontation with the spells building effects. It is to no avail however, their feet acting as a homing beacon for this spell. This time it is much stronger, the heel rising as it gains another two inches, now a respectable pair of three inch Mary Janes. Your opponent doesn't seem to notice your efforts however, too busy stroking their new silk skin and moaning, hardly noticing how hollow and empty they have become so that the spell has material to work with. The target has shrunk too, becoming far smaller in their torso whilst their legs remain unaffected by this change. They desperately concentrate to ignore the pleasure and dispel the effects.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Their body lurches as if trying to jump, but the spell had already struck them, their feet becoming heavier than the rest of their weight put together. You can easily see why, and so can they now; they're completely hollow and in the process of shrinking, arms sinking into their sides as they become a simple pair of bobby socks. The spell almost sounds pleased at the new events, the heel finally rising to a full five inches, shiny black leather style with sleek curves, a perfect pair of shoes for such socks. Not quite however, noticing that the socks maintain the resemblance of a small white person standing in the new five inch heels, waving their tube shaped body until the magic is dispelled. </TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>Your target doesn't even attempt to jump, simply turning on their heels and running. And heel would be the key element in this statement. Smirking at their effort, the target's feet rising and legs slimming into a sexy pair of high heels and what could be mistaken for stockings, if the affliction did not appear across their entire body. They try to turn, but they're too far gone, arms collapsing into their sides and shrinking rapidly. The last look on their face is one of relief and almost happiness, mouth becoming the opening to the pair of socks which now inhabit those Mary Janes. As a final touch, the lace trimming finally collects together, forming a ring around the top of the socks, fulfilling their complete role as a pair of bobby socks and high heels.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
