<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>Your enemy's spell strikes you in the abdomen, but its first effects are not felt there. A sudden cramping in your toes alerts you to something happening down below. The cramp moves swiftly up the arch of your foot, forcing your heel to rise off the ground. You feel your toes fusing together, the nails merging into… cloven hooves? An itching sensation travels up your new, digitigrade lower legs as coarse, grayish brown fur springs forth. With a frown, you dispel the effects and return your legs to normal.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>On the next cast your opponent hits your knee. You feel the magic rippling outward from the impact as your feet once more turn into the cloven hooves of some beast, the gray-brown fur racing more quickly up your legs than before. The fur passes your knee this time, reaching as far as mid-thigh. As you move to reverse the changes you hesitate, distracted momentarily by the sudden warmth of arousal building in your loins. Shaking off the distraction, you quickly restore your legs to normal.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>Your opponent strikes low again, this time hitting you in the crotch. Heat ripples outward from the point of impact, sudden, overpowering arousal almost bringing you to your knees. You barely notice this time as the transformation progresses rapidly up your legs, leaving in its wake a pair of furry, cloven-hoofed limbs. As the changes reach your crotch, a penis springs to full attention (wait, was that there before?), further befuddling your lust-addled mind. Embarrassed, you hastily conceal the evidence of your arousal with both hands, but the raging beast is too big for you to hide completely. To your relief, the fur stops at your waist. You quickly dispel the transformation before any further changes begin, restoring your body to normal.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>A burst of magic strikes dead center of your chest as your opponent attacks again. Unbridled lust dulls your wits, forcing a moan from your lips as your eyes glaze over. The spreading magic leaves your chest muscularly sculpted and broad, a not unwelcome development. However, it doesn't quite compensate for the furry, beast-like legs that dominate your body from the waist down. A seething erection again forces its way into view, driving away any concerns you had about your legs. Is it bigger than before, or is that just your imagination? Fascinated, you can't help but caress the tumescent organ, appreciating its power. Feeling pressure toward the back of your skull, your reach up just as a pair of ribbed horns grow out of your head, curling to spiral around your ears. Ram's horns? Are you turning into a goat-man? With some effort, you manage to suppress the unnatural lust and reverse the changes to your body… but you're starting to wonder if you really want to.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>As your attacker's next cast slams into your torso, you realize, perversely enough, that you are actually looking forward to it. Your body, already suffused with the spell's energy, swiftly returns to the half-man, half-goat form to which you are growing far too accustomed. You lift one of your legs, admiring the cloven hoof at the end, and feel a sudden urge to caper across a meadow. That impulse is driven from your thoughts as your cock swells to life again, overwhelming your mind with urges of a far more carnal nature. Your gaze wanders, searching the vicinity for any creature with an empty orifice that might serve to satiate the needs of a horny goat-man. And then it strikes you - you're becoming a Satyr! From your cloven hooves to the curled horns atop your head, you now have the form of a lusty goat-man of myth. Panic surges in your chest, giving you enough presence of mind to shake off the arousal clouding your mind and reverse the changes before it is too late.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>You know what's coming, and this time you don't even flinch as your opponent's magic envelopes you. Now saturated with transformation energy, your body reverts to the form of a Satyr in a matter of seconds, sadly affording you little time to appreciate the changes. Then the lust hits you, washing away any petty thoughts or worries unrelated to copulation. Feeling suddenly free of all moral constraints, you skip around on your hooves with wild abandon, eager to embrace your new existence as a free spirit. Your cock, bouncing between your thighs, stiffens and demands your attention. Ah, yes. Your cock. You need to find something to fuck. Now, where did that other spellcaster run off to?</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>Your enemy's spell strikes you in the abdomen, but its first effects are not felt there. A sudden cramping in your toes alerts you to something happening down below. The cramping moves swiftly up the arch of your foot, forcing your heel to rise off the ground. You feel your toes fusing together, the nails merging into… cloven hooves? An itching sensation travels up your new, digitigrade lower legs as grayish brown fur springs forth. With a frown, you dispel the effects and return your legs to normal.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>On the next cast your opponent hits your knee. You feel the magic rippling outward from the impact as your feet once more turn into the cloven hooves of some beast, the gray-brown fur racing more quickly up your legs than before. The fur passes your knee this time, reaching as far as mid-thigh. As you move to reverse the changes you hesitate, distracted momentarily by the sudden warmth of arousal as your cock stiffens to attention. Shaking off the distraction, you quickly restore your legs to normal.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>Your opponent strikes low again, this time hitting you in the crotch. Heat ripples outward from the point of impact, sudden, overpowering arousal almost bringing you to your knees. You barely notice this time as the transformation progresses rapidly up your legs, leaving in its wake a pair of furry, cloven-hoofed limbs. As the changes reach your crotch, your penis becomes almost painfully erect, further befuddling your lust-addled mind. Embarrassed, you hastily conceal the evidence of your arousal with both hands, but the raging beast is too big for you to hide completely. To your relief, the fur stops at your waist. You quickly dispel the transformation before any further changes begin, restoring your body to normal.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>A burst of magic strikes dead center of your chest as your opponent attacks again. Unbridled lust dulls your wits, forcing a moan from your lips as your eyes glaze over. The spreading magic leaves your chest muscularly sculpted and broad, a not unwelcome development. However, it doesn't quite compensate for the furry, beast-like legs that dominate your body from the waist down. A seething erection again forces its way into view, driving away any concerns you had about your legs. Is it bigger than before, or is that just your imagination? Fascinated, you can't help but caress the tumescent organ, appreciating its power. Feeling pressure toward the back of your skull, your reach up just as a pair of ribbed horns grow out of your head, curling to spiral around your ears. Ram's horns? Are you turning into a goat-man? With some effort, you manage to suppress the unnatural lust and reverse the changes to your body… but you're starting to wonder if you really want to.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>As your attacker's next cast slams into your torso, you realize, perversely enough, that you are actually looking forward to it. Your body, already suffused with the spell's energy, swiftly returns to the half-man, half-goat form to which you are growing far too accustomed. You lift one of your legs, admiring the cloven hoof at the end, and feel a sudden urge to caper across a meadow. That impulse is driven from your thoughts as your cock swells to life again, overwhelming your mind with urges of a far more carnal nature. Your gaze wanders, searching the vicinity for any creature with an empty orifice that might serve to satiate the needs of a horny goat-man. And then it strikes you - you're becoming a Satyr! From your cloven hooves to the curled horns atop your head, you now have the form of a lusty goat-man of myth. Panic surges in your chest, giving you enough presence of mind to shake off the arousal clouding your mind and reverse the changes before it is too late.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>You know what's coming, and this time you don't even flinch as your opponent's magic envelopes you. Now saturated with transformation energy, your body reverts to the form of a Satyr in a matter of seconds, sadly affording you little time to appreciate the changes. Then the lust hits you, washing away any petty thoughts or worries unrelated to copulation. Feeling suddenly free of all moral constraints, you skip around on your hooves with wild abandon, eager to embrace your new existence as a free spirit. Your cock, bouncing between your thighs, stiffens and demands your attention. Ah, yes. Your cock. You need to find something to fuck. Now, where did that other spellcaster run off to?</TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>Your enemy's spell strikes you in the abdomen, but its first effects are not felt there. A sudden cramping in your toes alerts you to something happening down below. The cramping moves swiftly up the arch of your foot, forcing your heel to rise off the ground. You feel your toes fusing together, the nails merging into… cloven hooves? An itching sensation travels up your new, digitigrade lower legs as grayish brown fur springs forth. With a frown, you dispel the effects and return your legs to normal.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>On the next cast your opponent hits your knee. You feel the magic rippling outward from the impact as your feet once more turn into the cloven hooves of some beast, the gray-brown fur racing more quickly up your legs than before. The fur passes your knee this time, reaching as far as mid-thigh. As you move to reverse the changes you hesitate, distracted momentarily by the sudden warmth of arousal building deep within your sex. Shaking off the distraction, you quickly restore your legs to normal.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>Your opponent strikes low again, this time hitting you in the crotch. Heat ripples outward from the point of impact, sudden, overpowering arousal almost bringing you to your knees. You barely notice as the transformation progresses rapidly up your legs, leaving behind a pair of furry, cloven-hoofed limbs. As the changes reach your crotch, a disconcerting tugging sensation on your labia draws your gaze down. You watch in amazement as your womanhood reshapes itself into a pair of testicles and a penis, which swells to full erection in seconds. Embarrassed, you hastily cover the evidence of your arousal with both hands, trying in vain to shove the raging beast back inside you. To your relief, the fur stops at your waist. You quickly dispel the transformation before any further changes begin, restoring your body to normal.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>A burst of magic strikes dead center of your chest as your opponent attacks again. Unbridled lust dulls your wits, forcing a moan from your lips as your eyes glaze over. To your dismay, the spreading magic deflates your lovely breasts, smoothing out your chest to leave it muscularly sculpted and broad. Of course, the loss of your tits seems trivial alongside the furry, beast-like legs that dominate your body from the waist down. A seething, erect cock again replaces your poor pussy, driving away any concerns you had about your legs. Is it even bigger than before? Fascinated, you can't help but caress the tumescent organ, appreciating its power. Feeling pressure toward the back of your skull, your reach up just as a pair of ribbed horns grow out of your head, curling to spiral around your ears. Ram's horns? Are you turning into a goat-man? With some effort, you manage to suppress the unnatural lust and reverse the changes to your body… but you're starting to wonder if you really want to.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>As your attacker's next cast slams into your torso, you realize, perversely enough, that you are actually looking forward to it. Your body, already suffused with the spell's energy, swiftly returns to the half-man, half-goat form to which you are growing far too accustomed. You lift one of your legs, admiring the cloven hoof at the end, and feel a sudden urge to caper across a meadow. That impulse is driven from your thoughts as your new cock swells to life again, overwhelming your mind with unfamiliar urges of a far more carnal nature. Your gaze wanders, searching the vicinity for any creature with an empty orifice that might serve to satiate the needs of a horny goat-man. And then it strikes you - you're becoming a Satyr! From your cloven hooves to the curled horns atop your head, you now have the form of a lusty goat-man of myth. Panic surges in your chest, giving you enough presence of mind to shake off the arousal clouding your mind and reverse the changes before it is too late.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>You know what's coming, and this time you don't even flinch as your opponent's magic envelopes you. Now saturated with transformation energy, your body reverts to the form of a Satyr in a matter of seconds, sadly affording you little time to appreciate the changes. Then the lust hits you, washing away any petty thoughts or worries unrelated to copulation. Feeling suddenly free of all moral constraints, you skip around on your hooves with wild abandon, eager to embrace your new existence as a free spirit. Your cock, bouncing between your thighs, stiffens and demands your attention. Ah, yes. Your cock. You need to find something to fuck. Now, where did that other spellcaster run off to?</TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>Your spell strikes the enemy in the abdomen, but its first effects are evident much farther down. A troubled expression crosses their face as their feet arch, heels rising off the ground. Their toes fuse together, the nails merging into cloven hooves, as grayish brown fur springs forth and travels up their new, digitigrade lower legs. With a frown, they dispel the effects and return their legs to normal.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>On the next cast you hit your opponent's knee. You watch with satisfaction as their feet once more turn into the cloven hooves of some beast, the gray-brown fur racing more quickly up their legs than before. The fur passes their knees this time, and as it reaches mid-thigh they suddenly seem flushed and distracted. Shaking off the distraction, they quickly restore their legs to normal.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>You strike low again, this time hitting your target in the crotch. They stagger, suddenly weak in the knees and barely seem to notice as the transformation progresses rapidly up their legs, leaving in its wake a pair of furry, cloven-hoofed limbs. As the changes reach their crotch, a penis springs to full attention (wait, was that there before?), further befuddling their lust-addled mind. Clearly embarrassed, they hastily conceal the evidence of their arousal with both hands, but the raging beast is too big for them to hide completely. To your disappointment, the fur stops at their waist.  Before any other changes have a chance to begin they hastily dispel the transformation, restoring their body to normal.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Your next burst of magic strikes dead center of your opponent's chest. Their eyes glaze over, a lusty moan escaping their lips. The spreading magic leaves their chest muscularly sculpted and broad, but still very human. It contrasts nicely with the furry, beast-like legs that dominate their body from the waist down. A seething erection again forces its way into view, even bigger than before, or is that just your wishful thinking? You can't help but smirk as your victim reaches down to caress the tumescent organ in wonder. Their hands suddenly dart to their head, just in time to feel a pair of ribbed horns growing out to either side, curling to spiral around their ears. Ram's horns! They will make a fine goat-man. It appears to take them some effort to overcome their lust, but they manage to reverse the changes to their body.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>As your next cast slams into your victim's torso, they almost seem to embrace it. Their body, already suffused with the spell's energy, swiftly returns to the half-man, half-goat form for which the magic is patterned. They lift one of their legs and seem to admire the cloven hoof at the end. Yet their attention is soon diverted by the impressive cock that swells to life again between their thighs, and the carnal urges it floods into their mind. Their lusty gaze wanders, as if searching the vicinity for some creature with an empty orifice that might serve to satiate the needs of a horny goat-man. For a moment their eyes focus on you, and you resist the urge to flee from your creation, this Satyr drawn straight out of myth. Just then they seem to regain control of themselves, and reverse the changes before it is too late.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>Your target seems to know what's coming, and this time they don't even flinch as your magic envelopes them. Now saturated with transformation energy, their body reverts to the form of a Satyr in a matter of seconds, sadly affording you little time to admire your handiwork. You can see it in their eyes when the lust hits them, washing away any petty thoughts or worries unrelated to copulation. The newly-created Satyr skips around on his hooves with wild abandon, apparently eager to embrace his new existence as a free spirit. His cock, bouncing between his thighs, suddenly stiffens as if preparing for action. He pauses and looks around, a lusty glint in his eyes as he searches for something to… fuck. Maybe you should beat a hasty retreat. Or not.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>Your spell strikes the enemy in the abdomen, but its first effects are evident much farther down. A troubled expression crosses his face as his feet arch, heels rising off the ground. His toes fuse together, the nails merging into cloven hooves, as grayish brown fur springs forth and travels up his new, digitigrade lower legs. With a frown, he dispels the effects and returns his legs to normal.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>On the next cast you hit your opponent's knee. You watch with satisfaction as his feet once more turn into the cloven hooves of some beast, the gray-brown fur racing more quickly up his legs than before. The fur passes his knees this time, and as it reaches mid-thigh he suddenly seem flushed and distracted. To his evident surprise, his cock stiffens to attention. Shaking off the distraction, he quickly restores his legs to normal.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>You strike low again, this time hitting your target in the crotch. He staggers, suddenly weak in the knees and barely seems to notice as the transformation progresses rapidly up his legs, leaving in its wake a pair of furry, cloven-hoofed limbs. As the changes reach his crotch, his penis suddenly stands at full attention, further befuddling his lust-addled mind. Clearly embarrassed, he hastily conceals the evidence of his arousal with both hands, but the raging beast is too big for him to hide completely. To your disappointment, the fur stops at his waist.  Before any other changes have a chance to begin, he hastily dispels the transformation, restoring his body to normal.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>Your next burst of magic strikes dead center of your opponent's chest. His eyes glaze over, a lusty moan escaping his lips. The spreading magic leaves his chest muscularly sculpted and broad, but still very human. It contrasts nicely with the furry, beast-like legs that dominate his body from the waist down. A seething erection again forces its way into view, even bigger than before, or is that just your wishful thinking? You can't help but smirk as your victim reaches down to caress the tumescent organ in wonder. His hands suddenly dart to his head, just in time to feel a pair of ribbed horns growing out to either side, curling to spiral around his ears. Ram's horns! He will make a fine goat-man. It appears to take him some effort to overcome his lust, but he manages to reverse the changes to his body.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>As your next cast slams into your victim's torso, he almost seems to embrace it. His body, already suffused with the spell's energy, swiftly returns to the half-man, half-goat form for which the magic is patterned. He lift one of his legs and seem to admire the cloven hoof at the end. Yet his attention is soon diverted by the impressive cock that swells to life again between his thighs, and the carnal urges it floods into his mind. His lusty gaze wanders, as if searching the vicinity for some creature with an empty orifice that might serve to satiate the needs of a horny goat-man. For a moment his eyes focus on you, and you resist the urge to flee from your creation, this Satyr drawn straight out of myth. Just then he seems to regain control of himself, and reverses the changes before it is too late.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>Your target seems to know what's coming, and this time he doesn't even flinch as your magic envelopes him. Now saturated with transformation energy, his body reverts to the form of a Satyr in a matter of seconds, sadly affording you little time to admire your handiwork. You can see it in his eyes when the lust hits him, washing away any petty thoughts or worries unrelated to copulation. The newly-created Satyr skips around on his hooves with wild abandon, apparently eager to embrace his new existence as a free spirit. His cock, bouncing between his thighs, suddenly stiffens as if preparing for action. He pauses and looks around, a lusty glint in his eyes as he searches for something to… fuck. Maybe you should beat a hasty retreat. Or not.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>Your spell strikes the enemy in the abdomen, but its first effects are evident much farther down. A troubled expression crosses her face as her feet arch, heels rising off the ground. Her toes fuse together, the nails merging into cloven hooves, as grayish brown fur springs forth and travels up her new, digitigrade lower legs. With a frown, she dispels the effects and return her legs to normal.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>On the next cast you hit your opponent's knee. You watch with satisfaction as her feet once more turn into the cloven hooves of some beast, the gray-brown fur racing more quickly up her legs than before. The fur passes her knees this time, and as it reaches mid-thigh she suddenly seem flushed and distracted. She bites her lower lip and crosses her thighs as if to shield her sex. Shaking off the distraction, she quickly restores her legs to normal.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>You strike low again, this time hitting your target in the crotch. She staggers, suddenly weak in the knees and barely seems to notice as the transformation progresses rapidly up her legs, leaving in its wake a pair of furry, cloven-hoofed limbs. As the changes reach her crotch she opens her mouth in surprise and looks down. Her eyes widen in shock as she watches her womanhood reshape itself into a pair of testicles and a penis, which swells to full erection in seconds, further befuddling her lust-addled mind. Clearly embarrassed, she hastily conceals the evidence of her arousal with both hands. You can't help but smirk as she wrestles with the raging beast, as if trying to shove it back inside. To your disappointment, the fur stops at her waist.  Before any other changes have a chance to begin, she hastily dispels the transformation, restoring her body to normal.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>Your next burst of magic strikes dead center of your opponent's chest. Her eyes glaze over, a lusty moan escaping her lips. The spreading magic deflates her lovely breasts, much to her surprise, smoothing out her chest to leave it muscularly sculpted and broad, but still very human. It contrasts nicely with the furry, beast-like legs that dominate her body from the waist down. A seething erection again forces its way into view, even bigger than before, or is that just your wishful thinking? You can't help but smirk as your victim reaches down to caress the tumescent organ in wonder. Her hands suddenly dart to her head, just in time to feel a pair of ribbed horns growing out to either side, curling to spiral around her ears. Ram's horns! She will make a fine goat-man. It appears to take her some effort to overcome her lust, but she manages to reverse the changes to her body.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>As your next cast slams into your victim's torso, she almost seems to embrace it. Her body, already suffused with the spell's energy, swiftly returns to the half-man, half-goat form for which the magic is patterned. She lift one of her legs and seem to admire the cloven hoof at the end. Yet her attention is soon diverted by the impressive cock that swells to life again between her thighs, and the carnal urges it floods into her mind. Her lusty gaze wanders, as if searching the vicinity for some creature with an empty orifice that might serve to satiate the needs of a horny goat-man. For a moment her… well, his… eyes focus on you, and you resist the urge to flee from your creation, this Satyr drawn straight out of myth. Just then she seems to regain control of herself, and reverses the changes before it is too late.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>Your target seems to know what's coming, and this time she doesn't even flinch as your magic envelopes her. Now saturated with transformation energy, her body reverts to the form of a Satyr in a matter of seconds, sadly affording you little time to admire your handiwork. You can see it in her eyes when the lust hits her, washing away any petty thoughts or worries unrelated to copulation. The newly-created Satyr skips around on his hooves with wild abandon, apparently eager to embrace his new existence as a free spirit. His cock, bouncing between his thighs, suddenly stiffens as if preparing for action. He pauses and looks around, a lusty glint in his eyes as he serches for something to… fuck. Maybe you should beat a hasty retreat. Or not.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>

</Form>
