<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>The spell resembles a thin tube, zipping forward through the air until it strikes you directly in the mouth. It pushes its way through your lips into your mouth, acting as a solid mass despite its nature. Your lips brighten into a cherry red and inflate, involuntarily wrapping around the tube length and tasting cherry before you bite down and wipe your mouth, dissipating the spell.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>Your lips inflate as the spell grows closer, forming a slight O to allow easier entry, no matter how tightly you press them together, trying to ignore the sensations of pleasure emanating from them. You can’t quite bring yourself to stop the spell again, the cherry sensations causing you to shudder with pleasure as your body begins to grow aroused, your penis becoming especially hard and unusually red, likely from the level of blood. You reach up and pull the spell from your mouth with your hands, though they feel slightly smaller than usual, your nails a cherry red.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>You open your mouth willingly this time, tongue licking the tip of the spell, causing its magic to penetrate deeply into your body. You shrink, losing body mass as it becomes more feminine, large breasts beginning to round upon your chest. You reach up and grab the spell once again, but it refuses to budge, only causing you to pull and push the spell in and out of your mouth. Your other hand is too busy with your cock, rock hard and a very bright red, almost as pleasurable as your lips. You wrench your hand away and pull using both, ripping the spell to shreds in the process. </TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>The force of the impact knocks you onto your knees, the spell now pulsating and moving inwards and outwards without your manipulation. Both of your hands are too busy masturbating, though it is becoming increasingly difficult as your penis has become completely solid, losing sensation and turning the perfect shade of red. Your body is also smaller, not in any particular area, simply losing height and mass overall, shrinking to roughly four feet. You resemble the complete cock sucker now, whorish face painted a bright red with make up, your lips dominating its bottom half. The spell dissipates in your mouth, leaving you with a strange sensation of emptiness. You glance down at your new cock, licking your lips at the sight of its sweet surface, but you manage to resist temptation and stand shakily, the magic disappearing.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>You fall to your knees and grasp the spell with both hands, greedily sucking it until nothing is left but a sense of longing, your body once again becoming that of a cock obsessed sucker, large red lips pouting with sadness and desperation, the need to taste that flavour! A thump from below draws your gaze, your penis having fallen, becoming a large cock shaped lollipop, its red surface too much for you to resist. You grab it and begin to suck upon it with wanton abandon, its flavour beyond anything you could have imagined. You find yourself shrinking yet again, the shock of your incredibly small size enough to draw you out of your obsession, throwing the lollipop to the ground before rubbing it against your crotch until it attaches itself again, the magic fading once more.  </TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>You can’t resist. It’s too much. The bright surface of that lollipop draws your eyes like a magnet, its previous nature as a part of you forgotten as you lick and suck its length, the shrinking sensation now gone, replaced by more of a pulling. The lollipop seems to suck back, what little of you that is left drawn into the head of the dick, becoming the creamy center. For a moment everything is dark before all of your sensations return at once, realising without surprise your nature as a large red lollipop on the ground. Your desire to suck is not gone, though it has changed; the desire, no the need to be sucked upon is desperate, the ground rubbing against your permanent surface an orgasm unto itself. Imagine what it will be like when your new owner starts to suck....</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>Your lips inflate as the spell grows closer, forming a slight O to allow easier entry, no matter how tightly you press them together, trying to ignore the sensations of pleasure emanating from them. You can’t quite bring yourself to stop the spell again, the cherry sensations causing you to shudder with pleasure as your body begins to grow aroused, though your vagina feels odd. A sudden pushing sensation is all that announces the rise of your new masculine member, long and terribly hard. You reach up and pull the spell from your mouth with your hands, though they feel slightly smaller than usual, your nails a cherry red.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>You open your mouth willingly this time, tongue licking the tip of the spell, causing its magic to penetrate deeply into your body. You shrink, losing body mass as it becomes more feminine, breasts becoming larger and rounder. You reach up and grab the spell once again, but it refuses to budge, only causing you to pull and push the spell in and out of your mouth. Your other hand is too busy with your new cock, rock hard and a very bright red, almost as pleasurable as your lips. You wrench your hand away and pull using both, ripping the spell to shreds in the process. </TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>You form a hole with your finger and thumb, blowing through it as if you were creating a bubble, but instead a tube of magic is shot forth towards your target. It strikes them in the mouth, forcing its way between their lips before it begins to work its magic. The most noticeable change being the inflation of their lips, brightening into a cherry red. The rest of their face quickly becomes more sexual and suggestive, eyelids heavy with red make up. Your target bites down upon the spell however, crushing its structure and causing the spell to fade away.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>This time the spell affects them before it physically strikes, lips becoming large and accepting of large insertions, not needing to force its way through their lips, no matter how hard they try. Not only their face changes, but their body becomes smaller and whorish, wide hips and large breasts swaying as your target moans with pleasure. Their penis looks especially odd, not only because it is upon what is clearly a woman’s body, but because it is an unnatural shade of red, now long and harder than it has ever been. Your target resists temptation however, and wrenches the spell from their mouth, but not before a look of longing shoots across it.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>The strain of resisting the spell is clearly apparent now, your target opening their welcoming lips and sucking earnestly upon the spell before they attempt to pull it out once again. They are not quite successful this time, only managing to pump it in position, resembling a whore more by the minute. Speaking of which, their body has becoming nothing but slatternly, built for nothing but sex. One hand pumps the magical dick within their mouth whilst the other at their crotch, now clearly a solid object, nothing more than an imitation of a penis. Your target manages to force the other hand to stop masturbating and assist it however, wrenching the spell from their jaws.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Instead of blowing between your fingers this time, you practically throw it forwards, the force of the spell knocking them onto their knees, though that may have been nothing more than desire. Your desired changes grow closer, their body becoming significantly smaller as it fully resembles a back alley cock sucker, desperately working the spell in and out of their mouth. The other hand has stopped masturbating, though this is only due to the lack of a functioning penis, having solidified fully, a cherry red cock for a cherry red sucker. They are beginning to look slightly less solid themselves, surface wobbling mildly as if it were a liquid. Unfortunately your spell disappears as planned but your target does not give in to temptation, negating the further changes.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>The magical cock is barely out of your hands before they pluck it from the air, hungrily ingesting it. They are clearly upset when it disappears, but there is no need to worry about failure now, as they grasp their old cock with both hands and lick its surface. Too busy with their desire, your target fails to notice their increasingly shortening stature and liquid nature, most of them having been absorbed into the penis to full the hollow ball sections. The sudden realisation that they are so close to the ground now is enough to force them to drop the lollipop, desperately rubbing their crotch until it rejoins. </TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>Your spell lasts for only the briefest of movements before it is gone, leaving the cock sucker nothing but her own tasty treat. This time she fades away entirely sucking upon its surface, the rest of her body becoming its creamy filling. The last sight you see of your opponent is a pair of lips in the air, still wrapped around the cock before they are gone, leaving a never ending lollipop for your troubles. Its cherry flavour and size will never end, allowing you to enjoy sucking on it as long as you wish.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>This time the spell affects them before it physically strikes, lips becoming large and accepting of large insertions, not needing to force its way through their lips, no matter how hard they try. Not only their face changes, but their body becomes smaller and whorish, wide hips and large breasts swaying as your target moans with pleasure. Despite this, they aren’t masturbating, though you realise why when their vagina seems to press outwards, forming a large cock. She, or should I say he, is shocked for a moment, before being replaced by bliss as they stroke the head briefly with their hand. Your target resists temptation however, and wrenches the spell from their mouth, but not before a look of longing shoots across it.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>The strain of resisting the spell is clearly apparent now, your target opening their welcoming lips and sucking earnestly upon the spell before they attempt to pull it out once again. They are not quite successful this time, only managing to pump it in position, resembling a whore more by the minute. Speaking of which, their body has becoming nothing but slatternly, built for nothing but sex. One hand pumps the magical dick within their mouth whilst the other at their crotch, reveling in their new found appendage. It will not last much longer however, as it has become a mere imitation of a penis, nothing more than solid red sugary goodness. Your target manages to force the other hand to stop masturbating and assist it however, wrenching the spell from their jaws.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>

</Form>
