<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<Description>A sexy young woman in a school uniform of a white button-up shirt that barely contains her breasts, a plaid skirt, and long sexy legs wearing white stockings. With her red hair and emerald eyes, she gives a playful smirk. You can tell she doesn't keep her good grades through studying. Looking at you over her glasses she smiles and licks her lips.</Description>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>You feel the spell hit you and find your hair growing longer and turning red. A plaid skirt poofs into existence around your waist. For a moment you realize you might be missing class before you shake the thought from your mind and reverse the changes.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>Your red hair reaches your shoulders again and the skirt makes a reappearance. You take a moment to admire it and straighten it out with your dainty new hands before you realize you were hit by a spell again and turn yourself back.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>Everything gets a little blurry and you push your lovely red hair out of your face as you look for your glasses. You find them tucked into the pocket of your uniform's button-up shirt and put them on, admiring your nails before you shake your head, realizing this isn't right, and change back.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>This time you remember where your glasses are and put them on, smiling at the feeling of your long white stockings clinging to your sexy legs. You love how sexy your uniform makes you look and you know your professors do too. You may not be the best student, but you know how to please them well enough that they overlook a few mistakes in your homework... Suddenly you remember who you really are and, with a bit of effort, reverse the changes.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>You feel so sexy as your breasts nearly spill out of your tight uniform top, briefly doing a spin and giggling as your skirt flies up, revealing your lacy panties. You remember you have a test today, but you can always skip it. After all, the professors seem to prefer when you do your make-up tests on your knees anyway... You lick your lips before coming to your senses. Though you can barely stand to tear yourself away from your 'scholastic' thoughts, you manage to change yourself back.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>Red hair flows down to your shoulders and a sexy schoolgirl's uniform clings to your curvy body, cleavage openly on display. You giggle and adjust your glasses, looking at yourself with your new emerald green eyes. You know you're not the best student around, but you are the best cocksucker, and that's the skill that's keeping your grades so high and your professors so happy. You have become a Naughty Schoolgirl!</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>You see the spell hit your target and watch as their hair grows longer and turns red. A plaid skirt poofs into existence around their waist. They look as if they might have forgotten something but clear their head and reverse the changes.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>Your target's red hair reappears and reaches their shoulders again as the skirt makes a magical return. They take a moment to admire it and straighten it out with their dainty new hands before realizing they were hit by a spell again and turn themselves back.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>Your target squints for a moment, brushing away the long red hair that's come back before they grab a pair of glasses tucked into the pocket of their school uniform top and put them on. Now that they can see they take a moment to admire their painted nails before realizing there's been a change and reversing your spell.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>This time your target seems to remember where their glasses are and put them on, smiling down at the new long white stockings clinging to their sexy legs. They don't seem to notice it but as they think, they absentmindedly suck on their finger. It looks like they have a bit of experience sucking on things. Eventually though they clear their mind and, with a bit of effort, reverse the changes.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Your target moans sexily as their breasts nearly spill out of their tight uniform top, briefly doing a spin and giggling as their skirt flies up, revealing their lacy panties. They briefly suck on their finger again, an erotic display you have to admit, then look at you and lick their lips. Suddenly they seem embarrassed and change themselves back, but you see a look of regret in their eyes.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>Red hair flows down your target's shoulders and a sexy schoolgirl's uniform clings to their curvy body, cleavage openly on display. They giggle and adjust their glasses, looking at themselves with their new emerald green eyes. This isn't the kind of student who earns her grades through hard work, but rather on their knees or on their backs for their teachers. The new girl seems to know this, too, as she flaunts her body.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
