<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>Your rival sends a blast of magic your way and you brace yourself for the impact. To your surprise, the blast separates into three rings of energy, two of shimmering black with a hot pink one in between. They soar over your head as you raise your hands defensively, but the rings descend to the level of your hips, where they begin to rotate around you like a trio of hula hoops. For a moment you feel strangely giddy as your hips gyrate in sync with the rhythm of the hoops. Then, to your dismay, your pelvis begins to widen before your very eyes. Startled, you quickly dispel the changes before the magic can progress any further.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>Once again, your opponent hurls the three rings of energy at you. Even though you're expecting them, there is nothing you can do to prevent the rings from resuming their orbit around your hips. Strain as you might, you can't keep from rolling your pelvis in time with the rings' motion, looking like an enchanted hula dancer. Your hips spread again, making room for a generous bubble-butt to push out behind you, and a sudden feeling of giddy girlishness makes you feel like giggling. With a coy smile, you look around to see if anyone is checking out your ass. As you ponder whether this spell is designed to turn you into some sort of bimbo-variant, you notice that you seem to be getting shorter, your legs and torso shrinking toward your middle. That's far enough! A quick counter-spell forces your body to return to normal.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>You sense satisfaction in your rival as they again conjure the three hula hoops of energy and set them to spinning around your hips, a dizzying blur of black-pink-black that has you gyrating like a go-go dancer. Your torso and legs shrink as your middle expands, exaggerating the proportions of your broad hips and bubble-but as they form anew. A feeling of flirty girlishness permeates your thoughts. You want all the boys to be staring at your butt as you flip your skirt saucily in the air. Oh, they can look, but they can't touch! As you giggle at this thought, you realize that the rings of energy have contracted and are now rubbing directly against your body, merging into your flesh. In a panic, you cast a counter spell and reverse the changes. </TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>The energetic hoops fly at you again, and you barely resist as they settle around you to work their magic. In a series of changes becoming far too familiar for your taste, the rings turn you back into a bootylicious babe with exaggerated hips, rolling your pelvis saucily. You want every eye focused on that perfect ass as it bounces and rolls, flipping up your hem as you teasingly reveal your owner's panties underneath... Your owner? Where did that come from? As you consider the implications of that strange thought, you realize that your torso and legs are shrinking further. The rings of energy are still spinning around your hips, black-pink-black, but they are moving within your body now, and your flesh looks alarmingly like fabric where they touch. You desperately reverse the changes with a counter spell.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>You want to avoid those magic rings, knowing they bode ill for you, but they home in on your body with uncanny accuracy. The changes come even faster now, as the hoops orbit your body with dizzying speed. Your hips and ass widen, gyrating wildly against your will, as your torso and legs retract into your pelvis, which is rapidly turning into some sort of garment, ruffled layers of black, pink, and black fabric. You feel a desperate yearning to sit atop a luscious bubble butt, riding your owner's hips as she dances and flips you saucily in the air to flash her panties (if she is wearing any!). Feminine, flirtatious, and sexy – that's how you feel. You realize that you are turning into some sort of ruffled, tiered skirt! With shock, you notice that your legs and upper body are already gone, leaving your head nestled within the sexy ruffles of a skirt. Summoning the last of your will, you just barely manage to reverse the changes.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>You are barely hanging onto your self-awareness, let alone your physical form, when your attacker flings those terrible hoops of magic at you one last time. The spinning rings waste no time, battering down the last of your physical and mental resistance in a matter of seconds. There is a sensation of falling as your body collapses into its new form, three tiers of ruffled, flirty skirt, layered black-pink-black. Confusing images flash through your thoughts, forcing your old identity to retreat into memory. You will make your owner look so sexy, riding their hips wherever they go, flashing the goodies for random passersby to ogle! The very thought sends a tingle of anticipation through what remains of your mind, reshaping your consciousness to embrace your new purpose in life. You're going to love being a skirt!</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>With a flourish, you send a blast of magic at your enemy and watch as it separates into three rings of energy, two of shimmering black with a hot pink one in between. The rings soar over your victim's head as they raise their hands defensively, but the rings descend quickly to the level of their hips and begin to rotate around like a trio of hula hoops. Much to your amusement, your opponent's hips begin to gyrate in sync with the rhythm of the hoops. Their pelvis suddenly begins to widen, and you can see the spark of fear in their eyes. Startled, they quickly dispel the changes before the magic can progress any further.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>Once more, you hurl the three rings of energy at your target. They are unable to prevent the rings from orbiting around their hips again. You can see the strain on your victim's face as they try to keep from rolling their pelvis in time with the rings' motion, looking like an enchanted hula dancer. Their hips spread again, making room for a generous bubble-butt to push out behind them, and they suddenly burst into a fit of giggling. With a coy smile, your opponent looks around as if to see if anyone is checking out their ass. Just then, they notice that they are getting shorter as their legs and torso shrink toward the middle. In a panic, they cast a quick counter-spell to return their body to normal.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>You cannot suppress a feeling of satisfaction as you again conjure the three hula hoops of energy and set them to spinning around your rival, a dizzying blur of black-pink-black that has them gyrating like a go-go dancer. Their torso and legs shrink as their middle expands, exaggerating the proportions of their broad hips and bubble-but as they form anew. Your victim suddenly giggles and winks at you, turning to give you a delicious view of their ample butt as it rolls and wiggles under the power of your magic. As you smirk at their flirtatious antics, you see that the rings of energy have contracted and are now rubbing directly against their body, merging into their flesh. Your opponent suddenly realizes that as well, and casts a counter spell to reverse the changes. </TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>The energetic hoops fly from your hands again, and your target barely seems to resist as the rings settle around them to work their magic. In a series of changes becoming far too familiar, the rings turn your rival back into a bootylicious babe with exaggerated hips, rolling their pelvis saucily. They clearly want every eye focused on that perfect ass as it bounces and rolls, flipping up the hem of a flirty miniskirt that teasingly reveals their panties underneath. You can't help but chuckle at the irony, for you know the outcome will be rather different than they suspect. Their torso and legs shrink further. The rings of energy are still spinning around their hips, black-pink-black, but are moving within their body now, and their flesh looks like fabric where the hoops touch. To your disappointment, they reverse the changes with a counter spell.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Your delightful magic rings home in on your rival's body with uncanny accuracy. The changes come even faster now, as the hoops orbit their body with dizzying speed. Their hips and ass widen, gyrating wildly against their will, as torso and legs retract into their pelvis, which is rapidly turning into some sort of garment, ruffled layers of black, pink, and black fabric. You can see in their eyes that they now understand their fate. Even so, they cannot the resist the urge to wiggle their ass flirtatiously, flipping the ruffled skirt saucily in the air to flash what lies beneath. It is clear now that they are turning into a ruffled, tiered skirt, just as you had planned. Yet it seems you will have to wait to claim your prize. Summoning the last of their will, they just barely manage to reverse the changes.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>One last time, you fling those terrible hoops of magic at your target. The spinning rings waste no time, battering down the last of their physical and mental resistance in a matter of seconds. Their body collapses into its new form, three tiers of ruffled, flirty skirt, layered black-pink-black. As the skirt flutters to the ground, a confusing flurry of images flash through your thoughts, broadcast telepathically by your victim. Your opponent's old identity retreats into memory as they are overwhelmed by a desire to make their owner look sexy, riding their hips wherever they go, flashing the goodies for random passersby to ogle! The thought sends a tingle of anticipation through your mind. You're going to love wearing this skirt!</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
