<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>You feel odd as a wave of music washes over you, the area around you is now a club.  Your heart begins to beat with the clash of the chains; beginning slow but increasing in pace. The wails of pain and pleasure become more noticeable and you begin sweating as your skin heats up changing to a reddish hue. Noticing something is wrong you plug your ears and reverse the changes.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>Someone taps you on the shoulder and you unplug your ears without thinking about it. Forgetting what happened earlier you turn around but don't see anyone nearby. The music wraps itself around you once more and you feel heat surging through you. This time your skin changes to almost a dark red in color, a shade just lighter than blood. Your skin seems to be folding in on itself, hollowing out before your very eyes. You stop and reverse the changes by tuning the music out through will alone.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>You hear a sudden shift in the room and try to figure out what it is. The sound of whips has replaced the sound of chains from before and you feel out of focus as if the entire room has begun to spin. Losing focus on drowning out the music it begins its eerie assault once more. Your body shrinks steadily inward with each crack of the whip against the floor. Anticipation floods within you making you wish to be a part of the action. You shake your head trying to rid these feelings emerging from deep within you. You tear your gaze away from the scene and reverse the changes taking more time than the last.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>You begin to move towards the door but are stopped by the sounds of both the chains and whips combined. You turn around and glance at the scene as it unfolds. Your skin darkens once more as you watch as the brute is whipped. He tugs at his chains and you feel yourself slowly sliding towards the scene. The changes begin to erupt as you are enraptured even further. Your legs feel like jello as they hollow out and shape around something unseen. You collapse onto the ground, jolting you back into your own mind. You lay there for a moment and reverse the changes, taking an exuberant amount of time.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>You stand up slowly, hearing the soft click of boots on the marble floors. The clicking sound of the boots gets closer as the speed of the whipping increases. The whips sound further away from you as you look around for whomever is wearing the boots. In your gaze a vixen in a latex corset and knee high boots is walking up to your table. You pick yourself up off the floor to see her better. She takes up your entire vision and nothing else in the room matters. You don't notice the changes as they take place, your torso hollow out completely  as your skin becomes glossy and the dark red hue returns spreading over your entire body in waves.  She reaches the table you are beside and smirks at you watching as you shrink to less than a third of your old size. Her mouth opens but you don't hear any words come out. Reaching up you feel that your ears have changed into metallic rings about the size of two or three fingers . In a panic you focus on reversing the changes. </TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>The vixen stands up and looks at you bending forward to kiss you. The changes resume as your mind emptys of all thought, just getting sucked into the pleasure and the pain. You hollow out completely as your eyes and ears become rings that encompass you in the four locations. Your skin changes back to the dark red hue that can mask the splashes blood. Your body rolls in on itself until it is a solid ring. Your hair changes into a clasp on the back of the ring, and you feel a lock that seems to be hanging from the clasp. You fall to the table completely changed. You feel warmth as you are picked up and opened, being placed on to the neck of someone else. You drain little pieces of their pleasure and revel in it for it is what you have become.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>Your wave of magical music encompasses your unknowing subject, making them enter a different realm shifting them into your very own club like domain. You watch as they seize in place as they acknowledge the music you have picked. The sounds of chains clashing and tugging from the walls as the speakers blare from all of the corners. With a flick of your wrists you begin to make the illusion a reality for all who listen. Your target begins to darken in color changing to a reddish tint. Their skin sweats as this occurs from either the heat or the pleasure from the sounds you do not know. They plug their ears to block out the sound and they revert back to normal.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>You send a gentle push of breath to tap your foolish adversary. As expected they unplug their ears to see if someone was trying to talk to them. You add more power to the music making the illusion more material and closer to being seen to the eyes. You watch as their body begins to roll inwards and hollow around the joints as if they are empty inside. Your unwitting foe’s skin changes once more darkening even more to before changing to a color slightly short of blood red. Their joints refill as you watch them change back to a semi fully structured state and the color reverses to a bad sunburn as your power take their toll upon them. </TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>You change your tactics as you add even more power and focus to the spell changing the sounds from chains to whips. Reveling in the sound of the whips you watch as your manifest becomes closer to reality, shifting the entire room to accompany it. Your adversary sways around as they adjust. They begin to shrink in succession with the whips cracking across the floor and walls. The image blends into focus and the cracks shortening in time, shrinking the target faster. You watch as lust fills their eyes, but after a moment they shake their head and tear their eyes away from the scene you have conjured for them. They reverse the height changes, mostly anyway.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Your victim tries to leave the club so you add the chains back into the mix to tease and tantalize their interests. Adding a person within the chains seems to regain the victim's attention. They turn slowly watching as the brute who is held to the pole by chains struggles against them futilely. Hes trying to get at the vixen who is whipping him with no mercy. They walk over to the table and stop, captivated by the scene entirely. Their legs hollow out all the way to their waist causing them to fall to the floor. You see them lay there reversing the changes no longer captivated by the illusion with it out of sight.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Your magic reaches its pinnacle and control of the final part of the scene becomes yours. You move the second dominatrix vixen towards your future item. Her heels clacking loudly on the marble floor. They gaze at her approaching them, unsure if this part will last for long on them after the previous waves have failed. They pull themselves off the floor and gawk at the vixen. You watch as their torso hollows out still held upright magically and their skin darkens to the dark red color of blood.  Their skin becomes glossy all over the parts you can see. You smirk at their nearness to your goal, your vixen imitates this motion as she arrives at the table of your foe. This enacts even more changes to your enemy, they shrink to almost a third of their normal size. They continue changing as their ears open and shift into metallic rings opening so a small chain could fit through. You watch as your vixen asks the opponent a question and in a panic they touch the rings noticing the changes and reverse them frantically. </TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>Time for the final distraction you think. You make the vixen bend forward to kiss your new item. Their lips touch and you drain the victim's mind through your link to the vixen. You replace their thoughts with pain and pleasure filling them completely to the brim with these thoughts only. The target's ears and eyes change into the metallic rings growing larger creating four rings, on the front of what was once their face. The skin glosses over changing back to the dark red that can hide the occasional splash of blood. You watch with glee as the target's body rolls into itself shrinking into a single ring of red hollowed all the way through. Their hair recedes forming a clasp with a lock hanging from it. They fall to the table and you disperse the illusion and call your pet into the room. Picking your collar off of the table you place it around your pet's neck. Allowing for total subjection to drain their will and make them even more subservient to you.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
