<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<Description>Being little more than an inked design on a scrap of a scroll you are left to feel naught but a void until someone claims you activates your magic by pressing you somewhere on their skin.  While you are bound to the paper you can't help but feel as if you're suffocating, desiring a host to keep you warm.  Once bound you become a part of your host in the form of an intricate tattoo, ink strong and colorful, your pattern shifting to match the emotional state of your host.   Today you've channeled some anger and lust from your owner so you've taken up the face of a mischievous demon girl.</Description>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>Upon being struck with the spell you feel a faint, almost warm, embrace, hugging you gently. You shrug off this somewhat awkward, yet not unpleasant feeling.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>The repeated attacks by this specific spell are starting to yield more prominent results. You feel a much more encompassing hold all over your body and your flesh begins to turn pale. You steady yourself and shake away these feelings before they become too concerning.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>This constant barrage is beginning to be too much! With the next cast, you start to curl up, feeling as though you are being compressed. The hugging sensation becomes more of a pressure, all over your body, as your legs start to roll up and your upper body does the same, beginning to take on the appearance of a parchment.  With more than a little effort, you reverse these effects, but the lingering feeling of the hold is getting to you...</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>You don't know how much longer you're going to be able to fight off these sensations. On this particular cast you return to the same fetal position you were in as your body thins out.  A small, intricate, gleaming blue symbol forms on your whitening body, and you can feel the same sense of an inescapable embrace coming from it, radiating from it. Your body just barely starts to bunch together as you take on more familiar characteristics of a scroll, before you break free of this magic.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>The ominously repeating spell strikes you again and your entire body goes limp immediately, the returning effects rapidly striking you and giving you little chance to resist. You can feel your body taking on the form of this spells design, and you understand now that it's a particular sort of binding glyph, a small parchment with an intricate and magical design.  The terrible part is, it requires your help! The glimmering symbol on your paper-like stomach glows brightly, and the moment you feel as though it was going to be too late, you feel a hint of weakness. You break the spell through some force of will or luck, but you don't think you can be struck even one more time. </TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>Your fate has been sealed... quite literally. With this final cast, your body falls over and even as you lose your footing, your form changes, shrinking rapidly and rolling up into the telltale signs of a small scroll, your sweat darkening into lines of ink that decorate your body.  You can do nothing to stop it now, its power washes over you, claiming you.   As the transformation finalizes you have little other option than wait for someone to pick you up, to press you against their skin and let your magical ink flow into your skin where they can wear you proudly.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>As you cast this spell, a bright blue gleam surrounds your target, and you see them wrapping their arms around their self. This lasts but a moment before they shake off the spell. </TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>On this cast your target seems much more shaken by the attack, curling up somewhat. In the blue aura they're radiating, you can see their body beginning to change, but before long they break free... Interesting.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>Your next attack is met with significantly more success, and you can see the changes starting to rock your victim. The runic symbol begins to take hold and their body shrinks to begin assuming the form of a scroll..  Unfortunately it doesn't take long to reverse the spell, though you would assume it took effort. </TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Your victim most likely cannot take much more of this relentless assault.  Your cast is more than enough to reveal just how powerful the magics were taking hold of them as they curl up once again, their body folding into itself and shrinking even further into naught but a parchment.  However, they somehow resist the changes.  You feel confident that your final victory is coming soon.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Your victim most likely cannot take much more of this relentless assault. Your cast is more than enough to reveal just how powerful the magics were taking hold of them as they curl up once again, their body folding into itself and shrinking even further into naught but a parchment. Their form is all but lost to them, though at the last moment, the scroll unfolds, and grows once again. Nothing but force of will and blind luck saves them, though you know that it won't be the same if you strike them once more.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>You've done it.   With your final cast, your target can do nothing to halt the power of the binding spell you cast on them. Swiftly, they change, shrinking and curling into themselves as the change works on their body, forcing them into nothing more than a inked slip of paper to be bound to your skin at will as you please.  You step up to collect your prize and walk away confidently.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
