<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<Description>She's one of the most attractive women you've seen in a long time, long red hair gently hugging the top of her prominent breasts. She's got wonderful emerald green eyes that could pierce the soul of every living being looking at them. Her perfect milky white skin with black sensual tattoos just begged to be touched. You can see by the way her nipples are standing proudly on the top of her wonderful titties, that she's really aroused, always will be. Her body was made for carnal bliss, the second she becomes completely naked, she loses a big part of her reasoning system, and all she can think about is someone or something relieving her of her extreme horniness.</Description>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>Your attacker's spell hits you on the right hand. You can feel a little tingle going through your body, as you look at your arm, you can see your skin becomes a little whiter and your hands begins to slowly become softer and daintier. You can suddenly feel something pushing your groin, as you have a sudden urge to remove your clothes. Not wanting this to overcome you, you shrug it off and transform back to your original form.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>Your attacker's spell hits you in the face, feeling dizzy for a second you reach your face with your hand and as you touch your lips a shiver of pleasure pass through your body. In shock, you remove your hand only to realize that your now longer and red hair are in the way. While you ponder on what is happening, your tongue finds its way to your newly sensible plump lips and sends shiver of pleasure trough your body, you gasp in shock. You suddenly realize that you have a really high pitched voice and it makes you realize something is wrong, you shrug it off and return to your original form.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>Your attacker's spell hits you right in the chest, you feel your nipples harden immediately as your breast start to expand, the sensation sends tingling of pleasure through all you body, making you mindlessly rub your nipples with your hands. The sensation make you fall back on the ground but you're newly found growing buttocks absorb most of the shock. As you look down, you can see your penis stand to attention, seeing that it seems smaller then normal it makes you come back to your senses and you return to your original form wandering if you'll ever have a chance to play with your breast like that again.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>Your attacker's spell hit one of your butt cheeks, almost instantly you can feel your hips and ass starting to widen, stretching you clothes and making you feel really uncomfortable, without thinking twice you remove them. Feeling the air caressing your now white and soft skin make you feel very horny, and you feel your member responding as it now stand to attention. Gently stroking your member with one hand and caressing your ass with the other your start to wonder what would it feel like to feel something inside you. As your finger gently approach your backdoor, you suddenly come back to your senses and take back your original form, with that last thought still wandering in your brain.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>You attacker's spell hits you right on the forehead sending little shocks of pleasure all over your body and especially to your brain. You fell that your skin is becoming aware of every little sensation as you pull down your top. You instantly go on your back and start playing with your right tit sensing it growing in your hand. You mindlessly put the index finger of your other hand in your mouth and start sucking at it with your sensible lips expecting something to happen. You can feel your penis throbbing as it becomes smaller and smaller now looking like a huge clitoris. You can feel your waist slimming down and your hips expanding, but you don't care, you've never felt that good before, as you remove your hand from your mouth to reach between your leg you have a sudden wake up call, realizing this is not normal, you take the last of your willpower to come back to your normal form, but deep inside you know you want to feel that way again.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>Your attacker's spell hits you right in the groin, as the spell hits you, a massive wave of arousal come over you, without even thinking you remove all your clothes and take in hand your already erect penis and start masturbating not realizing that within second you're now on the ground fingering a newly formed wet snatch. You're so busy playing with yourself that you don't see your pectoral becoming bigger and bigger transforming into huge tittites with rock hard nipples standing to attention, as they do, you take your other hand and start massaging them vigorously.  Your ass and hips start to expand to complete your newly hourglass form while all you body hair disappear as your skin becomes paler and paler. A big chuck of your red mane gets in your face as your about have a mind shattering orgasm that complete your transformation for good.</TFMessage_Completed_1st_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>Your attacker's spell hits you on the right hand. You can feel a little tingle going through your body, as you look at your arm, you can see your skin becomes a little whiter and your fingernails become a bit longer and reddish. You can suddenly feel a little emptiness between your legs, as you have a sudden urge to remove your clothes. Not wanting this to overcome you, you shrug it off and transform back to your original form.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>Your attacker's spell hits you in the face, feeling dizzy for a second you reach your face with your hand and as you touch your lips a shiver of pleasure pass through your body. In shock, your remove your hand only to realize that your now longer and red hair are in the way. While you ponder on what is happening, your tongue finds its way to your newly sensible plump lips and sends shiver of pleasure trough your body, you gasp in shock. You suddenly have the urge to suck on something bigger and it makes you realize something is wrong, you shrug it off and return to your original form.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>Your attacker's spell hits you right in the chest, you feel your nipples harden immediately as your breast becomes firm and rounder taking the size of cantaloupes, the sensation sends tingling of pleasure through all you body, making you mindlessly rub your nipples with your hands. The sensation make you fall back on the ground but you're newly found growing buttocks absorb most of the shock. As you look down, you can see your that your vagina is squirting lubricant like no tomorrow, surprised by the sigh you come back to your senses and you return to your original form wandering if you'll ever have a chance to play with your breast like that again.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>Your attacker's spell hit one of your butt cheeks, almost instantly you can feel your hips and ass starting to widen, stretching you clothes and making you feel really uncomfortable, without thinking twice you remove them. Feeling the air caressing your now white and really sensible skin make you feel very horny, and you feel your crotch responding as beads of a thick liquid are now apparent between your legs. Gently fingering your clit with one hand and caressing your ass with the other your start to wonder what would it feel like to have something in both your holes. As your finger gently approach your backdoor, you suddenly come back to your senses and take back your original form, with that last thought still wandering in your brain.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>You attacker's spell hits you right on the forehead sending little shocks of pleasure all over your body and especially to your brain. You fell that your skin is becoming aware of every little sensation as you pull down your top. You instantly go on your back and start playing with your right tit sensing the nipple becoming rock-hard between your fingers. You mindlessly put the index finger of your other hand in your mouth and start sucking at it with your sensible lips expecting something to happen. You can feel your clit throbbing as your snatch becomes really wet at the thought of something filling it. You can feel your waist slimming down and your hips expanding, but you don't care, you've never felt that good before, as you remove your hand from your mouth to reach between your leg you have a sudden wake up call, realizing this is not normal, you take the last of your willpower to come back to your normal form, but deep inside you know you want to feel that way again.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>Your attacker's spell hits you right in the crotch, as the spell hits you, a massive wave of arousal come over you, without even thinking you remove all your clothes and start to vigorously fingering your now permanently wet snatch. With your other hand you start massaging your titties as they become rounder and softer, your nipples standing to attention. Your skins becomes white as snow and you suddenly feel every single breath of air touching every part of your bare skin. You can see your now red mane of hair falling in your face as you furiously lick your sensible lips dreaming of something good to put in there. Your ass and hips expand to complete your hourglass form. The thought of masturbating in front of everyone, like your doing right now,  makes you feel even better and you have a mind shattering orgasm that finish your transformation.</TFMessage_Completed_1st_F>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>Your spell hits your target on the right hand. You can see little tingles of electricity run across his arm as you see his skin becomes a little whiter and his hands begins to slowly become softer and daintier. You suddenly see you target rubbing his legs together and grabbing his clothes as something seems to bother him, but he quickly shrub it off and transform back to his original self.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>Your spell hits your target in the face, you can see that he's feeling dizzy for a second as he reach his face with his hand, the second his hand touch his lips you can see him shivers as a little moan escapes his mouth. In shock, he removes his hand only to realize that his now long and red hair are in the way. You see him standing there in shock as he instinctively start to lick his own lips with his tongue, only to let out some other little moans of pleasure in a really higher pitched voice. It seems that hearing himself screamed like that brought him back to his senses as he return to his original form.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>Your spell hits your target right in the chest, you can see his nipples harden immediately through the fabric as his chest start to expand, you can see him struggle with the pleasuring sensation as he start to mindlessly rub his nipples with his hands. The feeling seems really good for him as he falls on his back only for his expanding buttocks to absorb the shock. As you look at his crotch, you can see his member stand to attention, but it seems to become smaller and smaller. Your target, having seen the same thing, came back to his senses and transform back to his original self, but you could see that he had enjoy the experience.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>Your spell hits your target on one of his butt cheeks, almost instantly you can see his hips and ass starting to widen, stretching his clothes and making him feel really uncomfortable. He then suddenly removes all his clothes, and you can see by his erect penis, his hard growing nipples and his little gasps of air, that you target is becoming increasingly horny. He then start to gently stroke his member, and with his other hand caress his expanding ass. You see his finger slowly approaching his backdoor with a dreamy look on his face, but he suddenly realize what he's about to do and change back to his original form. Still, you can see that your target seems to be still positively bother by his last thought.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>Your spell hits your target right on the forehead sending little shocks of pleasure all over his body and especially to his brain. You can see that he's becoming aware of every little sensation as you see goose bumps appearing everywhere on his soft white skin. He then instantly go on his back, removes his top, and start playing with his right tit sensing it growing in his hand. He mindlessly put the index finger of his other hand in his mouth and you see him sucking it vigorously as if he was expecting something to happen. Somehow, he removes the rest of his clothes only for you to see that his genital looks more like an big clitoris then a penis, your vision is confirmed when you see little beads of liquid dripping from between his legs.  His hand is about to reach his newly form vagina, when he suddenly come back from his trance and transform back to his original form, but you can see in his eyes that he wants this to go further.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>Your spell hits your target right in the groin, as the spell hits him, you can see that a massive wave of arousal is overwhelming your target. He removes all his clothes and take in hand his already erect penis and start masturbating not realizing that within second she's now on the ground fingering a newly formed wet snatch. She's so busy playing with herself that she doesn't see her chest become bigger and bigger transforming into huge titties with rock hard nipples standing to attention, as they do, she takes her other hand and start massaging them vigorously.  Her ass and hips start to expand to complete her newly hourglass form while all her body hair disappear as her skin becomes paler and paler. A big chuck of her red mane gets in her face as she's having one really loud orgasm in front of you that complete her transformation.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd_M>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>Your spell hits your target on the right hand. You can see little tingles of electricity run across her arm as you see her skin becomes a little whiter, her nails becomes a little bit longer and tattoos start to appear. You suddenly see you target rubbing her legs together and grabbing her clothes as something seems to bother her, but she quickly shrub it off and transform back to her original self.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>Your spell hits your target in the face, you can see that she's feeling dizzy for a second as she reach her face with her hand, the second her hand touch her plump lips you can see her shivers as a little moan escapes her mouth. In shock, she removes her hand only to realize that her now long and red hair are in the way. You see her standing there in shock as she instinctively start to lick her own lips with her tongue, only to let out some other bigger moans of pleasure. It seems that hearing herself screamed like that brought her back to her senses as she return to her original form.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>Your spell hits your target right in the chest, you can see her nipples harden immediately through the fabric, as her breast becomes firmer and rounder, you can see her struggle with the pleasuring sensation as she start to mindlessly rub her nipples with her hands. The feeling seems really good for her as she falls on her back only for her expanding buttocks to absorb the shock. As you look at her crotch, you see that's she really turn on as her vagina is squirting liquid all over the place. Your target, having seen the same thing, came back to her senses and transform back to her original self, but you could see that she had enjoy the experience.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>Your spell hits your target on one of her butt cheeks, almost instantly you can see her hips and ass starting to widen, stretching her clothes and making her feel really uncomfortable. She then suddenly removes all her clothes, and you can see by her constantly dripping pussy and her rock hard nipples that you target is becoming increasingly horny. She then start to gently finger her clitoris, and with her other hand caress her expanding ass. You see her finger slowly approaching her backdoor with a dreamy look on her face, but she suddenly realize what she's about to do and change back to her original form. Still, you can see that your target seems to be still positively bothered by her last thought.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>Your spell hits your target right on the forehead sending little shocks of pleasure all over her body and especially to her brain. You can see that she's becoming aware of every little sensation as you see goose bumps appearing everywhere on her soft white skin. She then instantly go on her back, removes her top, and start playing with her right tit sensing them becoming more and more sensible with every seconds. She mindlessly put the index finger of her other hand in her mouth and you see her sucking it vigorously as if she was expecting something to happen. Somehow, she removes the rest of her clothes only for you to see her big throbbing clitoris ready to attention, your vision is confirmed when you see her squirt like crazy her pussy lips moving by their own expecting something.  His hand is about to reach her hungry snatch, when she suddenly come back from her trance and transform back to her original form, but you can see in her eyes that she wants this to go further.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd_F>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>Your spell hits your target right in the groin, as the spell hits her, you can see that a massive wave of arousal is overwhelming your target. She removes all her clothes and start to vigorously finger her now permanently wet snatch. She's so busy playing with herself that she doesn't see her chest become rounder and softer transforming into super sensible titties with rock hard nipples standing to attention, as they do, she takes her other hand and start massaging them vigorously.  Her ass and hips start to expand to complete her newly hourglass form while all her body seems to shiver in pleasure as her skin becomes paler and paler. A big chuck of her red mane gets in her face as she's having one really loud orgasm in front of you that complete her transformation.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd_F>

</Form>
