<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>Your hit by the cloud of magic, coughing as the spell enters your lungs. You wheeze and gasp, you swear you sound like you're braying almost. You stare angrily at the person attacking you. "I'll show them!" You tell yourself as you imagine bending them over your knee and spanking their rump until they beg you for an apology. As these thought cross your mind you fail to notice your clothing hardening and darkening, while your ears just barely begin to lengthen and sprout grey fur. With a final wheeze you change yourself back, reversing whatever it is they are trying to do to you.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>Your opponent send another cloud of magic dust at you. You inhale it once again and begin to cough once more, this time you are unquestionably braying loud and proud. You smile darkly at your opponent, knowing they will have to be punished even harsher for this act. You fantasize about strapping them to the bed and pleasuring them, but stopping right before orgasm, and doing this again and again until they understand who their Mistress is. As you lick your lips, lost in your dominant thoughts and dreams. You fail to notice as your top tightens again, changing into a black leather corset, while your bottoms change into a tight black thong and thigh length leather boots. Your ears lengthen again, this time growing longer and forming into unmistakable donkey ears, covered in coarse grey fur. You feel a pinch in your tailbone as a ropey rail sprouts, covered in grey fur and tufted in dark brown fur. You huff in annoyance and change yourself back to normal, still wanting to show that rude opponent of yours how to properly respect you.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>You bray in pleasure as the spell hits you once more, your clothing quickly returning to the tight black leather dominatrix outfit. It is beginning to feel so natural to you, mabye your opponent doesn't deserve to much punishment. You smile as your face begins to push out into a broad donkey muzzle, your ears fully changing one again. You coo as your head becomes covered in grey fur, your hair styling and changing to a brown color. You flinch a little as metal piercings form in your ears and a single stud in your bottom lip. You run your tongue over your new stud as the memories form inside your head, one piercing for every pet you have broken. You giggle as your breasts begin to plump up in your corset, stretching it nice and firm. The sudden tightness causes you to gasp in shock as you realize you were transforming again, you quickly counter your opponents spell. After you return to normal you can't help but lick where the stud had been, missing the proof of what a good slave maker you are.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>You smile, calm and collected as the spell begins to change you again. You adjust your corset so that your nipple peek over the hem, your plump breasts straining the tight leather outfit. You shake your hips as they widen and your newly formed donkey pussy twitches with anticipation of your pet being rewarded by being allowed the privilege of eating you out. You coo and imagine all the good little slave you will make after you break your opponent, bimbos, bunnies, mouse bois, all of them crawling behind you as they worship their Mistress. You run your hands over your body as more grey fur sprouts, most of your changes mental this time around. You open your now brown eyes and sigh, gaining control over your ambitions again and changing back to normal. You rube your thighs together, missing the feeling of your black lipped sex.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>You can't help but bray loudly, your body changing back rapidly to the form you know you belong in now. You want to break their minds and wills, train them to be your pets. Everyone will serve you and worship you as a beautiful mistress! You licks your lips stud and eyes your opponent as a riding crop and leather collar and leash appear in your hands. You giggle in excitment at all the possible ways you can break them down into a whimpering submissive toy. You begin strutting towards them and in their own nervousness lose control of their own spell, stopping your changes just before they became permanent. Your body would slowly change back to normal and you can only sigh softly, not sure what you want anymore.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>You can't help but bray loudly, your body changing back rapidly to the form you know you belong in now. You want to break their minds and wills, train them to be your pets. Everyone will serve you and worship you as a beautiful mistress! You licks your lips stud and eyes your opponent as a riding crop and leather collar and leash appear in your hands. You giggle in excitment at all the possible ways you can break them down into a whimpering submissive toy. You begin strutting towards them with your collar and leash ready, you will start with this pathetic opponent of yours and soon you will have the whole city as your own personal harem of slutty, broken pets. After all you are a sexy Donkey Dominatrix.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>Your target is hit by the cloud of magic, coughing as the spell enters their lungs. They wheeze and gasp, you swear they sound like they're braying almost. They raise their head proudly, puff out their chest, and stare at you with angry eyes. It sends a shiver down your spine and Is almost enough to make you want to stop casting. Their clothing hardens and darkens, while their ears just barely begin to lengthen and sprout grey fur. With a final wheeze they change back, reversing what you trying to do to them.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>You send another cloud of magic dust at your opponent. They inhale it once again and begin to cough once more, this time they are unquestionably braying loud and proud. Your opponent smile darkly at you, making the hair on the back of your neck stand on end. They seem to be fantasizing about doing sadistic things to you and start licking their lips. As they lick their lips, lost in their dominant thoughts and dreams, they fail to notice as their top tightens again, changing into a black leather corset, while their bottoms change into a tight black thong and thigh length leather boots. Their ears lengthen again, this time growing longer and forming into unmistakable donkey ears, covered in coarse grey fur.  A ropey tail sprouts, covered in grey fur and tufted in dark brown fur. They huff in annoyance and change them-self back to normal, still wanting to show you how to properly respect them.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>They bray in pleasure as the spell hits them once more, their clothing quickly returning to the tight black leather dominatrix outfit. The mean look in their eyes seems to soften.They smile as their face begins to push out into a broad donkey muzzle, their ears fully changing one again. They coo as their head becomes covered in grey fur, their hair styling and changing to a brown color. They flinch a little as metal piercings form in their ears and a single stud in their bottom lip. You can't help but flinch too. They run their tongue over their new stud. They giggle as their breasts begin to plump up in their corset, stretching it nice and firm. The sudden tightness causes them to gasp in shock as they realize they were transforming again, they quickly counter your spell. After they return to normal they can't help but lick where the stud had been.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>They smile, calm and collected as the spell begins to change them again. They adjust their corset so that their nipple peek over the hem, their plump breasts straining the tight leather outfit. They shake their hips as they widen and their newly formed donkey pussy twitches with anticipation of naughty acts to come. They run their hands over their body as more grey fur sprouts. Since there aren't many new physical changes, you can only assume most changes this time are mental. They open their now brown eyes and sigh, gaining control over their ambitions again and changing back to normal. They rube their thighs together, probably missing the feeling of their black lipped sex.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>hey can't help but bray loudly, their body changing back rapidly to the form you both know they belong in now. They licks their lips stud and eye you as a riding crop, leather collar, and leash appear in their hands. They giggle in excitment at all the possible ways they can break you down into a whimpering submissive toy. They begin strutting towards you and your own nervousness lose control of your own spell, stopping their changes just before they became permanent. Their body would slowly change back to normal and they can only sigh softly, not sure what they want anymore.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>They can't help but bray loudly, their body changing back rapidly to the form you both know they belong in now. They licks their lips stud and eye you as a riding crop, leather collar, and leash appear in their hands. They giggle in excitment at all the possible ways they can break you down into a whimpering submissive toy. They begin strutting towards you with their collar and leash ready. They seem to intend to start off their new life as a dominatrix by calming you as a pet. If nothing is changed, they may soon have the whole city as their own harem of slutty, broken pets. After all, they are a sext Donkey Dominatrix now and it is all thanks to you.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
