<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<Description></Description>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st></TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st></TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st></TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st></TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st></TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st></TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd></TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd></TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>You unleash the spell again and you're delighted by its quickness; almost immediately your target's skin turns green, though it doesn't stop there this time! You watch as your victim's frame grows smaller and leaner, and their breasts slowly settles on a nice B-cup. Shortly afterward, their hair grows out and shifts into a bright pink! You're pleasantly surprised when they smile briefly before shaking their head and reversing the changes. Bummer...</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>The second the sweet smell reaches your target again, the effects are immediate! Their skin turns a healthy (for a plant) green tone, and their pink hair twirls atop their head, forming a bun that blossoms into a beautiful flower with a soft pop! The best part is getting to see the new alraune's face filled with joy for a short moment; sadly she shakes her head and reverts the changes before long.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>Your spell reaches your opponent once more, but this time they don't even try to avoid breathing it in; they actually stand there and take in big whiffs of the sweet scent! The changes are rapid; returning them to their alraune form in a matter of seconds. You see her close her eyes and seem to enjoy taking in the sun with a broad smile. She even giggles at you and shows off her new body for a bit until she seems to realize that you were the one that turned her this way. With an upset glare she counters your spell and returns herself to normal, though you know it won't take much more now!
</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>Your spells hits your opponent for the last time. In merely a second, the person standing before you is a happy alraune. She returns your gaze and smiles brightly while you observe her, expecting her to snap back to her own mind at any second. It never seems to happen though; you guess she has probably already forgotten while she was here in the first place. After a few seconds, she shrugs and turns to wander away. You smile to yourself, pleased that you managed to make the world just a little prettier today!</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
