<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>You shiver slightly as your opponent's spell hits you. You feel your skin become smooth as weak thoughts of submission sneaks into your mind. You blink and quickly and change yourself back to normal not sure what they are trying to do to you and non to eager to find out.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>The changes resume as you are hit by the spell and proceed further. Your shoulders narrow, your body shrinks a bit, and your head feels heavy. You begin to bow a bit to your opponent before shaking it off and raising you head. You manage to reverse the spell with a little effort.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>You shiver as the spell washes over you once more. Your hips widen as your genitals change into a small little cockette. You whimper and look at your owner...no....enemy. You wiggle your bottom as it plumps up, aching to have someone use you like a good little girl. You squeak in fright and quickly change yourself back, blushing deeply as the thoughts of being a good little boi still float around inside your head.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>Again the familiar feeling of change washes over you. Your skin smooths as before and all of your body hair falls out in addition. That won't be so easy to reverse even with magic. The physical changes come back in full force along with new thoughts. As you look at others nearby wearing girly clothes, you can't help but think you could wear it better. You look on the bright side. Being a slutty toy has got to be better than being clothes. Wait, what are you thinking? You barely manage to get a hold of yourself and change yourself back with great effort. Even after that thoughts of playing dress up persist.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>It seems like the end is near as the spell hits again. You start shifting around nervously as your body becomes more girlish in front of everyone. This is wrong but it feels so right. The magic has hit you so many times it's affecting all aspects of your being; even your clothes. They change to become more feminine as well. With your mental changes, it all feels natural. Luckily the faint voice of reason snaps you out if it and you change back. The strain has you panting, feeling hot and bothered. It'd be impossible for you to get out is this without a Miracle if another one of those hits cleanly.</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>It seems like the end is near as the spell hits again. You start shifting around nervously as your body becomes more girlish in front of everyone. This is wrong but it feels so right. The magic has hit you so many times it's affecting all aspects of your being; even your clothes. They change to become more feminine as well. With your mental changes, it all feels natural. Luckily the faint voice of reason snaps you out if it and you change back. The strain has you panting, feeling hot and bothered. It'd be impossible for you to get out is this without a Miracle if another one of those hits cleanly.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>Your victim shiver slightly as your spell hits them square in the rump. You can see their skin become smoother as a submissive look sneaks onto their face. They blink and quickly and change themself back to normal, but you are ready to keep changing them into a cute little sex object.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>Another hit! You're on fire today! Your target's shoulders narrow, their body shrinks a bit, and you swear you see them bow to you. Their face shows an expression on confusion and annoyance as they shake their head. They manage to snap out of it and reverse your spell, their body returning to normal.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>Your opponent shiver as the spell washes over them once more. Their hips widen and you can't be sure but it looks like something is going on in their lap. They whimper and look at you as they wiggle their bottom as it plumps up. It looks very inviting. They let out a squeak (most likely in fright) and quickly change back, blushing deeply. They look like they're thinking about something dirty.</TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Your spell hits the mark once again. Man you are getting good at this! Your target's skin smooths as before and all of their body hair appears to falls out. That won't be so easy to reverse even with magic. The physical changes come back in full force. They appear to look around at everyone's clothes. Their priorities certainly seem to be changing which is a good sign your spell is working. They appear to change back though and look at you in fear. If you keep it up, they very well may get stuck.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>It seems like the end is near as the spell hits again. They start shifting around while their body becomes more girlish in front of everyone. Your opponent's clothes change to become more feminine as well. Unfortunately, their faint voice of reason snaps them out if it and they change back. The strain has them panting, feeling hot and bothered. It shouldn't take more to make them like that permanently.</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>Your one time opponent giggle girlishly as the spell hits them for the last time. They begin to wiggle their hips and booty as soft silk panties form around them, barely showing their tiny bulge. They run their hands over their smooth skin and moans softly, long silk stockings appearing up their legs followed by fingerless long gloves on their arms. You smile and imagine how happy they will make other people with their sexy little body, because their the best of both worlds! they're girly and submissive but also have a cock that can be used if needed. With a giggle they eagerly embrace their new life as you watch them run off with a smirk.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
