<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Form xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<Description>You're the latest and greatest model of vibrator, "The Pink Pulsar". You're pink, you resemble a penis, and your center is filled with rotating black beads. Your purpose is to provide pleasure to your owner whenever they so choose to use you. Depending on their sex, you'll likely be inserted into different orifices. The only thing you can manage on your own volition is a tiny wiggle, and you can't resist the urge to vibrate like mad when your owner commands it. You come equipped with three possible settings, and the fastest always makes you dizzy . . .</Description>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>Your entire body feels stiff, and you can barely move an inch. You easily reverse the effects of the spell.</TFMessage_20_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>The stiffness returns, and your skin turns pink along with it. You reverse the effects of the spell just as spikes begin to emerge from your neck.</TFMessage_40_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>Your body goes stiff and pink once more. This time several spikes fully emerge from your neck, and your legs fuse together. Your new fused legs begin to expand, molding themselves into some kind of rectangular object, and your feet fuse together to become some sort of gear. "I'd love to vibrate in someone's nether regions . . ." you think to yourself. You manage to reverse the effects with a bit of magical know-how  just as you begin shrinking.</TFMessage_60_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>Yet again your body stiffens up and goes pink as spikes emerge from your neck, and your legs create a rectangular object. You can feel your insides being reshaped, like there's a pinball game going on inside of you. The skin surrounding your torso is replaced by a clear material, and you quickly realize why. You can see dozens of rotating black beads inside you, wrapping around your lower torso completely. With a great deal of difficulty, you reverse the effects of the spell.</TFMessage_80_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>The changes sweep over your body once more, leaving you in your odd pink position. You feel horrible pain as your head mushes itself into resembling a penis head, and your spikey neck stretches itself greatly, bloating outwards. You sigh as your groin begins transforming as well, becoming a pink cylinder with grooves around it, connecting cleanly to your clear beady torso. You've shrunken to about the size of a large vibrator now. "Vibrate . . .  I need to vibrate . . . inside someone . . . I need it .  . ." you think to yourself. Through a great amount of struggle, you're able to reverse the effects of the spell.  You doubt that you'll last much longer . . .</TFMessage_100_Percent_1st>

<TFMessage_Completed_1st>The spell hits you directly in the face, and you submit to to changes. Your body stiffens, your skin turns pink, your legs fuse together and become a rectangular object, your feet fuse together and become a gear, your neck grows spikes, expands, and stretches, your torso becomes a clear display of rotating black beads, your groin becomes a cylinder with grooves, and your head becomes a penis head. You feel another rectangular shape emerge from your new square legs, and you feel three buttons appear on this new shape. The spell finalizes by locking your soul into this vibrating form, and your owner comes to collect you.</TFMessage_Completed_1st>

<TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>Your victim stiffens up, pushing their legs together and standing at attention. They easily reverse the effects of the spell.</TFMessage_20_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>The stiffness returns to your victim, and their skin turns pink along with it. They reverse the effects of the spell just as spikes begin to emerge from their neck.</TFMessage_40_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>Your victim's body goes stiff and pink once more. This time several spikes fully emerge from their neck, and their legs fuse together. Their new fused legs begin to expand, molding themselves into a rectangular object, and their feet fuse together to become some sort of gear. They manage to reverse the effects, just as they begin shrinking. </TFMessage_60_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>Yet again your victim's body stiffens up and goes pink, as spikes emerge from their neck, and their legs create a rectangular object. Your victim begins coughing as they feel their insides being reshaped. The skin surrounding their torso is replaced by a clear material, and you can quickly deduce the purpose. You can see dozens of rotating black beads inside of them, wrapping around their torso completely. With a great deal of difficulty, they reverse the effects of the spell.</TFMessage_80_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>The changes sweep over your victim's body once more, leaving them in their pink position. Their head mushes itself into resembling a penis head, and their spikey neck stretches itself greatly, bloating outwards. Your victim sighs as their groin begins transforming, becoming a pink cylinder with grooves around it, connecting cleanly to their clear beady torso. They've shrunken to about the size of a large vibrator now.  Through a great amount of struggle, they're able to reverse the effects of the spell.  You doubt that your victim will last much longer . . .</TFMessage_100_Percent_3rd>

<TFMessage_Completed_3rd>The spell hits your victim directly in the face, and they submit to to changes. Their body stiffens, their skin turns pink, their legs fuse together and become a rectangular object, their feet fuse together and become a gear, their neck grows spikes, expands, and stretches, their torso becomes a clear display of rotating black beads, their groin becomes a cylinder with grooves, and their head becomes a penis head.  Another rectangular shape emerge from their new square legs, and  three buttons appear on this shape. The spell finalizes by locking their soul into this vibrating form, and you walk over to collect your new toy.</TFMessage_Completed_3rd>

</Form>
